<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[HURRY UP PLEASE IT'S TIME]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's get ready to Trumble https://t.co/P0PPVq6Qph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All this 'ha ha look at us Aussies calling our politicians cunts' might be funnier if we actually called them to account, like, ever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two billionaires have a fight on the phone over who gets to not help people literally setting themselves on fire to end their suffering.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thelittleidiot although we are trying to offload desparate refugees we're currently holding on an island gulag so there's no good guy here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomas_violence a word which here means 'an ongoing selection of truly delightful suits']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh dear, Malcolm. And still you cravenly toady... : On call with Australian prime minister, Trump badgers and brags https://t.co/qVGTeiIcQ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liberal Donor Insists He Has No Influence On Party Policy https://t.co/kulpcBCLfL #humour #feedly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll confess I've never read a @jk_rowling book but man, her Twitter burns are some quality shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Often I get caught up in the Trump admin terrors but then I see things like this and realise they're just dumb as s… https://t.co/o65Gi88y0P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ruminski indulge them! 24 minutes and you'll feel right as rain until you check twitter again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a cogent and surprisingly optimistic view of the current situation. Worth a read. https://t.co/0MLj6Ehh79]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks (as ever) Richard!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Yesterday was the trial balloon for a coup d’état against the USA. It gave them useful information."  
https://t.co/TXbjuEsFoe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[trio of spineless creatures carried along on the tide, containing no  trace of humanity, often found on the shoreli… https://t.co/cuwVgPprZp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know what they say, Chris. "Some days you fuck the dog, and some days the dog fucks you." https://t.co/ONwka9UTzz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is great. https://t.co/5vFOIUyyys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulshipper Wow! Swell work Mr Shipper.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hear Jeremy Irons Read the Poetry of T.S. Eliot https://t.co/JLQsjTcxHR #feedly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here’s What Happens When A Liberal Donor’s Business Got Caught Dumping People’s Private Information https://t.co/rXwDt28yG9 via @MarkDiStef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worth remembering in time for the annual disgrace that is Australia Day #fuckaustraliaday https://t.co/1P5Ds4WbwQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Trump, Three Days On: The Sound and the Fury https://t.co/ktv2Ijolhq via @longreads]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh god, seconded. Absolutely fantastic, nailbiting, tense, heartbreaking, awful, panic-inducing and rousing film. C… https://t.co/6CGG8CdbTY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If anyone is looking to cut government expenditure might I suggest starting with asking why state film bodies need new logos every 2 years?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is President. Here is what to do now. https://t.co/Z5yJxi47P7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a day like today let's all try to take a leaf out of Chuck Tingle's book (no, the other leaf) and PROVE LOVE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RIP Miguel Ferrer. Not many actors could have chewed their way through this scene https://t.co/EcMhOI7zOj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A.V. Club Live: Everything about this A Dog’s Purpose story just keeps getting worse https://t.co/BJKKqjQ3ps #media #feedly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh god thank you. https://t.co/lwh4tBhXyu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ruminski It was supposed to be printed on *yellow* paper! He was quite clear about it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When asking your designer to make an actor's boobs bigger, always remember to assure them that she's a good sport and wouldn't mind one bit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[aside: Poor typographical decision on the artwork for his first single leads to his being known as Moby Go for next 2 years of his career]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HIghly recommended holiday reading. Lowlight: drunkenly dancing in his own sticky ejaculate while surrounded by Ste… https://t.co/WoJpCbmnDw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good on John Pilger for calling it: let's not let the horror of Trump blind us to the horror of Obama https://t.co/lLPKfbPN5V #news #feedly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know it's not the zenith of mature debate but the moment that Martin Shkreli realises he's been hit in the face with dogshit is great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah! Here (finally) is the key art for KILLING GROUND, a movie that disturbed me so greatly I had no choice but to w… https://t.co/qk5efySDbg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Billy CHildish's PRESIDENTIAL CUNT ELECT 

via https://t.co/UTQ952kL6X https://t.co/5zjK6mDVGd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“A film without a provocative campaign and titles is like giving a gift in a paper bag.” Sandy Dvore

https://t.co/ZP5liB1zhd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is good - TV highlights from the Scottish Herald (via Billy Bragg) https://t.co/eXHSQeVQ96]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That we can't even be bothered to look after the most iconic and beloved example of unique Australian fauna is fran… https://t.co/InwdL8IonD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ENHANCE YOUR CREATIVITY WITH OUR NEW PREMIUM FILTERS https://t.co/Q8OI1YA4B6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank YOU, Byron flea market. https://t.co/BOr608PT9h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TROMP VOTERS REGRET ALLOWING VOID CRABS ACCESS TO THEIR BRAIN, CLAIM THEY DIDN'T UNDERSTAND WHAT "SKULL NEST" MEANT https://t.co/HtbYNtBpbt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America Asks 70-Year-Old Man to Piss All Over Them https://t.co/KAGEDBKibg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your annual reminder that design awards that you to pay to enter are a scam. You're better than that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is fascinating. https://t.co/WU7CcnQKHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A real must-read, this. Everything that comes out of his mouth in this interview is so clear and true. https://t.co/4iQJWmR2z0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A couple of character posters for Tusi Tamasese's upcoming ONE THOUSAND ROPES https://t.co/nhS7fMmEyY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All sung in what my good friend D McCormack would refer to as 'a questing falsetto'. The washing machine is fine, by the way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3yo's first songWASHING MACHINE (ukulele, naïve tuning) Washing machineNeeds powerNo power It has run out for the night]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @VirginAustralia not having inflight entertainment on international flights is disgraceful. My 3yo doesn't own a fucking iPhone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stumbled across Hanna last night and discovered the origins of Milo Yiannapoulos' entire shtick. https://t.co/qdIMTB81X5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonathancou ah, it's a good one. And just gets better as it goes on. Have you played firewatch? Amazing- and with great @ollymoss visuals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Martin McKenna on making his debut feature. A must-read for all Australian filmmakers https://t.co/QFMxR8RYwi via @cinemaaustralia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just discovered this amazing resource of 200 exhibition catalogues from the Guggenheim available to download https://t.co/g5Z3pbFBP4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello Wellington. Like Bono, I have come here to play Jesus to the leopards in your hair.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You had me at "hell"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyway today I was wandering around a shopping centre and saw a TRACTORS OF NEW ZEALAND CALENDAR 2017 and remembered I was in Christchurch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonathancou especially when it rhymes with france schmacadeny and I know that you'll be watching eagerly. Rest assured: LOVELY unused art]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and because the terrible design is one of your terrible designs you can't even be mad, just ashamed and happy christmas everybody]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you take a job on &amp; do a wonderful design and then everything goes 180* and the terrible design they chose gets 20k likes in 24 hours]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's the motion poster for Tusi Tamasese's upcoming ONE THOUSAND ROPES https://t.co/7jFStMBv4G (sorry abt the facebook link)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lemon &amp; Paeroa flavoured Whittaker's white chocolate is as close as I ever hope to get to eating a urinal cake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As befits her Australian passport, 3yo daughter just had a brawl in the airport to start the holiday off right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And yes I would include myself in their number. It has been a tough year for us all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every guy in the Gold Coast Airport looks like a photofit of themselves, assembled in the aftermath of some grubby scam gone bad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["cataloguing dozens of stabbings proves a surprisingly ineffective method of tracking a powerful metal non-apple"
https://t.co/GI3VzzfjAZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's one of my new artworks for LION. Probably not where I would have put the nominations bug but what can you do… https://t.co/AjxO8pYBHS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hand Solo, euphemism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God, I love Bill Drummond. Bill Drummond's 10 Commandments of Art https://t.co/Ikl2pdrLF6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little Things #45 - https://t.co/8xfMTUEHfh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HERE, AT LONG LAST, IS MY "BEST OF 2016" TOP 10

1.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomas_violence those hot takes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kid has decided she wants to be called "De-gay" which I am a little concerned about shouting across Byron Bunnings tomorrow morning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benchessell @nakkiahlui apparently Titanfall 2 is wonderful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Party Till Dawn by name, Party Till Dawn by nature https://t.co/HzIKhuTDoQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nakkiahlui Is it that they all have the letter 'c' in them?  wait til he finds out HIS NAME BEGINS WITH C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US threatens to take action against another country for meddling in its election while irony beats itself over the head with a CIA logbook.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plus, is there a better, more cherishable format than 10" vinyl? No, no there is not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For xmas I'm treating myself to @TheMagFields 69 Love Songs &amp; 50 Song Memoir. That's 119 songs, for the less mathematically-inclined. VALUE!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@palacefilms I'd like it to be a Tanna re-release but I'm gonna go with Land of Mine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elanor Digby, The Biggest Dog in the World
Wearing the face that she keeps in a jar by the door
It is Jim Dale's face
Sit, Digby, sit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An important community announcement from our sponsors https://t.co/k4Jrp1uEQL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the kind of shit that Uber pull all the time under the guise of being 'disruptive' when it actually is 'ill… https://t.co/gUoI0iwQjQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be evil. But if evil summons you to a meeting in his gold tower, I mean, you have to go, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're working in tech in the US, please consider the points in this manifesto and sign up https://t.co/d6ddKx7zbY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ruminski DOES INFLAMMABLE MEAN THIS CAN'T CATCH FIRE OR NOT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SHOCKING NEWS https://t.co/AtZRbWFMvP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was going to tweet
About how Brian May
Is the only living man
with Brian May hair
But then I recalled
Dave Mustaine
and that spoiled it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The worst thing about 2016 is that we're probably going to look back on it with fondness compared to what's coming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The good news is that if you wanted to kill Trump as a baby, you wouldn't actually need to build a time machine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A progressive future for VR: Why VR is already getting worse (and how to make it better) https://t.co/434Fn1njl4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@missdlight any awards ceremony celebrating Paul Hogan in 2016 is automatically invalid and you can declare the results void (in your heart)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Last Unknown Man                        
https://t.co/sqvcd1DNVQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Import multi-channel EXR files into photoshop as individual layers https://t.co/qJpj70uDFJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Showrunners call rape-for-shock-value a “plague on the industry” https://t.co/NCb3bTkDta via @TheAVClub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His performance in Our Friends in the North is one of the best pieces of acting I've ever seen. https://t.co/9kEObiBXWe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Fucking Hogan. 

Paul. Fucking. Hogan. Seriously?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Portraits of abandoned cars in 1970s New York – in pictures https://t.co/DMTH6A6j7l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dyLABs @robbie_shepherd I don't get how people work, relax, deal with their kids &amp; maintain adult friendships so I'm the last person to ask]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>