<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Try not to get distracted by the tweets of a disjointed executive. https://t.co/ubrlt2Zh23]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shawnmicallef @ivortossell I'll leave this right here https://t.co/z9H9rfAg2Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sdbcraig @AD_Humphreys @nationalpost Can't wait for the Vice doc on this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not all heroes wear capes. https://t.co/LKDsP2IXy7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess Trudeau just got tired of taking selfies. #electoralreform]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sdbcraig It really is. I stand corrected.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sdbcraig Alternative good, maybe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@asmaam Twitter is considered lethal now. Browsing Netflix is what keeps you up all night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always this https://t.co/JsFyjjbyNC via @theonion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KGallagherCTV Hi Kevin, I'm working on a story about political journalism for the RRJ and I'd love to chat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[O'Leary's alternative facts game is way ahead of schedule https://t.co/6nbtbBbst8 via @ipoliticsca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnjhudson That, toxic mould and rotting banana paste.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[brb dropping everything for the new @HardcoreHistory]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TerryGlavin Hi Terry, I'm writing a piece on the Georgia Straight's 50th year in print for the RRJ. Are you able to chat at some point?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anchovies + thing = better thing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaijaKappler Trudeau lied to us. He can't run a circus at all!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaijaKappler but Ringling is finished. We need it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@kevinolearytv But hey, who needs pesky facts amirite?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@kevinolearytv re: McGuinty gov't deficit. It only started running one in 2009, after, you know, a global economic meltdown.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevinolearytv Nice job working in those sirens, tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also: "In short, O'Leary had sold Mattel a turkey." Delicious, delicious $2-billion-in-shareholder-value-lost-in-a-day turkey.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a year old, but worth reading now more than ever. Best quote: "...a history of ineptness as a businessman." https://t.co/SvXardXvff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grubstreet You'd be surprised how many people tell you they're allergic to nuts only before ordering dessert. https://t.co/4MQGCqZyXt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charliesmithvcr Hi Charlie, I'm working on a story about the Straight's 50th year for the RRJ. Are you able to chat?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING SPECULATION #Buzzfeed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Since Shakespeare isn't using "Not Without Mustard" on his coat of arms, does that mean I can? https://t.co/VLEZHs5LUv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great story that makes you say "what the fuck?" to yourself every few paragraphs: https://t.co/AmSeU1pCFU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's Christmas Eve and my mom asked me if I've seen Die Hard and if I'd like to watch it and I'm like https://t.co/6t2snywUCu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnjhudson Those post-goal shenanigans just slow down the magic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnjhudson Fifa: the video game that changed football | Simon Parkin https://t.co/OhvkAEaXVH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JillKrop Hi Jill! I'm a Ryerson MJ, and I'd love to chat with you for a project I'm working on!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh dear... https://t.co/v97Iuy06LS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Score one for gerrymandering.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come for puns, stay for top-notch headline analysis. https://t.co/lqvHkCDSao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't check the news, check RRJ's Weekly Wire: https://t.co/lZhI7mjwCx (but actually you should check the news too)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nerds telling stories about nerds. Checkitout. RRJ Recommends: Reply All&amp;#8217;s &amp;#8216;Boy in Photo&amp;#8217; https://t.co/9PVy4bQJYs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/2 @jjjarthur ...until later, and how they handled it. Totally confidential—just for an assignment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/2 @jjjarthur Asking journos if they've encountered tricky ethical or legal situations where they didn't initially know what to do...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jjjarthur Arthur! Long time since I've seen you in the grad lounge. I have an assignment I could use your two cents on. Can you help?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My left eye has been twitching for a few hours now, and I'm willing to bet it's a prelude to something. But WHAT?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The coolest and scariest thing I've seen today. Interactive local news map put together by RSJ prof @aprilatryerson https://t.co/AW8C1pBjZi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starting paragraphs with "And" is my power move.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A new season of High Maintenance is out today, so today is a good day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I type F into a google search it autofills with frozen burrito.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsbengordon Is it because you decided to lie down on the floor of a movie theatre?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have so many MS Word docs open right now that the most self destructive thing I could do is close them all without saving.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone read this thing:  https://t.co/8CuhIxIVKx via @newyorker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidinnanen That's about 40 ounces. Well, was.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labour (Day) of love. https://t.co/sBXsm5w6tf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moral crisis: I ought not go to a bar on Labour day because workers working is an anathema, but I need a pint, y'know?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know @torontolibrary has all those Criterion Collection flicks, but do they have Fast and Furious one through six?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AshleyCsanady In fairness, it wasn't every night, just a lot of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guy at the next table just told his date not to worry about her greys because she's great in the centre.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@jayrosen_nyu Because it's punchy two-syllable jargon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidinnanen I've mastered one of your two criteria, but I don't think I'm even close to halfway successful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@k_delamont @jm_schneider @phillyzoo The gorilla should obviously be named Boaty McBoatface]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jm_schneider @k_delamont I really hope they go for Harambe 2: Electric Boogaloo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So were the deadlines for the Eglinton Crosstown unrealistic to begin with, or is Bombardier just unreliable?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnLorinc @SpacingStore Board games take up too much space and slow everyone down. The people want video games, video games, video games!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@k_delamont April's "you will fail" note is still my favourite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@k_delamont To quote Bill, when I told him I had to trek to Ward 7 regularly: "Why are you still even in this program?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@k_delamont We had better. Gotta get ice for these burns.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Orientation more like BORE-ientation #rsjorientation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@asmaam They get to be journalists from day one while I gotta go through two full years? C'mon!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You check out Casper mattresses just ONCE and all of sudden you're bombarded with "mattress startups" because I guess that's a thing now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnjhudson No doubt, but this? https://t.co/UzboO0AGaA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My favourite part about Trump's "astonishingly excellent" bill of health is that he also apparently eats fast food all the time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidinnanen That nerdlinger's bra bomb had better work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Serious question: Do snakes need to go for walks—but obviously not walks—like dogs, to get some air and exercise?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You just know something's going down when you see two young guys wheeling a clawfoot bathtub around a university campus in late August.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidinnanen That is incredibly astute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll say this: I fully support Trump ruining Anne Coulter's book launch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well I guess I'm making chicken tonight. https://t.co/kyECcXP5YR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jaclynym JN8765: Animal Stories, with Dr. Barks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If this is how Skynet will kill us then I accept my fate. https://t.co/QLeeKWZ5GR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jm_schneider The article says to get BETTER friends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jm_schneider I'm TRYING https://t.co/70kFWcH0yl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidSRudin @AJPlener If using the bus is so important why not just start your own bus service?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AJPlener @DavidSRudin I like to build media empires on my phone during my commute to my unpaid internship at a national newspaper.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jm_schneider I imagine it as demagogic American version of Bob and Doug McKenzie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Podcast idea: "Five drinks in, with Paul Manafort and Corey Lewandowski"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just waiting for Trump to replace Kellyanne Conway with Ryan Lochte.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some good reading for those in mourning: https://t.co/MszxcmdARu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad news about @Gawker. Even sadder that one angry rich guy, wronged or no, can silence the press.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turns out monetizing basic human rights and dignity isn't a great idea. Whodathunkit? https://t.co/RiP9MfBnsm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChebabyTO Your choripan more than lives up to your hype, which is considerable. Please, please occasionally visit Ryerson come September.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@huxley4ever Best way to get involved is to contact your MP and go from there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ugh, terrible news about @reportedly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eating gratuitous amounts of chocolate, or sweets generally. https://t.co/RNAZeCUev0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@k_delamont And what about Olympic tag? And Olympic butts up?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@k_delamont The only good that piece did was remind me that handball is a thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@k_delamont BREAKING NEWS: Young people fuck. They also have phones and a spectrum of sexual preferences.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@dailybeast Forget .@NicoHines's poor judgment for a second. Is hookup culture at the Olympics even newsworthy anymore?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give me all the lobster puns you got. It's important.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Re: Rob Ford .@TorontoStar has frontpaged their own story as the "one that started it all." Didn't .@Gawker break the news?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know the RNC wrapped up weeks ago, but I still think there's time for Clint Eastwood to yell at an empty chair.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@VanityFair Changed this pretty quick, eh? https://t.co/RK1MQRVgPR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaijaKappler Probably in German, yeah.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next level poetic justice. Maybe slam poetry justice? Anyway: https://t.co/Nsgo1YEMEl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pesky gunfights getting in the way of good journalism. https://t.co/lpCN2FUvyj]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>