<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@sheilabapat oh, this idea is back? I think I wrote about it a decade ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have not been arrested by anyone in Donald Trump's government.

This tweet will repeat tomorrow if it remains true.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Resistance works. Democrats are learning how to play this game! https://t.co/e5Wul9pZDb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[:Opens Twitter:

Sees that it is still bad.

:Closes Twitter:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to Atlanta for their Electoral College victory!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bencjacobs Wherever you go, it's the same trolls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That thing where a Supreme Court nominee made up his pro bono work in law school. https://t.co/J6FAIF8Zct]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With less than 10 minutes remaining, Atlanta is struggling to overcome New England's commanding lead in the Electoral College.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus and I will never stop tweeting together! https://t.co/mN0ODXev2d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miri_iron My cynicism and your cynicism should grab a craft beer together. But not an IPA. My cynicism only drinks dark beer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrendanNyhan Yup, but they could have pulled the ads if they though they were a bad business move.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our president is a monster who could end all life on earth, but at least the crappy watered down beer is with us!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Corporate American is betting hard tonight that Trump is the death throes of a dying movement and not something here to stay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the sportsball teams is doing much better sportsball than the other sportsball team.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's almost as if feminism is now completely mainstreamed! https://t.co/rDJL0fDiU0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KStreetHipster I hope it's the sex kind and not the animal sacrifice kind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait, Anthony Hopkins is in a Transformers movie?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems significant that entirely mercenary profit-driven companies are betting that trolling Trump is a way to attra… https://t.co/WXljRivCt9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait, someone bought a Super Bowl commercial to sell water?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perhaps I should have made clear that this tweet was about the Schuyler Sisters. https://t.co/U7WbSewAh6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bringing out the one living not-horrific Republican is a pretty good Super Bowl subtweet of Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IamMikeRich that was in response to the Schuyler Sisters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America was already great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Greg651 I'm not anti-law review article. I just think that a lot of effort gets put into a lot of articles that don't accomplish much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[19 mins before kickoff, and I just finished the first draft of a law review article I've been working on for a few months. My life is lit!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoy the Super Bowl. Remember that a touchdown counts for 6 points, unless it is scored by a white guy from Wisconsin. Then it's 9 points.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This guy thinks he should get to put someone on the Supreme Court. https://t.co/Da88I9JfHo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have not been arrested by anyone in Donald Trump's government.

This tweet will repeat tomorrow if it remains true.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This rally is smaller than @realDonaldTrump's fingers. https://t.co/VIJrZizvRq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who has the most search-engine optimized page saying when the Super Bowl happens this year?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need to let the American people have their say. No new justice until the next president is sworn in. https://t.co/lyqxTHaFkx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Alex_Lily will you post the recording online.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile, on Earth 2, President Clinton was briefed on the Fifth Circuit's decision restoring the Labor Department's overtime rule.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But her emails.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You voted for Rex Tillerson. https://t.co/K6xPtEtuVg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is fine. https://t.co/sEHkBOlgZK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smart thread. The way to save America is to do whatever you can to undermine Trump's popularity. https://t.co/kSzwYBEorw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fatal flaw in Trump’s legal defense of his Muslim ban https://t.co/VpsvF4UzFC https://t.co/EKb39xylUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5) And if the Court doesn't apply Hobby Lobby to Trump, it would give away the game that this is all raw politics.

https://t.co/VaCrYi9HCj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4) I still believe that conclusion in Hobby Lobby was bullshit, but it is the binding command of a SCOTUS opinion.

https://t.co/VaCrYi9HCj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3) But, in Hobby Lobby, SCOTUS said that there is a "complete separation" between 1st Amendment caselaw and RFRA.

https://t.co/VaCrYi9HCj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2) Trump relies on a 1st Amendment case that requires extraordinary deference from courts in some immigration cases

https://t.co/VaCrYi9HCj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1) I read the Trump admin's request for a stay and the fatal flaw in it, IMO, is that it doesn't mention RFRA. https://t.co/VaCrYi9HCj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, although if it is 4-4 it won't be hard for Trump admin to revive case if new justice is confirmed. https://t.co/kCb9c0gFUi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You want to repeal Medicare and replace it with a coupon. https://t.co/xCsvQM1RP8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisgeidner @dominicholden And Hobby Lobby holds that RFRA still applies to religion cases and 1st Ad precedents do not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisgeidner @dominicholden Interesting. Although the standard applies to First Amendment claims, and the only 1st Ad issue is religion...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisgeidner @dominicholden that's fair, although I have literally never heard the term "facially legitimate" before today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rpbp I don't know. Maybe it is a term of art in this context. But it means nothing to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rpbp I'm not sure that I've ever heard that term before.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have not been arrested by anyone in Donald Trump's government.

This tweet will repeat tomorrow if it remains true.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If these judges aren't stopped, there could be another Bowling Green Massacre any day now! https://t.co/Xvznx0guoE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Better video of great Americans giving a Republican member of Congress all the respect he deserves.

https://t.co/CiYe09VTuM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robert Bork said that banning whites-only lunch counters is rooted in "a principle of unsurpassed ugliness.” https://t.co/mj6G92AU4O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These great Americans hounded their Republican member of Congress in public and you can too!

https://t.co/D6Pz9aE68R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DLind Trump also has a RFRA problem. Ironically, in no small part thanks to Hobby Lobby. https://t.co/d1lcmLAXuq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roberts. Alito, because he is happy to see a Republican in charge. Breyer, because of some backhanded democracy the… https://t.co/qKvbwHBjU8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much depends on whether Justice Kennedy is watching Trump and thinking "maybe I was wrong to enable gerrymandering &amp; voter suppression."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessewegman @ezlusztig I'm quite troubled by it, but I'm troubled because it is an extension of his prior lawlessness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never, ever, ever, ever, ever agree to host the Olympics. https://t.co/RIA9lm9GVA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessewegman @ezlusztig It is. My point is simply that blanket statements against questioning judicial legitimacy box us in in bad ways.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessewegman @ezlusztig If Gorsuch is confirmed, he will be illegitimate. That's Merrick Garland's seat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ezlusztig I'm thinking ahead to what I'm going to say when Justice Gorsuch strikes down the entire Clean Air Act.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessewegman I'm thinking ahead to what I'm going to say when Justice Gorsuch declares the EPA unconstitutional.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Supreme Court is likely to be controlled by very bad men for the foreseeable future. We should preserve our rig… https://t.co/5ah8p02TT1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Problem with Trump attacking a judge isn't that he attacked a judge. Some judges are wrong. The problem is Trump's order is evil &amp; illegal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, the ship sailed on not having utter political chaos on November 8. https://t.co/65nqqXcht3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Carter, a Dubya, and an Obama. https://t.co/ZfNypz4eAt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattyglesias In fairness, the real reason he picked Gorsuch was because he delegated the task to the Federalist Society]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Electoral College is bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consider the possibility that we shouldn't let this man put anyone on the Supreme Court. https://t.co/aSpLz1VBBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clearly the appropriate thing is for the appeals court to demand full briefing and schedule a full hearing three or… https://t.co/VNFkC2HbWC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can win. https://t.co/ht95luh7rh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaraJeffery @BrookeErdmann that's a big if.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PithyPunk @HeerJeet from a National Review editorial. "Why The South Must Prevail."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do people care what the National Review has to say anymore?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeerJeet instead of replacing the later with the former.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeerJeet It's remarkable how fast Republicans fell in line once they understood that Trump is racism AND gutting Medicare...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeerJeet “The sobering answer is Yes—the White community is so entitled because for the time being, it is the advanced race.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeerJeet Wait, what did they do this time?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have not been arrested by anyone in Donald Trump's government.

This tweet will repeat tomorrow if it remains true.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They're also offering free children's lattes laced with a drug that will make your son gay. https://t.co/i8CQISAZR3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I miss being bored so much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidbadash not my doing. I wish I could claim it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got an email from the Clinton Foundation about great work it does. Don't understand why I never received it from the Clinton Campaign]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DLind @sarahkliff How come I've never seen both of you together in the same place at the same time, then?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After holding SCOTUS seat open for a year, Republicans plan to rush Gorsuch confirmation https://t.co/910qHTQpRc https://t.co/wclgRnoe42]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Important counterpoint to my last tweet. The OLC memo reported by Buzzfeed may not be the main document.

https://t.co/vB9atxAru1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is bad. The entirety of the "analysis" is one sentence: "The proposed Order is approved with respect to form a… https://t.co/Dl5bQfNBnp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@allisonmpreiss I'm doing the Lord's work, Allison. https://t.co/5BxAodo4HT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IDEA: A directory of GOP chief of staffs emails and cell phones so that angry voters can yell at them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Based on the email formula, Toomey's chief of staff's email is probably christopher_gahan@toomey.senate.gov. Email… https://t.co/mCjhHglOp5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@allisonmpreiss I don't really have sympathy for recent grads that choose to work for Toomey, but I'm skeptical targeting them will work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is good. But if anyone has a business card for his Legislative Director or Chief of Staff, that would be even… https://t.co/lVy2UsuXil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has James Comey caught the people behind the Bowling Green Massacre yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The obvious solution to the Bolling Green Massacre is to ban guns.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm just tweeting this picture out again because it pisses off @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/xuCoSWS4uY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been at the dojo for a couple hours working out. Did Trump hang up on any world leaders while I was gone?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SenatorBaldwin joins #TeamSpine. Will vote against Neil Gorsuch.

https://t.co/WhObi4UBFD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facism Forever should be taken seriously but not literally.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>