<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@ozboxfan @theprojecttv a friend recently had a bad injury falling from the 4th step of a ladder. Helmet would've helped]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Champion Federer! https://t.co/rhDAGEtMQT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smartystrides Courier is non-stop commentator on tennis #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smartystrides now Jim Courier is trying my patience beyond human limits! #lovemydog #Couriernotsomuch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can someone shutup Courier? He just never stops his verbal diarrhoea #stfu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LisaRobey @JaneCaro @DailyLifeAu Au contraire! Reading is a 'doing' word.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@9NewsSyd and that is in prime time news in Australia because why??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisEvans @HalfOnionInABag @realDonaldTrump followed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sabinewolff @firstdogonmoon my pup is redecorating lounge room with a botanical look Plants dragged inside.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@watt_shane @RodLurie Charming!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@64AnthonyP @Greg_MarineLab @IndigenousX A shallow, but wide, gene pool to choose from]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am in the running to win two @Emirates Business Class flights thanks to #EmiratesReturn #AusOpen https://t.co/HtQzfXq11q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Greg_MarineLab @IndigenousX just to be sure, they can all take a running leap!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GreenJ @thetimes @realDonaldTrump the hairdo?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrigadierSlog @FoxNews I understand it's another type of shower he prefers!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whiteswine just enjoying your blog, Sir Wordsmith. Much fun. Nice to meet you. Cheers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whiteswine ha! That'd explain the bursts! Isolation has its rewards. Hope someone helps out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whiteswine Same. Over myself being a twit! One is too many, a pack not enough!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whiteswine better to 'tetch' I've decided than the wretchedness caused by the fags.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whiteswine day 2 without a smoke ..sorry!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kon__K @guardian Shame on us! Shame.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarlKatter @Greens becoz that's them, not you! You seem a fine person and I thought u sounded down. Sincere good wishes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Each hang up/missed call is monitored &amp; recorded so they know exactly how many calls are missed. https://t.co/IqEEn9CQOT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wendy_harmer @DrLivGibbs @BuryArtMuseum  the bells were my fave too ..the pressed milk bottle tops, not so much!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Checkout my #BigBloodyLegend from @UBET. You can create yours too https://t.co/sCgShrzp8o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lotzalozza @wendy_harmer @thomas_violence My mum gave me a half-slip every year, &amp; contd well after mini's came in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cher publicly humiliated her in her hometown, on stage, saying she wasn't the brightest! etc. unbelievable jerk!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cher exactly how he treated Jennifer Hawkins on stage &amp; boasted he always gets revenge by humiliating his opponents]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JulieBishopMP @Senator_CFW @SenatorWong @SenClaireMoore churlish to cut Penny W out of photo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dfblokes @LaTrioli @mjrowland68 @MikeCarlton01 @JoshFrydenberg @cpyne of course will retain the Perpetual Trophy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dfblokes @LaTrioli @mjrowland68 @MikeCarlton01 
I believe @JoshFrydenberg has emerged clear winner in our competition.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dfblokes @LaTrioli @mjrowland68 @MikeCarlton01 nope, Frydenberg definitely takes out 'boring' title &amp; in the lead for 'fake sincerity' gong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ABCNews24 when did that poor French tourist die (in the N.T)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dfblokes @LaTrioli @mjrowland68 @MikeCarlton01 you have a good point!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaTrioli @mjrowland68 is there a more boring, transparently self-serving politician than j frydenberg? @MikeCarlton01]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#auspol do politicians understand we watch Parliament &amp; know when they are being duplicitous?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephenCena @DavidOldfieldAU each to their own.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Forthleft2 @krONik you got flirt out of that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephenCena @DavidOldfieldAU have you met his wife? Charming couple!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephenCena @DavidOldfieldAU Fuck David Oldfield. Pardon my heartily felt language!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevethompson49 @LaTrioli Nobody puts  @tanya_plibersek in the corner.  Love you Virginia but mind yr manners!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not really. Nail polish remover does the trick. https://t.co/POSlZNSqoj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Were you laughing at her reflection? #wheredidyougetthathat ? https://t.co/QMUPQgH4Ly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeCarlton01 In Iceland they jail crooked bankers and politicians.  Simple.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And in the late 50's/60's!! https://t.co/I58EA1iorS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elite Dirt Under The Carpet Cleaning Services? https://t.co/h4cfN9GE1j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You lucked out on venue &amp; speakers, didn't you? https://t.co/YGBQ3MbUWJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei Remember the uproar over Bill Clinton proposing “2 for the price of 1” with Hillary!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeCarlton01 unprompted Vanstone said Pell is a friend of hers but they disagree on politics but he's a great guy Italian cooking show ABC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight Amanda Vanstone said she &amp; Pell are friends @MikeCarlton01 but disagree on politics. HELP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She is over represented by the media. https://t.co/a6avNDLuWm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going to call out any person who denigrates anyone Full stop We are lucky to live in this country but it doesn't make us superior]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you ask her the question we are all thinking? https://t.co/IsXbcZl97k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abcnews a very dignified interview with the American Indian. Made me cry with her compassion ❤️]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm having trouble with the vomiting! https://t.co/0dYCCF39S0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes. Originally from behind Barnaby. https://t.co/MBCBgQspRp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, I was too mesmerised to think of it. She &amp; Barnaby were nodding in tandem. Too many carbs for lunch! https://t.co/x8LzZpIga6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barnaby &amp; Frau in blue behind Kelly need to revise their lunch choices. Both struggling to stay awake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not to mention her snide remark to Tanya P.  Sometimes her jealousy is writ large. https://t.co/1GKlMVdzDh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As she popped a bottle of sparkling Chardonnay? Her Royal Thickness! https://t.co/tHQZLlqwXK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeCarlton01 Ordnry 'strayans will be horrified 2 notice Hanson's been having elocution/voice training How very aspirational of her #noice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benpobje MatthewBevan. Worst episode of Little House on the Praire ever! https://t.co/O9dCLh1vwu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cld  our elected representatives  stop their infantile bickering and lying &amp; standup like decent human beings #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was it because Abbott was a bully, fool and not taken seriously by many Australians? https://t.co/FExGoObzeQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How dare he call you old!!! X https://t.co/sEDkz4gyCW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it correct her first husband was a refugee, or from a refugee family? Olde Yugoslavia, or similar? https://t.co/K1PkaeWR75]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David, I admire yr stance. I've also evolved and my love of animals has increased exponentially through thinking it… https://t.co/1GYO3EacSL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cld the 2004 cutoff go a way to explaining the frenzy of snouts in troughs? Get it while you can? https://t.co/yty0AthL8s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KieraGorden And his lady friend has two of its babies above her eyes? https://t.co/7xOg5QREWv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the '60's, Nthn Beaches teens wldve mocked you mercilessly as u waited for help! Lol. https://t.co/JnLCXTik2e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We are going to STOP THE DRUGS,  Sniff!" https://t.co/FAhEZ29Xzh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeCarlton01 @NRMA  Did your Jaguar 'fail to proceed'? #60'sjoke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ginnylowndes @MikeCarlton01 
Broadband with DODO. Unlimited for $70pm &amp; great customer service.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeCarlton01 how do we stop his appointment to the UK post?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@krONik @MikeCarlton01 @Dehler45 @smh as a box of dice, too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustedon1962 @PSyvret Thanks Tony, I only saw yr comment, tbh, but Paul cld u also refrain? Ta! Have a nice day too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustedon1962 @PSyvret. Good morning, Tony.  I, for one, wld thank you to kindly refrain from Trumpesque lockerroom language. TIA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulineHanson I'm as sure as hell not listening to your uneducated piffle, so don't assume u speak for me https://t.co/4V5VozXYdn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How long before cocaine wears off?  #debate #debatesr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've thought better of commenting on your  correspondent's surname! @dodona777 https://t.co/TGJCK4CdQG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@macdonald_julie Agree, but it's an imaginary status they've elevated themselves to, which IMO, is reason to be amused and repulsed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No such thing as 'upper class'. Just wealthier, perhaps. https://t.co/6vv1xNxDH7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BernardKeane Jeebus! You clean floors?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Try the New England H'way at end of mining shift. Don't get btw a white ute &amp; a bottle shop! #cashedupbogans #idiots https://t.co/eyTbRXI36B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@inkymcfee @MikeCarlton01 Me too. In fact, just found my copy of "the very best in Pom-bashing".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alcohol? You're welcome! https://t.co/TWBjojNOgg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeCarlton01 Notice someone leering from the furnace? Hilarious!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BernardKeane Ha! You're funny!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wendy_harmer Nooo!  Mine hasn't arrived yet. Dreading it. #jinxedmyself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeCarlton01 Hate to rub it in but have been watching The Durrell's on my IPad in the Hunter Valley. It's a miracle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeCarlton01 how beautiful. Om.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That'd be 'Nicknok', Moiky! https://t.co/jU4pBdS8ap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ABCNews24. For Vanessa @rvkgrapevine very informative &amp; funny site all things Iceland. I've links with Island since working there 72/73]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe he was wining &amp; dining with Pell in the Vatican? https://t.co/jeCnIEygcV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any chance of finding out what  time flight was booked? That'd be verry interesting, yes? #auspol https://t.co/9oFARzU85Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CamoKeyring On cue, big yawn. He's definitely struggling to stay awake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barnaby looks like he's hungover &amp; can't focus .
#auspol #qt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Natski82 Lady on camera right of her does an impressive "shame"!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeCarlton01 Typed on an Olivetti manual typewriter?  Oh, &amp; remember indentation at beginning of new paragraph?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeCarlton01  start on a Yuge Wall for Trump ?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>