<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Kellyanne's current gig is just a curtain raiser for her future career in Nashville as a Country and Western singer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kellyanne Conway's current gig is just an interlude on her career path as a Country and Western singer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls I have a feeling that you don't believe a word you say but you're having the time of your life!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you sure the Bowling Green Massacre wasn't in an episode of Midsommer Murders?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a bit of a snowflake over this 'Trump has small hands' business.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good cartoon but I think it, or, rather, some healing force in response to it, can work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's extremely close, and inching closer: https://t.co/O39hQueOKK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this Fake News? When I put the same query to Bing, the response I get is totally different. How about trying it… https://t.co/RxZulEO424]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently, human beings share 50% of our DNA with bananas. In the case of the Brexit voter on #bbcqt the percentage is considerably higher.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a resounding reply to supporters of the Corbyn line. And it's from Rotherham-Rotherham ! https://t.co/XctljU9kql]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#bbcqt Panelists: Conservative Chairman and Editor of Conservative Woman. How come? And speaker from the Quilliam Foundation?????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2) The Labour Party's contribution to democracy is to represent its voters, so that all interests are fairly represented.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Labour Party is not there to bow to the majority. Democracy is about the interplay of groups, opinions, and principles. (1)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3) The Border issue can be fudged now with vague promises but after Brexit, either there will be a border or not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2) If there is no border with Eire, EU nationals will enter U.K. that way. But if there is a border, it will endanger the N.I. Agreement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May is talking rubbish about Ireland. If we are to be in control of our borders, we will have to have one with Eire. (1)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many felt Ken Clarke made the best anti-war speech on Iraq. Now he has made the best speech on Brexit. No real answers to his Brexit speech.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It has been said that, when Labour and the Conservatives unite, it is on a calamitous policy: Iraq, Afghanistan and now Brexit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can it be 'democracy' when Labour fails to represent the views of the left-leaning, most of its own supporters, and those under 50?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marthasydenham In a democracy, you have an opposition which, by definition, has a licence to oppose, surely?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lukeakehurst @EllieCumbo As a therapist, I believe that people have a right to change their minds-don't you believe that too?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lukeakehurst @EllieCumbo Surely a party is a means to an end, the end being concerned with policies and principles?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonDennis @lloydshep Farage, as you rightly imply, is the real enemy of democracy. What sort of democrat wants no opposition?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LabourEoin Yes, but not because they had suddenly discovered that they respected his leadership.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By that time, it may be too late. Labour needs to vote now on the likely outcome. https://t.co/njavt00NuP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the Labour amendments-asking for a final vote-has surely already been granted by May? And useless if Labour acts cravenly again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melaniekmelvin @catethetwaate @jeremycorbyn No, it's not. It's his Euroscepticism and crude electoral calculation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labour has taken its most important decision since World War 2 on the basis of Corbyn's Euroscepticism and crude electoral calculation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This shows how intelligent analysts see the most important decision since World War Two. The https://t.co/fvQW0FwVyw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A-level History exam question, 2040. 'Why, when they knew it was disastrous, did MPs vote for a departure from the EU?']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not just trade deals, but everything about Brexit is 'Alice in Wonderland.' Brexiteers will shift the blame when the truth is revealed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@notwaving I once had a conversation with Lulu at a dentists. 'She looked like Lulu, I said.' 'Because she is, ' the receptionist replied.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrisonPlanet I have taught English in a predominantly Muslim area. The children and their parents were largely delightful and admirable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SocialistVoice @KittieCreighton @LabourEoin UKIP is now on about 14%. The real threat is that Labour Remain voters will abstain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LabourEoin @Carolynoflondon  A strange argument. If some members of the Opposition do some opposing.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mtpennycook @franceshinde What is already encouraging the far right is yoking ourselves to the whims of a mad President. Brexit emboldens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mtpennycook @franceshinde When Brexit seen as huge mistake, Conservatives will say "You voted for it."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mtpennycook @franceshinde Lab. failed to argue strongly it wasn't to blame for crash, now accepted as truth. Repeating this mistake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mtpennycook @franceshinde Craven. Case that losing side surrenders its democratic rt.to oppose would have been rejected by Leave.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BirgittaHeiller If Labour was in power, and had promised to implement the Referendum. But, if there is no opposition, there is no democracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LukeBurstow @AmiableNoodle Yes, he found that really hard. For him, the arguments are clearly evenly balanced.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't you wish you were as articulate as Trump? And could match his moral clarity? https://t.co/gy3LBQ7ZVE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is why Stella Creasey should lead Labour! https://t.co/bOEFrJz8zy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you thought #BBCR4today was biased this morning, wait until Sarah Sands becomes its editor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last week, I suggested Stella Creasey should be the next Labour leader. And after her fiery performance on #Newsnight I'm convinced.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As the mosque terrorist turned out to be a Trump supporter, it would make sense to ban all Trump supporters. #trumplogic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@politicshome Hasn't the US embassy denied that story?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now it has become clear what the alternatives are, Labour needs an urgent re-think. It's not a democracy if there is no opposition.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now clear that a trading nation has to make alliances and compromises. Do we do this with our neighbours or with Trump and Turkey?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will Teresa May declare that no deal is better than a bad deal with Trump?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeaveEUOfficial Why is Nigel Farage all over the BBC? Why not Tim Farron? Or AC Grayling? Why the preference for the Right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rachael_Swindon But isn't this a misunderstanding of democracy? You should always campaign for your beliefs and principles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrisonPlanet Disgusting slur on a courageous man. Much admired in London.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrisonPlanet That's what happens in Britain at Conferences. You share a platform with your opponents. Khan always anti-terrorist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Cabinet Office Code of Practice specifies a MINIMUM of 12 weeks' consultation before a Bill is introduced to the Commons. EU Bill????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If people realised that Brexit is hitting their living standards, they would turn against it. The BBC is failing to tell the truth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC website leads on the Resolution Foundation report on wage and price trends. The report emphasises Brexit. The BBC makes no mention of it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Trump visits London, the march against him will dwarf even that against the Iraq War.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prince Charles can be outspoken. Cannot believe that, with his multi-faith convictions, he could favour the Muslim ban. Hope he speaks out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Queen has nothing to loose. It would be wonderful if she spoke out against Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the London Mayor cannot visit America, Trump should not be welcomed in London.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3) How welcome will Muslims feel in Britain if the British Prime Minister is supportive of racism against their co-religionists?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2) As there are over 3 million Muslims in Britain, it is for the government to represent their interests.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1) Of course, you can comment on other countries' immigration policies. India and Australia have said they want access to Britain !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the news of the century: China thinking of going to war with America. https://t.co/LwR4uw4aV1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls A man of action, for sure. A man who forgets that you are supposed to think before you act.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bbclaurak did exactly this. Full credit to her and to the BBC. https://t.co/JxFClmXEvo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the Leave campaigns favourite scare stories was about Turkey joining the EU. Now Mrs. May goes there to discuss a trade deal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@christoclifford The three line whip to vote for the motion. That is why he has faced opposition and resignations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@christoclifford Not if you say you are going to vote for the Bill anyway even if the amendments are lost.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@liamyoung @JoyMillward Because the phrase is a trick! About half the electorate, including the Labour supporting half, willed otherwise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent news. Shows principles and character: https://t.co/wxCCV6r2Dd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a principled decision, and let us hope it will encourage others to do the same: https://t.co/bc7uNejwoH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing could be as excruciating as Corbyn evading a question. https://t.co/RNJ7G1lBxs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Keir_Starmer What's the point? If Labour gives May carte blanche now, why believe you would not rubber stamp later?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@christoclifford Or you could try standing up for your principles and the good of the country?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@christoclifford Isn't there a party called the Libdems?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taking back control. Closing our borders to NHS workers. Opening our borders to US private health companies taking over the NHS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeremycorbyn And using a three line whip to make your MPs vote for it is a great way to achieve this objective?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what intelligence looks like as it defines what madness looks like: https://t.co/JSIaSjqpox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeremyCorbyn4PM Nor do it vote for Labour to support the Tories to make it happen!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@djhiom It is liberal in that the Libdems see the EU as representing Free Trade and democratic in that they give voice to the 48%.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May 's section on Russia was extremely clever. It appears to agree with Trump while steering him away from isolationism. A wise strategy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying to avoid history repeating itself is essential. The task now, however, is to reach beyond partisanship to show that Trump is mad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrisonPlanet Because he's mad. The man with his finger on the nuclear trigger is mad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robbeardmore7 In the North, there aren't a lot of bicycling bearded, pacifist, non-drinking vegetarians either. And not just in the North.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Opensout True but the SNP would work with an anti-Brexit Labour Party.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Opensout In the Sleaford election, UKIP declined by about 14%. Where is the evidence for UKIP growth?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robbeardmore7 It would be a good start to have a leader who appeals to anybody (activists apart). Warmth, humanity, humour liked everywhere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Opensout But their support is now showing a half of what it was at the time of the Referendum.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robbeardmore7 I like Stella Creasey. She talks human and is good on TV. She would contrast very favourably with May.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Opensout Some sensational newspaper polls in the north have suggested that in industrial areas, opinion has changed dramatically]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Opensout I The 25% of Labour supporters who are neutral or pro-Brexit won't desert the party, given how right wing its opponents are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robbeardmore7 The world has moved on. It's now Trump versus the NHS. With a half decent leader, the case can be decisively won.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cutter78 2) Argue that people have a right to change their minds. Refuse as a party to endorse a bad deal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cutter78 Start by asserting the democratic right to oppose. Offer a clear line. Publicise the facts. (1)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Opensout How is betraying their own supporters going to help the Party? It is like McDonald forming the National Government.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump promised to build a wall a thousand miles long. As the Mexican border runs for 2 thousand miles, perhaps he overrates his smartness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cutter78 It's the Labour leadership that is destroying the party. And supporting a policy that will destroy Britain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Opensout But not the Labour supporters in those constituencies. Labour has a right to represent the 48%.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>