<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Priest To President: This Founder's Religious Background Led To Green Home Improvement… https://t.co/N4cu89wKts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Crunch Report | 100 Companies File Opposition to Trump’s Immigration Order… https://t.co/L3cWBzAvpr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing So much terrible content, so little time to consume it: Why brands need to abandon interruptive…… https://t.co/Ygf7AHT1wc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Time Inc. chases video dollars with new brand, Coinage https://t.co/DXiKtoqRq6 #Media https://t.co/hBLgB7WbJa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Periscope CEO Kayvon Beykpour is now running all of Twitter's live video products, too… https://t.co/25xtOm2occ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Chan Zuckerberg Initiative donates $3.6M to fight SF Bay housing crisis https://t.co/EEhaiz1Lf2… https://t.co/BiFDnTs8gM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Survey: Is outstream video in or out? https://t.co/vQ6B562c6b #SponsoredLink]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Why brands are increasingly creating experiences &amp; adventures to woo consumers https://t.co/H93TR8QQfA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing SMX West low rates expire Saturday. Register now to master SEO and SEM! https://t.co/oydCCMcU7S… https://t.co/YXy3uWVffy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Surprise: Trump Could Be Fantastic For Honda And Toyota, Total Disaster For Mazda And VW… https://t.co/JObmbUac0C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Super Bowl posts on social media are up from last year, but didn’t top 2015’s record…… https://t.co/dgerYSIhly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing IBM’s Watson joins H&amp;R Block to explain taxes to humans https://t.co/qR2Cu3cN4v… https://t.co/6sfKWzDfoo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing ‘Diamonds come from diversity’: How Translation president Pat Lafferty made it in…… https://t.co/Yx0NQIb4dC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Recode Daily: Dozens of tech companies have joined the legal battle against Trump's travel ban… https://t.co/SMoBn5X2gU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Fast Communication Helps Business Community To Unite After Anaheim Fire https://t.co/Q4DGaBrSdG https://t.co/uGocpfmXPa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing WTF is fake news? https://t.co/DkCVwTfEaa #AdvertisingTech https://t.co/tveNhplh2j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing ‘Make it bigger and better’: A day in the life of Buick’s marketing director before the…… https://t.co/tzo3GxgTvk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Elon Musk says activists should be happy that he’s advising President Trump… https://t.co/a4QjuHh3ap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing #HashtagBowl Live Blog: All The Super Bowl 51 Advertising Action In Real Time… https://t.co/Hig3UNh0zK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Viber now lets users set photos and videos to disappear after they’re viewed… https://t.co/QF2X7mS0kr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing The definitive oral history of the Oreo ‘You can still dunk in the dark’ Super Bowl tweet… https://t.co/MRFQyNRA9e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Today’s the day: The 2017 Marketing Land #HashtagBowl is here! https://t.co/7GdFyLcuQQ #Alerts https://t.co/eERXsR2GVu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing How To Measure Agile Marketing: Perspective From 5 Experts https://t.co/nCaVHUGCri https://t.co/3LV8qt6HZQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Technofascism and the three percent https://t.co/Seh3Kkdj7Q #Opinion https://t.co/Yafry9MHDV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing The state of voice-activated platforms in 4 charts https://t.co/EMSFXNTw2J #Media https://t.co/m5JzGuQsIE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Help! How Do I Increase My Business Presence On Social Media? https://t.co/XDVOBZI4YR https://t.co/0EW4b5Phn5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Drain the swamp https://t.co/4W4nlbQnwu #Column https://t.co/OZ1r3VNUxG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing The WSJ is exploring an ad-free digital offering https://t.co/aAhEvQ3nhS #Media https://t.co/ITCU6ZFexI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing NFL ratings were down all season, and there’s no reason to think they’ll get better next year… https://t.co/1b7LsBOxXK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Google told to hand over foreign emails in FBI search warrant ruling https://t.co/OaeEv9L54L… https://t.co/HlPlbnoHoJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Why retailers struggle to adopt mobile payments https://t.co/xdeniBSG0d #Brands https://t.co/hI1BVK1b05]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Digiday Media welcomes two new reporters for Tradestreaming https://t.co/AxIN77PLYf #Announcement https://t.co/vy0CLQON1d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing The one chart that should scare Snapchat investors https://t.co/HTiRHsPVkp https://t.co/MmKkRwEJh5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Is Your Social Media Strategy Not Working? Here Are 9 Ways To Fix It https://t.co/eRwkc3f1cv https://t.co/saE5SvPPOW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing ChitChat is Silicon Valley’s spammiest new app https://t.co/Kh2pgcYDKR #Mobile https://t.co/HvzgXGrNxu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Why I refuse to preview any of this year’s Super Bowl ads https://t.co/aKqncfIbwV https://t.co/9L2wRfriCW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Best of the week: Havas teaches programmatic while ad land remembers a famous tweet… https://t.co/9BNHmcIWYs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing After being sued, BuzzFeed has apologized to a Russian executive named in the unverified Trump…… https://t.co/gtzUTUgjGV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Trump’s FCC just dropped all investigations into zero-rating practices https://t.co/vFvGuJNtwL… https://t.co/LIb17tEVnG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing To Outsource or to Not Outsource – Now That is a Question https://t.co/ISKa1vq2xr… https://t.co/xT55eTCoJd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Twitter reacts to Nordstorm, Neiman Marcus dropping Ivanka Trump line https://t.co/1J4yGmLgwH… https://t.co/6jlaLsKlTs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing 10 astounding digital marketing stats from this week https://t.co/UuKWpOcZHO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing The 3 Strategies Barlow Herbal Uses For Vibrant Marketing In The Digital Age… https://t.co/jNM4anfYhT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Don’t risk your business and consumer relationship over ‘alternative… https://t.co/zu4YJdSTP2… https://t.co/i1tzSs2qOW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Watch Hulu’s Super Bowl spot for original series The Handmaid’s Tale https://t.co/8ydd36dNa2… https://t.co/iOXOu3gINX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing What if Super Bowl commercials were like digital ads? https://t.co/wuYN1XI7fq… https://t.co/9RzCk71th5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Creepy brand mascots refuse to die https://t.co/Wf6cydpASQ #Brands https://t.co/LYtXOXi7nO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Recode Daily: Here are the numbers inside Snap's IPO https://t.co/SBUFMZ3c5k https://t.co/hOTAAiuP4c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing What States Don't Make The New Heartland Cut, Part 3 https://t.co/Vt62Em0ztj https://t.co/D0EXqGMkJp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Medium plans to launch a consumer subscription product this quarter https://t.co/iPSFQAbKpY #Apps https://t.co/QCPI3V6VBt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Big game, big stakes: gaining a guarantee on Super Bowl advertising investment… https://t.co/AzhJfy9tEl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Snapchat parent’s IPO paperwork, annotated https://t.co/u31SHTpyLz #Media https://t.co/hkPZZQ0La2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Working from home? Google wants to create a drone to go to meetings for you.… https://t.co/SLyRQ60rkZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Case Study: How Penguin 4.0 Has Affected Anchor Text Optimization https://t.co/NoyWn4Mjuv… https://t.co/sALtUvMl3a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Take Complete Charge of Your Content https://t.co/lqlOzH3krf #ContentMarketing https://t.co/NwWkjQtg8z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing The future of the American mall https://t.co/ebyEKxX4Dl #Brands https://t.co/DlnYrQKGJK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing What marketers need to know about Pinterest's new search ads https://t.co/4sdCwYwnIk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing 10 Things You Should Be Doing With Snapchat Snapcodes https://t.co/bBv8Qh5RIh https://t.co/APcSCrldzz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing A bot for Kia Motors is the first to debut a new Super Bowl ad https://t.co/hvCK2zO1tF #Branding https://t.co/Ui59YMn9xA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing This squishy robot can catch fish on the fin https://t.co/JTyY4P38cH #TC https://t.co/tiK5m9ZbVe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing The State of Shopping Ads Report: What works, where and when https://t.co/yxRA5HSWEF #Sponsored]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Three paid social features you need to try in 2017 https://t.co/eQgUgXXyTT… https://t.co/UHkNk21Wtq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Recode Daily: Tech giants are planning a united stand against Trump's travel ban… https://t.co/P94TmZ9ePx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing The best APAC digital marketing stats from January 2017 https://t.co/4g9i7D4q31]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Are We Overdue For An SEO Revolution? https://t.co/39wPSl01Bp https://t.co/QqpDVlu2NR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Report: Pokémon Go has now crossed $1 billion in revenue https://t.co/fUaeo7524v #Apps https://t.co/xUeJDlDmIr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Online video has evolved, but has your brand’s comms strategy? https://t.co/UbrlJYlwir https://t.co/v2VdQSmJqW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing It’s official: Facebook wants to be your next TV https://t.co/wQIgTxr5q3 https://t.co/2RuqEGeORs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Instagram won’t fix Facebook’s ad load dilemma yet, but video might https://t.co/dULa9YdhjT… https://t.co/D9T62cd6XU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing 4 Ways to Find Untapped Keyword Ideas With Great Traffic Potential https://t.co/ZYytFzIj9K… https://t.co/dVp7WzqSG0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing ClearMotion lands $100M to swap software for car shocks and boost self-driving UX… https://t.co/g7hEjgdbe6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Speaking, Storytelling, and Making Sense of the World https://t.co/SglD9oOt7A #Podcast https://t.co/eK457te1K8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Does ‘buy now, pay later’ reduce mobile basket abandonment? https://t.co/XsI0OLmvA4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing The most treasured mobile marketing trends for 2017 https://t.co/LEMkInfrTW #Sponsored https://t.co/WapEXjctAq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Customercentricity: A Big Word That's Even More Strategic Than It's 18 Letters Indicate… https://t.co/J6o47Jz9in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Act now: SMX West early bird rates expire next week https://t.co/YppT1OrewV #ChannelCMOZone https://t.co/W6I01hNW19]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Cardlife is yet another SaaSsy management tool https://t.co/NfJKQnojYI #Europe https://t.co/ybrbyAersA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing How publishers manage header bidding: Server-to-server vs. browser-based wrappers… https://t.co/fzZ7h0P2Lf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Recode Daily: Trump picks Judge Neil Gorsuch for the Supreme Court and sets up a Senate battle… https://t.co/9Tq4qixuTy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Pinterest introduces Search ads with Keyword and Shopping campaigns https://t.co/Or8TcdeHCq… https://t.co/X9fJtfwK0f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing How Ebay Sellers Can Increase Sales With Just a Few Tweaks https://t.co/fvSdqmjbN3 https://t.co/eUv8jhvQoH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Facebook, Google &amp; Amazon need to adopt a Walled Garden 2.0 approach or they will face a decline…… https://t.co/X25sE6hxQn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing ForeScout Technologies filed confidentially for IPO https://t.co/HsPv4B1JVq #Finance https://t.co/WzuXhvMCXa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing ‘It’s hard to find thinkers and doers’: The challenges of hiring programmatic experts… https://t.co/SmzPLZObwE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Watch: The paper-airplane drones that may one day save your life https://t.co/UzPEU2yGFJ https://t.co/eniLWmHhku]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Marketing Day: Snapchat’s ad tech, Budweiser’s Super Bowl ad &amp; Facebook news… https://t.co/A8o94ygPQA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing In Silicon Valley, plotting to get foreign-born workers to Vancouver https://t.co/P0nP8AQ3Xq #TC https://t.co/wnMVmZ0afP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing The Secret to Business Growth https://t.co/qFC5mPmwIy #MarketingConsultant https://t.co/aoMlEOMIoR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Prudent UX for banking? Monzo designs 'positive friction' https://t.co/8vJZ29a6Bm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Entertainment and lifestyle publishers thrive even as interest in hard news spikes… https://t.co/oiC62jCVzA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Meet The CEO Building A $75 Million Global Landmark For African American History… https://t.co/Lujc2b0CmD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Facebook opens its ad network’s video ads to independent… https://t.co/2wsX4ZkXFC… https://t.co/PHWZVkshIF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Challenging job search and HR giants, Comparably raises $7.25M https://t.co/4UUVtPhaTx #TC https://t.co/RznGnqiXIT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing ‘It’s our lifeblood:’ How publishers meet the video challenge in 5 charts https://t.co/qvMIUGlzp6… https://t.co/ipV9igcCDi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing How travel tech evolved over three decades during my three trips to Russia https://t.co/lq3mKpuFI7 https://t.co/FD2RQGWg6N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Square offering merchants $12K in free payment processing with Apple Pay https://t.co/n6IZZqGkAH… https://t.co/OxT9e4GbOj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing How We Branded BIOHM, The Tesla Of Probiotics https://t.co/hKIR7DrNH0 https://t.co/9zfDeeR0Hp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing Google’s bad ad report: A mixed blessing for ad quality https://t.co/vb16M6XTtq https://t.co/bNFPfHOC5k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing We need startups to build democracy tech https://t.co/ix0A0qZTgD #Apps https://t.co/B0qkvHFEqb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#digitalmarketing ‘Real change needs to happen:’ Publishers shrug at platform overtures https://t.co/JQuEIuP5SN… https://t.co/v4M4xXLTyl]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>