<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["Alternative facts" 😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So thoughtful of Santander to redefine prosperity, just after cutting the interest rate on my account.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see Comical Ali is back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GaryLineker don't understand why you give this bloke the time of day tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jeremy's batch of jam better be a corker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Realised why May speech outside parliament: so Hammond can simultaneously announce to parliament we are leaving the single market. Diversion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jjdens indeed, just bobbing and weaving. Mr cool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LydiaJane13 I had the same reaction when I heard he'd been knocked out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still think they're 20 runs short]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paperclipracket it's on tomorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Mensa rule proven again https://t.co/ytjuvvFaUR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@profanityswan any idea why he went? He was great fun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mo_Liverpool and yet, so sure of themselves]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@norcrosscricket his sister is probably good enough to make the team also. Reached the semi final of the men's straight pool world champs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bakewellstephen haha, you were Time Person of the Year 2006, or were you not aware?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bakewellstephen trivial pursuit at Xmas? Of course.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bakewellstephen not that I'm comparing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bakewellstephen and you in 2006.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jjdens masterchef on catch up for me. Vikings over the weekend at some point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GabbyLogan in the cup, yes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you left your iphone on the westbound platform at Wanstead tube tonight, I've handed it in to the station staff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ErinNYC75 I'd laugh, if only everything wasn't so fucked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paperclipracket told you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@btsportcricket can someone pass on the details of the drs rule change to Mark Taylor please?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And Smith is being his usual contemptible self]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia are currently 16/5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We shouldn't be surprised that the man can barely dress himself https://t.co/dDmSG75S3C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paperclipracket @jjdens aha. Never seen it. Is it like the South Bank Show?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paperclipracket @jjdens got confused with Jonathan Richman there and was about to take you to task. Who is Adam?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilippeAuclair the handle is outrageous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilippeAuclair what a mug!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lygd ffs. You ok? Just a flesh wound?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The mind boggles https://t.co/mUnIGTNPYI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BizFleury I think you're being very optimistic there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natluurtsema how exciting!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tompeck labour leadership election?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking: yahoo has 500m users, or more! https://t.co/g9mswWaoIT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paperclipracket also my hometown.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More updates as we get them, stay tuned. https://t.co/twFfBgGTz8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crwbanod @paperclipracket not a horse-whisperer then?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crwbanod @paperclipracket he's over-egging that a little. Certain colleges, definitely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cynic would say he's deliberately trying to get sacked https://t.co/VtHv0xzBft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thameswater it returned to normal after a couple of hours. I'm assuming nobody mans this account at the weekend?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thameswater hi, any idea when water will be restored to E11 Wanstead area?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The disgraced Liam Fox is basically trying to get out of a job he knows he can't succeed at, isn't he?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lygd well, yes. But I can't help but think that someone with such obvious social problems would be rejected quite often.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lygd wt actual f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goal against Barca from the only Yorkshireman in La Liga: Ibai Gomez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ErinNYC75 bang on. Schmeichel did extremely well to keep that to 4.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apart from the obvious, Lucas has been excellent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jjdens and you've just lost the Keith Vaz game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jjdens there are an infinite number of universes where he's died during Vaz/Oaten-style fun times though. And that's indisputable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jjdens @paperclipracket spent 10% of his life at the crease in the roses match.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paperclipracket finger on the pulse (possibly)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sod off mate https://t.co/Iuk1Ihp923]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This fielding is not at all suspicious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KEStorey ugh. That's horrible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like I've missed the cricket then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stage_manager think you should meet her just in case]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stage_manager *cough* *cough* https://t.co/GuhHulkrFY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paperclipracket you're kidding nobody there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can highly recommend this https://t.co/VBoOYILIoF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FryRsquared watched it last night. Absolutely superb work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh my. The Quincy Jones prom must've been so much fun to play.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The axis of the earth is tilted 23.5 degrees. Meaning Dan Roan's head is actually held up straight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marchant, Marchant....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So many good sports that could take the place of boxing at Tokyo 2020. IOC shouldn't put up with this shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thoughts @Susie_Dent ? https://t.co/L687aV47zQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mo_Liverpool indeed mate. That's a photo of it 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Durham's done a Terry Butcher. https://t.co/LLtsd2cwrg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bidlett is that on?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's hope he's more Ragnar Lothbrok than Cliff Klavan. Right guys?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How are we going to know the #coupplotters from the #coupplotters?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couldn't last until the end. Too awkward. Too clueless. https://t.co/v0Nftkiluy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilippeAuclair oh they are just waiting for their time to strike, I'm sure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leadsom's supporters are trying to defend her thus: "she says at the start she doesn't want to be nasty". The "I'm not racist but" preamble.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@martynziegler to be fair, she may have made that up too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theanalyst absolutely deadpan delivery from the analyst there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nickw84 did he do "the babestation" again? #callme]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unbelievably, I'm seeing people on here, thinking that that wasn't a penalty. World's gone mad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish the BBC would employ someone who can pronounce Boateng. It's been my pet hate of the tournament. Along with the poor quality footy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Given the UK's recent performance at the polls, you can't really rule out a vote for the complete fraud.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The disgraced Liam Fox, leaves in disgrace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Third favourite to be the next England manager and doesn't understand zonal marking. https://t.co/i32T284Vj9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@liz_buckley that's adorable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man who thinks he can "cure" gay people thinks he can cure our current political, social and economic woes. Forgive my scepticism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What an absolute shitshow this is. 

 https://t.co/pvwuyUs4Ez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Martha_Gill 'tis but a scratch!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@josh_t12 @Vitu_E wow! Missed that one. I clearly sleep too much at night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vitu_E joking aside, their DJs are superb. Just classic party tunes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vitu_E we need to import some kiwi cricket DJs, to show us a positive brand of DJing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LydiaJane13 I never did understand why he's not called Eidur Arnorsson.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May I suggest a total and complete shutdown on white guys in baseball caps while we figure out what is going on?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John McCain doesn't know what "directly" means https://t.co/wHljNUalQQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jjdens they'll need to improve for that. Significantly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Evra is Rothen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glenn Hoddle pronounces "Sagna" as you would "Lasagne".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jjdens belgium reassuringly shite, mind you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jjdens I rushed it a bit. Based my view on Croatia on them having Suker up front and Biscan in midfield.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jjdens can't remember one where my predictions have been so wrong.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>