<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomasfoster96 I would love to see you on this show tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assault rates will always be high with the current model https://t.co/ch3Eu83ZtR #auspol #politas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is terrible - have you heard about this? @ASRC1 @Kon__K @thomasfoster96 #auspol https://t.co/iuzWhBGAmw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This shows how backward our government is. Once again, they've refused to stand up despite Canada &amp; UK doing so.… https://t.co/TULKD48s1i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now it all makes sense #auspol https://t.co/TxQNoacnfq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Much more debate this year around #ChangeTheDate. Let's hope parliament chooses to hear it. #alwayswasalwayswillbe #NoPrideinGenocide]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's #ChangeTheDate so we're not celebrating the start of systematic dispossession and genocide. #InvasionDay #Solidarity #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So accurate. There is nothing progressive about violence. #richardspencer #uspolitics #auspol https://t.co/7zp6mBZDKW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeathWhiley @unimelb @realDonaldTrump @tim_lynchphd @ArtsUnimelb @Government_UoM very good point (I hope)!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia Day lamb ad tackles Indigenous land rights and immigration – video https://t.co/sob00t7Nav]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All you people talking up over misuse of public funds need to shut up, you bloody socialists(!!!) #auspol https://t.co/zq3njdLWhX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SharifahZaliah @thomasfoster96 I say the Muslims are to blame, or maybe the gays(!!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@C31Melbourne is an @AuntyDonnaBoys Australia Day special planned for this year?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[what a kitsch selection!! @clientliaison @itscopycatt #triplejhottest100 https://t.co/Pfrc4Sam7U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope this is true, but very much doubt it @cassiusetc https://t.co/lOwW5Jn8o2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClarkCooley can I wear the colours at Jane commencement? @SharifahZaliah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SharifahZaliah I am also now looking for work, as the former NUS commentator himself. #poorstudent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomasfoster96 @SharifahZaliah collective tribal council from Dance Moms and Real Housewives of Melbourne to decide the fate?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ironic? Tell 'em they're dreaming. #auslaw https://t.co/v9tpkCqNlz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SharifahZaliah @peterhart648 Royal London Yacht Club embroidery also]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When ppl say white ppl have no culture. Umm sweetheart plz have you seen #NUSNatCon ?? @NUSnatcon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomasfoster96 very true!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomasfoster96 I'd argue the Jesus depicted in the Bible is generally a massive leftie tbh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will never understand the Christian Right. #auspol https://t.co/b1hYkgyyXO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheCalebBond @dailytelegraph he used to be the chair of the ARM. Is it really that surprising?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brighton Grammar needs to admit its toxic culture &amp; aim to fix it, not deny that it exists #auspol https://t.co/mwVFctS8nW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reflection on #nusnatcon: what's so bad about bipartisanship? Focus on outcomes &amp; doing what's right rather than political bollocks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So disgusting. Invest in some class and decorum @NUSnatcon. The official commentator has spoken. #nuscronin https://t.co/juUdcKihof]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kasterepai These posts are getting more and more disgusting #shame]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaciintaMx This is so disgusting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As another #NUSNatCon comes to a close, here is one last vid from your Official Commentator #nuscronin https://t.co/I32QRDhSnQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think @NUS_Welfare said it best about Enviro Department. Everyone who followed is stark raving mad. #nusnatcon #nuscronin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ana_stinc wow harsh, but no I am completely dedicated to my work. I was going to say like a Catholic priest, but maybe not the best idea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ana_stinc I'm not interested in any sexual or romantic prospects - only comedic material.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ana_stinc i'm just trying to have as bad of a sense of humour or a lack of like most student politicians.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ana_stinc you're a UNITy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ana_stinc it's a SAlty wound ://]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SharifahZaliah @heardatnatcon @ClarkCooley and something other than MB. Geez...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ana_stinc well + truly ripped]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SharifahZaliah wife goals @LauraCruse_]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SharifahZaliah @LauraCruse_ That's up for your interpretation, Sharif]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ana_stinc love it #nusromance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ana_stinc so accurate xoxo. What faction u in?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ana_stinc I think I'm slightly in love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heardatnatcon would this be me if i went? @SharifahZaliah @ClarkCooley #bigquestions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[replace communism with capitalism and this is SAlt #nusnatcon #nuscronin
https://t.co/uL9bNv1Uai]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[thoughts? #nusnatcon #nuscronin https://t.co/toeVYDhf4H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SharifahZaliah I would argue that SAlt are not the working class, and do not represent the working class.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[seconded #nusnatcon #nuscronin https://t.co/XpHakf6NnP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaciintaMx well I have staff obviously, plus I like to retain my independence from a distance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaciintaMx As I am commentating from outside Victoria, it would be difficult to transport ://]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaciintaMx Not referring to anyone in particular. Just calling their policy regressive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaciintaMx technically as official commentator, I'm fully independent. But let's talk after.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When a socialist protestor on SAlt's website is wearing a Ralph Lauren polo. That you? @ClarkCooley #nusnatcon… https://t.co/p16LCnWn75]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaciintaMx I find it odd that the far right probably has more progressive views on mental health/disability than SAlt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow April... I thought socialists liked trigger warnings? Also, can SAlt not say 'fuck' every 2nd word it's a bit rude. #nusnatcon #edgy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[accurate #nusnatcon #nuscronin #WhoIsCronin https://t.co/qeRUGwhWWf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch for a @ClarkCooley emerge at 1:47. #nusnatcon #nuscronin https://t.co/GFr9ZKQSH1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaciintaMx k this tweet was the closest thing to a longest yeahboi. I'm joining your faction. Which one is that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NUSnatcon Am I a real person or an NUS parody account. That is the real question. #nusnatcon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NUSnatcon seems a bit biased. Note: as independent official commentator, I am factionless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LauraCruse_ for your interpretation xoxo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hmm I wonder which faction the admin of the @NUSnatcon page is from #nusnatcon #nuscronin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heidilapaglia @NUSnatcon surely there wasn't before either??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NUSnatcon @SharifahZaliah who was the outgoing exec? Are you talking TUU or NUS Tas?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danprobert00 I thought the 2016 head honchos were all Indies?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SharifahZaliah @NUSnatcon Libs would have disaffiliated anyway, plus I don't think our Prez or GenSec are NLS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Continuing to stand against sexual assault and harassment on campuses and colleges is so, so important #nusnatcon https://t.co/gQS6l0ROBn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sugoogled what is a thot?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jackmcnally_ are you a fellow Ralph Lauren-wearing Labor supporter, comrade?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SharifahZaliah so true. *creates exclusive event for charity*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FarragoMagazine @honi_soit @togatus_  if you're interested let me know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@left_homunculus will be interesting to see]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To @FarragoMagazine @honi_soit et al, open call to interview me as official NUS commentator. #nusnatcon #nuscronin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What are factions doing re disability policy? #nusnatcon #nuscronin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I unlocked exclusive @MulgatheArtist prints and entered @CocaColaAU’s #SummerClassic competition. https://t.co/JlbqSnEOv1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will donate to whichever faction does a long yeahboi first #nusnatcon #nuscronin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me #nusnatcon https://t.co/JW7y9vM8bg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClarkCooley I like this for the Clueless gif]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty shocked at how many people seem to think it's ok to torture kids if they're crims. Is this Nazi Germany?  #auspol #dylanvoller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Completely agree with this. That said, also find it highly amusing that the US think they're in a position to criti… https://t.co/oGFA8Moo2d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danprobert00 no surprises there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_katiekendall_ probably because you still reference it in your bio? Doesn't seem like you've left it behind to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Says they're against exclusivity *goes to private student politics conference and votes against sharing any of it with public* #nusnatcon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ffs why do I pay for this. On the bright side NLS is the hottest side according to 2 polls. #nusnatcon https://t.co/BJYJlYdq2r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UPDATE: #nuscronin is awake and ready to take calls for comment. #nusnatcon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I unlocked exclusive @MulgatheArtist prints and entered @CocaColAU’s #SummerClassic competition. https://t.co/npml0jS7az]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cunning_Plot @thomasfoster96 @matthewhayden yeah literally me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cunning_Plot @thomasfoster96 @matthewhayden someone hasn't studied their criminology.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomasfoster96 @Cunning_Plot @matthewhayden what? surely there's only torture or walking free? revolutionary!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomasfoster96 @Cunning_Plot @matthewhayden also, you can kind of put someone in prison without torturing them. There is that option.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cunning_Plot @matthewhayden prison would be a good option. Torture not so much... I'm not against prisons, I'm just against torture.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matthewhayden It would really depend on the individual. It's a pretty vague statement that has little to do with political ideology.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HooGraham Also I don't think you understand. I'm not pro-crime or anti-prison, I'm just against torturing prisoners.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HooGraham lol so therefore you have no idea about his criminal history, but endorse torturing a child anyway.. nice!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HooGraham @300 It does deserve incarceration. It doesn't deserve torturing kids...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matthewhayden relevance? This is about kids having rights and not being tortured in prison, regardless of what they've done in the past.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How about we rehabilitate &amp; support youth offenders instead of depriving them of basic human rights? #dondale… https://t.co/RTBMD1Hwor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To those shaming Voller in comments and claiming that offenders shouldn't have rights, have a look at this.… https://t.co/xYj0JUskuj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's talk about Boycott CUB already... #nusnatcon #nuscronin]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>