<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Homophobia makes your food taste like shit. https://t.co/F9br43t2ng]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#SCOTUS So basically, we are going to have all of these religious people telling us what to do?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's important to stay clear of hypocrisy. We have to be. Address other immigrant bans. We can't stay quiet on them. #RefugeesWelcome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We, on the left have a responsibility to be honest and factual. Here is a fact about Bill Clinton. #RefugeesWelcome 
https://t.co/gzUdUqNCAv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigStu32900678 Yet Syrians are dying, but Trump throws them under the bus. But not Saudi Arabia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigStu32900678 Plus Iraq had nothing to do with 9/11. On the list. Most attacks here were barely committed by refugees.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigStu32900678 Plus I mentioned that Trump had business in Saudi Arabia. It's not on the list. Gonna address that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigStu32900678 Trump did not add Saudi Arabia, due to his business ties. https://t.co/rPrba503J1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigStu32900678 Giuliani called it a ban,  even your dear Trump called it that also.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigStu32900678 Is refugee ban better? According to the Atlantic All admissions would be stopped for 120 days; Syrians would be banned.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigStu32900678 I meant England. Just picture if they all denied Christians. And they were all seen as the KKK.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigStu32900678 I want to know if you are really this childish.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigStu32900678 Just imagine if Europe banned Christians. They would be the face of hypocrisy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigStu32900678 I would like Trump to be impeached because he uses religion to hurt others because of Pence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigStu32900678 Okay. I can see this is not a smart convo due to you side. But it's not butthurt to care for others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigStu32900678 Do you know how much people are hoping Trump gets impeached?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigStu32900678 If Obama did anything wrong, he wouldn't have lasted 8 years. The people would have voted him out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigStu32900678 And replace them with Goldman Sachs people, and billionaires? I thought you supporters wanted to drain the swamp.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigStu32900678 So, basically he is a sensitive man. This is about lives. We can't all protect his fragile ego.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshNoneYaBiz You supporting a man who wants to ban a certain religion will not be accepted in a better society.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshNoneYaBiz So no one should go against the president because you like him as much he likes himself?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just add strings to his arms. https://t.co/x5UIW4Ewz0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is disgusting that we are not getting our voices heard by the one who is supposed to listen. @realDonaldTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Store owner: What will you need today?

Me: I need two brass knuckles, please. https://t.co/TN4H8jxR5h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump: Tiny hands 

Supporters: Tiny Brains

Inauguration: Tiny crowds 

#boycottstarbucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#BoycottStarbucks If you want to know real evil, just ask a Republican how they feel about refugees getting jobs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh. So black lives matter now, huh? https://t.co/kw0RJ153OA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you get to close to the White House, you will notice everything has turned black and white. You are now in the 5… https://t.co/GrsXN42Rbm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah. Manufacture guns, but fail to work with solar energy companies. Maybe you could take your guns to the grave, huh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OGustavoGama Your hair is 👌]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump And the memes, and others pointing out his hypocrisy and fascism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The only thing I will enjoy about Trump's presidency is laughable tweets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You dropped something. https://t.co/AGmmovrfoC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He meant bad hombres. https://t.co/YFArMCQyZs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Maybe you should focus on solar energy jobs, instead of obsessing over oil. Think about the planet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ktgonkt This tweet is life in the purest form.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmandaaParkerr @kennabbby What did it say?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instead of building the wall with bricks, cement, or gates, we'll just use Bibles since so many Christians agree with Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America is in the hands of idiots. https://t.co/FQhnZVusqb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder if Jesus would visit Israel after this tweet. https://t.co/poVhxA0RQ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No wonder the Trump admin approves of Israel. #NoBanNoWall #MuslimBan https://t.co/YST0bGGoQA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT to let @MelanieLBBH know you want a show in your city! #WeDemandMelanieLBBH @WeDemand https://t.co/EgIWzpjQCI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mary Tyler Moore Buried at Private Funeral in Connecticut https://t.co/BxN3hYE6j3 via @UsWeekly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calling people snowflakes when they call out Trump will not change the facts. He is a hateful man. #MuslimBan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much for helping the unfortunate. 

 https://t.co/Khst78d4p2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do you get offended by somebody promoting healthy food, but are in favor of a restaurant spewing hate?… https://t.co/yzwCSN2dJC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She must not value her children if she believes other children should be taken away. #NoBanNoWall https://t.co/K9DiJM2365]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I know you want to impress your fans, but it's really affecting others. So I advise you to stop! #MuslimBan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Basically, Trump is affecting the ones who didn't agree with him. I haven't seen him do anything to the Christians.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God must have said be racist and xenophobic, because, you know. 
#ChristianHypocrisy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@armorist1776 Thank you. I'm a liberal JFK was a liberal, I'm proud. Bye old man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just picture how Christians would react if there was a ban on them. https://t.co/YBLMMyAiQU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@armorist1776 You are the one bringing up Hillary and Obama. It's irrelevant. Not very intelligent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@armorist1776 Okay. I'm a communist for trying to fix America. That's logical. https://t.co/55vhEXNNDe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@armorist1776 I said I'm not going anywhere. I'm going to fix this country however I can.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@armorist1776 For the last time, Trump is president. It's on him. Maybe you should tell him to stop tweeting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@armorist1776 America was never great. Slavery, Jim Crow, Suffrage, etc. I feel America is repeating itself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@armorist1776 I'm not going anywhere. This is where I belong. And I'll make sure make America great for everyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@armorist1776 You don't worry about healthcare, clean water for others? Have you heard of Flint Michigan?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@armorist1776 I'm talking about his cabinet. That swamp is not drained.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@armorist1776 He's declaring war on women, Muslims, and Mexicans. He's making America prejudice again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@armorist1776 You're not going to talk about his gag order?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@armorist1776 He is so thin skinned. All he talks about is people being "meanies."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@armorist1776 He is not going to undo protests, it is a right. All he does is cry over their opposition.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@armorist1776 Yeah, he can do that with the Goldman Sachs peeps. Don't think so. Bannon is not pro America. Millionaires is in the WH.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@armorist1776 He's even accused of messing with other elections. Do you trust Trump over the CIA?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@armorist1776 That's not the point. Putin is hurts other Russians, what makes you think he cares about America?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@armorist1776 Again. This is not about Hillary or Obama. It's about Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@armorist1776 Trump is not for the people, when he has no plan for healthcare and clean water but for a division wall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@armorist1776 And Trump is doing it with Russia. Hello? The sanctions!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@armorist1776 America first is bullshit. It's America only. If you really cared, you would lock up your American rapists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@armorist1776 This convo isn't going anywhere due to you not accepting Trump's corruption and discrimination.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@armorist1776 I'm 17. So I did not vote. But I supported Hillary. I informed you of who you probably voted for. Do you accept?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@armorist1776 How? What did liberals do? Did they chant build a wall, ban people, what?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@armorist1776 Last time I checked Hillary wasn't president. You can't point fingers anymore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@armorist1776 You accused me of not knowing what I was talking about, that is why I showed you the pic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@armorist1776 I don't watch cnn, though at least they don't support alternative facts. Look it up. https://t.co/dU8YoLqijD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@armorist1776 No, sweetheart, you need to be educated, Trump has business ties in Saudi. And they're not marked. https://t.co/Emq595rAxA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chuuzus She reminds of Sade.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Only Americans can kill other Americans. " https://t.co/mnQs9ixKbn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I like Trump because he tells it as it is."

Why did he say that?

"He didn't mean that!"

OK...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@armorist1776 The places Trump chose to ban had nothing to do with 9/11.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, let's all "move" to Islam. We'll all be floating on air. Bigots don't even know how to be bigots. https://t.co/Jyweoc5zcz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@armorist1776 And obviously, you will never be, so bye.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@armorist1776 Well civilized people call it hate speech.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NuckChorris81 What does Bush have to do with this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So according to Trump, @nytimes is more important than refugee lives. #muslimban https://t.co/hyMO6GFkm7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NuckChorris81 You mean like this? https://t.co/DClUa6sezR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When are we going to list Americans as terrorists? Remember the KKK? Mass shootings? Setting fire to mosques?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NuckChorris81 America is a hateful country. People really feel bold to spew hate, especially now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NuckChorris81 Don't flatter yourself. Europe is an option, and America was never great. Slavery was a trend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shia LaBeouf: Angry Jew

Michelle Obama: Angry black woman

Literal Nazi: Misunderstood https://t.co/CyPhc6Mjoi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We love our veterans!"

*criticizes Trump*

"Take away their healthcare."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NuckChorris81 @BNONews You really believe that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is how America treats others. https://t.co/ICPRj2fCr2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America is not a privilege anymore when it's controlled by hate. https://t.co/3rtlw5ypYY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one wants to do what you do.  @mike_pence https://t.co/1o1cOwni8N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrxngeGirl56 You let him do this. You let him attack other Americans and legal citizens. And it's disgusting that you watch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrxngeGirl56 Pence wants religious control over the non religious, and Trump wants control over you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrxngeGirl56 You went crazy over Trump because of his Religious VP, without realizing that they planned to hurt others...]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>