<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@mirtle If the #leafs get 93 or 94 points playoffs or not that's a pretty successful season]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This man is not human https://t.co/cjyyIOSbtp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andersen one win away from 100 for his career wonder if he will get a chance for it Monday against NYI #leafs #tmltalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marner Matthews and Nylander all with multipoint nights tonight Connor Brown as well #leafs #tmltalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffVeillette good luck with that...that joke will never die]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dalter which when you think about it is pretty crazy that 3 games is the longest skid they have had]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a game #Leafs didn't make it easy but they won in regulation huge 2 points]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roman Polak on the ice with 30 seconds left dear god #leafs #tmltalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love these #leafs no quit tonight!#tmltalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andersen has had no chance on most 9f these goals #leafs #tmltalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In my opinion if the whistles are away they should be away #leafs #tmltalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somehow the Bruins get a pp wow...#leafs #tmltalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matthews with 3 assists tonight #leafs #tmltalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brown! Thought for sure that Gardiner giveaway was going to end it #leafs #tmltalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see the refs have put the whistles away #leafs #tmltalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do the #leafs know the game is tied? Holy dump outs man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll take this game over the game against the Stars or Blues games thanks #leafs #tmltalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PuckDontLie sure he's had a bad night but that doesn't mean he should be put on waivers or permanently in the press box]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Totally_Offside I'll take Hunwick Marchenko I guess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PuckDontLie oh they are not in terms of play but neither should take the amount of heat they do on here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really would like to see a Marincin Marchenko pairing tomorrow night but alas I know this won't happen #leafs #tmltalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People love Matt Martin and Roman Polak and hate Jake Gardiner and Martin Marincin https://t.co/VvXSazMLoN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey look Polak with a bad pinch...and Marincin has to cover https://t.co/4JBPZTzRJt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteveBurtch people have their minds made up your talking to a wall...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marincin I'm trying to get people to like you...your not helping me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffVeillette playing with Polak and the 4th line a lot does not help him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is going to be a long third period in #Leafs nation #tmltalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matt Martin is dumb...why fight and get the crowd back into the game? #leafs #tmltalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I go to the kitchen and miss Nylander getting a hat trick... #leafs #tmltalk https://t.co/Bn4XsGtTiY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making dip for Superbowl Sunday going to be delicious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 4th line is the only line who is struggling right now #leafs #tmltalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really like Gardiner and Marincin so I'm just going to point out when they make good plays #leafs #tmltalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marincin has a really nice shot and draws a powerplay! #leafs #TMLtalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andersen has settled in controlling puck much better now, nice play by Gardiner to push Pasternak wide #leafs #tmltalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ben Smith bless his heart is just not really very good #leafs #tmltalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matthews Kadri and Nylander is an insane line that will never happen long term #leafs #tmltalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a nice goal! Nylander and Kadri are great together #leafs #tmltalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's a pretty weak tripping call #leafs #tmltalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good response from the #leafs getting more zone time and chances need to do the right things and results will come #tmltalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Morgan Rielly limping off is not good for the #leafs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Andersen has looked bad lately" *was third star of the week last week and had 2 shoutouts #leafs #tmltalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@draglikepull @NHL you know it's not going to be the time they say it will though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally a trade that involves an actual NHL player ... Predators going for it, though I'm not sure Fiddler will help that much]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your trying to eat healthy and you see a picture of cake on twitter https://t.co/S9x96xK7hI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every time I watch Crazy Stupid Love I think how great would it be if Ryan Gosling would show up in my life and help me with a new wardrobe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait the Avalanche actually won a game? Isn't that against the rules? https://t.co/YaW5bn3yMs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[32 games left in the #leafs season after tonight, this game is important yes but still going to be lots of season left after]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Totally_Offside plus the NHL needs to add West teams not lose them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taking both strikers off is a bit confusing, I know with 10 men want to sit back but at least pretend we might go forward sometimes #AVFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come on #AVFC get another, we need a win]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If your not watching #WSHvsMTL right now on @Sportsnet tune in; great fast entertaining hockey being played]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Board delay has not slowed down this game! These teams are going at it #WSHvsMTL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know I said I wanted to watch hockey all day, but I didn't mean I wanted the game to take all day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is why we need to score more than 1 goal #AVFC ...can't rely on the goalie right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have never seen a board dasher have to be replaced mid game #MTLvsWSH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewBerkshire embrace the dark side]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some great afternoon hockey being played between  #Caps and #Habs right now...of course there is a hole in the boards to interupt play]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Capitals open the scoring in what has been a fast paced first so far..Jay Beagle beating Price #WSHvsMTL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thejustinfisher perfect world Corrado clears gets sent down #leafs trade Polak and play Marchenko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamWylde @Ronson1313 Aston Villa will be back, and we will get you next time Wylde! But probably not bc we have to get into the PL first]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's better #AVFC! More goals please https://t.co/RX7iKhSx4f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamWylde @Ronson1313 I think Arsenal is the least offensive top team to cheer for...maybe Tottenham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffVeillette exactly why would you play 2 rhd together when you have Marincin or Hunwick to play on the left]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think some are a little too excited about Marchenko. Do I hope the #leafs actually play him; yes. My hope is he is better than Polak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder if Corrado clears waivers...not like he has played much to entice other GM's]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@draglikepull is he better than Polak? This is the information I need to know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[* #leafs claim player * Twitter explodes*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope this means the #leafs are willing to actually play Marchenko preferably over Polak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Steve_Dangle and claimed Marchenko. ..welcome to purgatory Marchenko be free Frankie!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomFox90 wasn't me, but yes it is a rare combination of fan bases lol!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure I will get this lucky but it would sure be nice to see a #AVFC win and a #Leafs win today https://t.co/RIDfPTXYVi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure I like the Marincin- Polak pairing they looked pretty awful against the Blues...Hunwick Marincin would be better I think #Leafs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's important to see some improved play from the #Leafs tonight, getting 2 points against a rival would also help out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeteBlackburn apparently something people wear on their legs...IDK I don't get this new fashion trend...looks awfu… https://t.co/uLpkh3FhUc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope Scott Hogan does well today, and if he doesn't I hope #AVFC fans won't jump all over him...give the new boys some time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My reaction when I can watch hockey all day today https://t.co/ZocnxskFlf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Afternoon hockey today? Oh you bet there is!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DamoSpin they can't even keep their own lies straight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thejustinfisher The Fall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Bruins could be without Rask or Bergeron tomorrow night when the #Leafs come to town...need to take advantage of that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottcwheeler Still have a tough schedule going forward with so many games left, next 2 games important @ BOS and NYI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your boy Phil flying under the radar in Pittsburgh but still #Winning https://t.co/TNLj2UKy95]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its only 1130 but all the hockey games are done...that's weird]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ronson1313 is that even a real question? NYC all the way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ASU pulling out of Tempe arena deal means Coyotes left out in the cold once again...unless Suns need new arena might be running out of time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just realized how many Monty Python gifs are on twitter...oh yes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RamCNN @leafsweetie that whole thing is OUTRAGEOUS https://t.co/I2DR6hCDCH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Steve_Dangle @Sportsnet west coast bias and no cups probably doesn't help]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WongSN590 having DeRozan back would be nice for a start]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am I worried about the #Raptors yes, am I ready to fire the coach and make huge trades, no]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People calling for the #Raptors to fire Casey blow up the team... maybe let's give the team a little more time to get out of this slump?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crazy how quick this city has turned on T Ross #raptors #rtz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamWylde it's a love/hate thing with Corinne, she is very quotable though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KiSS925 @AdamWylde Corinne from #thebachelor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Say Yes to the Dress is my guilty pleasure don't @ me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OverDrive1050 "Leafs lose in Boston; Fans outraged over state of the franchise" #FutureHeadlines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davelozo Twitter was a simpler place before now it is a wasteland of depressing news and people trying to "stick to sports"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mirtle @rayferrarotsn @JasonGregor both teams hope to be in the playoffs...which will add even more games and if either has a bad series...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffVeillette @reddit I commented "sarcasm" I hope that suffices]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mirtle @rayferrarotsn @JasonGregor This is why I hope the Leafs can find some times to rest Andersen down the stretch 65 games is a lot]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>