<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@terriemiddlemas Sounds like the lad wants a g/f in name only, with none of the commitmentðŸ˜³ #In for a penny In for a Â£ Is how it should beâ˜º]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ALS_Fanzine Still among the poorest excuses for a footballer ever to pull on an #SAFC shirt...one Ball/Catts-style tackle changes nowtðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmmaMcfc93x Ditto. Been feeling crappy and listless for 3 days now ðŸ˜³â˜¹]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@safcianpeterlee 5 points with 15 games to go....more than 'recoverable'....even for Sunderland....can't see it happening this time thoughâ˜¹]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WiseMenSayPod #SAFC-hater Matt Le Tissier thought it was a red....but he would say that ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@safcianpeterlee Can't think of anything more depressing than a David Moyes press conference.... ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Iamrol The lad that won has my surname (different spelling), got 5 correct scores, the only one he got wrong was Sunderland! ðŸ˜³ #Super 6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kieronellis_21 Don't know what to make of it tbh Didn't see that one coming at all ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marathon_mick69 And that sole, 'token' substitution, did nowt to alleviate my totally-pissed-off-at-Moyes mood ðŸ˜’ #Safc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty sure Graham Taylor will be 'looking down' with that trademark smile tonight and a cry of "Do I like that!" ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #Arsenal 1 Watford 2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidNunn73 It's way beyond "worrying", David....any slim chances of a SIXTH successive 'escape' have now been firmly extinguished ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜’ #Safc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevinoneillmitt Exactly. And the chances of signing an "affordable" forward (of the quality needed) who also happens to be a free agent? â˜¹]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sunderland1879 "Rodwell" and "superb" in the same sentence??!! ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜‚ #Oh, come on!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moyes is officially a tit. "Ulloa or no one"ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜ˆ Apparently he didn't want to go "further down the list" of his striker targetsðŸ˜’ #FFS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@safcking You're right, it's not enough (unfortunately)....given that Palace &amp; Swansea both wonðŸ˜’ðŸ˜’ But it's still a point no one expectedðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Swansea &amp; Palace both winning ðŸ˜’ðŸ˜’ #FFS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fannewssafc the VERY best â˜¹ #but so far, so good ðŸ‘ #ha'way the lads ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OrwiteTreacle But shocking refereeing decisions are ten-a-penny every fecking weekðŸ˜³ Are they therefore even worth mentioningðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OrwiteTreacle So I heard....but Lee Mason (just a YARD away?) inexplicably failed to do us a favour and send the useless cunt off ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ridderz86 No fan more 'bereft' than me about Borini ðŸ˜³â˜¹]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh fuck....Le Tissier covering our match on Gillette soccer special on #ssnhq ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜ ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SunderlandAFC Let's just try to keep the score respectable tonight, lads ðŸ‘ #had our bellyful of embarrassments &amp; humiliations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just seen the team....Fraudwell in starting 11 ðŸ˜³ #FFS ðŸ˜’ #Safc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leemcm1976 Hard game for Boro, maybe, but not compared to ours....  ðŸ˜“ðŸ˜‰ #SAFC #Ha'way The Lads]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ridderz86 calibre, surely means the death knell is now tolling at the SOLðŸ˜³â˜¹ Doubtful those 'voids' can be filled via #free agents]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ridderz86 Failing to bring in some pace, plus a big man up top to compensate for Vic's enforced absence, AND a cb of, say, Jagielka's]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChloeStrattonxo Not going myself. Could've used my mam's season card but didn't take up offer #Will know soon enough if right decision ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PawleySteven ZILCH happening, mate ðŸ˜³â˜¹ Be interesting to see what tonight's attendance is? #crazy fixture scheduling ðŸ˜’]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ALS_Fanzine Moyes spins the Wheel of Fortune....and yet again it stops at Everton ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜‚ #Sunder-ton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinMackevtra That simple &amp; sensible philosophy has proved to be beyond the comprehension of a succession of Sunderland managers....ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜ˆðŸ˜’]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkySports_Keith Great news ðŸ˜‚ But NOT the time we've wasted pursuing this player ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜’]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ALS_Fanzine NO ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ (not even HALF that) #move on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1973anth03 Think we'd be paying way more than just a couple mil over the oddsðŸ˜³ #not worth it with Ulloa imo #need to look elsewhere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@safcking Now THAT'S a way more attractive proposition ðŸ˜‚ #Leicester, they (continue to...hopefully!) say 'NO' ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimmy_chop @dpcoverdale Championship team, would be invaluable to them and ultimately beneficial to #SAFC (especially if we're relegated?)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimmy_chop @dpcoverdale would only be counter productive. BUT, the 'experience' they'd gain by going out on loan to say a mid-table]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimmy_chop @dpcoverdale I agree....players from the U23s should only be 'blooded' when the team is winning games &amp; doing well. Doing so now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nightmar3s23 @SkySports_Keith bloody hope so ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkySports_Keith Hope that 'light' stays RED until 11 o'clock tonight ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SunderlandEcho @SunderlandAFC   FFS!!! ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜’ #MOVE ON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donjuan72FTM love a "double negative" on TDD ðŸ˜‚ think your probs right, though â˜¹]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@roker_71 Wish you could have a whole year of them â˜º x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@safcianpeterlee You forgot 'scouse- turned-geordie' in between the words 'fat' and 'bastard'ðŸ˜‚ And you missed off 'who ate all the pies'ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dpcoverdale Which is crazy, when Moyes pretty much refuses point blank to put any of them on the pitch in a first team gameðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dpcoverdale Please God, let it be Jack Rodwell ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Safc1879_ @MaxHanaghan Think you're probably right on both countsðŸ˜³ Although paying over the odds for any player is still hard to acceptâ˜¹]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaxHanaghan Exactly ðŸ˜³â˜¹]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JHunterChron Pity....Moyes could have had an "embarrassment of riches" to choose from tomorrow night! ðŸ˜‚ #Safc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkySports_Keith Then we've paid over the odds for them....sadly the norm nowadays, but we shouldn't complain after getting Â£14m for pvaðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidNunn73 But has Ulloa proved he can replicate his Championship goalscoring feats in the PL? Above Â£3 mil has to be a "no-go" imo ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevinoneillmitt @TheMightyNews and they've NO chance of getting that, imo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leemcm1976 So I heard. All of this is the last thing Boro need when you're only a few points above the bottom three....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidNunn73 Go elsewhere....despite the 'imperativeness']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leemcm1976 Totally. Can't be having a manager slagging off the fans....that's a line u just don't cross ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NDJ0602 Anything above THREE mil for Ulloa would be daylight robbery ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JHunterChron Hopefully back for Southampton game, then #Pickford #Safc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leemcm1976 That is one very pissed-off managerðŸ˜³ Sounds like Karanka himself may want out ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ridderz86 @JohnnyR1Red He takes that 'dour' reputation bestowed on many Scots âš½ managers past &amp; present to a whole new level imo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ridderz86 @marco_ten Id put Flo on the list of players who, for multitudinous reasons, we should never, ever, have even attempted to signðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ridderz86 @marco_ten I remember Bellion, of course, but no1 could touch Gabbiadini for pace ðŸ˜‚ #blistering]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MVG is a like a fuckin MACHINE, a flawless ROBOT ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ #Masters ðŸŽ¯ champion-in waiting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevinoneillmitt @MaxHanaghan @welderboy34 honestly believe relegation now would be a disaster on a par with 1987 and the old 3rd divisionðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daveg_safc @MaxHanaghan @welderboy34 @kevinoneillmitt In 46 yr Iv never 'accepted' shit in any form, same goes for our numerous relegations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@s26kel ImpressiveðŸ˜ŠðŸ‘ In my 'away days' - a mini-lifetime ago, now ðŸ˜‰ - I only beat that total once (equalled it twice) #SAFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@welderboy34 @kevinoneillmitt Exactly. And those frustration levels are immense ðŸ˜³â˜¹]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@roker_71 The Power's match had (just) finished when I got in from taking my boy home to his mamâ˜¹ â¤ a bit of the darts #The Masters ðŸŽ¯ #itv4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OrwiteTreacle @podmundo @leon_flint @Mattyosafc We did with Phillips/Quinn and a decade earlier Gabbiadini/GatesðŸ˜‚ Suppose we could again...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@welderboy34 I agree mate. God, it's depressing, isn't it â˜¹ #that's Sunderland all over]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OrwiteTreacle @podmundo @leon_flint @Mattyosafc We'd be "bashing our bishops" every week ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mattyosafc Minimum of FOUR signings needed but doubt we'll make even oneðŸ˜³ Moyes fuckin well &amp; truly shafted any miniscule chance we hadðŸ˜’]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UlloaðŸ˜³ FFS SunderlandðŸ˜³ You can't be seriousðŸ˜³ #enough said]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Referee Martin Atkinson not exactly covering himself in glory today ðŸ˜³ #shocking #useless wanker #Milwall v Watford #FA CupðŸ† #bbc1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@terriemiddlemas If you were awake  before 8:30 on a Sunday morning, do u need one? ðŸ˜‰ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaxHanaghan Iv noticed thatðŸ˜† HATE double-barrelled names at best of timesðŸ˜³ #naff #pretentious #and totally incongruous with âš½ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leemcm1976 Former Sunderland loan player too (during his 1st Boro spell)...and the goal ironically set up by ex-SAFC mf Grant Leadbitter ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marathon_mick69 a pretty forlorn hope, I think, Mick â˜¹ #Safc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jayne__90 Two out of three ain't bad, Jayne ðŸ˜‰ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@azysafc That's now TWELVE 'away' FAðŸ† ties without a win for the geordies                                              ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #FTM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EddyBlackadder One so cunning, you could put a tail on it and call it a weasel ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["players in"....thanks to the monstrosity that is FFP we can't do the latter without selling at least one, probably 2, players ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜’]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul MersonðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ "criminal" his opinion of SAFC decision to sell pva...then virtually in next breath he states the bloody obvious that we need]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChloeStrattonxo Actually there ARE some very cute pics of me from back thenðŸ˜‚ Something clearly gone horribly wrong in the years sinceðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChloeStrattonxo How cute r u?! ðŸ˜‰ðŸ˜ƒ #wish I could say same of pics of me as a bairnðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaxHanaghan So iv just discoveredðŸ˜³ Still, even 10m would be huge profit of 8.5m and surely we could never have expected that on pva!ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChloeStrattonxo Isn't it just ðŸ˜‚ and trying to explain to my boy why Sunderland aren't playing today is a small price to pay for that ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@9December1892 @ALS_Fanzine 1996? No, as recently as 2009, actually....Mags n Smoggies were BOTH relegated while we stayed upðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SAFCliveupdates Oviedo then, please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootsySAFC Don't know about clubs and chatting up girls...pub(s), pool, and an Indian were my staple Friday night 'recipe' for 20+ yr ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@safc_lex Seriously doubt the fee will be anything like Â£14m but it'd be a refreshing change for #Safc to do OUTSTANDING business on a saleðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thecentretunnel (2/2) shirts; and the most ðŸ˜« boring ðŸ†Final in the rich history of England's (sporting) 'Twin Towers'ðŸ˜³â˜¹ #joy unbounded #not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thecentretunnel Crap team; a should've-been-stoned-to-death chairman whose name was narcissistically emblazoned across the players' (1/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaxHanaghan Shocking decision from Clattenburg ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootsySAFC Doubtless that's trueðŸ˜³  And yet instead of Darren Bent the "legend" he will be remembered in Sunderland as Darren J. IscariotðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TarquinSmythe73 Yeah...am now wanting them to preserve or extend this 2-1 lead ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McClaren's 'brolly' has been noticeable by its absence in the rain at Pride Park tonight ðŸ˜‚ #lessons of past ridicule learned? #dcfc #lcfc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TarquinSmythe73 Yeah, they'll finish above at least 5 other teams I reckon mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TarquinSmythe73 We may appear to be, but we've been here so often I'm taking nowt as a given #still time if not much in way of genuine hope]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TarquinSmythe73 have 'distraction' of the ðŸ† for as long as poss in hope it has adverse effect on their league form/benefits us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TarquinSmythe73 Not sure about that. Those teams around/close to SAFC in PL who like us are in a relegation battle Id prefer them to have]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Parkersafc Id be first in the queue! ðŸ˜‚ Wish we WOULD make a bid for Gabbiadini, just for the hell of it ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>