<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The official @EAMaddenNFL #SB51 Prediction is here! Who are you picking to win? #MyMaddenPrediction = #PatriotsWin https://t.co/9L03p3AzVP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DubDotDUBBY @EASPORTS_MUT @EAMaddenNFL care to comment on this story?  https://t.co/HHzSGZEgvT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Raptors becoming a theme lately]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AbbyMartin wow.. that guy is a nutjob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timandsid it's an exhibition game.  Who cares?  I'd rather they just have a fantasy draft and add a few hall of famers and celebs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jon_Call_David when I glanced at the tv I thought the same for a moment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fs1otoole sorry Dan, should have clarified it wasn't specifically towards you but the people all across twitter attacking the kid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fs1otoole it's been speculated he has Autism.  Make fun of the father or his adult children, but leave the 10 year old out of it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Inauguration No nation is rich enough to pay for both war and civilization. We must make our choice; we cannot have both. Abraham Flexner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rambobiggs Russia behind the professional protesters?  Lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OriginalYoni looks like a professional protest group to me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rambobiggs @YouTube Bill just be doing Bill things]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarissaRoberto exactly..never heard a president basically rip and insult all the politicians sitting behind him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bruce_arthur I do like that he spend 10 minutes insulting all the politicians before him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bnicholsonsmith Sanchez is the ace and Marcus is the 5th]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What I Learned From the Intelligence Report on "Russian Hacking" https://t.co/TPgz9TxrJV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RexDEAFootball @TeamFIacco @JohnBarelli8 flacco fan.   That says it all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaddenBible what are they keys (personal wise) for setting up a lock down 4-4 for 3rd and short and red zone defence?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealAlexJones it's a shame Michael Hastings isn't alive right now.  We need a journalist like him on our side]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeRiouSMoE1 the hair reminds me of that scene from Something About Mary :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeRiouSMoE1 EA and the NFL are a perfect match for each other]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FAN590 @jonmorosi @ItsDeanBlundell @BennisSnet @Sportsnet there are no offers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timandsid that's awesome sauce right there.  Can't beat the love for your child.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sgibs7 @MaddenBible aww look at the backseat for Farls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeRiouSMoE1 MF Peters is a goon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SNJeffBlair @Wilnerness590 Cav to the Raps feels like the A's to the Jays in the late 80s early 90s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeRiouSMoE1 definitely not Kiv.  His reads are in braille]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Muthead they should have kept Moss to be the Goat set.  Still had the NAT 87 Moss in solos and released some other WR legend a few back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Muthead 5 tickets should be 85-87 elite.  15 tickets 87-90 elite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EASPORTS_MUT once again, catering to the 30 year olds at home living in Mom's basement]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProblemWright @smokedope4life lag seems to be the problem with most of my misses.   The speed of the meter changes as well which f's me up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Muthead what can I get for 20 tickets? Lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clutchsilver Walker hasn't lived up to the hype.  Better to get something now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrGoldenSports thank god for SC this year.  Most of the cheesier dirt bags hang there now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsDeanBlundell Vegas..because I expect that shit from greasy Montreal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BleacherReport so how long till they move ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@the_ironsheik so why did he defeat Lesner so quickly?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeBatardShow Jeff Fisher looks like he's from a Magnum Pi rip off who drives a Fiero]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EASPORTS_MUT swerve me up a plate of glitch stuffing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@uneedseattlebum @thatdudecarter3 Blount has that pop you need sometimes.  so many times a perfectly timed hit and knocked the ball out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MUTGuru @Panthers 84 speed?  That's it?  Plus his base with tier 2 cover linebacker Chem ftwk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't think 'posse' was used more as a elitist slam towards Lebron's friends then it being racist @ItsDeanBlundell @RYANFABRO590]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OwensDamien because that appealed to the lowest common denominator, and they came out in numbers to vote for him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeRiouSMoE1 making 18 mil at the backup position is pretty sweet as well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Muthead game changer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MUTGuru not sure who to ask, can we get the draft champs stadium for regular h2h Mut please?  Love playing in that stadium]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First they swerve us with pack odds and now with actual game play #MaddenSwerve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jon_Call_David for the 4-5 year deal he was looking for]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jon_Call_David the wasn't going to be a replacement for EE.   This signing is an acceptable replacement at DH though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Muthead @ZAN_4PM @YouTube agree 100%. Preach on Zan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ImSteveyJ @MrGoldenSports @RexDEAFootball @RG_Madden just find s glitch that counters this glitch..and so on and so on..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewStoeten I like the move.  He's solid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewStoeten who is actually thinking that? Good grief]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MUTGuru I take 2 weeks off Madden and feels like I've missed a year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bottom of the barrel  #Next4YearsIn4Words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeRiouSMoE1 swerve is a bitch move by bitch players]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#proudtobecanadian #TRUMPapocalypse #USElection2016 https://t.co/MF04XZ8t11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YourAnonNews a vote for the establishment or a vote for racism/sexism bigot.. clearly America spoke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America, go sit in the corner for the next 4 years and think about what you've just done. #proudtobecanadian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America just got in bed with the worst kind of slump buster.  Enjoy that walk of shame this morning @RYANFABRO590 @ItsDeanBlundell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey America, how's that walk of shame this morning? #ElectionResults]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YourAnonNews the real issue was these were the best two candidates from supposedly the "best" country in the world]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DamoSpin his victory shows the bigots and racists done need to hide anymore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vegas got odds up yet on when Trump gets impeached?  @RusicSN590 @RYANFABRO590 @ItsDeanBlundell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YourAnonNews just a figure head.  I'm more concerned with the Supreme Court]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pyroinfernia @CohhCarnage I'm sure Vegas already has odds out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewStoeten USA already had their mulligan with that second Bush term.  They deserve to wear this one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DJ_Sneak Republicans will work to undermine him.   He'll be impeached in record time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#countdowntoimpeachment #ElectionNight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GroupAnon sorry America.  You need to wear this one and sit in the corner for the next 4 years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanKnapton @YourAnonNews We Canadian will gladly pay for it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YourAnonNews we've reached our crazy limit.  Please come again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edstetzer I blame it on the Cubs using up the universe's good karma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmyMek yeah a vote for a rich, old white guy who cheats the system is a revolution lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@the_ironsheik crickets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AwesomEmergency pretty much.  We have room up here in Canada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@the_ironsheik USA could really use a camel clutch right about now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cdlowell @Zeisberger well maybe babies of kissing cousins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhitneyCummings you're drunk America.  Go home]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JShahryar but the walk of shame will be epic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SNFaizalKhamisa @Zeisberger classic, old school and great use of the state in question.  5 stars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ochocinco @Zeisberger Florida need a timeout from voting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't worry Trump.  Canada will gladly pay for our wall #ElectionNight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RandallHandle Vegas odds up on when Trump gets impeached?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffSammut yes.  Vegas odds must be up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YourAnonNews scratch NC off the vacation list]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SNJeffBlair @ClintIrwin I wonder who Barker voted for]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YourAnonNews add another to the list of States I'll never visit moving forward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FUT_CrUnK_MUT @MrGoldenSports you realize the GOP controlled house hasn't allowed anything to happen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrGoldenSports America tanking for next year's 1st round pick?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BennisSnet epic walk of shame tomorrow morning for our neighbours to the south]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pattonoswalt America is gonna have one epic walk of shame in the morning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America is gonna have quite the epic walk of shame in the morning  #ElectionNight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least now I'm confident I will never visit the mid west..EVER #ElectionNight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America, you need to go sit in a corner and think about what you've done.  #ElectionNight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheGarfoose you guys used on your mulligan on that Bush election. Now you guys need to go sit in a corner and think about what you've done]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YourAnonNews now Biff is gonna be president]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YourAnonNews I blame it on the Cubs winning the WS.  Threw the whole universe out of wack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DamoSpin start the clock on Trump's impeachment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FadooBobcat Ohio is Red]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>