<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Nailfie moment while me and Little Miss watered the gardens - - with the tiniest watering can but it was an... https://t.co/6Mg9X6z9Oo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New to Jamberry or been a fan for a while but don't have some of the tools, then this Bundle is awesome and made... https://t.co/0Dnb6Hin2B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These cute boxes in the doorstep are my favourite thing! â¤
.
.
.
.
.... https://t.co/EOjXiXoPs2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where is summer? Rain,umbrellas, puddles.... school pickup in the rain! â˜”ï¸â˜”ï¸
.
.
.
.
.

#rain#puddles... https://t.co/D4OCHFmUKm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm ordering on Thursday if anyone would like to order with Free Shipping - just message me to order..... or shop... https://t.co/bKkd6Ct8pT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/N9dxtviEVA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrating a beautiful Wellington summers day with a fittingly beautiful floral and fancy Jamberry #mani -... https://t.co/O6hPqynYWM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Summer - and a beauty of a summers day here in gorgeous Wellington! Celebrating with a summer #mani that's... https://t.co/PWAyocH7iV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a fridge magnet - one of three. When we had our little family,  I put the magnets to their height â¤ðŸ˜  
.... https://t.co/f736zGXmxF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We love FREE GIFTS with Purchases right? I'm always hoping my favourite brands have a gift with purchase... https://t.co/2A99WfjTfv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving Colour of the Year wraps released today.... Greenery - I love the Glittering Greenery design - I have that... https://t.co/ZGmvsqVoHz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Monday already! Feeling fresh and ready for sunshine with my #mondaymani â¤â¤ my signature look I think - glitter... https://t.co/VmWTrP3qui]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's not to love about a sunny Friday! Little Miss hitching a ride here for this selfie xx 
.
.
.
.
.
#love... https://t.co/QGDqKoHcJW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every year I put the most precious family photos of the year - from camera and phone cameras -  into our Family... https://t.co/cNrJkYLoFW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was photographing our garden's daisies today. There's just something about them that makes you smile and fell... https://t.co/0uccDYX7xo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New week. New mani. Fresh start. Beautiful Daisy from the garden. What's not to love about pretty nails on a... https://t.co/nxxSPbx6EY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a level of satisfaction with getting back to basics and parking technology to make pizza dough! Saturday... https://t.co/niIPgqco1g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This happened today!   I'm previewing them over here - I'd love you to join us  â¤ï¸ðŸ°ðŸ€... https://t.co/eQoeLBzcK8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell me I'm not the only one - new #mani or #christmas decoration you ask? ðŸ¤£ All Christmas decorations back in... https://t.co/jtJKBsAAzt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see a mixed mani in this outfit! A day outdoors today - fresh air and great adventures were the name of the... https://t.co/RjJxexFkhC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[25 minutes left of 2016 - my #2016bestnine ... Happy New Year â¤ #jamberrywithheather https://t.co/tU3xRBt721]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a year 2016 was! A fabulous year needs fabulous #mani - #trushinejn #onholidaytwistjn #pinkfizzjn... https://t.co/G7VVH7tFk7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My 'why' for pretty much every choice I make in life these days â¤â¤ My mini-me's and a wee happy dance for a cute... https://t.co/vnGPyjuLIy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Summer #mani .... love the December hostess exclusive and gorgeous #valleygirljn .... come on Summer catch up â˜€â˜€ðŸ’…ðŸ»ðŸ’…ðŸ» https://t.co/fEBewI1MmX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These two Boxing Day specials end at 11am today! 
Cuticle Care set $80
Style Box Exclusives - 2 wraps for $40... https://t.co/M16otvyuhj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello Boxing Day! The sun is shining, the paddle pool filling, leftovers being eaten .... lazy sunny family days.... https://t.co/fm6Tgxlm6k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All ready for #santa. Bling'd up with #lightitupjn and #bachelorettejn - just enough Christmas, sparkles and... https://t.co/lsaYmuiO7Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7.30am Christmas Eve! I need a coffee ðŸ˜´ and then there's a long list of chores around the home ðŸ¡ to complete and... https://t.co/LpkaKjVGMK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A little classic white for the last few days of Christmas week! #snowboundjn #whitechevronjn #jamberrywithheather https://t.co/zydzAt4BxK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This weeks Jamberry giveaway - such a gorgeous bag! â¤ https://t.co/eeTDYPLdIp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you want stylish nails? Ask me how! #Jamberry https://t.co/5AcmQuQfcs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A peek at Boxing Day specials is at the link below ðŸ‘‡ðŸ»... a place of information, early preview of what's coming... https://t.co/DDcc5cogk7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you have so many Jamberry wraps you forgot you'd sorted the New Years ðŸŽ†ðŸŽ‡ #mani ..... paired with some... https://t.co/iAWimO8qQA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see red, sparkle and Santas! A winning combo for Christmas ðŸŽ„ðŸŽ„ðŸŽ„ .... the kids are running around with santas on... https://t.co/V1oLqivXIh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello summer and French #mani.... I did my French tips using Trushine after seeing another consultants video and... https://t.co/nlX7C2ge7K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Monday! Frantically wrapping the kids gifts while I have an hour of alone time in the house! ... necessary... https://t.co/r0WW5LC9Ai]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love my Christmas tree and decorations - pretty much every single decoration has a story and the kiddos are... https://t.co/JRNyjmHwbO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My first Christmas #mani from last year popped up in my news feed today (about the same time my fab... https://t.co/Yp6JfvpVwn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a September baby so no surprises I LOVE sapphires &amp; sparkles and this #mani is no exception.  Mixed things up... https://t.co/CpNCMduzdK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#nakednails ðŸ˜³ .... but I'll tell ya - these nails take on the world - gardening, family, cleaning, life,... https://t.co/mAJ0ojuDrM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surprised the kids with a box of old decorations and they decided the back yard needed some extra Trees! The... https://t.co/ZTKwQYsK43]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So grateful for all the lovely hostesses and their friends that partied with me this year! I feel so lucky that I... https://t.co/U39YuEuVKk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This one is for the Frozen fans - The ultimate Christmas gift! Disney Collection by Jamberry - Disney Frozen &amp;... https://t.co/iodiaCGJ2Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love the Wellington Advent Calendar....something for everyone ðŸ˜˜https://t.co/1NB9YvJtgX https://t.co/Jqjb76vimS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy 1st December! ðŸŽ„ðŸŽ„ðŸŽ…ðŸ»ðŸŽ…ðŸ»   I promise you all this is the only elf photo from me on here  this festive season... https://t.co/OAxm7Wpdyc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top 20 wraps for November.....How many are in your collection!   I LOVE Metallic Chrome Silver.....Anything... https://t.co/54WCy9tv7A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When beauty boost meets Mexico . #nailfie perfection with #amoresciegosjn ..and the most exciting bit. _... https://t.co/RRS4pyeoO8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Summer toes - hello sandal ready pedi!! #fiercefuchsiajn with #geodiamondjn accents for the big toes!  Anyone... https://t.co/lq1dHaXD4J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeling very glam for the cocktail party this evening! First night away from my babies in at least 18mths! ðŸ˜²ðŸ’…ðŸ» https://t.co/8MW2Gu54z8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the flash sale deals are in one place on my website!... https://t.co/3RKaalsH2A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a great deal! Our TruShine system is amazing and uses an LED light not UV - so sun smart too ðŸ˜ŠðŸ˜Žâ˜€ï¸ https://t.co/yNq7wcSyn3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is an amazing deal - this weekend only! Our TruShine system is amazing - no more trips to the salon, do them... https://t.co/Pqm9Tb9MSR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr 5 looks to have abandoned Mickey! Looks so lonely sitting there! ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜²ðŸ’…ðŸ» https://t.co/I8pQTj1uUb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm wearing a midnight blue silk cocktail dress with a floral design down the front and need a #mani - for... https://t.co/8ooTo7lkzQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friday Night Fun - Jamberry's Flash Sale Battle of the Jams giveaway... over here:... https://t.co/JG6BcgN6fO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello Friday .... this little ray of sunshine knows how to start your day with a smile! Never a dull moment https://t.co/4CJZbNWONM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black Friday Promotion Ladies!   â¤ï¸
Free shipping on Saturday for orders over $167 - and I'm also ordering... https://t.co/BqLN9Y3ckc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come and join in the fun! https://t.co/Pizhzx9vWi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I apply my Trushine Glitter Gels like #birthdaybashjn,  with an eye shadow applicator. The best way I've found to... https://t.co/yRoE4hxkTb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/bubcLIjHzr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Summer berries ðŸ“ are looking soooo good for Christmas! ðŸŽ„....perfect for my mani #picnicpartyjn ðŸ™ŒðŸ˜˜....hello... https://t.co/tEBFSZub3o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Saturday! This crazy funny kiddo is my mini-me - larger than life and adding a tonne of sparkle everywhere... https://t.co/CbNujdbg7d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Santa's chief Elf has told me Jamberry orders should be placed by 10 December - either through me or on my... https://t.co/KBSFu0K1DA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello!! 
Christmas Gift Sets are Gorgeous! I LOVE the exclusives.... 
You basically buy the usual 4 wraps (and... https://t.co/BbmeThDYWb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One year Jamiversary...- year of so much fun, pretty nails, friendships that stretch the globe and so much more... https://t.co/oqc1H148gl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sunrise through the bathroom window is a great start to the day ðŸ˜ðŸ™Œ https://t.co/ImGvEM6P2p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunday - I get up early and I bake for the weeks lunches. Special request from Master 5 for gingerbread men this... https://t.co/HcBKg5DwXK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haha... I think I really wanted to be a Jamberry Consultant to have this little moment, (and many more - she's... https://t.co/n1AltIdvK9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little Miss M sat still the 20 minutes needed to get her first full #jamicure #berrycutejn â¤ï¸â¤ï¸ https://t.co/SdkvQiIrYy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...and relax ðŸ˜ŠðŸ’‹ https://t.co/btSvFQgkeZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I â¤ï¸ these! I'm 41 (ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜Œ)and I'm finally growing my nails, instead of having them break and I've started wearing... https://t.co/LpjTxXeWvN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ladies....ðŸŽ„ðŸŽ„Christmas gift sets have launched, so if you were hoping Jamberry would delivery some super awesome... https://t.co/JhkxnoVqyX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nom nom Monday breakfast - avocado tomato pita pockets â˜ºï¸ðŸ…ðŸž
.
.
#avocadotoast #healthyfood #mondaymorning... https://t.co/eMpipkOoUk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fresh #jamicure! #finechinajn #porcelainjn under #birthdaybashjn #addictedtobling #bling #sparkle #lovesparkle... https://t.co/BiTGznpIil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your #jamicure compliments your little ones writing homework book  ðŸ¤—ðŸ™Œ #school #wahm #motherson #homework ðŸ‘ðŸ“–... https://t.co/uKimE5r4S9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would you believe I've never tried white wraps till today! #prettynails #haciendajn #mattetopcoatjn #mixedmani... https://t.co/cwx88O2kW5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Friday ladies! Our Freddy is in his weekend groove already!  #friyay #weekends #familytime #chillax... https://t.co/SJBzFdC9gT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's love â¤ï¸ -  Me, #sarapesunsetjn, #rumbajn (and a wee #trushinejn #jamaddiction in the background) .... step... https://t.co/QqAJ0zWfTS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[....the next jamicure starts here - 1st world 'jam' problems ðŸ¤— #firstworldproblems #prettynails #nails... https://t.co/ND4Rv2w3fq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wellington Weather is BEAUTIFUL when it's on form right? What a fabulous spring day!  
What's your Saturday night... https://t.co/a0k1bgosfG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because it's Friday and CUTE! â¤ï¸ .... happy long weekend everyone ðŸ˜˜ https://t.co/NnJHsD8zb0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Long weekend coming up and it's been a while since I've done a full wrap mixed mani so here's my happy mani for... https://t.co/BK4bdfbiu2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Arrivals - check it out! https://t.co/dqUqLoBpra
What a busy Jamberry week - when Jamberry says there's great... https://t.co/JxPD5YAZI8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well if you've met me personally, know my family, or can guess from my name, there's a whole lot of Scottish... https://t.co/XqeGqjNVrn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a bit of a convert when initially this pr duct didn't appeal but I love the nail care products so I added... https://t.co/1idMa0Y0i4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple Pay launched in NZ today - I proudly romped into the local supermarket armed with car keys and my iPhone... https://t.co/0AUQ1rbNTT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would it be wrong to have at the last cupcake?? â¤ï¸ðŸ¤” ....#jamwithheather #thinkhappythoughtsjn #birthdaybashjn... https://t.co/kf2KWpblrH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would it be wrong to eat the kiddos last cupcake? - two of them, one cupcake, one of me â¤ï¸#nomnom... https://t.co/f58bRZftAD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I â¤ï¸ finding little goodies for my lovely VIP ladies ó¾Œ¬ #jamwithheather #prettynails #jamwithheathersvips https://t.co/Z3Xy86bvf4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saturday night! Hello!! I LOVE TruShine #cherrypickerjn ..... the most PERFECT red .... and I've glanced it a... https://t.co/wktW3r8eIK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Order going in today - this Geo Diamond isn't expected to last so hopefully I can get a couple when it goes on... https://t.co/aPEoSK9wU1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty in pink! #jamberrynails #sisterstyleexclusive #floralfusionjn #rosyquatrefoiljn #jamwithheather... https://t.co/e6u7hJECZB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hostess rewards and orders arrived all at once today! Christmas came early - and looks like these lovely ladies... https://t.co/3f9PB395CO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[October - Mystery Hostess month! Woohoo....one of my lovely customers wins the rewards (we're starting with 140... https://t.co/81O1Kbw74F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[October Sister Style: Retro Glam 
Must Have!! â¤ï¸â¤ï¸â¤ï¸â¤ï¸â¤ï¸â¤ï¸
Remember all orders in October are entered in the draw... https://t.co/vt9R4RB0WL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[October - Mystery Hostess month!  Woohoo....one of my lovely customers wins the rewards (we're starting with 140... https://t.co/0LlAwWQyXb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.....that weekend went fast and October appeared even faster! 

October is an exciting month - I'll share all the... https://t.co/QQqO9kJRnW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Funny Friday everyone! 
#funny #jammail #jamberrynails #funnyfriday #jamwithheather #loveparcels https://t.co/Da0tRrieWQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We all have those favourite Disney movies, and characters and I love Tinker Bell - so it's super exciting to now... https://t.co/l5Mp97AyAt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something super special is coming - Christmas gifts solved - these are so special!   Come and join my VIP group... https://t.co/OF0epbACVS]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>