<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Hat trick for my boy Nylander!!!!! #tmltalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caps and Habs... Some good ole afternoon hockey #NHL #capitalstalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12 points clear at the top of the table now!!!! Will probably be 9 by the end of the day...on the way to another championship #CFClive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Told you guys man Arsenal ain't close to Chelsea or being a championship caliber team!! #CHEARS #CFClive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks Cech Ahhaah Fabregas makes it 3-0 Chelsea!!! #CHEARS #CFClive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't get tired of watching the Hazard goal!! What a great solo run... Put Coquelin on his ass and made Koscielny look like a fool #CFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HaZarddddd!!! 2-0 Chelsea #CHEARS #CFCLive #EPL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Real_ESPNLeBrun many off ice issues with Ribeiro... Real talented guy though .. IMO was one of the better passers in the league years ago]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Wild bench boss Mike Yeo takes over as Blues head coach following Hitchcock firing #NHL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow Ken Hitchcock out as Blues coach ...won't be long till he gets scooped up by another team ... Solid coach #NHL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best of luck to Ivanovic at Zenit.. You will be missed at Chelsea #CFC #transferdeadline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lmao once again at shitty Arsenal Ahhaah #EPL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's gorgeous!!! David Luiz 1-0 Chelsea #LIVCHE #CFCLive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gretzky coaches Ovy and Crosby to victory #NHLAllStar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Myyyy boy!! Finally getting some recognition... Such a underrated player! Wayne the train Simmonds! One of my fave #NHLAllStar #Spyder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the Metro division wins the 2017 NHL all star game! #NHLAllStar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mcdonagh with a great kick save haha ... Intense end to this one #NHLAllStar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Atkinson.. Ties it up... But look at Gaudreau skating hard to catch up to him ... Games pace has kicked up a couple of notches #NHLAllStar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahaha Wayne with the successful coaches challenge... Metro only trails by 1 #NHLAllStar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Metro vs Pacific in the final! #NHLAllStar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matthews first NHL all star goal #NHLAllStar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Burnzie makes it 4-1 Pacific... Centrals getting lit up early on here #NHLAllStar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cam Fowler off a Johnny hockey pass opens the scoring at the 2017 NHL all star game .. 1-0 Pacific #NHLAllStar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Central Vs Pacific in game 1..winner gets Metro or Atlantic in the final #NHLAllStar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My fave jerseys of the 4 divisions are the Central division purple... With the white mitts ahhhh #NHLAllStar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So will Gretz put Ovy and Crosby on the same line today ? Interesting to see #NHLAllStar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beibs only guy wearing a cage ... Tryna save his face #NHLAllStar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walk in the park win for Chelsea! And off to the next round we go!! #CFCLive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biebs and Cuba Gooding Jr two of many celebrities taking part in the NHL celebrity shootout  #NHLAllStar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Real_ESPNLeBrun well who are you gonna replace from that list then ? Not everyone can make the list .. Always will be snubs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's NHL all star weekend time!!! #NHLAllStar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FreeShia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Atta boy Brady! 10-0 Pats #NFLPlayoffs #PITvsNE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wowzers Matt Ryan...17-0 Falcons #GBvsATL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some good old hockey, NFL playoffs... A good Sunday!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 goals in 6 mins... In comes Elliot #NHL #EDMvCGY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[T boo! All knotted up #TMLtalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andersen looking sharp early ... Some solid stops early on #TMLtalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seth Griffith is back with the Leafs... Leafs reclaim him off waivers from the Panthers #tmltalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck you Trump!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dreams are not those in which we get in our sleep... Dreams are those that don't allow us to sleep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a goal... Reimer nearly kept it out... Oilers win in OT off a Mcdavid breakaway #FLAvsEDM #NHL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going upstairs ... Mcdavid game winner in OT or did Reimer snag it #FLAvsEDM #NHL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Letterkenny is too jokes .. I can't get tired of this show]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another big win by the boys in blue!!! #TMLtalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FriedgeHNIC would be a solid hire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Capuano out Dougiee Weight takes over on a interim basis #NHL #Isles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to Jujhar Khaira on his first career NHL goal!!! #PunjabisProud #NHL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peg leg and hockey = life!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a hit... Almost a hattrick for Marcos Alonso... Who's been lights out today!! #LEICHE #CFCLive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marcos Alonsooooo again!!! 2 nil Chelsea!!!!!! #LEICHE #CFCLive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's go Chelsea!!!! #CFCLive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Mcgregor and Mayweather ends up happening, it's solely for money ... There's no contest there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a Mcgregor fan to ... But if anyone thinks he'd stand a chance in a boxing bout with Mayweather.. You my friend are an idiot...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Puck #WhatILiveFor #Puck #ThisIsLiving https://t.co/bikiSU2S9K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great career for a true legend in women's hockey Hayley Wickenheiser ! #HockeyCanada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[King Henrik spoke earlier today about playing street hockey with William Nylander years ago...And look who opens the scoring on him #TMLtalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Willllyy 1-0 Leafs!! #TMLtalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1,000 for OVYYYY!!!! #Ovechkin #NHL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Leafs claim Curtis McElhinney off waivers from the Blue Jackets... Worth the shot IMO #tmltalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Metro division is stacked... Ouch #NHLAllStar #NHL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auston Matthews repping the Leafs at the 2017 all star game in LA!! His first of many! #NHLAllStar #tmltalk #NHL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ohda phone number, mereh cellphone vich save aj Tayi eh, nameh sim-ch suchhi naameyan di kar tyar Layi ohneh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Willian!! 3 zip Blues #CFCLive #FACup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michhhhyy!! 2-0 Chelsea #FACup #CFCLive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow Andersens gotta have that #TMLtalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nonetheless proud of you boys... Great tourney!! 🇨🇦🇨🇦🇨🇦#TeamCanada #WorldJuniors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Up 2-0 and then 4-2 ... Couldn't hold the lead... Let it slip right outta our hands #WorldJuniors #CANvsUSA #TeamCanada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great game by both teams... Unreal!! Let's win it now Canada #CANvsUSA #WorldJuniors #TeamCanada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shootout to decide a game like this ... Stupid #TeamCanada #WorldJuniors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is nuts #CANvsUSA #WorldJuniors #TeamCanada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerplay for Canada!!! This is our chance to end it now boys #WorldJuniors #TeamCanada #CANvsUSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll never forget when John Carlson broke my heart in 2010 #WorldJuniors #CANvsUSA #TeamCanada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My prediction .. Blake Speers first 10 minutes of OT wins gold for Canada #TeamCanada #CANvsUSA #WorldJuniors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should be continuous OT like a playoff game ... A Shootout deciding a game like this is stupid #WorldJuniors #TeamCanada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are headed to sudden death OT for 20 mins... And if still no winner a shootout #TeamCanada #WorldJuniors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's my guy Mathieu Joseph #WorldJuniors #TeamCanada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chelsea's winning streak ended yesterday and the Blue Jackets ended today ... Sad but reality #NHL #CFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 period will decide the game ..0-0 game going into the 3rd #WorldJuniors #TeamCanada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exactly what I said... Loads of game to play calm down after that 2-0 start in 10 mins #WorldJuniors #CANvsUSA #TeamCanada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like the blue jackets won't be setting the record... Down 4-0 end of the 2nd to the Caps #CapsJackets #RockTheRed #NHL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep playing hard boys... Only 10 minutes into the game... Anything can happen... Don't let up!! #WorldJuniors #TeamCanada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best Dman in the tourney Tommmmy Chabot puts Canada on the board #WorldJuniors #TeamCanada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's go Canada!!!! #WorldJuniors #CANvsUSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We got this boys!!!! Dubois to open the scoring, followed by Speers ... You heard it here first #WorldJuniors #TeamCanada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People who haven't watched a game all tourney will be watching all of a sudden now.... #WorldJuniors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lost to USA in the last game of group stage... But we will prevail tomorrow and win gold!!! Let's go Canada!! #WorldJuniors #TeamCanada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Julien Gauthier coming off a two goal performance against the Czechs comes up big again! Puts Canada infront here in the 2nd #WorldJuniors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come on Canada man!!! Pick it up #WorldJuniors #CANvsSWE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[USA is through to the finals.... Canada will see you there !!! #WorldJuniors #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Win today and that's 14th straight premier league wins!!! Let's Go Bluesssss #CFC #EPL #CFClive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Derby day!! Big game today! Let's get the win like we have been for 13 games straight!! Chelseaaaaa!!!!! #CFC #EPL #CFClive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arsenal fans are celebrating a draw with Bournemouth .... Just goes to show u what being an Arsenal fan does to you lmao #EPL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lmao at Arsenal! As usual they are officially now outta the title race Ahhaah ... #BOUARS #EPL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada is through to the semis! Will play Sweden on Wednesday #WorldJuniors #TeamCanada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chabots really impressed me this tourney ... Sens got a beauty in him #TeamCanada #WorldJuniors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The French connection line strikes again to regain the two goal lead... Julien Gauthier again 5-3 Canada #WorldJuniors #TeamCanada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Czechs just don't go away ... 1 goal game #WorldJuniors #TeamCanada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Julien Gauthier!! 4-2 Canada !! #WorldJuniors #TeamCanada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chabottt! Another great shimmy by Chabot this time he finishes it 3-2 Canada!!! #WorldJuniors #TeamCanada]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>