<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Antarctic Sea Ice Likely to Hit New All-Time Record Lows Over Coming Days https://t.co/VWAafp6oT1 via @FantasyScribe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Arguments Against “Innovation in Education” and How You Might Respond https://t.co/5RC0pZBdKK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Q&amp;A: The Art of Coding https://t.co/dRLC2yQljV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Small Steps Can Create Outdoors Experiences In Schools https://t.co/2CosZrPZfc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New energy forecast has good news for Elon Musk, but spells trouble for Trump https://t.co/SvhYkLlbkS via @mashable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The vexed problem of nationality in the history of science https://t.co/cwMgM0qeVu via @rmathematicus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MIT built a wearable app to detect emotion in conversation https://t.co/QdhWpvMYxt via @Verge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Preleminary Results In NASA Twins Study Released https://t.co/DVfhfUdyx8 via @universetoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teaching Middle Schoolers to Patent Their Creations https://t.co/52bsNmIJLW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Designing School Recess To Helps Kids Learn, Play And Eat Healthy Foods https://t.co/TxBQsVkMYJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reproducible Research Needs Some Limiting Principles https://t.co/ljXjIQVa0n via @]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SpaceX’s hyperloop race was a milestone for the futuristic transportation system https://t.co/ukh6yGnmOT via @Verge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is a Butte? https://t.co/BSPkOrSfQz via @universetoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Peter_J_King @DavidJSilcock @johnqgoh @abcnews great work by you and your staff Peter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social inequalities in education are not set in stone
 https://t.co/u6Ot5vq5mk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teaching Why Facts Still Matter https://t.co/gvkEHyuFGG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is eLearning Dead? Is Instructional Design Dying with It? via @kkapp https://t.co/F2hjuggkXm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education delivers high incomes and low unemployment https://t.co/f230h6PGpB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CHRIS BONNOR &amp; BERNIE SHEPHERD. The vanishing private school | John Menadue – Pearls and Irritations https://t.co/f93Tm4Mxsz via @EMAILiT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will we now take information literacy skills seriously? https://t.co/G8cipqL3RM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reframing the Debate About Screen Time https://t.co/JXKXUY5z0N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using the iPad to Develop Student Agency https://t.co/SQMpFCP6wT via @kristimeeuwse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does professional development improve teaching? https://t.co/5yWITq9wGJ via @AustAssocResEd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Spatial Reasoning Is Crucial For Early Math Education https://t.co/AJHOsCbeQ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remedial Classes Are A Huge Stumbling Block On The Way To A Degree. Thats Why This Community College have none https://t.co/WFsSotIHxE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hattie Effect Size 2016 Update https://t.co/9Et7QDc7rV via @shaunkillian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teacher credibility: why it matters and how to build it https://t.co/joBIAEQsHr via @shaunkillian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Principal's Reflections: Learning is Not Linear https://t.co/LsxICAYFHJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Networks: An Engine For Scaling Learning And Innovation (Part 1) https://t.co/HiDDNXhD3x via @wordpressdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes he will be greatly missed. He made a significant difference for students schools and teachers in NSW https://t.co/WksyHPV3mV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you Minister Adrian Piccoli via @johnqgoh https://t.co/Lwmy5Jyg0n - An education Minister who made a difference for all students]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just the right amount of data https://t.co/SJyCKj99km]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enhancing STEM Learning Using Virtual Reality https://t.co/guZF30wc6Q via @teachercast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NASA releases first results from 'Year In Space' twin study https://t.co/3vLVMIUCTg via @NewsHour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ask Ethan: What Is Spacetime? via @forbes https://t.co/1Ir6247Dre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are All Hurt Tonight, as John Hurt Has Died. https://t.co/DEmpvENdNO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who are the winners and losers of the expansion of education over the past 50 years?
 https://t.co/6ZGga6H3Rs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gender Equity in the Classroom https://t.co/lTy3NjKVOs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why every teacher should look into project based learning https://t.co/w5zTlkfihF via @aliceleung]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Challenges of Big Data in Education https://t.co/auzU38Ldxq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Climate science isn’t political. Lying about it is.” by @StartsWithABang https://t.co/fzMCdNFgf5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the QWERTY Keyboard and Education Have in Common https://t.co/Bpxrfn2VbW via @ajjuliani]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backreaction: What is Physics? [Video] https://t.co/MbX5Wf1ADE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PMP 051: The Shocking Truth About Your Decision-Making https://t.co/OPCb5gcn3c via @williamdp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can Personalized Learning Flourish Within A Traditional System? https://t.co/48vQoDimpm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Growing Role of Technology in Personalized Learning https://t.co/uVUms9b45G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Guide to Mathematical Emotions https://t.co/gIMFsLoy5R via @benorlin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump silences government scientists with gag orders https://t.co/ok1n4oo4BI via @Verge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Story of NASA's Real "Hidden Figures" https://t.co/iXJvh26nAN #science]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arctic Summer Ice Has Decreased by 72 Percent Since 1980 [Graphic] https://t.co/xyeWDOfUI8 #science]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abnormal Antarctic Heat, Surface Melt, Giant Cracks in Ice Shelves -- More Troubling Signs of a … https://t.co/hHkrEYMHwR via @FantasyScribe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Afternoon walk - the cows are finding it a tad warm https://t.co/BqEgpux6ET]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bringing Art Back With Technology https://t.co/axDbC2iTPf via @edudemic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Encouraging Students to Own Their Work https://t.co/rgZb5Ekxd7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Edtech Developers, Please Leave The Pedagogy To Teachers https://t.co/fgA6ydJPH9 via @teachthought]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The mathematics of sidewalk illusions - Fumiko Futamura https://t.co/3SFFQTtFLq via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want Students to Be More Creative? Try Adding More Play. https://t.co/FmR7MVjeQQ via @spencerideas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @DavidGeurin Blog: Why Successful People Are Open to Coaching https://t.co/FfHAX1P8o6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does your ideal classroom look like? https://t.co/Dc844nc6sO via @KatieMTLC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Your Country's Leader Is A Tweeter - Action Innovative Educators Can Take https://t.co/FTfTxgFCBt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ask Ethan: Is 'Zero Gravity' Really A Thing? via @forbes https://t.co/mqSk4AFH7N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GM launches partnership with Girls Who Code https://t.co/5mETRoVk0j via @Verge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is an outstanding Minister - still much more to do - he needs to stay https://t.co/JJzQFod2np]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NASA Data Shows the Rate of Global Warming is Accelerating -- 2016 is Third Consecutive Hottest … https://t.co/pDOMgqDjdS via @FantasyScribe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An example that isn't that artificial or intelligent https://t.co/6GuGrYKY3g via @]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five Compelling Reasons For Teaching Spatial Reasoning To Young Children https://t.co/8epUV7mbye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Basic but important physics questions: What does it mean to say Energy is conserved? https://t.co/DDIYBzvEBJ via @wordpressdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kauai Shows Solar + Storage is Starting to Become Cost Competitive With Fossil Fuels, Nuclear https://t.co/FEs2nkq5pO via @FantasyScribe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NASA: 2016 Was the Warmest Year on Record... Again! https://t.co/xrAy7cjqzb via @universetoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backreaction: Dark matter’s hideout just got smaller, thanks to ... https://t.co/QoDMhJ0TIO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Librarianship as a subversive profession https://t.co/5VkmGj2LRU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Machines Are Coming For Poker https://t.co/RbWmAK6tfs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, this detailed 3D-printed model was sculpted in VR, and it's just the start https://t.co/BcoToX8EX3 via @mashable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is artificial intelligence https://t.co/PmKjauOtig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A brief history of numerical systems - Alessandra King https://t.co/SW7YlipoPw #mathchat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Climate science isn’t political. Lying about it is. (Synopsis) https://t.co/dkH5WUriH7 via @Scienceblogs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Non-Digital Distractions: Backing Away from the Screen https://t.co/QyViqPfGOJ via @chronicle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PMP 050: The 5 Marks of a Learning Culture https://t.co/jRxHbc0q0Y via @williamdp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helping Struggling Students Build a Growth Mindset https://t.co/HWTXlF2tRv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Living in a Personal Case Study - Curiosity-based Learning https://t.co/kxqP6020TI via @boadams1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These 3 graphics explain 2016’s record warmth https://t.co/HbMw7yqyTX via @mashable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[surface of the sun https://t.co/kEgUswwle1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016 Was The Hottest Year On Record https://t.co/HUGsW5doP8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Predictions Are Not Enough https://t.co/PMU0h3rLZe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“The two questions that determine your scientific literacy” by @StartsWithABang https://t.co/UEUo9YEwcS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Octavia Spencer bought out a whole cinema so families could see 'Hidden Figures' https://t.co/Bd2aR5TUtN via @mashable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Can Schools Protect Student Data Without Training Teachers In Privacy Basics? https://t.co/AqdO1i3nyb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CIA puts almost 12 million declassified files online for the first time https://t.co/TAoDygziZO via @Verge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who was Max Planck? https://t.co/sufop4MDc2 via @universetoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Innovation is a process, not a product. https://t.co/yeM0HH0qDN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9 Ways to Inspire Student Inventors https://t.co/An4q7T3CXr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How The Systemic Segregation Of Schools Is Maintained By 'Individual Choices' https://t.co/vC42xkr5ly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How taking email off my phone helped me win the inbox battle and live more in the moment  https://t.co/xbassRi7yj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Classroom Technology: What's New For 2017? https://t.co/4i3bSkA9cQ via @edudemic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/lbSoKgGQcZ Bitcoin and the surprising “disturbance in the force” that will upend our financial systems | DaVinci Institute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Addressing Maslow's Hierarchy of Needs with Technology https://t.co/babHa6tlDT via @jackiegerstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting a new iPhone – which plan should I choose? https://t.co/pilv0orOIo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnqgoh @ewathekids5 @mefergus @rudd58 @_iEndo @kim5241 @JohnSelby6 25-30 years good timeframe for a picture light clean out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Things Every Teacher Should Know Before Starting Their First Day In The Classroom https://t.co/vTrjcvYsM9 via @shaunkillian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roll back curriculum constraints and give teachers the freedom to make professional judgements https://t.co/6w2bW2MTNB via @AustAssocResEd]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>