<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Indigenous health program to be axed after two decades #auspol @AAPNewswire https://t.co/Al46vJoe14]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DeanSmithWA is he preferencing   Hanson over Labor?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shorten calls for end to Trump executive order immigration policy #auspol https://t.co/PRO59t7ReW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump asked for advice on a 'Muslim ban' https://t.co/gWEgfn8KbW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McKennaattheOz Congrats on gig as Qld editor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BurnerDesign What was the reason?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fact checking the Trump refugee @RefugeeAction policy #auspol https://t.co/1mDFXlQ6np]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phonics? https://t.co/TEXRsIliLY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abbott: "Voters will punish governments and parties that they think have lost the plot — and so they should." #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AustralianOpen polly watch: just spotted bearded @SenatorFifield #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Thinking_Of_God @davidould great idea David. Jan 26 start of #Recognition]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Envious of Dmitrov's forehand @AustralianOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nadal's pumped for a win @AustralianOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@David_Speers Any idea who are the Sky political guests this weekend?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smurray38 see anything interesting in it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidLeyonhjelm When was that originally published?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SquigglyRick you'll be heading to the waterloo soon then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Wawrinka knee thing has thrown Federer off balance @AustralianOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cporterwa That's not a tie, it's a lobster bib]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyNewsRicho Lots of references to Trump and his agenda...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyNewsRicho love the intro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaveGillespieMP Kew is on the cutting edge as usual]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is AMAZING. A piece of steak in the shape of Australia on Australia Day. #auspol https://t.co/ZoaIdtXA06]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worth noting - Steve Jobs, son of a Syrian migrant. https://t.co/TUvaZXYgev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TurnbullMalcolm inspects the troops on #AustraliaDay https://t.co/UMGJGsZo1H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting gas policy decision by Queensland #auspol @FinancialReview https://t.co/GZM8JvA8SB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is that @JoshFrydenberg in the top right corner? @AustralianOpen https://t.co/PDuDNUMDTT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raonic seems in pain. Great match  @AustralianOpen #Nadal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously? Journalists arrested for covering a protest march??? https://t.co/LTaGDEEN02]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's an #AustraliaDay emoji thing happening #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SabraLane Good luck. You'll do a great job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spread the word #auspol #CBR via @AAPNewswire https://t.co/9Ap0L1WBuG https://t.co/8IL5Nkxw5R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#geography101 https://t.co/4E58kDwkrp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Possible the shortest press release in Australian political history. https://t.co/26CBglBRET]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelSukkarMP starts his trajectory towards the leadership #auspol https://t.co/vwWU9eNyaR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GregHuntMP becomes health minister #auspol https://t.co/HznKL8DMIc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@georgefwoods @janet_rice Not to mention these guys https://t.co/2KlvajhIPF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not a beat up, a heat up @mjrowland68]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laureningram Good advice. The non-Twitter world is a much better place to find empathy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'll like this @DavidLeyonhjelm https://t.co/Dn0eKmEfyC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cracking new WWII story out today https://t.co/1IJ5SUTBKV #auspol @RSL_National @AWMemorial]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forget about the holidays. Look at all these new movies coming out @mjrowland68 https://t.co/9peA0Ija0r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How good is Nishikori's court coverage. @AustralianOpen #FederervsNishikori wow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump orders a military upgrade. About time ... https://t.co/rizOSErg6u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump finally mentions Clintons: 'I have a lot of respect for these people']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump in statue hall with painting Vetdict of the People #InaugurationDay https://t.co/3s5m9oG6mx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JmarrMarr that's aap's thing. Has been for 85 years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Latest - full statement from @VictoriaPolice on Bourke St car incident in Melbourne #auspol https://t.co/LvvbkblmXI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This guy tries to stop the driver with a baseball bat #BourkeSt https://t.co/2fnQfyznuC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three dead, 20 injured. Latest on Bourke St Mall car incident via @AAPNewswire https://t.co/rEzJObwtyx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 dead. At least 20 injured. Not terrorism related. Connected to stabbing in southern metro region Vic. #BourkeSt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FJKeany Basically setting out some procedures for next week's two day special hearing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Trigg Ambulance service has issued a statement]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is worth a second look, pre-inauguration. Lunch with The Trump from @FT https://t.co/91jXtwTcH7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did @corybernardi spend New Year's Eve aboard Gina Rinehart's luxury cruise liner, The World? #auspol question of the day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bedeapk he let his membership lapse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In case of doubt there is a WA Senate vacancy due to Culleton's bankruptcy, these are the docs #auspol https://t.co/D0R0z3CklO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mike Baird doesn't lack confidence. Maybe he should coach #Kyrgios @AustralianOpen https://t.co/YW2fcTOk7H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Labor leader Latham is raising funds for the Liberals. #auspol https://t.co/uSdaxlM1nM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's always Andy. We're still a British colony, right? @AustralianOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So close and yet...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Kyrgios needs some confidence @AustralianOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rohan_p what does SBR1 cover?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rohan_p just before the planned outage over the weekend just gone?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hunt appears genuinely excited to be health minister #auspol More to say later about policy revision. https://t.co/esXZj7v6sA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does @MurrayWatt have a Kylie poster on his wall? https://t.co/9PRunFaHRA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Temperature around Tarago bush fire area is 36 degrees #auspol #Fire https://t.co/dkM83oFwma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bushfire near Tarago is getting bigger. Two aircraft and a crane now in place. #auspol #Fire https://t.co/o8rR3G6SAl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advice given to skiiers in the Nozawa Onsen ski resort area #auspol #ausdisaster where a family is reportedly missi… https://t.co/USQxB36gK5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nozawaonsen Do you have any information on an Australian family believed missing in your area?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TPP has merit but is dead via Trump says @JasonClareMP #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorMRoberts Can you please tweet and attach a full copy of the invitation?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimWattsMP It will leave a hole]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TonyHWindsor calls for federal ICAC to restore public trust in politics @RNBreakfast #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neat video summing up #inaug2017 thanks to @CNNPolitics #auspol https://t.co/JuajmffPU9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting question - Given that Hanson has no registered party (yet) in WA, should she have a role in replacing C… https://t.co/gcnoHtcKnN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TonyAbbottMHR offers economic and leadership advice to @TurnbullMalcolm #auspol https://t.co/OyLQVUFKvN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Parry expected to make Culleton decision soon #auspol https://t.co/2K3zzrngE0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Craigallenabc one for you? https://t.co/wFAxzzKIEJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#LIVply #liverpoolfc No Coutinho, Matip, Henderson, Milner or Mane. But good squad @espn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expecting news this week on @PaulineHansonOz party registration in WA #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laureningram welcome to living with six year olds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StAndrewsHist Many thanks for the book Brand Luther. It's a fascinating and very readable work and so timely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cpyne #auspol Late holiday reading: Line of Fire 4th Estate https://t.co/HmCO8aTi59 via @amazon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turn, face the strange #2016In4Words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nightmare scenario for @TurnbullMalcolm and @cpyne #auspol https://t.co/7QHKTAHZHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unexplained but not suspicious? Police-speak gets the last word for 2016 https://t.co/ElrgihZJql]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anglican Dean of #MEL: Come together as a community and deliberately celebrate that which others who seek us harm want to disrupt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SmartState1 formidable team and plenty of crossfaction firepower]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@naomiwoodley Seriously, can everyone please just go on holidays and enjoy life for a few weeks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Santa and the dying kid' news story may not be true. What a surprise.  #auspol https://t.co/Ki0cWJk5ZG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labor and Liberals have preselections for candidates. One Nation has this #auspol https://t.co/vVFmi7KjK1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Queensland to host filming of new Aquaman movie #auspol says @couriermail https://t.co/rdQ73atfgl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hockey: when US and other countries imposed trade sanctions on Japan in the 1940s  Tokyo "resorted to other means". #pearlharbor #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rharris334 they think the overflow is some IT glitch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ato_gov_au says many of its online services are running today but some may take a little while longer to restore #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lyndalcurtis try using all of the functions.... *tumbleweeds*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guess who's been in the Middle East? #auspol @billshortenmp briefed on ops and thanked troops https://t.co/4QOGRLZnSM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katrinawalker @SenPaterson funny way of spelling Palpatine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenPaterson wants Triggs to comment on QUT case. Triggs says she can't #auspol and so it goes round and round https://t.co/t7CjEwlp7G]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>