<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[FT: Dublin 0-18 Cavan 0-11. Both teams played the last 10 mins as if they were content enough with a 5-7 points gap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Official attendance at Kingspan Breffni Park: 16331. Dublin lead 0-11 to 0-8 after 40 mins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HT: Dublin 0-10 Cavan 0-7. Cavan staying in touching distance but Dubs look capable of opening that gap https://t.co/VmkvvhukZA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jack McCaffrey, Niall Scully &amp; Jason Whelan start for Dublin. Cavan unchanged. Dublin sub Robbie McDaid injured his… https://t.co/sx7EINbtLm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pearsecorcoran that's up there now Pearse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@p_cunnane sure hosting headline games is second nature to ye Mayo boys Paul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahead of today's game, here's a man who played for both Dublin and Cavan. #TangledUpInBlue https://t.co/1ysnIflkYE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cianrpmurphy of course. Though these are hard times, we've Division 1 Blues to our left and our right at the minute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cavan v Dublin delayed by 15 mins due to heavy traffic. Crowd in excess of 10,000 expected at Kingspan Breffni Park https://t.co/10Ek0ujUjq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is some dedication for club &amp; county by Gary Brennan @ballyea_club @GaaClare #warrior https://t.co/lSJAAeDJ7z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FT: Kilkenny 0-15 Wexford 0-14. Frantic injury-time. Winning free by Alan Murphy,Cathal Dunbar shot saved &amp; resulting 65 missed by Lee Chin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[41 mins. Wexford 0-8 Kilkenny 0-8. Great start to the second half by Wexford - Lee Chin with three of their second-half points so far]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HT: Kilkenny 0-7 Wexford 0-4. Not much hurling, but there's an undercurrent to the game.3 yellows so far, probably not the end of the cards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@standavid10 here's how they started https://t.co/CmHLHwfxvB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[18 mins: Kilkenny 0-4 Wexford 0-3. So far there have been lots of frees, crowded rucks, a couple of yellow cards and a Wexford sweeper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The view from the press box in New Ross - big crowd here braving the weather for @OfficialWexGAA v @KilkennyCLG https://t.co/RybG0MiKu6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mbutler27 @Copenred @GaynorBrian @brenmurph @declander @WildThingV Grove sent Si on a warm weather training camp but he ended up in Denmark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mbutler27 @brenmurph @declander @WildThingV and if the Kingdom lose I'm taking the ball home]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mbutler27 @declander @brenmurph @WildThingV Kells loves fossils from Heritage to Hay festival.This'd b a festival of soccer plyd by fossils]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@declander @brenmurph @mbutler27 @WildThingV this has cropped up before - we should make it happen, summer 2017, a one day blitz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great pic - the Nally Stand as it is today in Tyrone https://t.co/ab6ALYByjA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Denis_Hurley you sound like a man who Ian just considering a bet. Wind was with UCD in the first half - but it's not exactly a gale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Denis_Hurley there is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HT here in Parnell Park.UCD lead Dublin 1-6 to 1-1 in the O'Byrne Cup.It took Dublin until the 30th min to get their first score of the game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@me_stafford keeping him under wraps until Meath play Louth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lemallon Seems like they'll have to be given a chance to shine now anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Padraic Harnan named among the Meath subs v DIT as Andy McEntee starts a completely different 15 from the side that… https://t.co/JptoGJaJGb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Further blows for Donegal with Rory Kavanagh,Christy Toye &amp;David Walsh retiring.2012 All-Ireland winning side is really starting to break up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It seems there could be a couple more Donegal retirements confirmed in the next hour. They are losing a lot of experienced players.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@depboyle don't pretend that back in the day around Meath Hill you never swapped two Dan Marino head shots for a gl… https://t.co/ztzD3rX0bZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OCowzer @depboyle he's a big fan of the mark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@depboyle it's a valid point. But what a rocket he launched in there.He's almost as deadly with his hand as Brian Stafford was with his foot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unreal by Rodgers https://t.co/PL88Gqq9Re]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FT: Meath 2-22 Wicklow 0-9. 12 different scorers for Meath. But should be noted it was a very experimental Wicklow team]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HT: Meath 1-13 Wicklow 0-2. Wicklow's only score from play arrived in the 32min. All six Meath forwards have scored from play. #OByrneCup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlanaganMorgan money??? I do it for the love of it Morgan 😀]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[20 mins gone of Andy McEntee's first game in charge of Meath. Meath 1-8 Wicklow 0-1. Cillian O'Sullivan with the go… https://t.co/Ak9Dh56N14]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graham Reilly has been named as @MeathGAA senior football captain for 2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GaynorBrian @irlsport @IrishSunSport I've saved Meath for the 'counties with things to prove in 2017' list 😉]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CPA aiming for 150,000 members - that's more than the individual populations of 19 diff counties in the country #GAA https://t.co/jt6ntNZboE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FiFinnymac ha,I don't know which will come back first Finny, The Book or Sam Maguire. I fear we'll be waiting a while for both]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time for The Book to come home https://t.co/bFfWy94dwb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hill16Army a gent of a man who always had a smile for people when you'd see him around the tunnel at Croke Park on match day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeMoynihanEx @JwcaJwcricket or mention a clash of the willow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael D was a Leonard C fan. #Cohen https://t.co/P3UyNgqcdE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Records,history &amp; curses coming along like Dublin buses in Chicago right now.Mayo should push for 2017 All-Ireland final to be played there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sweeney_Peter @Tomtomskk gone to the Drogs you mean P, it's all gone to the Drogs tonight #goingup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant stuff by Drogheda. https://t.co/dz76Jzh7io]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listened to this while driving home earlier. An inspirational and fascinating documentary. Well done to all involve… https://t.co/SUpJfKXUvD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShinerTomas how's the form Tommy. The locals said Cha has retired from club now as well. He's filling his evenings being a DJ apparently]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FT: O'Loughlin Gaels 0-19 Ballyhale Shamrocks 1-12.Second-half comeback sees O'Loughlin Gaels win their fourth Kilk… https://t.co/iazL9OQBfi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HT:Ballyhale 1-7 O'Loughlin Gls 0-8.TJ Reid goal.HShefflin,CFennelly,BHogan &amp; MComerford among the multiple All-Irl winners playing.Att:9130]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big crowd in Nowlan Park for Kilkenny SHC final - Ballyhale Shamrocks v O'Loughlin Gaels https://t.co/cP1gomhlCX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobertReid64 serious running Rob. Well done]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@p_cunnane congrats Paul. Well deserved]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Woolberto well it's around since before you started working in the media. New members welcome......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great night at Gaelic Writers' Association awards @CopperFaceJacks https://t.co/B5ceMwivCu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@boarsheaddublin cheers for dropping up Hugh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConorMcKn it's @CopperFaceJacks you could have done better https://t.co/pSHv4Tv7xE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CrazyLikeNeil Can't be, sure LMFM will always be home to the greatest radio quiz ever imagined - Dead or Alive @mbutler27]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So disappointing to see the best music station in the country closing. #ThanksForTheMusic @TXFMDublin https://t.co/DBBtmo8C4N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noriordan @Cunneen92 @McDonnellDan true that, this year they absolutely should get it - unless the Drogs secure promotion that is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[St Rynagh's are @Offaly_GAA SHC for the first time since 1993 after a 2-16 to 1-15 win over Birr https://t.co/MWURtYQHpm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[45 mins: St Rynagh's 1-13 Birr 1-10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pat_nolan @MikeMoynihanEx they couldn't have played it without you sure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeMoynihanEx No sign of the pedantic one here today Michael.....@pat_nolan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HT: St Rynagh's 1-8 Birr 0-5. Joseph O'Connor with the goal. Rynagh's have also hit over 10 wides. Birr will have the wind after the break.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[15 mins gone here at O'Connor Park in the Offaly SHC final. St Rynagh's 0-5 Birr 0-2. Strong wind favouring St Ryna… https://t.co/KduvcJaMfL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irlsport one of the greats #oidioi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@moseyb86 shocking stuff. Bring on the shinty!!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FT: Thurles Sarsfields 0-27 Kiladangan 1-15. Dominant win on an emotional day for Thurles - they were never going to lose today  #TheRattler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@79Ceano not really Conall, Thurles just look far quicker and sharper. Lead now 0-21 to 1-10 with 50 gone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Half-time here at Semple Stadium. Thurles Sarsfields 0-15 Kiladangan 0-6. Thurles, with 7 diff scorers, are completely in control #TippSHC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irlsport one from Tipperary, the other from Meath - two hurling strongholds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KarlOKane @Woolberto uncanny likeness, to be fair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three Kells men in an All-Ireland @GAA_Handball final - Meath v Dublin #UpTheTown https://t.co/zgvaFchb1G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Dubs. What can you say..... https://t.co/VxtGVUiv7s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Etainmfinn ha, they're rubbing it in at this stage #Dubs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Conservative' Jim Gavin has rolled the dice: Fitzsimons, Mannion, Andrews all in. Byrne, MDMA and Bernard Brogan out. Hennelly in for Mayo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quiet outside The Big Tree https://t.co/0oce7tso40]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cormacpro @gavreilly main issue is that four diff provinces have to make their fixtures first. If it was all done centrally it'd be quicker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColmGannon @gavreilly @cormacpro ha, no more than yourself. From London to Croker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColmGannon @gavreilly @cormacpro if only they had a couple more months in the year to squeeze in all the games 😉]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gavreilly @cormacpro it's to do with allowing provinces arrange their fixtures, so GAA can formulate a masters fix list &amp; organise TV games]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Draws for the 2017 GAA provincial football &amp; hurling champs will take place in under 2 weeks - Thurs, Oct 13th.Feels like Xmas ads in August]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KarlOKane ha, sure they're all at it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taunted the Dubs by erecting a poster of Aidan O'Shea at a Luas stop heading for Connolly!!! #ThingsLeeDid https://t.co/PlLX0ay1bT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dublin out first again for Saturday's replay against Mayo. https://t.co/R2XB7O2vnj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LarryManninglm We live in hope Lar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justycl26 @MBarrett87 Ha, I wouldn't doubt that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CramptonNiall Ha, hadn't seen that before. Hard to believe it's 20 years ago #TheMillAtTheHill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[20 years on, found these in my Dad's Meath GAA memorabilia.Boy,Mayo found 1996 replay defeat hard to take… https://t.co/0c3kRrmEUO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mully___ yep, they got the squad shot, here's the @sportsfile  pic https://t.co/dMm6VCMHx6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter Creedon for the Laois footballers, while Galway give a strong vote of confidence to both their football and h… https://t.co/syKgY1RZgP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After taking a closer look at my pics from the drawn Dublin v Mayo game, seems Bastick &amp; O'Shea first 'met' in the… https://t.co/A6W7ZJ0Mfd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbrady21 @dublinladiesg yep &amp; for the disputed pt ball wasn't up in the clouds,both umpires should have spotted it was inside the posts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Correct decision by Dublin and not dragging the process out https://t.co/LvmlFfsQjX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrenCummins1 @NedzerB13 yep, would be a brave delegate to vote against introducing it to the ladies game next year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gaffer1888 @NedzerB13 @BrenCummins1 no, it's obv set for sliotars as well. Football, hurling &amp; camogie use it. Ladies voted not to.For now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NedzerB13 @BrenCummins1 couldn't just turn it on boys, whole system would need to be recalibrated for size 4 footballs. It's set for size 5]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>