<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[More indications on need to reform the patent system...It would be good to research the link between patent portfol… https://t.co/meO56liCQn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I´ve already read a great deal on #DBCFT, but if you want to get it right and short, read this piece by Bill Cline https://t.co/y0IaesIahf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conference at @PIIE on BAT. Proponents still deny is protectionist. Dollar adjustment myth tumbles but lives on. Ta… https://t.co/5UsrwgrcYU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EnriqueFeas @BrankoMilan Clinton left more prosperous, equal US Blair did expand, not downsize W State. What about GOP drift to ext right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EnriqueFeas @BrankoMilan So all the pathologies of globalised Kism are 3rd Way's fault. I'm no fan, but looks a huge&amp;unfair simplification]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the National Portrait Museum, with some of the great American Presidents... https://t.co/Q17M6n1gyc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Undercoverhist Thanks for this must read Real risk of constitutional regression in US; better not to wait for checks&amp;balances to do the job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rodrikdani If not through trade agreements and no through global gvn, how to help raise labour standards in develo… https://t.co/A48esMbafH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rodrikdani If the standard for social dumping is our rules, there wouldn't be much scope for north-south fair trade]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Agent-based economics arrives ready to face the real world...a new paradigm rooted in pragmatism and the complexities of being human" AMÉN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good thing to do if you happen to be in Brussels on 1 February https://t.co/azhOxbzE8b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Policies to support and raise labour standards, tax capital, spur growth can help curb inequality home and abroad. Pragmatic cosmopolitanism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With America First still haunting, great to read that more labor migration is highly efficient. Only part of the solution though 2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rodrikdani explores economic&amp;philosophical dilemma posed by @BrankoMilan Is rising national inequality price for l… https://t.co/M9ngfvk2Xp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lewis-type structural analysis to explore why growth miracles may be over Low L reallocation in Latam, low producti… https://t.co/VW5henqJh2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[News of another universal basic income pilot project. Plus some of the caveats... https://t.co/0IBucu1co0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much wisdom in a blog post. Polanyi, Keynes&amp;Schumpeter+post-keynesian, evolutionary, institutional&amp; behavioral s… https://t.co/9G84tFKJxH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mexico first target, TB doubling in 3y, ugliest could be end of term. Suggests China&amp;EU join forces to pour water i… https://t.co/wR08mCQCbu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WomensMarch https://t.co/vu4CdCXx69]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are so far from even grasping equality of opportunities https://t.co/NqqqQf0Cub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experts at @PIIE have diverging views about WTO compatibility of Border Tax Adjustments in Destination-based cash f… https://t.co/WLdWttikYb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something to watch from next Friday on https://t.co/Z43Rj6xY0z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheMinskys @rethinkecon @TheEconocracy @bradvoracek  A much needed change towards pluralism in economics, starting with education]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@INETeconomics @PaolaSubacchi I couldn't´t agree more. Heterodox econ needs  focus on alternative policy proposals, beyond orthodoxy bashing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent article In Spain euro jacket on predatory elites has been rather loose. Challenge is turn public support… https://t.co/lGIGpEIEdJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Y al final sonó Bruce Springsteen...So long]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DEMOCRACY NEEDS YOU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secular stagnation hypothesis seems to have survived the US elections https://t.co/AKpolB77P8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have these numbers appeared on the Spanish press? Pretty appalling https://t.co/pwSYeqFkQj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would have been wiser to ask him to pay the 13 billion dollars in unpaid taxes https://t.co/HZIIMWdoW3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@janzilinsky why don't these add up with data on gross average wages? I suppose it is because of massive unemployment (re Spain)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We live in an age of political exceptionalism. @georgesoros is a voice worth listening to https://t.co/ypeSoyPzTK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@georgemagnus1 @FukuyamaFrancis @Forbes  Many valuable things may be about to crumble. The dominance of the dollar is not one of them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Redefining progress, a daunting challenge but the key to a new social contract https://t.co/qndMzVGIwq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The benefits of free competition...for thugs´ money https://t.co/eGBflFXYSY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miotei @ProSyn @MFratzscher Both Fra&amp;Ita have tried reforms under recession&amp;instability. Lecturing others in good times shortsighted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One that was not surprised by 2016 events: The Crisis of Market Fundamentalism by Anatole Kaletsky via @ProSyn https://t.co/jy7X2bY0f6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProSyn @miotei @MFratzscher To lead Germany needs to be ready to change and help others change. And trust. Nobody wants a transfer union]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProSyn @miotei @MFratzscher How can an 8,5% surplus not affect the rest of € area? Problem is whole approach has been moral: virtue vs sin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProSyn @miotei @MFratzscher May have missed it, but has Germany put forward proposals for sharing risk with more sovereignty cessions?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProSyn @miotei @MFratzscher Since early 2010 Germany has been leading in € policy, trying to force reform by delaying ECB intervention]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nordhaus presents updated projections on climate change. And the news are pretty dire. More uncertainty from macro… https://t.co/iRtAlB0DgY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helpman reviews recent theoretical&amp;empirical research on trade and wage inequality. Conclusion: it explains just a… https://t.co/12HM4uuMLd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarolineFreund @AdamPosen Thought DBCF would tax M and exempt X Would not distort trade only if implemented globally. FX is second order]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarolineFreund @AdamPosen Why does Auerbach claim DBCF tax does not distort trade? Because of offsetting $? Don´t get it It´s like a tariff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How many from bottom 50% actually vote? How will US income distribution look like after the fiscal reform brewing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Redistribution less effective, Medicaid&amp;Medicare only source of growth for working age adults, Obama 2013 tax rise helped to reverse course]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously should read. Dismal picture of evolution of US income distribution. Golden years for K while bottom 50% s… https://t.co/xzpQc6ON3l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would prefer globalization for all, difficult for nationalism to be responsible Gains from global effort to tax K o… https://t.co/cCHXwJYu97]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnCassidy IMF grasping real world economics is among 2016's most encouraging surprises. Longing for support of FTT before year end]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarcusMcP_ @resfoundation @BrankoMilan @CarolineFreund Where did the Report by Corlett go? Can´t find it, links disabled]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@agarmora @Manuj_Hidalgo @Revenga_WBG Careful, self financing rates of tax cuts are still very high. Need a model closer to reality]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dr_malageli @pisaniferry @ProSyn Indeed¡¡ Could start by rebuilding trust and ditching zero sum games, focusing on making € work for all MS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recent increases in Min W at US state level have raised average wages with no negative effect on employment https://t.co/1XcJ3P5Hhl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True, intelligent and moral...worth reading as these together are in short supply. Humility, learn to share more https://t.co/nOKL6IQuD6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrankoMilan Thanks, nice to look deeper into the elephant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doubling down on vodoo economics. Getting ready to see that good old Laffer Curve again https://t.co/uqVb7IPBCb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrankoMilan The stakes of this debate are pretty high....Looking forward to reading your response (link didn´t work)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miotei Right. That´s why it is likely that US monetary power continues to dwindle while dollar strengthens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrankoMilan Don´t get old vs promising remedies Equality of opportunity rests on taxes needed to finance preferential goods like education]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sanjaygreddy Have you read this https://t.co/PC5zaMKioi? Agent based and stock flow consistent model]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In US they are no longer debating about minimum wage They´re fighting for it. #Fightfor15 and right to unionize. Wo… https://t.co/XknNkRPuq5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miotei Not convinced. Strong dollar will probably become their headache. Watch out for Mundell-Fleming: the revenge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prefer regulation over direct gvt control over credit or CA, but he is right to seek alternative instruments for macro&amp;financial stability]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caveat: monetary policy was very effective to stem the financial crisis, perhaps less so to overcome structural macro problems. 3)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helps to reflect on implications of low rates for inequality&amp;resource allocation Problem is not ZLB but failure to stir productive credit 2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JosephEStiglitz digs on extraordinary ineffectiveness of monetary policy Proposes direct intervention in credit fo… https://t.co/HcFe2Imtco]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rodrikdani When I read EconomicsRules sermed you didnt think changing econ theories (Ideas) was important. Essential for new narratives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great article...following up on last page of General Theory https://t.co/Bm2l5FYs1W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One new stylized fact economics has to explain: technology, labour's bargaining power, the mighty finance? Need to… https://t.co/ABwHSqdDxP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sanjaygreddy What is coming in US is neoliberalism with a tweak Agree on need to change course but would be foolish to renege on progress]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sanjaygreddy ARRA, Dodd-Frank, +20m with health insurance, higher taxes for rich, proposals for hiking min w &amp; expand early childcare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sanjaygreddy There is also backlash against progressive policies (eg Obamacare)&amp;support for tax cuts Rethink yes but no rush to conclusions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@INETeconomics @sanjaygreddy This account looks unfair to Obamanomics, which departed from pre-crisis orthodoxy in fundamental ways]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great short post by @MazzucatoM @michaelujacobs on way forward. Globalisation requires more active government Lot o… https://t.co/Fn2q74UJCx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope it were true...that he really blew up macroeconomics. There have been earlier and bolder rebels who failed https://t.co/yCoLY2qmOd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It will become scarier when the guy learns to give the speech without reading https://t.co/XnH15lYUBH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rethinkeco Bravo¡¡ Wish your peers in Spain followed your lead. Economics needs change and it should be towards pluralism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulkrugman at @PIIE After @BrankoMilan Elephant Curve. Is it trade or is it unfettered plutocracy? Time to flatten the trunk either way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, a very good reason why economists defend free trade is and has always been political: prevention against cheap nationalist politics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarolineFreund to @paulkrugman at @PIIE: Trump picked trade bc it helps blame foreigners. Anti-trade backlash masks xenophobia. Nails it¡¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full monty for capital...4 recommendations to lay the ground for globalization for all https://t.co/iFNjv5VAWg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Practical men, who believe themselves to be quite exempt from intellectual influences, are usually slaves of some… https://t.co/VdtTWe3GGD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And 5) Why present this as (yet another) Third Way? No need for juste milieu This is just good modern left¡¡ Surprised that values are facts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4) Ch True Kism sets out radical program for changing course Although ¿circulation? I´d think insuring in minimum equal freedom&amp;capabilities]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3)Great citizenship is favorite part Work of being in public, courtesy, showing up for each other,leaving place in better shape you found it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2) Contributes to the much needed effort to give concrete political shape to complexity&amp;evolutionary thinking I miss postKeynesian economics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1) Finished reading Gardens of democracy by @ericpliu @NickHanauer Inspiring metaphors and foundations for progressive politics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent article. Explains plainly why we should be worried beyond Tuesday with the way politics is evolving in th… https://t.co/YvvgfYwlBn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The time has come for predistribution policies. Change way markets and firms work not just wait for outcome&amp;struggl… https://t.co/n2obBBDZJ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The more I learn about Hamdi Ulukaya, the more I love him. I even changed my yogourt eating habits https://t.co/fYt0ith8GJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickHanauer Good to find out 35 years later RBC was post-real But crisis hasnt been kind to NK model which is now being deconstructed Next?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recommended reading for the US Treasury https://t.co/3KGalTdapr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tackling the accident of birth at its root. The idea is not new (Atkinson tracks the precedents in ch 6 of Inequali… https://t.co/dhJ7yLUrBH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They must be celebrating the New Heterodox Explosion. Helping #YSIplenary piece together a Paradigm https://t.co/hXhZSUOwPv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The New Deal saved capitalism from itself...by sharing the wealth. At @blognewdeal we concur https://t.co/P9PvFGd8eh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AngelUbide Inequality has roots deeper than austerity. Tax policy, for example.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Noahpinion Agent-Based Macro Models are already quite enlightening On one thing I agree: more focus on alternative and less on criticizing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Noahpinion AD influencing potential growth, heterogeneous agents and even the macro prudential approach are departures from mainstream]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Noahpinion I see Heterodox Explosion as convergence of Complexity, Evolutionary Economics and Post Keynesianism. And it is making headway]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>