<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I would like to see Julia Davis impersonate Kelly Anne Conway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no planes !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael O'Leary doing an Arsene Wenger. "There's no players available " https://t.co/xyiIA4Wc6J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desperate for new @sparksofficial material &amp; tour to distract me from the "bad dude" showing us that he can write his signature everyday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course ! @eolaoire @kumbrick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[Valentine] @eolaoire's Valentine should be @kumbrick! Who should be yours?
via https://t.co/uOGrdF5wCj https://t.co/0xR6fUUS3g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StromoUK I'm staring into your thighs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eurovision is going to be particularly special this year. I hope]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm reading Don Quixote in Costa and they are playing a tacky Spotify cover of Cher's 'Believe'. Existence is disgusting .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And doing every to make sure people don't question him either . (Brexit is complicit with helping him and the far right )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man consumed by egoism who will do everything he can to stay in power for as long, making impulsive decisions , never questioning himself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've seen people on my timeline question why we are so doom and gloom about Trump. I'm sorry. This is fascism we are dealing with]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I lost a follower after this. Come on. It's true]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[England and America continue to be the most overrated countries ever. At least they're consistent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clickblackburn blame the acid in my gut !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeoffArsenal in fairness he has had some dreadful moments this season ! Southampton on the league, that Spurs sub appearance ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisiain lifeguard etc . My new Grindr bio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisiain he's changed . Date again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I 💘 Danny Welbeck. Win us the title . Please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@santos_ldn definitely noted!! thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i've reached a month without a hungover. i must say. my skin looks 11% better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@santos_ldn what hotel was that pool at? looks lovely]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nightraincity nice armpit. well done]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkGodfrey777 @that_flojo @SkyNews @POTUS doesn't look like Donald can say anything either ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where's the answer 🤔@SkyNews @POTUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_Irish_Mike are you going to post it then ?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DickinsonTimes he didn't completely lose it when we were denied a blatant peno at 0-0 either. i've never seen him less animated tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DickinsonTimes one thing you overlook is that Wenger has actually improved his behavior over the last few years. he is more restrained]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["tall guys &amp; business class gym-goers to the top of queue"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimForde the last one....and he needed to use the bathroom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[today, a man gave me a free day bass to a "business class" gym https://t.co/CFBSuz624r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gpb1979 it is my fluffy hot water bottle. Thank you !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeling sick because of the dishonest media and my overrated stomach . Sad ! https://t.co/2fxoV8z6oI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@skattebu and Scandinavian 💘💘💘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for a full time husband . Preferably, Doctor or health professional. Bye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackNev20 @Ryanair next time I'll say "lol very funny ryanair" to keep you happy,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackNev20 @Ryanair OK.  Goodbye . I'll stop having opinions on things]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackNev20 @Ryanair and I am aware ryanair has a long history of silly funny ads but this is fucking stupid. End of]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackNev20 @Ryanair I don't know why you are so interested in trying to prove to me that it is a good decision by them ????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackNev20 @Ryanair I was obsessed with aviation as a child and loved ryanair 
 Wrote letters etc. Fine company. Stupid tacky advertising]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackNev20 @Ryanair I'm not pretending to be outraged.  I think it is in very bad taste, unnecessary and cheap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackNev20 @Ryanair look Jack, why did they delete it ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FelipeMurrelli how does he know that? Who has actually said there was a million at it? Who?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sleepy_medic google news aer lingus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_ConorQ there has loads of shitty unfunny ads but this is grotesque]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's something alluring about hotels beside main roads]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_ConorQ sounds great tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beau_jf it's so good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lovvejoy @dublinbusnews dishonest drivers!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @dublinbusnews half empty 123 just drove past dame st stop with about 15 of us at the stop &amp; hands out. Sad!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavQuinn @rtenews the reality is the majority of Americans voted for Hillary and Americans have a president who disregards facts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavQuinn @rtenews also do you have pics of Washington when he went through city ? Was it empty then ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavQuinn @rtenews I'm not sure what your point is ? The most alarming thing is the president of America is lying about the attendance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me going to Barcelona https://t.co/6icqvGF8bx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[probably errors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rip refereeing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiamPaulCanning as if he isn't going to get charged...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love the stewards coming to defend Arsene @TikiTakaConnor @ElSpanishGooner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joshday27 @LiamGeorge_ and koscielny is going to head the ball, could easily have denied him a goal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joshday27 @LiamGeorge_ how is a kick in the face not a penalty? He is offside. But he's kicked in the face 🤔]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How many late goals have arsenal got this season ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joshday27 @LiamGeorge_ arsenal were denied a blatant penalty . Live it was blatant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought it was gonna be that Eboue moment against Liverpool again....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiamGeorge_ @Joshday27 what about the absolute blatant penalty on Mustafi? Goodbye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My fucking heart . That was mental . Refereeing appalling.  Love Wenger getting aggressive.  All amazing and painful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Olearys https://t.co/X3vJcLWbGD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dcahughes Welbeck is a big plus, Perez is a great option , gives us more directness ? And I think Iwobi is looking more effective now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dcahughes yes. My predication is Arsenal are going to go on a strong run now! Providing Mustafi &amp; Bellerin are back to 100%]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arsene Wenger : "sometimes when you give success to stupid people, it makes them more stupid, not more intelligent" #trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sure these marches are killing Trump. bigger story than his inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We accept Hillary lost. But should we stay silent against a president who threatened to imprison his opponent if he was elected ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How dare you march against a vitriolic , aggressive , isolationist president who got 3 million votes less than his opponent !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buulshit on the liberals shutting down debate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Irish Times comments riddled with men 40years+ &amp; awful blurry profile pics attacking and insulting anything that goes against their views]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ref just handed that to Spurs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimForde v. nice ! we can hope he gets a divorce and goes on celebrity big brother or some trashy tv show and plays up to the cameras]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[what you have all wanted to hear from me. i predict Arsenal are going to go on a long unbeaten run after tomorrow/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[especially ones who say "happily taken" with a ring emoji]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#bancouplesfromTinder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Blue Friday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimForde I think those pics will transmit well on tinder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe I should change my instagram aesthetic from my face and bedroom wall, to me watering plants all the time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a crush on an Irish guy. This last happened in 1867]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contemplating the next 4 years. SAD! https://t.co/yRIz2EFnjp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WE WILL DO EVERYTHING]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America is so fucking overrated]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduce to your life, a specific day for you to have a bath . Life improves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(i'm booking it. OKAY is good enough for me)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[" Lola herself is okay " imagine reading that on AirBnB after they stayed in your house]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Conall_O_Riain @Ryanair it's been 4 mins. give it time Conall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brianocofaigh haha. good to hear ! but i think intermittent deactivations are the way forward !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hey @Ryanair lower your prices to Seville. Evan. x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aquae_sulis_ only a little]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Samsung pics are v shinny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eduardofitch a profoundly broken man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being a week without twitter is very good.  Being a week without Evan, I'm sure, must be very difficult . I apologise x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My favourite dishwasher https://t.co/EWVT7fmSCS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All elite overrated celebrities should come out with personal statements in unison so Trump can write a separate tweet for each individual]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brianocofaigh but it was obviously a casual interview, he wasn't writing an opinion piece]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>