<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Omg @AoibhinGarrihy amazing! Beautiful! #aoibhin #DWTSIrl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah poor hughie, he's devastated ðŸ˜¢He did so well tonight - wish there was a dance off ðŸ˜³#DWTSIrl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah des you were brill @sportsdes well done you â¤ï¸â¤ï¸ #DancingWiththeStars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done hughie ðŸ‘±ðŸ¼ðŸ˜‰ #DancingWiththeStars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Richard he's just not for you, keep looking Timmy you are just a tad bit immature! #FirstDatesIRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the couples on @cooper_m  2day hilarious as yer man bought her a hoover ðŸ˜‚ &amp; she said it was the best present ever #thencomesmarriage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lance wanted to read the monopoly rules because he wanted to learn more about mortgages ðŸ˜‚ really dude #thencomesmarriage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CatherineLynch she was brilliant #DancingWiththeStars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackConan1 getting closer to securing a place in the Ireland panel, great performance  #LEIvMON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's the story with the lads draping their arms on their partners shoulders.....around your ladies waist lads...ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚#DWTSIrl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Johnny looking very trim and fit  #LEIvZEB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was brilliant ðŸ‡®ðŸ‡ªðŸ‡®ðŸ‡ªðŸ‡®ðŸ‡ª#twoshadesofgreen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mickconlan11 when is your first prof fight Mick?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhotosOfDublin great photo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DareToTettey I know...sure Conor a local lad and as I said I do support him but I do wish he'd fight at a reasonable GMT time next time ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RTEsport mad yokes ðŸ˜‚ supreme at their sport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaHogan94 all amateur athletes working hard for funding to make their dreams come true @TheNotoriousMMA  is in a different ball game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McEvoyDamien ðŸ˜‚ can't wait]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DareToTettey he is amazing in his sport and I support him but I think that's the only thing that winds people up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DareToTettey far from it, just think Conor shud talk more about the training and sacrifices for the sport that the money - simple as]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DareToTettey far from it, c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[O'Donovan's v McGregor - Conor needs a lesson in humility - I might watch Conor in the early hours but..@TheNotoriousMMA    #rtesportawards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd #rtesportawards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh Conor you disappoint me with your words  #rtesportawards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomBarr247 @Scott_Evans1 lads I loved watching ye both - well done and keep on achieving - two good looking Irish heroes ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜#rtesportawards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nmuddles they are so subdued - give them a few shots ðŸ¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Stephen gets bored he could come back to Dublin and St Pats â¤ï¸ always a tear in his eye about his passion for football #rtesportawards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stephen Kenny is so humble, great man  #rtesportawards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG DANNY AND OTI!!!  ðŸ”¥ðŸ”¥ðŸ”¥ðŸ”¥â¤ï¸â¤ï¸â¤ï¸ðŸ”¥ðŸ”¥ðŸ”¥ðŸ”¥â¤ï¸â¤ï¸â¤ï¸â¤ï¸#StrictlyFinal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ian_odoherty #TheCrossing #CBLive What happened in your life to make you such an ignoramus - you have no humanity, u are nothing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cooper_m @poolfan81 @lstwrd @todayfm excellent will be listening]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take the hard decisions to solve the problems...whilst people die in the water.. Ian o'doherty if it was only that simple #thecrossing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeorginaQuinlan so young, what a brave young man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heartbroken watching that, I've a lump in my throat and a heavy heart #irishnavyheroes #irishdefenceforces #thecrossing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow Rory....beats Ed Sheehan any day!! #LateLateToyShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@the_augurey which kids]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those people not participating in the audience shouldn't be given any freebies ðŸ˜œ#LateLateToyShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Edie Rose put the fear of God in Ryan when she had that cream....so disappointed it didn't work for her ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚#LateLateToyShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cooper_m we were unfortunate, I thought we lost a bit of shape when Dallas went off but hey we did ok. Another Leeds on the box this Sat ðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cooper_m I think we will win ðŸ˜€ although I'd prefer to win more league games]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our team has gone viral ðŸ˜€ well done @goodcounselgaa @barry1217  https://t.co/kfgWvwyEcD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatieTaylor well done girl - so proud of you ðŸ‡®ðŸ‡ª]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@goodcounselgaa #camogie #TheMannequinChallenge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Platform for grand slam 2017 jeez Steve Hansen is a bit touchy ðŸ‘ŽðŸ» #IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for a ticket for IREvAUS just for me please but two would be great  #IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Eoghanlyons unreal stats but lack of penetration, too many handling errors at crucial times....the luck of the Irish was also missing 2day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NZ lived on the edge of the rules, ref's balls I think fell off somewhere in the 1st half, immense effort by the boys #proud2birish #IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovin that dress @CarterMarissa and love coco brown #latelate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Katie looks really happy and free - the best of luck in the pro arena @KatieTaylor - so proud of her  #latelate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What GMT is Conor expected to be in the ring? #UFC205]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Omg had it recorded...Ed Balls so funny...made me happy ðŸ˜€ðŸ˜€ðŸ˜€ðŸ˜€ðŸ˜€ #Strictly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jez he made Jordi hobble on for what 2 mins!!! @Jordimurphy dem skinny jeans acting as a compression bandage on that knee ðŸ˜€ðŸ‘ðŸ¼ #raydarcyshow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got to love George @ghook  #raydarcyshow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really enjoy listen to Jim Sheridan - a great and honest man #raydarcyshow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RTEsoccer why 2 goalies on the bench?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FAIreland #AUSvIRE why have we two goalies on the bench! Surely having an extra outfield player would give us better options]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DCCTraffic is this still in place]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's this family who have the life sentence, it's such a disgrace they have to deal with this #latelate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David McGowan is a tonic - puts a new perspective on what could happen in the back of a taxi ðŸ˜‚  #latelate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cormacd1 practice match...don't be talking rubbish...international test match ðŸ‘ðŸ¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah we have ref sound now  #IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The camera people are already annoying me  #IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ireland team standing in the figure 8 â¤ï¸ #IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rock to the beat #deadly #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RM_Heffernan #LateLateShow always great to hear from Rob, so deserved. I hope he gets his medal in London 2017 - good luck ðŸ…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anybody got a stream to the match #lufc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's happening ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ #lufclive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_stevedunn where u streaming it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are ye all at the match...raging it's not on the box #lufc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@starryboy14 #LateLateShow great interview, great footballer...but up the Dubs ðŸ”µðŸ”µ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh Darcey you so want to experience the stamina of Ore ðŸ˜ #Strictly but why did they get 10's #dannyrobbed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Anton...such fun #Strictly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should have been 10's for Danny &amp; Oti #Strictly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishTimes that's shocking. When leaving the Aviva on Thurs I said that the road lighting was really poor, i wonder was was this a factor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eoghanmcdermo â¤ï¸ Rose of Tralee 2016 #RayDarcy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Paul O'Connell...great set of teeth ðŸ˜€ #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WestCorkPaul Michael would be an ideal person for Gay to interview on that other show that Gay does]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WestCorkPaul it is a chat show but with Michael you would need an hour so maybe it should be another programme]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WestCorkPaul the last time he was on, they talked about it for quite a while]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always enjoy the honesty of Michael Harding...great writer #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RTEsport #COYBIG OMG did Hunt just call a Dundalk player Humpty Dumpty!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's very sad, many people to blame, ignorance at the heart of it, no compassion or respect assimilate not integrate..failure #thetravellers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has JOE Brolly has a glass of wine...maybe? #DUBvMAYO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No Cian O'Sullivan in half back line, that's disappointing #thesundaygame #DUBvMAYO #gaateamoftheyear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Omg @McIlroyRory You Beauty!!! Congrats  #FedExCup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just watching the late late show now and Michael D is amazing. I could listen to hm forever #MichaelDforPresidentAgain #latelate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SineadOCarroll #LateLateShow loving the hair style, fab colour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ParalympicsIRE @TeamMcKillop not televised!!! Any GB athletes in it? Hope C4 will go back for it...in the velodrome at the moment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyleNugentRTE @rte #ParalympicsRio2016 Really disappointed that RTE are not showing our athletes in this competition. Why Ryle??????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[15 years, so many tears #NeverForget15years  #neverforget]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Swit Swoo @TomBarr247 #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing results by everybody especially Elaine....incredible #lifestylechanges   #CelebOT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#seamuscallanan legend..brilliant hurler #delighted  #SundayGame]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FintanMusic #GAA is the best sport in the world...always something to talk about irrespective of what county ur from]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Niamhy79 has to be Callanan ðŸ˜ and that's from a dub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FintanMusic when Dubs win V Mayo they won"t use that type of language  ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ I'd say Bubbles mammy will give him a right schlap!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are they not at the Burlo? #SundayGame]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ireland  #ThanksRobbie everybody in the Aviva let's sing "One More Year" ðŸ‡®ðŸ‡ªðŸ‡®ðŸ‡ª]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_SomeDad incorrect...it's about the para Olympics competition...maybe you should watch Judge Judy or Jeremy Kyle for the "human interest "]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_SomeDad what a ridiculous thing to say]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>