<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@loesstather @callaghannz great to see such a good turn out! You should share this pic on edi Loes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, this nearly had me in tears more than once. There's something in here for every communicator and leader about… https://t.co/pLlKrfbu50]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing says summer like Mr Whippy in the sun. Thanks @hemiroll! That was fun :) #gracefieldlife #xmas @callaghannz https://t.co/jvJVcGEHiK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While you were all off gallivanting around Wellington, here's what you missed back at the office today @callaghannz… https://t.co/EFzk4SlvDh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could it be true that we are in fact the world's only innovation quarter with ducks? Insight of the day from… https://t.co/pG1mX88Vy0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving that commitment @hemiroll! And innovation... ;-) (see @ColmKear, knew you were the right person for the job!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Create stories pitched at a distracted eight-year-old and you will be getting it about right." https://t.co/LKgTchnmhx via @idealogmag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moral of the story? Get the basics right! Stay on message, focus your media energy, keep it simple... #pr101 https://t.co/WL64jTYAsJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She will be missed! https://t.co/D3aoTZpM3B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#brand innovation through the lens of #PokemonGo - via @callaghannz :) https://t.co/oG9t0Qzjcc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColmKear great pic! Definitely edi-ble :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#StolenRum "When I'm creating a brand, I always tell my clients to try &amp; find the truth in what they're doing." https://t.co/AMq1OqTrN7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chris Anderson: TED's secret to great public speaking | TED Talk | https://t.co/RcNTAPWGvK https://t.co/aRlHh8VVhP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Xero does corporate culture &amp; engagement, from the mouth of Happiness Engineer Julie Reddish, via…https://t.co/9JZy0Q3uZO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just signed up for a rat trap through predatorfreekhandallah@gmail.com - not excited about dead rats, but have to do our bit! #predatorfree]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Long week, so very relieved to realise I'm actually on the @FlyAirNZ flight to Akl tonight... Less stress + koru hour = :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewpbeaumont, top 10 mountain biking trails in Wellington - summer checklist! https://t.co/ybgatJeri6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The top 10 foods you shouldn't be eating (and 10 you should) | https://t.co/PLtcIpx37E https://t.co/DvBSHhKteF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crofton Downs shows it's not that hard to be #PredatorFree... https://t.co/tlcPMaahpL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this! - leadership lessons from dancing guy and how to create a movement - https://t.co/u0gkoVevdE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love @Wellington_NZ's annual Wondrous #WellingtonAdvent Calendar - cuteness, festivity and free stuff :) https://t.co/Q6sMZfqyAd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More on the art of #Sketchnoting. This is so cool. I need to buy a Sharpie and re-discover my inner artist! https://t.co/sSJCpvVoO6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#doodling. Great word. A way to stay focused in meetings. Also a powerful communication tool? https://t.co/VPGq2cYHyH @Melcrum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would you eat a hamburger grown in a lab? Here's why lab-grown meat kinda makes sense... https://t.co/6x3JlO6FVq  via @nzherald @medickinson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Filmmaker Andrew Stanton on the art of storytelling -- | TED Talk | https://t.co/RcNTAPWGvK https://t.co/RvFai2SvCb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These are the 'dangerous Syrian refugees' Americans are worried about - heartbreaking photos, many of hem children.. https://t.co/b8pcZyLeV6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future sounds amazing - https://t.co/7wDio8rUsQ @callaghannz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's something different, "gamifying" corporate strategy with board games and mobile apps... https://t.co/JF4fyGoQ0C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insights into how they "do" innovation at @Private_Flight; love the idea of a visual workplace... https://t.co/IT26wmtKnH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome @google mantras direct from their #NewYorkCity HQ - via @callaghannz https://t.co/7b4fOaxW1x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Spokesbird Hmm, not sure cute is quite the phrase I'd use Sirocco, but awesome never-the-less ;-) (they're going to be tall!) #kakichicks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["They all view culture as the single most important component of their future, their most critical asset." https://t.co/Mwij2XLSNV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewpbeaumont, we need to stock up on red wine... Red wine equal to a gym workout - https://t.co/ArijdI0c5z via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice blog from the lovely @SiobhanFile about uncovering great stories within organisations (go Cake Queen!) https://t.co/f0G3eJnMXR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Living in a (meta)material world- @callaghannz @andrewpbeaumont  https://t.co/2FvGktFoAm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is truly awesome news. Good on you John. https://t.co/rwzw8arTrk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yikes, 16% of the species in Finding Nemo face the threat of extinction. Just like NZ's own Nemo #FindingMaui https://t.co/T1VhuQmEUU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DawnUnplugged Hey hey! Well it's only week two, so it's not going very far yet! ;) but nice people, nice office, lots to do...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Case studies are good - but they don't take people on a journey, they don't have texture." @stevecla on stories: http://t.co/lqKP1sU05r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool tools for DIY infographics. https://t.co/PoSCIQftUo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These made me giggle out loud on the bus. (See, all my reasons for postponing exercise are completely valid...) https://t.co/dblZaniwmL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@callaghannz loving the famous apple trees :-) I can feel an apple related morning tea coming on...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This rings true - good leaders focus on what's possible, know what their people need from them (and deliver it), and…https://t.co/yzxVEcfYhE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What defines being a Kiwi? One for you @bird_o_paradise :) https://t.co/1WVkmDNtk2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[16 Ways To Increase Your Cycling Speed - @andrewpbeaumont  http://t.co/2wguLr6wTG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Been there!" moment -- wildlife spotting on the Kinabatangan River,  #borneo - http://t.co/IYJLayDf9g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Basically the cutest thing ever - "Bears in the pool!" http://t.co/wRhrbPtzXj http://t.co/08vxfvSZvM”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RadioHaurakiNZ hey what was that last tune you played just before the 4.58 ad break? Loving it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So positive to see senior officials in Borneo publicly commiting to stopping deforestation &amp; protecting wildlife http://t.co/i6wbkIZfnJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving the new living walls popping up around Wellington! #lovethiscity http://t.co/GAwd37Ms3u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewpbeaumont oh that explains it ;-) #delayfish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, stunning pics coming through from this year's Cook Straight Whale survey @whalesurvey #jobenvy https://t.co/4LF3Pgxnod]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant to see all the #pledgefornz activity for #conservation week! What's your whanau doing? http://t.co/fGFYBAgWQj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SiobhanFile That is very cruel, but still pretty funny ;-) Work is busy. We miss you! Enjoy your last week of peace - make the most of it!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SiobhanFile ha ha ha I am glad those were just bluetooth speakers Sio. You can tell your flattie he almost had me sucked in too...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @meetmikemorgan: Pin A Quote Lets You Highlight Any Text & Pin It To Pinterest - SocialTimes http://t.co/dDc9vK2J via @socialtimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guide to Pinterest for tourism businesses http://t.co/9NzGYfrp via @cabbagetree  and @CommsatTIA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another # gone wrong tale... RT @JustinFlitter: McDonalds Twitter campaign goes terribly wrong - http://t.co/qwxtsl2j #in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AdvocacyatTIA: When will NZ start taking this seriously? http://t.co/yPUBeOOt We have so much to lose...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, last ever Big Day Out today. And I'm at work!! This is an outrage. When did I get so old.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The MySky is set - RT @gregmilnenz: highly recommend you watch Frozen Planet on TV1 tonight. It's mindblowing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading: 30 Social Media Predictions for 2012 frm the Pros http://t.co/XKUCzBYP via @smexaminer @CommsatTIA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[V useful, thx @andymac03... Demystifying Facebook's "People Are Talking About This" Metric  http://t.co/mCvb9mMm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously cute RT @davidfarrier: baby sloths getting a bath: http://t.co/5Nc6fCc1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ATTTO_News: mgmt trainee & @keacampers superstar Chrissy Mackay is profiled on www.nzlifeandleisure.co.nz ths mth - looking fab Chrissy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was here almost 7yrs ago 2 th day... RT @BrilliantTips Panajachel, Guatemala – Where the Mayan Culture Still Thrives: http://t.co/1m3meE3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @swiftynz: Tonight marks a massive change to the NZ media industry as NZPA files their last report - http://t.co/QUAeiP3 via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exciting! RT @JustinFlitter: #RWC2011 Opening Ceremony preview video as the production teams gear up http://t.co/ONwPT5T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice wee guide to RWC for non-rugby fans... RT @lonelyplanet: A guide to New Zealand’s Rugby World Cup http://bit.ly/namGzJ #lp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ATTTO_News: Christchurch Press coverage of our workforce survey - Skilled Tourism Staff in Short Supply http://tinyurl.com/3lyjap6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HAPNZ is launching a new accreditation for "bike friendly" holiday parks. Great idea! http://tinyurl.com/3mfzs6p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're just getting started on Twitter you might find this helpful, an article I wrote back in my TNZ days: http://tinyurl.com/3oyk3hy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ATTTO_News Check out how we're promoting tourism careers & training to young Kiwis, we think Sam's a star! http://bit.ly/nReMKb #Rotorua]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Non-marketing wisdom from my fav brand guru Geoff Ross: http://t.co/QjKddCP. Awesome, thx @business_govtNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bobsyauncle: The EMA board were trying to brainstorm what went wrong with their CEO’s recent comments... http://bit.ly/mDOsIQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adorable. looks quite at home & doesn't seem to mind the cameras! RT @Spokesbird: emperor penguin in New Zealand! http://ow.ly/5mrAC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @daniel_baylis: 20 things I learned from travel - http://bit.ly/il96Ew #travel #lp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And it looks awesome... Nice work! RT @KimKiwi It's live, live, live - newzealand.com/int/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WellingtonZoo Beautiful! Not often you get to see a tui up close like that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quite like this: http://linkd.in/kFUafi. Reminds me of all the talk at #PRINZ11 last week about about being a good social media citizen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for a good NZ social media consultant to work with tourism business. Suggestions?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessedee Well it is the coolest little capital in the world! ;-) Would love to show you round, get in touch if you make it down this way!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So how is it I can travel all through SEAsia & get free wireless, but here in a rather nice Rotorua hotel they boot me out after 20 mins?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome group of ppl @ #PRINZ11. Luvd Duncan Stewart's talk - random networks, sticky marbles & flocks of starlings - all PR truths...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessedee loved ur talk @ #prinz just now. V inspiring! Will send suck @ ppt 2 all my workmates ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[V proud of my desk-buddy @blairhillyard , who's on his way down to #christchurch with SPCA's Animal Rescue Unit #eqnz Stay safe!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeling pretty sick to my stomach watching the footage from #Christchurch. Thoughts with everyone down there...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @business_govtNZ: Want to get the most out of social media for your business? Here's part 3 of our 6-part series... http://ow.ly/400gG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Campervans with wifi , great idea - now why has no one thought of this before ... http://bit.ly/et9RFa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Annual report time. Anyone have any examples of annual reports that are actually readable/interesting?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AngelaMoriarty yep definitely need to pop up at say hi! Will email you :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AngelaMoriarty love the pic of Ania, sav blanc in hand :) I also still love your new website, something about that blue!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So you need a smartphone to be a packpacker now? RT @jasons_travel: The essentials of being a backpacker http://bit.ly/fLsR1A #rememberwhen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CommsatTIA  Ahhh of course, I should have known :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CommsatTIA ha ha, yeah always a fan of stealing good content ;-) Where do you guys find all that stuff?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top Twitter tips: http://bit.ly/fK1Gj7 Useful for work-related twittery stuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last day in the office for 2011. Time for some procrastination and animal YouTube videos... http://tinyurl.com/3xettee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AngelaMoriarty Hey! Welcome back! Hope you had a great trip!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chance to get your mug into a Ridley Scott feature film...he's looking for footage from around the world 2moro. V cool http://trunc.it/9tphr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ha, nice! RT @ColeStanley: BBC: Why can't the rest of the world be like NZ? http://tiny.cc/6hm5b.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>