<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Congestion charge? Or even a city wide 20mph limit? https://t.co/XnxQYGwoQZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These are the stories of refugees learning English in Wales https://t.co/Qzdikyqy8b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A nine-year-old girl has written to Donald Trump to say that building a wall is 'just mean and selfish' https://t.co/N3q6LAXp8W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welsh schools, @JiffyRugby wants you to help support @WelshRugbyUnion and @Velindre. Will you? https://t.co/4yotVYi9NL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've had a @Kilner_uk catastrophe. https://t.co/d0vUkIuUZU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mainly against, some for...here's what people are saying about the Coal Exchange https://t.co/YN24Ex2YUF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My brave colleagues publicly donned lyrca and high vis for this #heroes https://t.co/0gJrRCgpwC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rachymain It's 9.55am and @tylerashleighm just handed out the Rich Tea's #biscuitThursday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DiscoBra I thought the same thing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The number of people sleeping rough in Wales is up 72% https://t.co/lX1xx99jmd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It could be a long time until May... https://t.co/SrYOZaP0LI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kerryhood Ok. Afraid am at home now but will ask Civic Society for explanation in the morning and let you know!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kerryhood Sorry Kerry but that's the release I received from Civic Society. Could someone else at STCE have approved said statement?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some new additions to the (cheese-related) bucket list https://t.co/cmfSpboHKO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some incredibly brave people shared their stories today https://t.co/7ptuGWYw2P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[City Road snaffle news - Oz Urfa is turning into...a burger place. https://t.co/hbt0kUULEI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rachel_Maycock That's fab to see!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're travelling through Bristol Airport in the next few months you may want to be prepared for this https://t.co/N5ZCz0tKyE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@compass_James Mine's a sour, see you there!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SaraGib With no hint of a joke...I've run out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robgood4 Many years on, yours still gives me nightmares.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*This* is a rock and roll Friday https://t.co/B5PuTiJzHj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So the City Deal has taken a step on...https://t.co/uA6kIckaue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CharlesHeslett Loving your work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Armed police close off large part of Cardiff suburb – live updates https://t.co/XopUABuWqM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@traumagasdoc SO excited to watch it on catch up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Lib Dems in Cardiff have their next leader...and it's @ElizabethCdf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deaf children were sexually abused at a now-closed Welsh school, AM claims https://t.co/p7LeOu374T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matgower I am delighted to be leaving the office having thought (and cooked) ahead #muhahaha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democracy fans - Senedd TV is back up, and they've kicked back off with a debate on bins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think the kids say #lolz https://t.co/Ga5TJ6qRX5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wpduk Thanks for this!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wpduk Thanks Drew - is the Wales Millennium Centre one of them?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wpduk Hi, are any other premises/homes in the Bay affected please?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The original Severn Tolls law would cut them to ZERO next year https://t.co/7Vfodh8Vbj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will bore anyone who listens about how interesting is @GlamArchives - here's the fruits of my latest nosy  https://t.co/K7jRRny1aq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cardiff's Lib Dem leader Judith Woodman has announced she will stand down and not seek re-election in May.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beicwrtaff Glad to hear it! Diolch!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beicwrtaff At the wish of sounding old school, it's in both our newspapers tomorrow (or just hit 'click survey' at the bottom)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Despite spending my Friday night writing those 700 words, it can basically be summarised as "It's their fault/no, i… https://t.co/yCsktt9msr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What happened when I took a rush hour (ish) train from Cardiff Central with Chris Grayling and @Craig4CardiffN https://t.co/MKwJNtEUVj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cardiff is an early favourite to be the UK's City of Culture 2021 https://t.co/ZGYqA9AZPe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Bush sisters have written a letter in @TIME to the Obama girls https://t.co/4osenlVJco]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jsiddle This is epic! https://t.co/qfpX6bOsve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Second emergency outing @Chiara__Rinaldi! https://t.co/9pjWjCNNWU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matthew_horwood My understanding is that even if two ways are brought in, total would still be £3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You could be about to pay an awful lot less to cross the Severn Bridge https://t.co/JagKGeyXN8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AledBlake I believe in cheese with most things. And oop north we even have fruit cake with cheese so why the hell not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cheesepantry You've started an office Twitter debate (see @AledBlake @shinyshughes) about the best crackers to join in. Can you pull rank?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AledBlake With Stilton? No, you obviously have it with Lancashire #duh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mayor of Yorkshire!? https://t.co/KGokxNPwoO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AledBlake Water biscuits? Good God man, have a word with yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This looks filthy (in a really, really great way) https://t.co/zlusAf51hX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotLeafy @gourmetgorro @FuudBlog @Gaddboy @cleanplateblog @SushiLifeCDF I adore the teamwork involved in tracking this down. Da iawn!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three hours and ten minutes into today's planning meeting, I'm down to my last satsuma #snackwatch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never heard the word "bund" so much as in the last hour https://t.co/ddWw3rLcGP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Defendant cuts his throat in the dock at Welsh magistrates' court https://t.co/HVPZgVEEIa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Residents protest about plans to open a 'sanctuary' for people with drug and alcohol problems 24 hours a day https://t.co/ewrADXkJRu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Four months til an election and Labour are still bickering - here's what @PhilBale says https://t.co/n1ZGpIwe7I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gaddboy Damn it...Review in 140 characters?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think a lot has happened already at Central Square - just wait for 2017!  https://t.co/p1EWNhbdHi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roath/City Road foodie news. The (Wellfield) Il Pastificio is becoming a sushi joint and Oz Urfa is getting a fancy makeover. All go!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh Roath, you beauty https://t.co/OMVGxXdXg1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbarnett1 It's an interesting and eye-catching job title with a great salary. We verified and then changed story. Can't win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbarnett1 Make your mind up, first it was story, now headline! In the motto of a varnish co, it does exactly what it says on the tin!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@john_rostron @paulbarnett1 @NeilCocker The original story was sent to us via freelance, I went to uni to verify - then see resulting story]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbarnett1 @NeilCocker @john_rostron Sorry to ruin the rants but check my print and online copy (no politician quoted!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An incredibly brave mum needs our help https://t.co/umV0xcfMPX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just discovered #ginuary (CC @jessicabest87 @EmilyHeward)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More cases of bird flu have been found in Wales https://t.co/Bofs2rFOtZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[M62 shooting: Shocking photographs capture aftermath https://t.co/fLeoFh5DmF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May be back at work after a supreme festive break, but one thing is a constant...I am still 90% Quality Street]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's true @westwalesjourno, I've seen it with my own eyes. https://t.co/EL7GGjLx0q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marksmith1985 @SamTegeltija @huwsilk Lads, a supreme tea round development... https://t.co/FOfmolaJ54]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hitting the four hour mark which means it's time for rendition number two of this (and miraculously no red lights i… https://t.co/MVSac6rvRT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This week I spent a night with @Saferwales on their incredible project working with Cardiff's prostitutes https://t.co/SHsf55qNC3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beer *and* a bag. Honestly @RoathBrewery you're quite the festive elves! Happy hic-mas! https://t.co/2mYL2AmfwB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ILovesTheDiff Given it's the season of goodwill, here's a freebie - hit "skip survey" and voila - newyddion!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember this name? Former council leader makes a bid for a comeback https://t.co/bZcDUU7jl0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A panini and a pikachu - what a lunch break! https://t.co/RVQxGpfDiF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cardiff's Big Weekend is coming back and @pridecymru say it will be bigger than ever https://t.co/gbpE5eY4C5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lovely winter morning seeing what's been going on at Llanishen and Lisvane reservoirs with @DwrCymru https://t.co/2tvndXSyBn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You just never know who you'll bump into in Aber @paulrowland1 #gettingthegoss https://t.co/iPhtaEJJgK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@westwalesjourno I really don't want to spoil it for you, but that's a lovely stretch of road.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice doing business with you @michellejfinney #caketrades https://t.co/0WUooynLML]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As well as excellent cake, there's brilliant outfitting by @WalesOnline today for the very deserving @HuggardCentre https://t.co/Z5BVjJpM6n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supreme turnout for the @WalesOnline cake day for @HuggardCentre! https://t.co/HyDycFdQ28]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These are the easiest and hardest places to pass your driving test in Wales https://t.co/tsfpmm9Wgw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty sure we all know someone who will be asking Santa for this (*cough* @Cemlyn @elin87)! https://t.co/J0OzGa9RxE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Planning committee is live. I've got grapes to eat (#snackwatch) and a pic of a hedgehog in the live blog #winning https://t.co/ExNXqUZBSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carys13 Hi Carys, would you mind if we used this pic on Wales Online? Ta!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessicabest87 Best line in a press release ever "Judging broadcasted live on World Cheese TV"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Diolch yn fawr @coednadolig! Mae'n berffaith! https://t.co/SJV1H4orjS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An epic list of who's who in comedy (and they're all in Cardiff next year!)  https://t.co/UZLGoOMfvj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Wales' first Syrian refugees are settling in a year on https://t.co/tUnU2KPGYh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More nom news. https://t.co/pFrGprk1LF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Assembly thinks it needs a new name and wants your views https://t.co/vIg58AbbWP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['An important step forward in the journey' - Tata have their say on today's announcement https://t.co/yLPqwLJzbQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*cough* @GHughes5 @Cemlyn @steffrhwill @gethinshughes https://t.co/wjBMwCptgq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The incredible @spanna_bates and her family are in all our thoughts today https://t.co/5APgQi882H]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>