<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Use my personal bonus code when you sign up for Carrot https://t.co/yHkjXQGwiA and earn 50% more points on me! graemeb7148]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heck yea- Win a Canon 5D Mark IV from https://t.co/pFoIRwJqzY! https://t.co/tTydfWvHOJ from @LensRentals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Make_It_Right Does this look like it's to code? I'm unsure about the drainage. https://t.co/DvN7l8ZP3F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snowplows don't have a lot to do after this "snowpocalypse". #yvr @globalnews @CBCVancouver https://t.co/fZkrdGMR2J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even better! #hahawithvtsl accidentally finding your way into ballet auditions rather than the chess competition]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#hahawithvtsl accidentally finding your way into orchestra auditions rather than the chess competition]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#hahawithvtsl suggestion: a wedding on surf boards during a tsunami]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First impression pepper? That's new.  @BacheloretteABC #TheBachelorette https://t.co/u0kF7BfD59]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@creativebcs @bcbusiness I did actually! It brought me here. Now to keep exploring.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OpenRoadCA #TagForAJag16 Getting really comfortable with the f-type in preparation for my weekend :) https://t.co/zo5hFTf9CF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VanAutoShow Some really neat cars today at the auto show including an 80's 911. #VanAutoShow16 https://t.co/R8CBrk0c0J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the auto show #AcuraNSXinVan https://t.co/WBVHzg8UDO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vote for me so I can win a trip to England to drive a @Porsche 718 Boxster at @SilverstoneUK   https://t.co/ipPqXmKyjs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It'd be worth @TransLink to do a marketing blitz on how trains aren't garbage cans. This morning: newspapers, nail clippings, coffee cups...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IanCallum @mph51 @JaguarPics Definitely looks like a 550 spider. Short door opening slightly upwards and narrow little windshield.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LandRoverCanada Hibernate? I don't think so. #HIBERNOT https://t.co/iHQXx3KpXY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fayemccreedy yeah we did too! Fell asleep on the couch, then "wha?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hibernate? I don't think so. #hibernot https://t.co/aj00iRBe7B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@phillipsbeer First day of my advent calendar is delicious! Kudos for the Christmas vacation ref. I'm excited for the rest!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OpenRoadCA I almost tried that with mine...until my wife saw where we're heading. When does it open? December?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fayemccreedy @NEWS1130 @deltapolice Yeah, it's about time they even started paying attention to it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TransLink Thanks. I'm guessing Skytrain hasn't talked to the paper people yet as they're still blocking the entrance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TransLink Can you ask 24hrs guy to move from blocking 2 of 4 compass gates at King G stn? East entrnce. Didn't listen to me #obstaclecourse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who needs a 4x4 when you have a @KiaCanada Rio? #hatchbacksruletheworld http://t.co/HXDSlMVvTI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@TransLink Free transit doesn't help when I have a monthly pass.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got to work earlier than usual by driving since @TransLink is down. Does the "free travel" pay for gas and parking? Thanks for the perks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@christyclarkbc "By moving foreign owners out of the market housing prices will drop." That's the whole point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SunChips are the plain flavour sun chips still available anywhere? I haven't seen them in years and still regard them as my favourite chip.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Starbucks There is nothing like a complimentary coffee on a beautiful Whistler morning! Thank you for the reward! http://t.co/h1lVWvtFx3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OpenRoadCA Thanks for the coffee! I hope Cars and Coffee becomes a regular event! http://t.co/ripJPbrO5d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HellyHansen My weekend adventure vehicle complete with Jolly Roger. #TakeFlightFriday http://t.co/WROAUteI5l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaguarCanada Are these going to be at the @VanAutoShow? #pleasesayyes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VanAutoShow Will we be seeing the Ford GT, AMG GT, Mini Superlegarra Vision, Acura NSX, Jaguar Project 7 in Vancouver? All drool worthy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Starbucks I think the barista really liked me! Look at all those hearts! :D http://t.co/zIkRzzTjjI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@replyall you guys should send me your mystery box b/c I'm in Canada and we are behind the times here and can't use http://t.co/AqWNA7kf74]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LUVBBW My wife tried a Fresh Balsam wallflower plugin and all of the oil is in our wood floor now. Any thoughts on how to get it back out?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LandRoverCanada Range Rover Evoque! I have one and love it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TransLink Ok, no need to be sorry. Just curious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TransLink Any idea why there is often a delay in opening the doors at Stadium when going westbound? Sometimes 5 seconds, sometimes 30.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT to enter to win tickets to @BalletBC’s #No29 from @Miss604 http://t.co/moJJ7qSR3O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PorscheVancity well if you're offering...I'll just drop by my parents house, then Whistler, for long way to Kelowna. And pick up groceries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McD_Canada here's my cuppa joe. #mccafeathome http://t.co/erYbonZr08]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AudiCanada aw nuts. I use a wicked jacket. #ConquerTheCity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AudiCanada my @HellyHansen jacket keeps me very warm and dry once I step out into the elements. And an umbrella would solve the hood hair!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AudiCanada I suspect an R8 or an RS5 would help me save time. Until then, speed walking does. #ConquerTheCity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SYSKPodcast @boyfmoz it isn't even available in Canada :(
One day...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AudiCanada One cup of coffee is usually nowhere near enough. One refillable mug is though :) #ConquerTheCity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had a healthy dose of @porsche today with @PorscheVancity at Crescent Beach. Thanks for the ride! http://t.co/4V1YzzYUzW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HTropic_CA ...she like the old stuff without sparkles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HTropic_CA BananaBoat is owned by same company as HTropic, do they use the same formula? My wife really liked the stuff without sparkles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HTropic_CA we tried that one this weekend :) No sparkles all over the boat and gear (yay!), but being thicker it didn't spread as easily...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HTropic_CA #HTSummerBucketList Tubing and wakeboarding at the lake last weekend, nothing better. http://t.co/6l9KuMjPXV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HTropic_CA what's the deal with the glitter in the sunscreen? I have trouble using it and feeling manly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TransLink 9am beer drinking and stashing the can under the seat acceptable these days? I guess it is a warm day... http://t.co/pXJI4RE9No]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PorscheVancity Help me win 3 days with the new @Porsche Targa. Vote for one of my photos every day until April 30: http://t.co/2vMP6Dx4fz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help me win a new camera and 3 days with the new @Porsche Targa. Vote for one of my photos every day until April 30. http://t.co/2vMP6Dx4fz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SYSKPodcast You guys totally got me. Ben is so good on Car Stuff, but then as he brought sysk down...I slowly caught on. Well done. Arghh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thriftycars Thanks for the response and info.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My wife is at Toronto Airport and finding @thriftycars doesn't use winter tires. How ridiculous is that? Telephone agent said they did...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SoftMocShoes Your Guilford store is not the place to be today. Long wait, saw the manager dismiss a customer away, and no gift receipts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PorscheVancity I saw a beautiful early 911 outside your building this morning as I passed on the train. Is that for sale? #oneofmydreamcars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrimetimeEmmys Who is hosting the Creative Arts Emmys? No where can I find the info or find whether its the same host as Primetime show.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shawhelp I skipped to Step 8 and called Shaw. The really long menu system ended up telling me Shaw knows there is a problem in my area.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shawhelp @VicFreelance I'm having issues in Surrey also. Internet and cable have been our for almost an hour.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PorscheVancity If you need an extra driver when you move all your cars to Terminal Ave, I'd be happy to help out :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elonmusk @TeslaMotors Just saw my third Model S around Vancouver, BC. The air is smelling better already!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@diveidc your website isnt working and hasn't been for a while, are you guys still around?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mmscanada I just had an m&m with no chocolate in it! Gasp! It was so unfulfilling. One side of the shell concave against the other side :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Talesofabryce @pre_planner oh I won't. I'll think of some more things to ponder where he'll question my level drug intake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elonmusk  youve bred giant birds and figured out how to mechanize them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elonmusk Do they hinge in the top and middle of the door? Like a gullwing but they fold in half!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CFAinvestored and you completely left out the Tesla Roadster that they've had on the market for a couple years. Otherwise, good article.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CFAinvestored Tsla article is a little off. Comparing the Leaf to the Model S is like a Civic to a Mercedes. And EV1 was unrelated to Volt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If rain were fire instead of water, what do you think umbrellas and coats would be made of? Or would we just evolve? #thoughtprovoking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@virgin953 I vote for not playing snippets of that bad Friday song by Rebecca black any more. I've had it in my head since 7:45!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bchydro Hey, your mobile site doesn't let me get to the full site. There's a button for full site but it refreshes the mobile on iPhone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A good motivating article to do what you need to do instead of sitting back comfortably. http://t.co/VGBo6AaW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enter to win 1 of 2 Canon 60D camera bodies & 1 yr @SmugMug Pro membership. Please RT. Info at: http://bit.ly/hDiOdy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonpegg Want to grab a beer before you leave Vancouver?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@goforjared http://twitpic.com/3zim55 - Its upside down, but says something "cloud services". Pretty cool looking sky writing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@merrelloutside Longest hike? Climbing Whistler mountain. Camped out overnight and peaked the top soon after sunrise. Fantastic!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enter to win a Canon 5D Mk II & a $500 designer photo album from @AlbumEpocaUS & Scott Bourne. Pls RT. Info at: http://bit.ly/hfjpxk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Camera+ 2 is out for iPhone! @taptaptap is giving out custom TSA #GropeFree Edition iPads each day for 12 days to celebrate http://campl.us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enter to win a Letus Hawk Viewfinder from @letusdirect. Please RT. Info at: http://bit.ly/letushawk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enter to win a Nikon D7000 & @PocketWizard BETA Nikon Mini & Flex from Scott Bourne. Pls RT. Info at: http://bit.ly/9zT3Lj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonpegg Count me in! Going boarding or skiing up there? I'll bring the women!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT to enter to win tickets to The Nutcracker @BalletBC2010 from @Miss604 http://ow.ly/3iPxT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[iPhone/iPod Full Size Jukebox Giveaway via @Coleman_Heating RT to enter: http://bit.ly/aUalBk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonpegg Dude! Are you seriously in Canada? It's a big place, where are you? Happen to be in Vancouver? Want to grab a beer?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m attending the @RegencyAuto #RegencyParty w/@Miss604 for a chance to win an iPad http://ow.ly/3f35p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow @wideopencamera to win a @genus_products Shooter Backpack. http://wideopencamera.com/genus-shooter-camera-backpack-deal/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell government representatives we want them to uphold democracy and to be accountable for climate change solutions. http://t.co/OzPulA9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rbostyle Wow I didn't know the new BC Place roof had inflatable cells either. Thanks for sending out the link!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@merrelloutside I'm curious of the differences between hanging vs flat. Why flat?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Facebook is lot up with statuses on how early @Starbucks has Christmas stuff out. They could at least wait until after Remembrance Day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enter to win a Nikon D7000 & @PocketWizard BETA Nikon Mini & Flex from Scott Bourne. Pls RT. Info at: http://bit.ly/9zT3Lj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow @wideopencamera to win a 77mm @lightcraftwork Fader ND filter. http://tinyurl.com/25l4bxe Please RT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow @wideopencamera to win a @jag35 shoulder rig. http://wideopencamera.com/contests/tweet-to-win-a-jag35-hand-held-rig/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT to enter to win a Coleman BBQ from @coleman_heating! http://colemanheating.ca/contest/bbq-giveaway/2010/08/27/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow @teradek via @goforjared to win a Cube HD wireless video transmitter. http://www.cinema5d.com/news/?p=4576. Please RT]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>