<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Take customer feedback seriously - the good and the bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Customer opinions of your business are what keep them coming back for more or urge them to run for the hills.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When planning social media for your business you have to ensure your interactions will be accepted positively.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tools Online Business Owners Can NOT Live Without https://t.co/42x1kOV2Rw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Create Social Media Marketing Videos Without Appearing On Camera https://t.co/sps1JOqp5Z via @smexaminer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Virtual Assistant Business is the perfect career for any military spouse. https://t.co/NNjiKzHmgg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snow Storm = Happy Dog https://t.co/uOoo9nYluL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't Be Afraid of Facebook Advertising. If you have a strong funnel and you know your market, it can be a good way to grow your business.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Find the Perfect Virtual Assistant https://t.co/gmRNURynjl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Answer comments. If your readers have a question or leave you a nice compliment, write back in the comments area.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing your business is easier than ever now-a-days with sites like Facebook, LinkedIn, etc. So what are you waiting for?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consider sending out surveys to ask customers what they think about aspects of your business and focus on these answers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ten Reasons Why You Need a Virtual Assistant https://t.co/U8VZCTmIwo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Use hashtags so that new people who are your market can find you and connect with your posts. #SocialMedia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five Reasons Why You Need to Be Using Lead Magnets https://t.co/fULvOmf2Zp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When we sell online, we aren't always there to help overcome our potential customer's objections so put together a FAQ.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By having personal interaction with those who frequent your social media platforms you are creating an online presence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top Three Social Media Sites for Small Business Owners https://t.co/4iXHIjVBuY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Treat customers as more than a purchase! Follow up with them &amp; make sure everything is okay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good opportunities don't come to those who sit around and wait for them. You have to go out and create them. https://t.co/S5wYrk0jDM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are able to work from anywhere which makes a Virtual Assistant career ideal for military spouses https://t.co/NNjiKzHmgg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How BackBlaze Saved My Business on More than One Occasion https://t.co/8zDXN2Dk1r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Optimize your blog post titles so when people tweet them, they're catchy enough for people to click on the links.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outsource What You Hate: If you loathe doing something like social media, give it someone else to do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social media can bring marketing success to your business in many ways but know your goals before you start.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make it clear to your buyers that you are a business who is very interested in providing for their needs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Ways You Can Integrate Your Email Marketing with Social Media https://t.co/WmHYYefOW8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manage your Time on social media. Be sure to get the things done that pay the bills before logging in, and set a timer if you need to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hire a ghostwriter to help you generate more content for your audience.  #BusinessTip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join social networking sites that specialize in connecting people &amp; begin building a network of 'friends'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep connections with your clients through newsletters or company updates.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top Tips for an Effective Social Media Campaign https://t.co/LINERqjeVM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Add Facebook Commenting to your Blog so when people comment, they have the option of posting their comment on their Facebook profile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Limit the distractions on your website by limiting advertising banners on the page.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Breathe New Life into Your Website for the New Year https://t.co/D5bDGi3Qbs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's your social media goal? If you don't know where you want to go, it's pretty hard to get there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smiles &amp; general pleasantry keep your customers on your side &amp; don't give them a reason to do business elsewhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Virtual Assistant Business is the perfect fit for a military spouse. https://t.co/NNjiKzHmgg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Grow Your Business with Webinars https://t.co/ZtdJf0ZH3n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be Visible Daily. Try to post daily, even if it's just a question to engage your audience. Being consistent is important on Social Media.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Write about an issue that is important to your business, and share what you're doing to help the cause.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8 Ways a Social Media Virtual Assistant Can Help Your Business https://t.co/iU0k4BKw3k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you make a connection on LinkedIn, make it personal. Talk about them - not you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Provide customers with case studies &amp; other useful information that will encourage them to sign up for your service.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 Simple Ways to Find Topic Ideas for Blog Posts https://t.co/aCRrYg8pWI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't follow more than a couple hundred people per day. Twitter might mistake you for a spammer and suspend your account. #SocialMedia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sponsor a local sports team. Your business name be on the uniforms &amp; provide an opportunity to garner media attention.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have an open house or customer appreication day. #BusinessTip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best way to market your business on Facebook is through a Facebook Page dedicated to that business.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're feeling burned out, overwhelmed, etc DON'T show this side of yourself to your clients/customers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top Three Social Media Sites for Small Business Owners https://t.co/bBwpQeLdXy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Use lots of pictures in your Facebook posts. Pictures draw the eye and increase engagement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Offer gift certificates for your products or services. #BusinessTip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top 8 Effective Email Marketing Strategies https://t.co/AbvinV2HkT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make sure your tweets provide value to your audience or there is no point in tweeting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember - bad news travels faster than good news! Keep your customers satisfied and happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Virtual Assistance is the perfect career for any military spouse https://t.co/NNjiKzHmgg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Danielle Beauchemin is NOT Naked and Afraid! https://t.co/qGXuRK87Qq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't Ever Complain about your Customers or Clients. This never looks good. Ever. Bad idea. Just don't. #SocialMedia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How BackBlaze Saved My Business on More than One Occasion https://t.co/8zDXN2Dk1r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donate a certain percentage of your sales for a given time period to charity. #BusinessTip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Images receive far more interest and generate higher response rates than text-only Facebook Ads.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any professional certification or award is a subject of personal pride, but don't overlook it as an opportunity to promote your business.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow 20 people with similar interests per day. That's not overwhelming, and reciprocal followers will add up quickly. #SocialMedia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DeeBlaregold Thank you for sharing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Ways You Can Integrate Your Email Marketing with Social Media https://t.co/WmHYYdYdxy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you've won an award, send out a press release about it. #Marketing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make sure you care about your customers or they won't care about you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[113 Content Types To Organize With Your Marketing Calendar https://t.co/2Oe2p3v7lD via @CoSchedule]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 Ways to Build Your Email Lists https://t.co/kL9XE4lmDI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Easy Dinners for Busy Entrepreneurs with @HelloFresh https://t.co/uiZdpMD9Az]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media is not Just Fun and Games. There are many brands that have taken the exposure to the bank.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five Reasons Why You Need to Be Using Lead Magnets https://t.co/fULvOmf2Zp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has someone used your service in an unusual way? Include testimonials or studies to back up your claims.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Charge What You're Worth https://t.co/68tHZPJqbl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your business will prosper when you take time to network with people both online and off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Build an All-Star Social Media Team in 5 Steps https://t.co/f10Gdf34kc via @buffer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Track which Tweets get more replies, retweets, favourites and clicks. Use this data to influence future tweets. #TwitterTip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Content Creation Tips for Social Media https://t.co/MI7fpkvITW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Use social media to make friends and build relationships.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Military Spouses: Now you can have a successful career that you can take anywhere with you. https://t.co/NNjiKzHmgg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today, for every tweet with #BellLetsTalk, Bell donates 5¢ to #MentalHealth initiatives! Help spread the word! Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tag only when it is mutually beneficial to both people. Don't use tagging to spam other people or to get their attention repeatedly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 More Ways to Build Your Email Lists https://t.co/O6DZ0jCprg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make sure you set up a signature that goes out on all your emails with a link to your website.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Personalize your website's navigation with distinct, relevant categories and a 'start here' page]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Optimize Your Images https://t.co/dB8pZ28AAt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Use images as visuals on social media whenever possible. #SocialMedia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Measure your Twitter success not by your number of followers, but by the quality and level of engagement. #SocialMedia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't Mass Post in Facebook Groups. #SocialMedia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top Tips for an Effective Social Media Campaign https://t.co/LINERqjeVM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be yourself, not just a representative of your brand or product.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To make your content stand apart from the crowd it needs to be personalized for your readers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Breathe New Life into Your Website for the New Year https://t.co/D5bDGi3Qbs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schedule your social media posts for when your audience is online.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Respond to unhappy customers on social media. If a customer has a legitimate complaint, handle it publicly with grace and style.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ten Reasons Why You Need a Virtual Assistant https://t.co/U8VZCTmIwo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Include a photo of yourself on your website. People like being able to put a face with your name.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to get traffic to your blog? Use a keyword phrase for every post and image]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9 Tips for Keeping Your Subscribers Happy https://t.co/Ry6Eh2AJkx]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>