<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@MindaugasLT @spin1038 "Sunny spells and scattered showers" are coming from March on, hang tight Mindaugas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oisin @colmisainmdom @WhoIsMyTD I'm doing my bit, I also signed up today to the register]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a first real act after getting my citizenship, I wrote to my local TD - thanks @colmisainmdom for @WhoIsMyTD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our own @JamesDesByrne shares his thoughts and experiences with #payments integrations at @ThePaymentWorks #fintech https://t.co/xuo3TnULrj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shout out to all the drivers who use fog lights in clear weather, and *no lights* in thick fog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colmisainmdom @EndaKennyTD I think he shouldn't go at all, but I'm afraid he doesn't have the courage for such a move.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@functionalKats @BearMarketCo did a Dogpatch event recently, might worth a shout?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gavinjoyce @brianw good auld rm -rf, solves all the problems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry, I don't speak chatbot https://t.co/OOmoLkd4Nx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oisin classy af]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can Enda present the bowl of shamrocks, and tell him it's a side salad? https://t.co/glWx6VVrLJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brandalisms I've been thinking about this all last year. Men fucked up so many times at leading things, count me in as a follower ✌️]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's time to read this again. https://t.co/RUi8q5RJ3b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gavinsblog very soon I'd say, it happened in days in HU after the election.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@martinmcwhorter @piersmorgan clear example of how to spot a manchild with confidence issues]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gavinsblog 'peace through strength' chilling 1984 rhetoric]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm convinced that most startup bios are randomly generated text:

"a single platform that connects you to your unique everything money."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The brightest button of them all #webdev https://t.co/T5kEZFjWvP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@martinmcwhorter why am I not surprised?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LEGO_Group no worries, I'll take a look at that form]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First time I've encountered a faulty @LEGO_Group product / package. https://t.co/7JG2nnmdO2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bilgehoor ok, but they sing republican songs, not to mention the flock of exchange students]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bilgehoor u sure about that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MajorThrill we have a German shepherd, and he's super gentle with kids (when he's not knocking them over by accident)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colmisainmdom my eldest just started signing 'Last Christmas' on his own yesterday...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2017 took the wrong turn after 2016 https://t.co/2k2DRgusaG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just got Christened again. Close contestant to 'Mt' by @WebSummit https://t.co/G2XS8QSS3a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Btw this is great for #elixirlang users too, if you don't like the smooth syntax of #erlang #myelixirstatus https://t.co/8CKKEeEBhM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Clearpreso maybe they should. #LEOxit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Clearpreso 31? I wonder which county got left out...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She was showing off his business card as evidence that it happened. It was buried in tabloids, article in Hungarian https://t.co/OAOXmfvET2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[entrant from Hungary, who said Trump grabbed her, and invited her to his room while in Moscow in 2013.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gavinsblog you might like this, there *might* be evidence after all to that Moscow hotel claim. Last year there was a former Miss Universe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patphelan @illannpower is this some band or product? I'm intrigued.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MajorThrill pretty much yeah, you can even substitute dicks with cats, same result]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll attempt to showcase fundamental Erlang stuff, like behaviours, async message passing and get processes communicating with each other]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be doing an Erlang workshop about airplanes and processes on @functionalKats Kats Conf 2 - https://t.co/A7QMh6pg9m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MajorThrill I watched his documentary about the internet, waiting for a similar monologue to happen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@martinmcwhorter it depicts politicians accurately though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sciritai I feel ya, it's alarming. Same as the tw*tweasel NF from the UK...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harris is just a commentator on current affairs, not a minister who could do...

Oh wait! https://t.co/jbsoHEFmPz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MajorThrill Jesus... I moved here to avoid that sort of crap. Well, time to look into Irish civil movements against these...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cloudsteph I've been using ddg for 5 years, never gone back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cloudsteph what's Brave like?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@orrc Madrid is a shopping mall disguised as a terminal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brandalisms more kindness and patience. (Also get healed from this flu).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oerhill you're welcome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bilgehoor that's my reward for taking care of 3 sick people in the house for the second day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bought this, now the fecking tune is stuck in my head https://t.co/kNC5IhrPSO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is already a good day - installed a printer driver on Ubuntu and managed to print a page within 10 mins #winning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulmwatson which you can leverage much better. Also learn better, from your peers, vs from a lecturer in a room..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulmwatson you do them alone, all the time, no help. Then you get out to the working life, and there you have 'group knowledge'...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulmwatson I always felt exams are a shit way to measure progress and acquired knowledge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bilgehoor them priorities, though #YOLO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wycats they gonna grow and develop in their own pace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wycats prepare lots of food for yourselves beforehand, and have them packed in servings. And don't compare their development to their peers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll spend Christmas hiding around the house #WheresMáté https://t.co/CD8BvWvgS5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Clearpreso I'm trying to sing Frankie Synnottra's "New-Ry, New-Ryyyy" now in my head. It doesn't work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@supergingerdave ah here, can't beat the Revenue sending it on snail mail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every 'if' statement you can think of, deserves its own NPM package #webdev #wtf https://t.co/BTQDIHYXl1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@martinmcwhorter @patphelan this is just a 'simple scam', right? It wasn't data or access they were after.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016, tech meetup, still can't handle simple UTF-8 characters. I think we're far away from skynet stuff. https://t.co/BIXaaAwmos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's still some work to be done there, lads #growthhacking https://t.co/lqpjRp0gjK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see the *fire* emoji is the new *rocket* emoji #progress #bliss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@meetup_support sure thing, I did submit a screenshot over the payment/billing FAQ form earlier.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Meetup tagging @meetup_support as well...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Meetup and TBH the FAQ section is not very reassuring... "If that doesn't work, submit a payment using the browser on a mobile device:"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @Meetup I tried to add my CC details for a subscription. Page said declined, yet my card was charged... Could you advise what to do now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sciritai @davemcginn_ie to the sheds, 'work party' with the saws and tools]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rbanffy but I mostly worked on CPU and memory heavy apps. And saw IO heavy ones suffer under compiled languages. I'm totally prejudiced :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rbanffy yes, I understand and appreciate that. That article dismisses a lot of the web though. Maybe my experiences are different ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rbanffy I was hoping the answer would be 'never']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Choosing Ember over React in 2016” by @jessepollak https://t.co/ymmih0bwmI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dart delays "due to swans on the line". The leaves on track hatched, it seems.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know when an API is written in Java:

* Documentation is 100+ pages
* Often cites ISO standards
* Claims to do proper REST (not really)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["hyper growth" https://t.co/pWDp3iyjcz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["... if you're interested in working for a pre-IP, Unicorn company that continues to go through hyper-growth"
nope, nope aaaand nope.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go home December, you're drunk https://t.co/Nl7FNkEl9D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leveled up with 'We wish you a dairy Christmas' just now #parenting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oisin Rage Driven Development is my favourite method lately]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also the same son '... So be good for goodness ACHE!']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Son's super power: Singing 'Jingle Bells' to _any_ tune he hears #parenting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulmwatson they can work now alright, it's just frowned upon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shane_Byrne3 there were zebras and giraffes as well. In a jungle book play, so https://t.co/4myenHSkTC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Our regular meetings are infrequent"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Clearpreso is that a tweet storm toy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oisin @theproductworks we do that service for some time now, happy to get references and all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oisin hi there. Talk to us @theproductworks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why yes, if I search for 'Keyboard' I'd like to see results full of iphones and laptops.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oisin I second that. My lovely wife even made brioche with mulled wine ✌]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You need a responsive site they said. It'll be grand they said. https://t.co/vcq9baSpQR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Clearpreso "Look, look! It's a snowman!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulmwatson the aliens took over the account]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is getting ridiculous now folks https://t.co/hgRaFiI5LK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorwogan fecking smiley gobshites]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Clearpreso 
✔ Hoodie
✔ Glasses
✔ Computer

What else would you need for hacking?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ideasasylum it's already started here in the EU, Hungary, Poland, UK, etc. We're heading back to nationalist quarrels between countries :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jaimebuelta :( what's your next step?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MindaugasLT did he do it 
*Takes off sunglasses*
In the name of love?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MindaugasLT he still haven't found the design job he's looking for]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>