<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@AgnesCPoirier We can but hope....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kartik__Raj You're welcome, my friend! At times, you gotta laugh... @donaeldunready]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you haven't already discovered @donaeldunready... Tweets as if #DonaldTrump was a deranged medieval king. Great… https://t.co/qn6Ef5cdwW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RossKeane Hello Ross, could you follow me for a DM, please? thanks, Alison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Puritans? Islamic fundamentalism? Religious right? Trump's America? Whatever inspiration, a new film of… https://t.co/VWspA2B1MZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@James16Matthews And "Oceania is our friend.....", etc #Orwell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thecupcakebloke Seriously? I could have done without that! @todayfm @ghook]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not to mention low opinion poll ratings; but they're all #fakenews, of course!
#Trump #PresidentTrump #Trumpocracy https://t.co/SrHndj0an4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#PresidentTrump doesn't trust polls or intelligence agencies, so what's the data source? And DON't get me started o… https://t.co/S2P5Q4VA9i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ianandbeverly I'm loving the concept of an indoors hammock!! #books]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Dutch ancestors are laughing! The #Netherlands welcomes #Trump in his own words https://t.co/x6RrEuqo9R via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FansOfCasey I watched it 3 times in 10 days. An outstanding film indeed. #ManchesterByTheSea @MBTSMovie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spring sunshine, @stpatrickscath park. At times, #DublinCanBeHeaven. #loveDublin #Dublin @libertiesdublin https://t.co/JAPv1kFJCn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Donal_OKeeffe Or casting the runes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'd almost think they found the idea of women enjoying sex on their own terms frightening... #CitizensAssembly https://t.co/2CQimwWHCC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LorraineLollie @MBTSMovie The moment where they embraced in the church, with few words, practically undid me. #ManchesterByTheSea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is magic. You're welcome. #Dogs https://t.co/RL55KbI6dr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Each morning now, I approach Twitter with trepidation to see what he's said / done... https://t.co/D9Osd82EPl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't tempt me. Just don't. *Head spins with the range of possible replies* https://t.co/3vy57Om67S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TheHandmaidsTale? It gets closer by the day. Why not #trustwomen instead? https://t.co/6zbqJulLQo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jk_rowling @JamesMelville And losing hurts, there's no denying.But we couldn't have lost to a nicer bunch of people than the Scots #SCOvIRE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 'so-called' judge was appointed by President George H. W. Bush, and received unanimous confirmation. I'm willin… https://t.co/T9eajBYbeu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#DressLikeAWoman: What will Trump's White House lady dress code entail? https://t.co/KTHLoCePVu via @IrishTimesCultr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter, have I told you lately what a magnificent film #ManchesterByTheSea is? A film for the ages, intelligent, authentic, moving.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katiedawson23 Stunning, as ever, and so moving. Thanks for posting that! #Casablanca #LaMarseillaise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things that are NOT #AlternativeFacts: Scotland 27, Ireland 22. 
Not good, not good at all. #ScotlandvIreland #Rugby6Nations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very expressive interview with #JosephOConnor on #Marian now,  speaking movingly about his book #StarOfTheSea and #TheFamine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First on the White House agenda – the collapse of the global order. Next, war? | Jonathan Freedland https://t.co/jAVCQ4i6dK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@officialNWHP @SheroesHistory And they're showing how to #DressLikeAWoman too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laudemhirjan Would ask Lee's permission to do things, signalling to me how much he loved Lee and needed him to step in and be his father.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laudemhirjan He was terrific, a mix of stroppy, horny, and self-absorbed, and so vulnerable at the same time. I loved the way he 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laudemhirjan the dialogue, and find it more moving. So much said without words, but what masterfully written words! 2/2 #ManchesterByTheSea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laudemhirjan I'd really appreciate it - I've seen the film 3 times in 2 weeks, each time I notice more in the performances, hear more 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brianmlucey @psneeze Or as I think of it, Dictator-chic.....? (Seem to remember Gaddaffi's place looked rather similarly gilded).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laudemhirjan Agreed, it is a stunningly well written film. How does one get one's hands on the script (if you don't mind my asking)?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@foliosociety I have an old Penguin edition, but the @foliosociety's one would be a real treat! #JamesJoyce #Ulysses @UlyssesLives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ManchesterByTheSea: A film for the ages, beautifully crafted depiction of grief, unforgettable performances by… https://t.co/QdcDGHtZXl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#DressLikeAWoman: Women respond online to  Trump’s comments https://t.co/ALwjrfeXDk via @IrishTimesWorld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['It will be called Americanism': the US writers who imagined a fascist future https://t.co/G2yDtLnp04]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Colmogorman Absolutely agree, it's an appalling image to use.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On higher matters than Trump, I'm lusting after @foliosociety's new edition of #Ulysses 
#JamesJoyce @UlyssesLives… https://t.co/YSVAmEVpNG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Noel Whelan: Theresa May  cares little about Ireland’s Brexit worries https://t.co/YwrZv431Gp via @IrishTimesOpEd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I keep thinking of #TheHandmaidsTale by @MargaretAtwood. We're nearly there. #Resist https://t.co/wnfNJ55d3A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fdelond Ever read #TheHandmaidsTale by @MargaretAtwood? We're nearly there. @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#DressLikeAWoman? Only another stick with which to - metaphorically - beat the President. Thank God for Twitter.… https://t.co/xBhODEyMeg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Shooting incident at Louvre in Paris https://t.co/nj4u1o49eo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ultimate in #AlternativeFacts? Kellyanne Conway blames refugees for 'Bowling Green massacre' that never happened https://t.co/0DrhFIsfLx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lindagash @Colmogorman I'd suggest that - not for the first time - the President is mis-using a word. A Beach-head is a defensive line.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apropos of that @RoguePOTUSStaff tweet...
#DonaldTrump https://t.co/3gnVywDW63]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rodwmacleod Couldn't agree more; #LaLaLand was hugely overrated, whereas #ManchesterByTheSea is an unforgettable masterpiece.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bravo, @SenJohnMcCain. Sad state of affairs that you needed to to.  
#JohnMcCain @Donal_OKeeffe https://t.co/Jhj7pxKEgo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An appalling comment; MPs are not 'enemies of democracy' for voting against Farage's wishes. And saying this, given… https://t.co/Q94LwzLzax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump signing executive orders has become a glorious meme https://t.co/EDzz7r1pYf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just found - and followed - @RoguePOTUSStaff; it makes for sobering reading, #WhiteHouse staff apparently tweeting their frustration.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pity #Cameron failed... 
@BBCNewsnight #Newsnight #PaulDacre #DailyMail https://t.co/KQ7oYuCzDM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KYNelly02 Easily one of the best films of the last 5 years. Moving, subtle, nuanced, a masterpiece. #ManchesterByTheSea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonaldClarke63 @KermodeMovie As long as I draw breath, I'll fail to understand how that moment didn't derail his campaign.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonmayo Just not Will Bailey. Anyone but Bailey. #TheWestWing @KermodeMovie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mehdirhasan Maybe he'll have them fight to the death, #HungerGames fashion, until only one remains... #realitypresidency]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm still thinking about it. Deeply moving, superbly acted; #ManchesterByTheSea IS a masterpiece. #CaseyAffleck say… https://t.co/Iw77TBv7Db]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kartik__Raj Without a shadow of doubt......!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kartik__Raj The horror, the horror.....!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some things should be un-invented. #PeakHipster https://t.co/eQX6PCNmpw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuliaHB1 And hasn't she welcomed the likes of #Mugabe in the past?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@twisteddoodles Or #Godfather ? I'm just waiting for the dead fishes to start getting delivered. #Trumpland #Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheTsel Denzel beats Gosling , hands down, but #CaseyAffleck  is unsurpassed in #ManchesterByTheSea. Finest screen performance in years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Firing the Acting AG because her legal expertise fails to back up your bully-boy tactics? I'm scared. #SallyYates https://t.co/gawcmmRu4P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And NOT going to fire senior Justice Department officials who refuse to implement his #MuslimBan and say it's unenf… https://t.co/dWGCZtu0fS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a sobering reminder. #NeverForget #Holocaust https://t.co/7bIXwtubIx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or water, perhaps....? #SteveBannon #TheWizardOfOz https://t.co/aJw4NburxP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahclazarus @PartAnnMarie Or throwing water on him...? #TheWizardOfOz #ImMelting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maureen Dowd: Who knew it would get so weird so quickly? https://t.co/laPcbq0vy0 via @IrishTimesWorld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The defence of fascist functionaries down through the decades....? #justfollowingorders #MusimBan @fdelond https://t.co/Nxbgx5Qr2O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sobering read, from @EliotACohen: "This is one of those clarifying moments in American history." https://t.co/ZlhAPqEeNR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aoifemrtn I'm crying reading that - so happy for you, Ax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@curtainqueen He is, by his own words, "a germaphobe", after all.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hatmangooner I've seen #ManchesterByTheSea 3 times; the silent embrace in church between Affleck + Williams nearly undid me. Masterpiece]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I heard it too - didn't like it at all. We're heading into #George Orwell territory as far as language is concerned. https://t.co/sgPpRjDKpk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Subtle,  nuanced. Not https://t.co/pbtynHmPwF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Reinstates Ducking Stool https://t.co/lUxoKIealr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesMelville He is a magnificent sportsman and champion. No question. #RogerFederer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could an Irish referendum delay or even derail  Brexit? https://t.co/dryNU7TVVK via @IrishTimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OTD 1533 #HenryVIII + #AnneBoleyn marry in secret. A thousand days to the downfall of history's most fascinating wo… https://t.co/ebzEkG9FVw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A television pioneer, and one I remember fondly. RIP #MaryTylerMoore. #MTM https://t.co/hUqnuFv9Tl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please, not those trousers again. ANYTHING but those trousers. @PressSec @EndaKennyTD #StPatricksDay #shamrockery… https://t.co/v4rpCiitey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still thinking about #ManchesterByTheSea, an object lesson in how you make a masterpiece with no special effects, just fine actors + script.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahhark2 Couldn't agree more - LaLa Land one of the most overrated films I've seen, #ManchesterByTheSea is a masterpiece. @MBTSMovie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bel_penny Couldn't agree with you more - I saw it twice last week. A masterpiece, deeply moving, brittle humour, subtle, powerful acting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kathy Sheridan on the power of marching against the US's evolving horror show: https://t.co/XniCdV2lMa via @IrishTimesOpEd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales of #GeorgeOrwell's 1984 surge after Kellyanne Conway's #AlternativeFacts: https://t.co/XUMCNSmG4L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@faintlyfalling Donald Trump has been known to do it also (as did the late Liam Lawlor TD). Enough said.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could the Academy save time and just give the #BestActor Oscar to #CaseyAffleck for #ManchesterByTheSea? #OscarNoms… https://t.co/To1dFGqXS0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simon_schama As long as they have enough sense to give Best Actor Oscar to #CaseyAffleck for #ManchesterByTheSea.....!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@francismaloney5 You'd have to wonder what the wonderful #AAGill would have made of Kelly Anne Conway.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Independent It's a bit late now, isn't it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelenORahilly It's like the Ministry of Truth in #GeorgeOrwell's 1984, isn't it? #MiniTrue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could someone more clever please enlighten me - what the hell are #AlternativeFacts? We're into #GeorgeOrwell territory here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamiraAhmedUK Can't speak for #Jackie (seeing it on Friday) but #ManchesterByTheSea is the best film I've seen in years. @DonaldClarke63]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StudiocanalUK Done! Best wishes, Alison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonaldClarke63 @GreenClouds4 You too, my friend.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>