<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[For an overview of #pollutingPruitt's ties with polluters and his awful resume, check out Bill Moyers' new video: https://t.co/AA8iKEQ063]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JerryMoran or 213 KS lives saved annually by smog standards #pollutingPruitt has attacked. https://t.co/bjI09TkGVn
https://t.co/wr3mWQkIPq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JerryMoran it's not about politics, but abt 160 KANSAN lives saved annually by mercury and toxics standards #pollutingPruitt has attacked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @EPWDems for standing against the efforts to push #pollutingPruitt's nomination without straight answers. https://t.co/B6GyLUAYdh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sen. @jiminhofe suggests Dems submitted too many questions for #PollutingPruitt. Well, he has a lot to answer for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the lives saved annually by state with just one of many enviro protections #pollutingPruitt has attacked: https://t.co/wr3mWQkIPq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @SenJeffMerkley for setting the record straight on #pollutingPruitt https://t.co/s5dC9vyVdS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#PollutingPruitt has not provided substantive answers to critical questions. Reasonable to demand them before any v… https://t.co/MMMeur91ej]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @SenSanders for demanding answers and action from #PollutingPruitt! https://t.co/m2hp5JkLTo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zachflanders @SenPatRoberts Sorry, meant did you try calling both DC and the district office - DC voicemails more likely to fill up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zachflanders @SenPatRoberts did you try calling in-state?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't let up! Call their in-state offices--not just DC! https://t.co/AKIiO8dQNQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good news! VA announces their largest solar farm. Days after NYC approved  largest offshore wind farm in U.S. https://t.co/uS356V9KK2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump and Bannon back Trump's decision to give power to Bannon https://t.co/d4OMWa4NLD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICYMI during #NoBanNoWall protests: Trump has elevated Bannon above actual experts on Nat'l Security Council. https://t.co/A12q0PsuSM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. That's a real all-lives-matter kind of thing to say. https://t.co/0we0hlxLo7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leaving the capitol, chants of "see you next week." Maybe don't plan on driving in downtown DC on weekends for a while. #NoBanNoWall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The view down Penn Ave marching from the White House to the capitol. Crowd stretched most of the way. #NoBanNoWall https://t.co/3SypeJ1sr0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today at The White House: protesting Trump's assault on core American principles. #NoBanNoWall #NoHateNoFear https://t.co/Ci6vXrPiAt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Head of Trump's EPA transition wants to abolish the whole agency.  We have an idea of what that world could be like. https://t.co/Mhpz5hcL2j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good thoughts ahead of the wknd, after 1 wk of Trump: activists need to take care of themselves. H/T @EliseHiggins  https://t.co/VdhhgJqJLH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. solar power generation is creating more jobs than oil, gas and coal. Combined. https://t.co/uHoYZPt6Sf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More detail - Trump's EPA transition head discussing how to abolish EPA completely. https://t.co/5FWFZjyzwD https://t.co/MQeEVasxoB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Head of Trump's EPA transition team says slashing workforce in half would be a "good start."   https://t.co/kMpD6BkYmG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["These are direct strikes, Mr. President, at our environment and health." From @Laurie_David of Inconvenient Truth: https://t.co/EoxSYdmHEr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AaronCouch while incepting a third of the American public?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's entire voter fraud conspiracy theory is based on a golfer's anecdote. Also, he got the anecdote wrong. https://t.co/KChC9gmZaE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here are the many barriers to Trump's effort to revive the Keystone XL pipeline, courtesy of @anthonyrswift:  https://t.co/Y2efUUrM3k #NOKXL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The view from the South Lawn of the @WhiteHouse is even better. @greenpeaceusa #ResistTrump https://t.co/ng01KJ8kUt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Resist action from @greenpeaceusa - here's the rooftop view from @NRDC https://t.co/IjAU5xNxEt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If the website goes dark, years of work we have done on on climate change will disappear." #ActOnClimate 

https://t.co/Bo7yqqHFgC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ALERT: @POTUS @realDonaldTrump to Environmental Protection Agency - stop talking about the most critical environmen… https://t.co/1bemVWDPPO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for RT's! To clarify: @PressSec called it "day 2." Count as you like, but welcome to the next 4 yrs of resis… https://t.co/ClxzZ1MwFV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Following in the footsteps of @BadlandsNPS, @GoldenGateNPS goes tweeting facts while also being part of federal gov… https://t.co/docvxnNhUz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disappointing. Tillerson epitomizes the polluted past of energy. @elonmusk, you're supposed to represent a cleaner… https://t.co/Zkd5n4CVvl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good to see this much fight in people 4 days in. Stay on your toes! #pollutingPruitt #cabinetofpolluters #NoDAPL #NoKXL #ActOnClimate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NoDAPL #NoKXL protest at the White House reacting to new exec orders: "we are not going away! Welcome to your four… https://t.co/5hUc5B8rF7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More than 870,000 messages were delivered at today's @EPWDems hearing to reject #pollutingPruitt. Get this fox away from our hen house.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting the answers #PollutingPruitt couldn't or wouldn't provide. @JWalkeNRDC testifying before @EPWDems here: https://t.co/c7MbUsNefT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost @petulad one intention may be to highlight that men can/should be feminist allies, but most of these quotes don't get there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They did edit the headline, but just delete the tweet too. Also, delete the article and write about the women. This… https://t.co/A5N3zOn5oz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right now, the Foreign Relations Committee is deciding whether to hand the State Dept over to recent CEO of Exxon-M… https://t.co/FinJA7VVza]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perhaps they're calling back to "a more civilized age."  @AaronCouch #TheLastJedi #EpisodeVIII https://t.co/ncvax8OsIW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["He doesn’t just represent a different view... he is opposed to the mission of the agency itself."  #pollutingPruitt https://t.co/Qb3pSXk1zx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which makes sense, unless he was to rally a congressional effort against DOMA, which proved unnecessary what with t… https://t.co/FUACu9pjmA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you Stephen Colbert for rocking our bandana! @NRDC #WomensMarch https://t.co/ZlKgWoeKpm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll say it again - the rally today was on Independence Ave, which was packed beyond capacity and isn't even in the… https://t.co/NzXtrThyT1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kansasalps @aaanastasia it will be hard to crop a photo to avoid signs about his ineptitude or corruption.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This isn't actually the turnout. Because the stage and most of the crowd is on Independence Ave... to the right of… https://t.co/bJgc74gzGr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bloomingdale detachment 1 heading to the rally point! #womensmarchonwashington https://t.co/kkueersK5T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump just signed the order to nominate #PollutingPruitt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If anyone was confused, downtown Kansas City is NOT the National Mall, and #Trump did not draw this crowd.… https://t.co/MuC3c2HxII]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huh. How 'bout that. @TheDarkNolan https://t.co/Rzj3F9sdpI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also this: 

"/our-government/executive-branch" could not be found."

https://t.co/RMveCfp6TH https://t.co/cMWYTupV8g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're ready, and we're watching. Join us:  https://t.co/3ukhaYJ9g6 #TrumpWatch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To the organizers, the activists, and the vast majority of Americans that oppose Trump's platform: 

We're all still here. Shields up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Pres-Elect Trump won’t protect and defend clean air, water and our future - we the people will.… https://t.co/fiS0Cjxchd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting how 3 Doors Down is known for a hit about a crazy person believing he's a superman/demanding your affection #TrumpInauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The clean air protections #Pruitt's fighting save 45,000 lives nationally each year.

https://t.co/bjI09TkGVn… https://t.co/jyO85LB5IF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC announces support for #PollutingPruitt, who is actively assaulting @EPA protections that save 1,293 lives *annually* in SC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His attacks on mercury and air toxics standards are just one part of a pattern, @RheaSuh explains. https://t.co/BS4296RQQG #pollutingPruitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no difference in the end result whether your leaders call climate change a hoax or just refuse to do anythi… https://t.co/QzbxB5dNEV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some complaints #PollutingPruitt is getting more questions than @GinaEPA did. Maybe because she had yrs of experience w/ enviro protection.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#PollutingPruitt says he tries to stay in his lane as AG of OK and not meddle elsewhere. He has sued against protections for Chesapeake Bay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to @SenBobCasey for a commitment to vote no on #PollutingPruitt! https://t.co/ELvszNA8yr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenCarper: all 17 counties in OK got F grades for clean air. What have you done about it? #PollutingPruitt's answer basically, not my job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When you say review, I hear undo the rights of the states." -@SenMarkey on state clean car standards. #pollutingpruitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JimInhofe musing at length on not-really-dark money and a fake scandal debunked by numerous investigations. #PollutingPruitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4) whether he'd recuse himself from anti-EPA lawsuits where he could be "plaintiff, defendant, judge and jury" in @SenMarkey's words.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3) which big polluters he's taken contributions from]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2) whether or not he'd support states' rights to standards for #cleanercars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We've learned a lot so far about what #PollutingPruitt doesn't know: 1) Whether climate change deserves action]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They're back, with @SenatorCarper's questions on the very real economic benefits of pollution reductions.  #PollutingPruitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patricey thanks Patrice!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good time to take a deep breath, drink some clean water, and tell your senator to reject #PollutingPruitt.… https://t.co/9azR40fcLg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenSanders response? If you refuse to acknowledge the science, you don't get my vote. https://t.co/M5l3sHS9iP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pruitt kept trying to tell @SenSanders human activity factors into climate change, refused to acknowledge serious impacts. #PollutingPruitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The vast majority of scientists are telling us we have to act boldly" and you're saying let's debate it, says @SenSanders #PollutingPruitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenSanders shows up to #Pruitt hearing suggesting majority perhaps shouldn't be double-booking critically important nomination hearings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pruitt refused to give a straight answer. "I would review that... one would not want to presume the outcome."  #PollutingPruitt #CleanerCars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris turned #Pruitt's arguments for state authority around to ask if he'll uphold CA's authority to create #cleanercars standards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Letter #Pruitt sent almost verbatim for oil companies keeps coming up. @nytimes has the exchange: https://t.co/XdwGRW0jl0 #PollutingPruitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Pruitt taking issue w/ the idea he acts on behalf of "just one" oil company. We get it that he's allied w/ many polluters. #PollutingPruitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JerryMoran complains EPA shouldn't tell a town to deal with H2O pollution instead of handing out bottled water... #Pruitt does not disagree]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Pruitt: I did not send a letter on behalf of one oil company

@SenJeffMerkley: 97% of the words in it were drafted by Devon Energy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenWhitehouse sees no #Pruitt record of work that "would give a mother taking her child to the hospital for an asthma attack any comfort.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Pruitt: the role of a regulator is to "make things regular."  Are 3 years of record temps regular? https://t.co/n4xWjVCnLE #PollutingPruitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#PollutingPruitt says he'll be a good listener. He'll hear from hundreds of thousands calling for his rejection. https://t.co/lhI4eIWjEW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sen. Barasso opens #Pruitt EPA hearing by citing the idea of "do no  harm." By that standard alone,  #PollutingPruitt must be rejected.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huge victory for cleaner air, smarter transportation and protecting the climate! Congrats to all who've been workin… https://t.co/3vkRxK780x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My friend and housemate got a pizza named after her non-profit. I can only hope to one day soar to such heights.… https://t.co/vuGq6X07Aw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pruitt hasn't just assaulted critical EPA policies, he failed to follow transparency laws outright. https://t.co/zz6G2NWL3F #PollutingPruitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exxon had already said plenty while Tillerson was in charge. @timkaine submitted some of it to the record. #cabinetofpolluters #ExxonKnew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So @timkaine is grilling State nominee and longtime Exxon head Rex Tillerson on climate denial. And he won't answer. #ExxonKnew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alright organizers, let's get our damn clipboards and hitch some effin' wagons #ObamaFarewell #yeswecan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Take the challenge of climate change." Don't mind if I do Mr. President #ActOnClimate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Connor for president/resistance leader 2020! https://t.co/6GKbWw5DIR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it just me or do the most obvious tenants of Obama's basic "America is good" stump speech sound like a bold political statement in 2017.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you had any doubt, well, you don't get to have it anymore. Russia has compromising info on Trump. https://t.co/4UbCM6bb2L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow @RejectPruitt for your regular updates on just how unfit Scott Pruitt is to serve as @EPA administrator. https://t.co/3clunC8yxr]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>