<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@suvyboy @RedwoodGirl as an immigration attorney I am right. CNN was just doing sloppy reporting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suvyboy @RedwoodGirl what? All visas are issued and revoked by state. CBP may know State is on board but they don't have authority]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is wrong. Airlines cannot reinstate a visa!!  Neither can CBP. Let's get basic facts straight https://t.co/4xjXcvWOnI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also DOJ is filing an emergency stay. Trust me I wish you were right. But that was misleading and incorrect. Don't… https://t.co/kTA9eio4Vq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First it's CBP. And they don't have authority. Only Dept of State can do that. https://t.co/RjpIp8IOiz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This CNN tag line is 100% wrong. CBP does not have authority to do that. And unclear when/if refugees will come in.… https://t.co/4C3f5dRamF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gsiskind it will be interesting.. even though refugees can come in it's clear President sets levels. So who can come, from where. Etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gsiskind do we have any idea logistically if Refugee orgs can get refugees on planes come Monday?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also the Judge was a George W Bush appointee... https://t.co/gxbDDtC8yH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dcseth well the media has to track it to find out right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dcseth Why? Its been a long tradition to do this to Presidents. They did it to Obama... W Bush...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@costadaniel @DavidLeopold Spicer announced two EOs will be signed around 1pm on Dodd Frank]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hill Republicans revolt over Trump's plans to build #Borderwall https://t.co/w7gmTrkdk7 #immigration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not Surprised:Hill GOP revolt over Trumps #borderwall https://t.co/w7gmTrkdk7 Considering @immcouncil new fact sheet https://t.co/j34QjV2QTX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DellaSeattle @AlexNowrasteh @CatoInstitute to be clear though the image in this tweet is wrong. Visa Waiver Program was not suspended]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dcseth its like the Bay of Pigs... planned for years under Eisenhower. But its Kennedy's failure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dcseth its a nice try but this, like many foreign policy things are put on the President in power even when they have no control over it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daniel has such a rough life. Is this guy ever happy? The world has been ending or over for years based on his writ… https://t.co/rxxO2oAUCJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But I thought Trump was going to let Bibi do whatever he wanted?!?! https://t.co/fnWL7uhdbC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seungminkim so we are setting up for an April showdown? Along with debt ceiling and keeping govt open??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@josekayemba @ppppolls haha this is delusional and fun. But nice try. If Ds wanted to do voter fraud, wouldnt they do it where it mattered?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@josekayemba @ppppolls what does that have to do with him getting 46% of the nationwide vote?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@josekayemba @ppppolls you realize he got 46% of the vote nationally right? So a poll now, on his policies likely would find them unpopular]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Barry__katz its always interesting how the trolls have less  than 20 followers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this is awesome... https://t.co/rOExugLb2E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ummm..Wow: @DHSgov Secretary Says Parts Of #Borderwall Will Be 'See Through' https://t.co/hHtj754oTz #immigration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@semog_de @ppppolls its a good question for PPP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@semog_de @ppppolls yes i posted the question. Its the right question since Congress is going to try spend $12-15 billion on it in April]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KmSmmns this is a good question, I think @immcouncil new fact sheet on this is a good start: https://t.co/j34QjV2QTX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By a 14 point margin Americans do NOT support Trumps #Borderwall via @ppppolls https://t.co/FBxLttrRDI #immigration https://t.co/B8s5T0Ph02]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Americans oppose a #borderwall 40%-54%
#immigration https://t.co/jynsNSjC5R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't get this logic. Won't Rs just threaten sand thing with next nominee? What is gained at this point, https://t.co/2wc3EI7pSK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is this? Is like putting them on double secret probation? https://t.co/ubogrUfavr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would love to see this rational in court. First of loyalty for your new AG? https://t.co/F8alW29PSe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These are #refugees https://t.co/ar21za31Dh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its sad to say... but I am not the least bit surprised @CustomsBorder is a rogue agency and has been for years https://t.co/cXE5TxsoMj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i hate to say this but if people had listen to the Muslim community the last 15 years they would know they ask this… https://t.co/NwbWIySM6X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[also there is this problem... cc @dcseth https://t.co/8MlHWs0ItH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dcseth right i mean id agree]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dcseth if they are lucky and dont lose any other Rs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They are on double secret probation... https://t.co/jkUIoxGEQB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jordanfabian i think you just heard it...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DLind right so any requirements on countries without a real functioning government are basically permanent bans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PocketParalegal i am willing to bite the bullet and do the inspection.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait... there are RESERVES?!?! Where are they kept? Asking for a friend... https://t.co/uOECRqxv2Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This was clear to anyone who read EO. How can countries without functioning govt improve info shared with US? They… https://t.co/62LFUD62bC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anchorbabyvevo @AdrianaMaestas I don't know how announcing her vote until the day of makes her centrist. Plenty of other things do that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anchorbabyvevo @AdrianaMaestas not saying you shouldn't primary her. But she has a long standing rule of not announcing pics until the vote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He has no vote or say over this FWIW https://t.co/s0RCLUdWsE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was fast... But I cannot say surprising. https://t.co/nRXSncNZ5Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Touche. Slack being cut https://t.co/mvkLZgC2V2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DLind to be clear doesnt the draft EO say... try and draft a rule that does this.It doesnt actually do these things, or am i misremembering]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet Plaintiffs Challenging the Discriminatory Nature of President Trump’s #MuslimBan https://t.co/aMCi1nvmHS via @immcouncil #immigration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Direct quote from @ICEgov acting director Homan today. Following through on Trump's executive order last week on… https://t.co/s5xhCFrX1P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DeanDeChiaro @ICEgov per the executive order, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotAcquiescing o maybe, not sure. It worked on my laptop with no login. Not sure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You mean #AlternativeFacts https://t.co/nzurEb26mc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotAcquiescing cspan is free]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenjySarlin well except for Kelly was on a plane right? Not the best coordination there...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[House Dems are in a conga line telling stories of those impacted by #MuslimBan. Watch: https://t.co/IYEcClFv7V #immigration #RefugeesWelcome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[House Democrats are on the floor now asking for unanimous consent to bring up bill to repeal Trumps Executive Order on #MuslimBan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[House Democrats now on the floor lined up to speak out against Trumps #MuslimBan, see them here: https://t.co/IYEcClFv7V #immigration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No. Because CBP has always done stuff like this. The rest of the media just never listened. https://t.co/Qc5CR9U6M2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good Piece: There are new signs Republicans are going wobbly on the #MuslimBan via @ThePlumLineGS https://t.co/00OloPwNIY #immigration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEW Practice Advisory via @immcouncil on #MuslimBan EO with practice tips for Attorneys &amp; outlines legal challenges https://t.co/qTfCDPIABu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@immcouncil @NWIRP @NIPNLG File Class Action Suit Challenging Trump's #MuslimBan https://t.co/g0szb3NoU3 #immigration #NoBanNoWall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdrianaMaestas as she always says... she announces her vote at the committee hearing. Never before.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdrianaMaestas so Feinstein is voting no on Sessions, just announced]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Public Responds Loudly to President Trump’s #Refugee and Muslim Ban https://t.co/ykhNuTU0oi via @immcouncil #immigration #refugeeban]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnJHarwood makes no sense. Homan leapfrogs Ragsdale to become acting. What happens when new ICE director is nominated and confirmed?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DLind @markberman I have to say that makes no sense. Homan gets to be acting until someone is nominated and then?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DLind @markberman so you're saying Homan leap frogged Ragsdale and was made acting. Homan wasn't formally nominated to head ICE?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This lawsuit is going to be bigly! The biggest and best! https://t.co/L4pcpSJ8Us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DLind also DHS Deputy was nominated?!?! https://t.co/kYpdt006E1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DLind it seems like a statement was sent out? I am hearing it multiple places]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ugh WTF... Tom Homan, who is widely believed to be retiring soon is now acting head of ICE https://t.co/nQe1uQA8pG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidMDrucker speculation is most of them are going to the admin anyway... so their new boss wont mind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ellierutledge i think if Trumo wrote it.. he would have spelled it "boarders"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mjs_DC she is from GA right? So senate seat??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THIS!!! https://t.co/ycvl4rMOIM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LizMair its hard to know much about refugees when all you do is try &amp; find ways to screw them over as Goodlatte and b4 that Lamar Smith did]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today Immigrants groups including @immcouncil Filed Suit Challenging Trump Administration’s #MuslimBan https://t.co/rXpuPZRFrf #immigration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is amazing... Agency's told NOT to talk to Congress https://t.co/xQRv5dAb98]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good Piece: How Democrats will try to roll back Trump’s #immigration ban via @ThePlumLineGS https://t.co/SdrEZWIoWP #RefugeesWelcome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its like a little mini Trump in the Senate. Is the Senator from Arkansas accusing Schumer of lying? https://t.co/keGMbGsUtP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We know who the new Jeff Sessions of the senate is... Tom Cotton.. https://t.co/PA7enlgs2G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dcseth @ABCPolitics or it's an example of a white nationalist, bannon, having to much influence..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So who were these #immigration staffers? CC @PressSec https://t.co/VJ6qWy5MOu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does he mean like Texas, IL, MA, FL, WA, VA and others where the protests have been? https://t.co/tkorbo7EDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ALT_USCIS do we know whether visas from the seven blacklisted countries are still being processed? Like N400s? N600s? I130s?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didnt he promise Day 1 action? https://t.co/fPawqaUgKn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So they made a mistake? https://t.co/hoLdAkxNn3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatthewNussbaum she was last week as well. At least two days i saw her there on cspan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get your popcorn ready! https://t.co/co2dZjnfrK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nycsouthpaw you're acting as if CBP and specifically customs officers haven't been rogue for years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is largely how CBP has always operated... https://t.co/nSobVK2Jv1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alvarombedoya to be clear though... this is a draft. No indication this is coming out yet right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BPC_TBrown @tedhesson @DLind right exactly. Although the border EO is a different story...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING NEWS:Full Text of Draft Dissent Channel Memo on Trump #Refugee and Visa Order https://t.co/844SgaomP5 #immigration #RefugeesWelcome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty amazing: Americans OPPOSE building a #Borderwall with Mexico by a 19 point margin. 34% to 53%. https://t.co/1QNw6IUuAS #NoBanNoWall]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>