<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArianeBeeston Your article about the Nude Night at the AGNSW was wonderful. It sounded like a remarkable experience.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First of the #pinp17 season.
@SeandBlogonaut @JodiCleghorn @angsavage https://t.co/VFT8ZTYDsS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeandBlogonaut @angsavage I'll show you my dishpan hands! ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeandBlogonaut @angsavage That's true. But domestic chores take priority. At it very soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeandBlogonaut And it's a cool poem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeandBlogonaut Love the characters at the end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A quiet and reflective moment in our school chapel after novena. https://t.co/oZIKMnUxiL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeandBlogonaut @angsavage It is very cool. Better get onto mine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Funny seeing all the new senior boys in their new shirts still with the crease marks from being in the box.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TFW when you see students on the playground you taught last year but for the life of you CANNOT remember their name.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Random Poll: Shower first thing in the morning or last thing before going to bed?
I am of the former preference.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nsmithonline *adjusts cardigan* Browse the ads. All you need to know is there. Kids will fill in the rest #olderiswhack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nsmithonline But how will you be "with it" and hip with the kids if you can't riff on the reality tv du jour? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bobbyllew You're a natural then. It's been brutally hot lately, and forecast for more of the same. Even we're a bit done with the heat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bobbyllew Beautiful place to be. Sorry about the torturous heat of late. Hope you have a lovely time around my home town.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeandBlogonaut @JodiCleghorn @JaxOfBo Post It Notes and pens on standby.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charlesdavis75 Gorgeous photo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids these days not having to know how to rule a margin. All their exercise books come pre-ruled. Not like in our day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aussiemoose Good policy. And yes, the world is still sadly screwed but we need to keep propping up the sky with goodness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charlesdavis75 Yep, looks like my girls. One of mine has taken to climbing the walls to reach the roof, like you would do between doorframe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm wearing pants. Professional courtesy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's the first day of Year 7 at my school today *grabs mic* TIME TO OPEN THIS PIT UP! CIRCLE WORK!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlbrtPtts1 I'm feeling sorry for my students who are back this week. So damn hot means learning hardly gets a look in when you're fried.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying to avoid the sun today, in fact this week, in Sydney lest I end up looking like this and exploding in little… https://t.co/RLur5tNPyk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excuse me while I take my frypan outside to cook dinner. Please hand me that raw egg and rashers of bacon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to change a few things then. https://t.co/KPzPhnOWcl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Students, we are going to learn about irony. Please open your iPad and follow the link to the article, "Managing Screen Time for Teens."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EduTweetOz Except if the tennis goes late and we all regret our choices in staying up to watch "just one more game then I'll go to bed."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenLeighHobson Do your students know you write/are about to be published or is that Your Secret Identity? *swirls cape*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenLeighHobson Colds suck. Heading back with forecast temps of 40+ Thinking of buying huge supply of Zooper Doopers for after lunch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenLeighHobson You've been back to the classroom already? I head back in tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenLeighHobson Back when action films had meaning and purpose and the hero actually got hurt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenLeighHobson And I was given a lovely fountain pen for my 40th by my faculty a couple of years back. Very nice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenLeighHobson I've used the same type of pen, the Artline 0.4 Felt Tip since high school. Now branched into using the 0.2 and a Lamy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenLeighHobson The Rock is good. Pearl Harbour is a monstrosity. Transformers needs to take a long hard look for a plot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlbrtPtts1 I'll have to break out the permanent marker and write it in the font style of AC/DC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's something very satisfying about having new pens for the new year. Makes me want to write, but not write because it's a new pen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenLeighHobson Have you been indoctrinated into the Michael Bay School of Filmmaking and Thought? Please tell me you haven't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlbrtPtts1 In reality I've been getting ready for the new school year by organising my school bag and pencil case #littlethingsFTW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlbrtPtts1 Sounds like you have something in common with The Orange Headed One.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know what's cool about the start of the school year? New stationery!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow this thread re: art and resistance. https://t.co/5vYPW1TCDh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone else summoning the rain gods by washing their cars?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had the strangest dream: was on my way to play a gig and for the life of me I could not find the venue. Kept searching to no avail #stress]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Amelia_Draws Didn't have them for my girls. Nor did we find out gender. Both were surprises. Nor did we reveal names.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melludee HAPPY NEW YEAR OF THE ROOSTER TO YOU!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow this thread for a minute. Worth your time. https://t.co/DT40NoRSiz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenLeighHobson Why not both?! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenLeighHobson Is that for a weekend of reading and no interruptions or appearing in someone's TBR pile or both? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aussiemoose I'd rather be teaching than sitting through administrivia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aussiemoose Yep, I'm back to school on Monday. Student free day. Hence day of relatively completely useless meetings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think I'd better back up my laptop before school resumes on Monday as I suspect it will crap itself when it tries to reconnect to the system]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlbrtPtts1 Man, you're raking in the legit followers now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlbrtPtts1 That's bot-tastic!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aussiemoose Because you're inhabiting the Twilight Zone between a public holiday and the weekend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's the day I'd better break in my new school shoes. Blister alert. Band Aids on standby.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brain wants to edit but body says, "Nope, ewe wood knot know what yew were righting."
#tootired]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And who needs to watch MKR because they've set up the personalities and stereotypes and shown all the good bits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not one for betting but what's the bet the personalities on "I'm A Celebrity Get Me Out of Here" will be stereotypically cliched as Oz TV?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know the "new and improved" Pizza Shapes still taste like stale disappointment but because the box is there &amp; open I'm still eating them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jazir1979 Just don't read the last 20 pages :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aussiemoose Fairy bread AND lamgintons combined into one delicious diabetic coma!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aussiemoose How did they taste?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsBessieBell No pressure then 😉]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsBessieBell The vignette is written but not edited. And a testament to writing dangerously I think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsBessieBell I'll start Orange Peel when home (only brought what I needed on hols) and finish the vignette I started.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsBessieBell As writer I love the playing with lang/image/emotion but I want the reader to be sucked in to the story.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsBessieBell characters to make them really engage &amp; it's showing in the depth of writing &amp; how we are writing. Stepping out to go deeper.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsBessieBell Stories are meant to be ugly (however we want to define/use it). In a collab novel w/ 2 others, we're pushing in deep to our]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsBessieBell Now read Muted and She. Very powerful. Inspires me to write more dangerously, with greater conviction, with renewed passion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsBessieBell Holidays are great times for reading. The covers are brilliant. Enjoying this book. https://t.co/hm5SMyTFv3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I predict English teachers will be required in the future to correct these monstrosities. https://t.co/QAMlimCt4I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@21stCscribe Yeah, it's the bubble we create around ourselves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@21stCscribe True. But maybe it's a start.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarkMatterzine We're stuck in a bind where DV should be jailed but needing more resources to assist all involved, esp victim.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RevHappiness It is right to protest issues that are problematic but it needs dialogue from a wider representation than simply soapboxers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RevHappiness "Throw them in jail" is knee-jerk, emotive, not thought out. It's simplistic w/out considering the wider implications.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RevHappiness Throwing people in jail w/out adequate resources does nothing to solve the wider issues. Overcrowded prisons don't help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheresaMilstein That is a gorgeous collection. Loved reading it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RevHappiness Yet I have not yet seen the media go to the Law Society/judges for their POV. Everyone has an opinion yet no one listens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RevHappiness In the wake of Melbourne incident the media goes to its regular mouthpieces about how bail laws have failed/lock them up etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Soapboxing will be a 2020 Olympic Demonstration Sport so all the shock jocks and celebrity commentators can feel good about themselves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A juvenile version of the almighty Sarlacc. https://t.co/2hZIVGrlZw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Game ON! https://t.co/xDHEfnhDan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kirbykirbybee That is pretty spectacular!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charlesdavis75 Love the silly family photo. All the goodness contained therein.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New ep of Red Dwarf delightfully funny. Some great one liners. And the banter is still spot on. But I missed Season 10. Need to borrow eps.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When asked, "How are you?" my answer might be, "Well, life is a complicated crapstorm &amp; I'm having difficulty keeping my umbrella up. You?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There should be a rule for tennis players to NOT WEAR THE SAME OUTFIT AT THE SAME TIME. Differentiate, people, so I know who I'm watching.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solar system or fairy lights in the garden? https://t.co/3OO7lMEmVV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aussiemoose Which is all a way of motivating me to get my writing finish and subbed out there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aussiemoose Maybe before the launch of Who's Afraid 3 :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aussiemoose Admittedly my daughters are not in their teens but it's important to support authors when we can, and show books are COOL!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aussiemoose My daughters were seeing Jacqueline Harvey for the release of the new Alice-Miranda. It's their 3rd launch they've been to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JacquelineHarve My Miss #2 wanted to ask you if there would be a book launch for Clementine-Rose in the future?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Under the trees for the new Alice-Miranda book launch with @JacquelineHarve. Beautiful spot #supportlocalauthors https://t.co/REZ9gzN6Yr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aussiemoose So full of kulcha!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aussiemoose That's cool. Bummed I couldn't make it last night or I would have said hi. Have taken my girls to a diff book launch thus arvo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the launch of @JacquelineHarve's new Alice-Miranda book for my girls. Fabulous storyteller.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smperris I played tennis when younger but switched to squash through high school. I'm rubbish on a court with no walls.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>