<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson I look forward to seeing your new skin in photos accompanying articles about the next book you publish. Which when is?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReneeStephen @ubermichael Two-metre skeleton of a dinosaur crawling along the floor frightening the cat? What's not to like?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thatcher a feminist? Dave never was very bright, was he? https://t.co/lLr8i78hQW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ubermichael Yeah, like maybe on a cat or something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maximum_z "It is not enough that I succeed, but that my friends must also fail."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just cleaned the bathroom. That mirror is so clean I can see my face in it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sinKEVitch @Neilhimself I would love to see this from you gentlemen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson That's why I never let anyone I know read my stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson Whoops! You answered my question before I asked it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson "More than if they were strangers" is interesting. Why's that? Do you feel as if your friends have let you down?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshRimer Remember -- you are what you eat!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Blade Runner 2049" teaser looks ... good, actually. How will they do it without crapping all over the original? https://t.co/MGMvMmHvO7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ubermichael His most menacing, chilling, crazy moment was before he became the Joker, standing between two guns grinning, "Better be sure."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ubermichael I'm a big fan of Jack Nicholson, but I was disappointed by his Joker -- self-conscious, mannered, no real menace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ubermichael Yer possibly right. They're both ridiculous and make no sense. Ledger was a better Joker than Nicholson and Leto put together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrentSpiner And just think of the product advertisements!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PoorQuentyn Thanks for the quick reply! I'll check it out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeerJeet Nobody has ever explained why "Eyes Wide Shut" is good. If you'd be so kind ..?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ubermichael I think the answer is contained in the question.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanebee "Why, I wouldn't touch you with a thirty-nine-and-a-half-foot pole!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pal's immediate response, when I read this: "Son of a bitch!" https://t.co/deLkRZ2Ls2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson "Made them with the skin side inside, made them with the fur side outside." What were Inuit wearing before Gold Rush in '98?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson I'm from the Yukon, and I always thought that mitts were mitts -- as long as they're *warm*!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColleenDoran The Tweet you quoted is a strange thing to boast about, but fuck that guy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maximum_z The odds are much lower if you don't try!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maximum_z Depends. What year were you hoping to attend?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Playbill" presents "The Definitive List of the 41 Best-Selling Cast Recordings of All Time": https://t.co/e5xX658l2I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AskeBay Alas, options to order listings do not exist when looking to buy items.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One good thing you could do, @eBay, is put back the option to order listings by date, price, etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, when did @eBay become so ugly and hard to use?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*Everything* needs a grim 'n' gritty reboot -- even (especially!) Lassie! https://t.co/7tlHCLAfu3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevecavers These Germans are crazy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevecavers Germanic tribe? Where?! Invading Germanic hordes aren't here again, are they?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @Adobe! Now Dreamweaver CC 2017 crashes only 50 percent of the time I open it. This is, alas, a great improvement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@corbett I have observed "force of nature" applied to women and men. I have not tallied how often to whom; might be interesting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tarakjpratt Perhaps you're bursting with fruit flavour.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanebee "There there, little bunny."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And he still looks the same as he always did: embalmed. https://t.co/3TffCQDNMC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A few minutes ago on The Crescent, Vancouver, BC, an @Amazon truck pulled out without looking or signalling and almost ran me off the road.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huh. Apparently somebody named @PiersMorgan has more Twitter followers than comedy legend @EricIdle. Well, well, we… https://t.co/4UmmEUHATP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching Butterscotch Candygram on "Saturday Night Live". Gad, the man just drips charisma.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dreamweaver Exact steps: Open Dreamweaver. Create new HTML file. Try to type anywhere on screen; nada. Program crashes. Repeat as needed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So apparently it is not possible to enter text in @Adobe Dreamweaver 2017. Bit of a drawback, that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I press "Record" on the camera. https://t.co/jT1rod3Mji]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColleenDoran Enjoyed this series of posts. One day, when you have some spare time (ha!) readers might be interested in seeing some entries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aww, "Luke Cage" -- what a disappointment. They rushed it into production, and it shows; godawful second half. Such a shame.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdobeCare So you are saying that your own software does not work, and your own update procedures do not work. Good to know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdobeCare No. My fault, trusting your software to do what it claims it will. Why is the default to delete the old version if that's bad?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdobeCare No. Both. The app displays the welcome screen ... and goes no further. Eventually Windows 10 reports, "... has stopped working."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdobeCare "If it did not install correctly"? How do I find this out, pray tell?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Luke Cage" continues to dribble away after the halfway point. Stryker and his whole plotline should have been amputated root and branch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So @Adobe, I have now opened Dreamweaver 60 times and it has crashed on opening 40 times. This is your standard? It works one time in three?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YoginSuhas @Adobe (This is statistical: I have opened the program 60 times. It has crashed on opening 40 times.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YoginSuhas @Adobe Just updated to the new CC2017. To start with, Dreamweaver crashes on opening two out of three times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Writing in "Luke Cage" takes a precipitous decline in quality in episodes 8 and 9 so far. 13 episodes trying to stretch out 8 eps of story?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @Adobe! When I type a line of text into Dreamweaver and then hit "Enter", I want to start a new paragraph, not delete the text.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the hell has @Adobe done with Dreamweaver? Is it actually usable any more?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @Adobe! You done fucked up good with CC 2017.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching "Luke Cage" and just noticed that as two characters talk about race, the white guy is eating his lunch with chopsticks. Nice touch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Viktory79 I'm not from New York and I'm not on the stage, and have no plans to be either, but add me if you'd like; I can't stop you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnCleese @Minainchina Two lawyers see a pretty girl. One says, "Boy, I'd really like to screw her!" The other says, "Yeah? Out of what?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ten years ago is more recent than I think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evanjstern Oatmeal-raisin cookies are easier to make than chocolate-chip. It takes forever to peel all those M&amp;Ms!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mistershrewd I don't think we've had even any new shirtless-Trudeau photos.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And those "actors" in these flickers! If they had any real talent they'd be on the stage, right? https://t.co/m58bLsU9OG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought I was wrong once, but I was mistaken.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evanjstern I'm afraid @jonvoight has been a right-wing-authoritarian bonehead for years. "Midnight Cowboy" is still a good movie though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck I'm afraid @jonvoight has been a right-wing-authoritarian bonehead for years. "Midnight Cowboy" is still a good movie though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson Ah! Thank you. My knowledge expands -- I love when that happens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson Aside: What means "ARCs"? Google is not helpful, alas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson Handsome beast!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck "I have magic breasts!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Emmy Awards are tonight! I'm sure the mothers of the winners and nominees are all very proud.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StacieBee Ah, whenever I hear someone say that, I think to myself, "Boy, that Bowie song holds up pretty well."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattdagley Blu-ray player might not recognize exFAT, but will recognize NTFS, which MacOS can use (but beware of creeping file corruption).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattdagley Yeah, that's the well-known filesize limit on FAT32. Reformat as exFAT for use on both MacOS and Windows.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WH_Woolhat @gerryconway Sam Rockwell is so amazing, I'm not sure he isn't played by Tilda Swinton.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["All 47 Woody Allen movies -- ranked from worst to best": https://t.co/dsmBSn2Ey0.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson Alas, I fear most creators don't really know who their audience is.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson (I've heard, "Crowd-funding is two parts, but if you don't have the crowd you won't get the funding." How to get the crowd?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson Biggest knowledge-gap is usually not how to make campaign, but how to attract backers -- put campaign before interested eyes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just heard that North Korea has banned sarcasm. Yeah, that'll work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MysteryIndie Just because you've lost doesn't mean you have to stop fighting!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck Also, by "River's last episode", do you mean "Silence in the Library"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck Donna's last episode was the saddest of all. She grew as a person, enlarged her world, and then was forced to give that up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson So your cups runneth over?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Lincoln Park Zoo names baby camel 'Alexander Camelton'": https://t.co/7CxOPSHiRW.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson I think that meal is more Chinese than pierogi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right to stand still! Left to walk! What's the problem, people? https://t.co/6RLatlAzlg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattdagley Well, maybe in Toronto.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson Reminds me of Margaret Cho's line: "My problem is that I look this way, but I talk this way."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NachosaurusRex I find it hard to believe there is such a thing as a good episode of "Voyager". "DS9" was good some of the time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NachosaurusRex Yeah, Myer's involvement is a good sign. He's (partly) responsible for two of my favourite "Star Trek" movies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NachosaurusRex The last coupl'a TNG movies, "Enterprise", "Voyager", and the last 2 reboot movies have kinda squashed the ol' enthusiasm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nostalgia ain't what it used to be. https://t.co/QOPR5fPrOX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tarakjpratt @akonkin That's not camping! I don't see a single pillow fort.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What kind of low-budget films break out?" https://t.co/rPPW1SXE2O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guy on CBC Radio says that Canadians' least-favourite word is "moist". Grrnnrghghgh ..! "Moist". It just feels unpleasant in the mouth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Panic Mooniverse expands by another small chapter, thanks to @ItsAdamCanuck, @lessicajee, and more!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nooMcinaP You've got me there. Two of my (many) favourite actors.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>