<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@CAIRCoalition My husband was in detention.  None of these people wanted to help him reopen an old case but they offer free help to islam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CAIRCoalition This organization didn't want to help my Hispanic husband with his deportation when he needed help!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DestellitoDeLuz @iArias07 @realDonaldTrump Photo shopped .  its obvious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NILC_org @SpeakerRyan @YouTube Nope.  Trump is right!!  Change is here!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[State Duma, adopt the domestic violence law in Russia - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/fcvmn6jicC via @Change]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erotao Send Millions to their countries and all the educated personnel to fix their countries.  Then, they wouldn't come here!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@manassaslabor Don't know a Jack.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhillyCustoms American the Stupid! !!!!  Not American the Brave]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@routefifty Google should be checking immigration status of its sub contractors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ErinFox5DC @fox5dc These people don't know how to drive like us who have been driving all our lives in the U.S.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ErinFox5DC @fox5dc Traffic is Manassas is ridiculous.  You have an unnecessary amount of foreigners who don't belong on the road.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DHSgov @ICEgov What crimes are considered serious by ICE?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AILANational @nytimes Shouldn't be transgender in the first place.  Born a male.  You STAY a male. Born a female. You STAY a female]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CareDotCom Not good.  Spare the rod. Spoil the child . destroy a life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewsChannel8 Ok.  What happened to their infant?  Nothing was stated in report. The baby is the one we care about. Not those losers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN Drug Dealer with a bad temper.   Time to eliminate this fool!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN Traitors!!!  Kiss ass New Yorkers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cnni Well.  The other concerned Governments need to seek and execute him. Problem solved! !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StayGratefulMan Northern Virginia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FAIRImmigration @WAFB Good,  they got her!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rockette Explains Inauguration Fallout https://t.co/UPeftl94qo 
The mentality of the Rockette's is obvious; Trump isn't the only pervert!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN Well. No shit! !  The minute he stepped onto Russian soil.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YahooNews I never stopped saying MERRY CHRISTMAS simply because society chooses to be ignorant.  I am NOT with society.   I am much smarter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instantly win $1,000 in points and a chance to win your #dreamcar #instantwingame #sweeps https://t.co/DWSFVHVzO3 via @SYWSweeps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woman accused of trying to calm baby with methadone https://t.co/EXxSU4xSVV   news/222921783-story.   The inmates will get her!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woman accused of trying to calm baby with methadone https://t.co/J3isLEooWs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN Melanie Hamrick wants security and nailed it with her son with the old pervert!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN Another valid reason to ban and get rid of Victorias Secret.  She was probably too fat for their store.   BAN VICTORIAS SECRET]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DC101 Who really cares!!   Why freak out on shopping.   Americans have it all wrong.  I am proud to say: I am not like the typical American]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WVWOnline @WTHRcom I am not paying my so called audited tax return due to IRS.  Help me instead!  U.S. born and raised.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pulpark Horrible.   Just no words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCWorld Another job for Trump to tackle and completely correct in 2017. No excuses.  Make children great again! !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wusa9. Very sad. Sounds like another child will be without parents and someone will have to raise the precious child. May God help them all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darrenrovell @ABC7Jummy Should have been Doves not pigeons.  Lord.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@schlichting1103 Its just a flag. Means nothing.   Whether U.S. or foreign territory.  God doesn't care about a Country's flag anyhow! !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just shared my birthday with iHeartRadio! Don't blow it, share your birthday too. @iHeartRadio https://t.co/qiEK5DQToy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Take away Citizenship for the low life's that travel to foreign countries to have sex with young children!!  Tackle that!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cnni Once again proves.  Smoking is hazardous to your health! !!  LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ABC7News @zekechanguris Thank you but honestly.  Should be nice everyday and we both are nice but speaking the truth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zekechanguris @ABC7John @ABC7News LOL.    We had no real good choices.  We are screwed any way we go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DEAHQ @DEANEWORLEANS @EDLAnews the best way to deal with these maggots. Blow up their entire compound.  2 a week for starters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ABC7John @ABC7News Ridiculous! !  Material obsessed stupid Americans out to show their display of pure ignorance! !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxNews Its about time! That damn thing should never have been built. Common sense here!!!  But stupidity rules in the U.S.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCWorld A typical politician!  Runs their mouth in public because that's what the public wAnts to hear!!  Anything to get elected! !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YahooNews President Obama is the worst ever!!  Accepting Ellen's disgusting choice to be gay and then honoring it!!  The works of Satan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YahooNews Medal of Freedom,  for what?  Being homosexual.  Please!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MomsRising @Rewire_News Abortion should be banned not a woman losing her job!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adidasoriginals @kanyewest I am sooooo sure these shoes will be outrageously overpriced! !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN What a dumbass!!  Then he gets tackled and can't defend himself.  What a total dumbass!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SusanAinVA People here are stupid and ignorant and ignored this man's life and now his children here are going to suffer tremendously.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SusanAinVA This is wrong on many levels and should have been corrected years ago and ICE has no heart when it comes to why he is a criminal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SusanAinVA  Once again another story of the legal system failing a man who as a young boy brought into this country as a child.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attorney says adoptee from South Korea deported from US https://t.co/q4wYofslgE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RefugeeWatcher @erotao @wordpressdotcom NO!!  That's the answer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@V_of_Europe @erotao Get rid of the Muslims then.  Problem solved]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN @lisaling First of all. These creatures are not Men.  Please rephrase.  Males or animals should not have any rights!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cnni LOL.   AT least it wasn't grandma this time.   LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erotao @WashTimes People panic before anything is set in stone. Knock it off already! Sick of their whiny asses!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peek_r I enjoy cold weather.  Warm weather brings out the creepy crawlie things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peek_r Cold is good.  Your blood should be thick!  Being a Veteran and a New Yorker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peek_r How is New York?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peek_r Like 2 months ago.  Sorry.  Its been a while but you have commented on some of my outspoken words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peek_r You were trying to help me with my own picture but I gave up for a while]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peek_r  Hope you are well.  Hows New York?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peek_r. Great picture of you.  As you see.  I still haven't loaded one yet!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WayneDupreeShow @peek_r I hope he changes his mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpeakerRyan Blow up the Assad regime and him!  Problem solved]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN @CNNOpinion You don't!  End of story]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YahooNews We all know Trump idolizes the $$$$$.  Not God but the greens. Many Americans who are truly smart will pay the price for Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewsChannel8 Typical.  Hes a politician. They always get off for their crimes just like Diplomats.  No justice on earth!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thejuliewright And foreigners do NOT know how to drive but obtain licenses anyhow.  Either by DMV or bought off the street!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thejuliewright Foreigners do this Julie.  They don't care.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DEAHQ @KazakhEmbassy @MVD_RK @TheJusticeDept @USembassyAstana Blow up the drug lord compounds for starters! !  I will lead!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxNews The horse was let out of the barn a long time ago!-  You will spend a lifetime catching it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thousands sign petition to publicly hang West Virginia man accused of raping, murdering baby girl https://t.co/XNdrNCayeo via @WTKR3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnacostiaRrkper @abc7Richard Yep!  Probably none. They wouldn't know how to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abc7Richard These kids have no idea what they protesting for! Clueless.  Looking for a reason to get out of school &amp; cause trouble.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gluegun000 @FoxNews @mercedesschlapp I agree 100 percent with you!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gluegun000 @FoxNews @mercedesschlapp Looks should never buy a persons way through life.  Ever!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxNews @mercedesschlapp Don't forget,  Trumps wife apparently broke some immigration laws along her way to success. Hhmmmm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimBurt @RealAlexJones @infowars Did anyone cry , this is a racist attack on a white man!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YahooNews Facebook should but won't stop people from allowing nudity,  partially nude and provocative pictures of women on it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnAdam33 @MailOnline The Devil in full force!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN Spoiled unknowledable about the world yet Brats!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Life isn't fair!! Fact of life.   Deal with it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics Not thrilled about that!! Trump picked her for eye candy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ndiblasio @USATODAY Flags mean nothing.  God doesn't give one hoot about a country's flag.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN Of course Trump will.  He's not Muslim or a coward!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cnni Ban all strip clubs, Casinos,  Hooters,  pornography magazines, numerous legal brothels, useless apps that promote infidelity! !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TonyPerkinsFOX5 @SSS_joshnelson We didn't approve of our only 2 choices for President.   We wanted God fearing candidates not boasting ones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxNews Sounds fishy!!  I wonder if Mistress, Jealousy,  or she knew too much.  Murder mystery.   Hhhmmm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fox5dc @wttg We have the most ignorant people in America! ! No wonder the Eastern parts hate us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@astridgalvan and what state is this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @CNN Are we surprised! !!  More damn unnecessary drama]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@USATODAY This guy is so right!!  Well put Colin!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics Remember Donald said the election will be rigged!!  He warned everyone constantly. How did thousands of emails get read in 24hr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thejuliewright Thank you.  Have a Blessed Day!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thejuliewright This is not a good description of where accident is.  Map isn't helpful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics She was never investigated!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN Great.  More power for the bad people to take over our country because most Americans will be stoned off their dumb asses.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>