<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Steps to create a secure connected car - Infosecurity Magazine https://t.co/Lgo1HamQQE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-NJ Transit boss named temporary MTA head in New York https://t.co/BApzkZSCUs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cisco Introduces New Innovations for Digital Buildings https://t.co/XxZU1TPqKx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cisco is launching products to transform workplaces into smart buildings https://t.co/tq81qPy9IQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Building the Internet of Things - Maciej Kranz https://t.co/WZ0uXRiple]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Audi tells dealerships to get behind electric vehicles because it will dominate the market within 10 years https://t.co/achTxHId9S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daimler is the latest company offering self-driving cars through Uber - Recode https://t.co/xLm1Vmeyw8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Survey indicates Kansas City streetcar is good for downtown businesses | The Kansas City Star https://t.co/uJJwKzpBAA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why carmakers want to keep Apple and Google at arm's length https://t.co/tCVZHfl5T4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Equipping people to stay ahead of technological change https://t.co/jssXyxoSzn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobility reshapes smart cities with apps, autonomous connected cars &amp; optimism https://t.co/TsNBRvGbnk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Musk confirms digging a hole beneath SpaceX, aims to improve tunnel digging speeds by 5-10x https://t.co/jthLwYEfIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Self-driving vehicles to be tested near Haneda Airport https://t.co/MAymi2qOmG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dubai's RTA extends driverless car trial run in Business Bay - https://t.co/zvW6yvCx6R https://t.co/P7fe7bCjrU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking Down the Financial Impact of Self-Driving Cars https://t.co/zxM3mEEwOk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elon Musk's Hyperloop Competition Draws Students from Around the World | WIRED https://t.co/TYsufbP7Ks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your IoT Journey: Taking the Right Steps | Iot-Inc https://t.co/medk8UPe7P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staying Ahead of the Evolving Threat – Announcing the Cisco 2017 Annual Cybersecurity Report #CiscoACR… https://t.co/CoRU8uQI7l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let’s Talk About Self-Driving Cars – The Startup – Medium https://t.co/qjaM8GlP8T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cisco 2017 Annual Cybersecurity Report: Chief Security Officers Reveal True Cost of Breaches And The Actions That Or…https://t.co/qb2qiCEEM6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Driving your fleet to the future https://t.co/zPoZBGDlrl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brand suicide case study: British Airways https://t.co/BiQdNF5Tf6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Driverless vehicle is a glimpse into Atlanta's transit future https://t.co/qmFRwmrz3P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cisco "plugs in"​ AppDynamics: Making 1+1=3 https://t.co/qd9RZ5dnwS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elon Musk's Tunnel Under LA Is Already in Progress | WIRED https://t.co/z4yafpU4sK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could we be on the cusp of an electric vehicle revolution? https://t.co/uhHX22f3se]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steps to create a secure connected car - Infosecurity Magazine https://t.co/Lgo1Ha5fZ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's Why General Motors Will Build and Test Autonomous Vehicles in Metro Detroit https://t.co/4EPLY2ixtb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coming soon to the enterprise: The self-driving network https://t.co/z5lhTGSgo8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google’s head of self-driving tech: We’re not building a car, we’re building the driver - Recode https://t.co/L6q9hHsPhB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take a virtual tour of the #IoT tech that’s shaping the future of homes: https://t.co/EoEWbz5RvR https://t.co/4sAGcVrSDd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can humans answer the call fast enough when autonomous cars need help? https://t.co/wEqYcgx3Pl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla’s Battery Revolution Just Reached Critical Mass - Bloomberg https://t.co/EpCbbfUjkG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Save the date: 1st European Conference on ‘Connected and Automated Driving’ https://t.co/ZC4YqVf4Sx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vehicle Connectivity: What is CV/AV? | Telecommunications Industry Association https://t.co/rCtrPllYfe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On The Road To Driverless Cars https://t.co/v0L47ovZSL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over-the-air updates may alter NHTSA recall policy https://t.co/TqfynfFaSC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smart cities: A matrix of information superhighways | Robotics &amp; Automation News https://t.co/S8sfGEQZ0j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US: Ohio Governor and the State University announce $45 million expansion in vehicle test center https://t.co/Aoe6JydgMa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill would pave way for driverless car fleets in Nevada https://t.co/HdZYnUhcK2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Tale of Two Companies: One Kit, Multiple Innovations https://t.co/syX8OywkET]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In China, low-speed electric vehicles are driving high-speed urbanisation https://t.co/r6YMExoCeT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Foxconn, Cisco, Bosch &amp; others join hands to form a new blockchain and IoT consortium https://t.co/CsaKVQBLA1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know what's in store for tech &amp; IT in 2017? @KevinBloch has shared his predictions....… https://t.co/MOapJ8XQPY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobility Game Changers: The Transportation Startups Reimagining How We&amp;#8217;ll Travel https://t.co/1N0n7jadKk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Autonomous vehicles could increase private car traffic, says new report https://t.co/roquRSqNHN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security in a Transport Revolution https://t.co/EXasq6P6dM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FEATURES AND EXCLUSIVE ARTICLES &gt;&gt; https://t.co/EiQWN0qsvI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Driverless cars are coming: Here are 8 useful facts about them | Brookings Institution https://t.co/UzlDRZFM3D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cohda Wireless Appoints a New European Sales Manager https://t.co/3KLk8O9CCq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a place for tech in infrastructure planning, experts say https://t.co/ajCrITQQXU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive: AppDynamics deal reflects one of Cisco’s (NASDAQ: CSCO) John Chambers’ secrets to successful innovation:…https://t.co/Od173MTSZi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Government invites bids to build HS2 trains for £2.75bn https://t.co/QGcTsgcd5T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Internet of Things: today and tomorrow https://t.co/w8AUOwEk94]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s a go for free Wi-Fi through 300 kiosks and on public buses and trains in Miami-Dade https://t.co/myOkhqAyXg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cisco Spark Board Launch https://t.co/xCkdzrA59T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shifting Gears to Driverless - World Economic Forum Annual Meeting 2017 | World Economic Forum https://t.co/k4lUwpPuTj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dallas City Leaders Making Plans For High Speed Rail « CBS Dallas / Fort Worth https://t.co/AZtdYf9zU4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who Knew A Volvo Ad Could Make You Re-Examine Your Life Priorities? | Co.Create | creativity + culture + commerce https://t.co/x7dzbSLV7s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From Campus Drive to Cisco: Our Journey with AppDynamics https://t.co/AuxPs8K8Dg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are autonomous vehicles a threat or opportunity? - https://t.co/OQtxgLTIBp https://t.co/UDWy8GTImu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Northeast Ohio accelerates self-driving vehicle effort: here's how it all will work https://t.co/p23nONrBfH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Save the Date for Cisco Connect Harrisburg https://t.co/gjLzONptcy https://t.co/NnPvbswEL6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toyota Unveils Its Connected Strategy, Sidelines Google And Apple https://t.co/SofUS0usqO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cisco Spark Board Takes Aim at Bad Meetings https://t.co/OKH506JHUu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FOCUS: Futurist | The Network https://t.co/Rct5Wbule4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ruderman White Paper on SDC Benefits https://t.co/GHvVtQhvvI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Q&amp;A with David Pickeral, Smart and Connected Transportation Industry Expert https://t.co/BlGSImzsHL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join our #CiscoChat on 1/27 to learn about the business value of creating digital-ready networks… https://t.co/R8cVIHvdYu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does the future of #IoT hold? Discover 3 key tips for starting the IoT journey: https://t.co/wgdUiit9Ts https://t.co/A6w8QBHGqx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What are governments’ roles in the #IoT implementation? Our @MaciejKranz points out some of them #CiscoInnovates… https://t.co/FsB0coKQT9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Gift That Keeps on Giving – The Digital Sports Experience via @CiscoSESG https://t.co/vllJ3JUUhW https://t.co/alWvYgEgjJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SanJoseSharks and @CiscoSESG Deploy Stadium Wi-Fi at SAP Center to Improve the #FanExperience. Read more… https://t.co/5UsubMy29n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Platform for Change: TTI Provides FHWA a New Way to Test CV/AV Technologies — Texas A&amp;M Transportation Institute https://t.co/WIWWiuf0DM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gazing at the crystal ball of connected cars – Part I | TU-Automotive https://t.co/BgozFjyTTI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a revolution happening in electricity.... https://t.co/fASEiFvxNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prepare for Self-Driving Cars or Become Obsolete https://t.co/GBLptWMkur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla Boosts Range of All-Electric Model S to 335 Miles https://t.co/QHk5xPiwHT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emerging trends in infrastructure 2017 https://t.co/ERorMKbBR7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cisco bets big on app-tuning start-up - Taipei Times https://t.co/1kgkVGIwgJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IoT and the Digital Transformation:  Leveraging Big Data to Remain Competitive - 1129956 https://t.co/Nl4enYU2qL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GM, Mastercard Want Your Car to Pick Up the Tab for That Latte https://t.co/2m1ymHdooZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hyundai Release The Future For Connected Vehicles With Mobility Vision - Torque News https://t.co/G3VHdHUJaO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In every industry there is a ‘next’. | KPMG | GLOBAL https://t.co/3M2EeDGNYh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aging and urban divergence | Brookings Institution https://t.co/9CPmIoKzcm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cisco snatches AppDynamics from IPO market for $3.7 billion | Network World https://t.co/ZEgL0swMcn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobileye Wants To Teach Your Robotic Car To Merge In Heavy Boston Traffic https://t.co/UlqULPWab3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great week ahead here @Mobility Talks, Washington Automotive, and ENO Foundation Events #MobilityTalks2017  https://t.co/dlF5ZKrmnn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla gets Guinness World Record for a massive Model S and X parade in China https://t.co/Arr3jnchDj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be Inspired By These Creative Leaders Who Are Changing The World | Fast Company | Business + Innovation https://t.co/9Te0Hyhdbi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mary Brown Leading the Conversation on Delivering Connectivity to Transportation #MobilityTalks2017 https://t.co/BqiQL2eF4Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[INFOGRAPHIC: The Internet of Things and the future of payments »  PaymentEye https://t.co/JebMBMtzT8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Miami-to-Orlando train chugging along in track testing https://t.co/ppDQu3SVak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hyundai reveals future vision for connected cars - Which-50 https://t.co/sfIXmToVwy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Asia best in class in smart #transport: https://t.co/GjJrHXDGoy @ciscoAPAC https://t.co/1Fc8ZkvqZO https://t.co/nf1X2lf54D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does #digitization really mean? Just announced our weekly 'Dive Into Digitization' webinar series. #OneCTO… https://t.co/tSM2M91sdx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ford allows some car buyers to purchase or finance vehicles online https://t.co/t2NGRt63xO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wal-Mart muscles into auto sales https://t.co/YQIpGn4CnU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Transit Trends to Watch in 2017 https://t.co/rpDy1Atf1U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MoDOT wins two national awards for innovation and technology https://t.co/nyOV60E9wb]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>