<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I just earned the 'Riding Steady (Level 3)' badge on @untappd! https://t.co/tpswd1PR00]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just earned the 'Wheel of Styles (Level 10)' badge on @untappd! https://t.co/Vmun6kNFvG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just earned the 'Riding Steady (Level 2)' badge on @untappd! https://t.co/VbqisExfce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColeyTangerina @izzyelle @simonpnz classic 90s porn. Not so sexy but HILARIOUS!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Morning https://t.co/XzltX3fuKl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Karey1975 @jackiembouvier When Karey? After they die a horrible painful death of starvation? I don't think much of your God's love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SlimRootboy @jackiembouvier @ninjadinosaur1 the lord doesn't exist. And that's the whole point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Karey1975 you're an idiot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Karey1975 @jackiembouvier @darksecretplace what about all the children who are born to parents who have never even heard of baby Jesus?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just earned the 'Better Together (Level 2)' badge on @untappd! https://t.co/YAG58TPK3c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#headintheclouds https://t.co/j0KT03bG7i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My morning view.
Great day for cricket https://t.co/58GdeMH3p6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Above the urinal in the men's at Shepherd. Intimidated much? https://t.co/kGc4Wa17p7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annanibbles FUCK yeah!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just earned the 'Wheel of Styles (Level 9)' badge on @untappd! https://t.co/jBZ6gulXCy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just earned the 'Riding Steady' badge on @untappd! https://t.co/cVA4Ct3dft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just earned the 'Find the Source (Level 3)' badge on @untappd! https://t.co/noRKKuv1J9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And here's the issue. We're racist and just don't see it, accept it and instead actively fight against the idea. https://t.co/iD5fd9Abbl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just earned the 'I Believe in IPA!  (Level 29)' badge on @untappd! https://t.co/MRqf3eVVfk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just earned the 'Cheers To You! (Level 3)' badge on @untappd! https://t.co/2noQIjRyO7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just earned the 'Happy Brew Year (2017)' badge on @untappd! https://t.co/8aTerIDztm #brewyear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amyharvard_ Yeah what is going on with teen vogue lately? I read an article on Trump and it was amazing. More of this!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just wanna punch 2016 in the face. Then strangle it with my slave chain #ripcarriefisher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck this shit. 2016 takes Leia, that's awful. Just truly awful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just earned the 'Bar Explorer (Level 28)' badge on @untappd! https://t.co/WcpE8jnm5O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck Fonterra. Fuck them very much. https://t.co/3EFaXG3Ogi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's too close to call. And the judges get to decide. Is a draw out of the question? #ParkerRuiz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As the more aggressive fighter I would have it 115-113 Ruiz. #ParkerRuiz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 round to go. Unless someone gets an 8 or a knockdown it will go to the more aggressive fighter and that looks like Ruiz to me #ParkerRuiz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's so tight. I haven't seen a heavyweight fight in the 11th with so much leather thrown #ParkerRuiz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big round for Parker. Two more like that and he wins the fight. More of those right hands needed #ParkerRuiz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looked like a Ruiz round to me. 10-9 #ParkerRuiz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And it's heating up. Exciting boxing. Throwing some leather. 4-3 Ruiz but he's cut. And traditionally fades now. #ParkerRuiz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is very good heavyweight boxing good punching. Evening out now. #ParkerRuiz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First round for Joe. Though no-one been shaken, no-one hurt. Parker has to knock out Ruiz to win this one #ParkerRuiz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andy Ruiz a shutout after four rounds, Parker has not fought anyone of this quality #ParkerRuiz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three rounds to Ruiz. Parker has to get much more busy #ParkerRuiz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Louisemcire no I never whinged about that, I just stated it as a fact. It was true. The head of world referees said it was true and we won!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Louisemcire we say the ref was in your side, but we won anyway, we're not complaining about the refereeing like you are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annanibbles OMG that sounds like THE most amazing mashup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AsherGoldman @NZGreens oh fuck Asher. You're right. Who do we vote for now???!!! Is there a MORE leftist party?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annanibbles where is THIS!!!???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Louisemcire, Sam Cane Suspended, Aaron Smith? You were wrong and you are whingers.ðŸ‡®ðŸ‡ª lost even though the ref was clearly on your side]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ABs cop dud call, says refs boss @Louisemcire The HEAD of refereeing in the world said this!!!  https://t.co/N37mq9Tiwl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cane's OK, Read's not bad either @Louisemcire  https://t.co/nHtGfzJxep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Irish, rugby's new whingers @Louisemcire  https://t.co/GT6UbBw4zX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Louisemcire and it just wasn't look at the judiciary's decision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Louisemcire yeah but that just didn't happen. Listen to the judiciary's decision FFS! Whinge whinge. I swear you're as bad as the poms.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SineadQuealy @TheEconomist how is "spirit of play" in any way relevant to being the best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BriMcS @TheEconomist and Wales. Don't forget Wales]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McGivern2010 alot is not a word. And I'm the dimwit ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McGivern2010 @Louisemcire  if they were red card offences they would have been punished as such. The ref definitely favoured Ireland today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McGivern2010 @Louisemcire @Sivuman @AllBlacks ahh a football fan, don't watch a lot of rugby then? ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey guys those that are complaining about the reffing https://t.co/KDFODMLGNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McGivern2010  no chance!!! A yellow card for a high tackle. For what mitigating factor???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Louisemcire @McGivern2010 @Sivuman @AllBlacks who did? The man of the match?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McGivern2010 @Louisemcire @Sivuman @AllBlacks just the facts Louise. The penalties all went in your favour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well played @IrishRugby another valiant loss. A shame the boyos couldn't convert so many chances #IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McGivern2010 @Louisemcire @Sivuman @AllBlacks look at the scoreboard!!! Look at the scoreboard!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Louisemcire @Sivuman @AllBlacks gee you Irish get tetchy when you lose huh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Louisemcire Bias has definitely been FOR Ireland today not against them. Have dominated all the stats except the scoreboard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Louisemcire @Sivuman @AllBlacks TWO yellow cards. TWO. And still no Irish try]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Louisemcire @Sivuman @AllBlacks and they have been consistently penalised for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Louisemcire @Sivuman @AllBlacks no chance!!! A red card is for punching or eye gouging or a deliberate act if foul play]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Louisemcire just take off your eyepatch and watch again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Louisemcire the whole IRISH crowd ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Louisemcire @Sivuman @AllBlacks that's it two yellow cards an enormous penalty count against the @AllBlacks and yet you still complain!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Louisemcire no chance. Backwards from the hand. Fekitoa standing BEHIND Perenara. What game are you watching?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Definitely backwards and how good is Beauden Barrett #IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As soon as Perenara came on its been a different game. #IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[15 vs 15 again. Stop giving away penalties #IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So many penalties 2 yellow cards. Hard to win with such poor discipline #IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh OK. I like that change, two playmakers #IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No not Cruden. Barrett has been the @AllBlacks best #IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do they kick this??? #IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discipline terrible in this game. Great D too many penalties #IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great defence today @AllBlacks no trys yet by @IrishRugby this is tense, tight, a real test match #IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12 penalties @AllBlacks only 3 @IrishRugby need to settle this down #IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @AllBlacks are being outplayed again by @IrishRugby #IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lucky lucky lucky ðŸ€ @AllBlacks should have been a try]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's high and completely fair #IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aaron Smith is a liability out there. Bring on Perenara. #IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Knock on. Otherwise brilliant Beaudy #IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look like an early tackle on Squire #IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[15 vs 15 now, only 3 points on in Smith's absence. #IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joe Moody neck roll definitely a penalty lucky to not be another card. #IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still no tries for Ireland. Time to take control ABs #IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good scrum AB's good work @AllBlacks #IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do they scrum? Do they take the penalty?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surely Ireland have to score here! #IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sexton off, Smith in the bin, Cane off. Huge game #IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a brutal game for sure #IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One eyed for sure but hard to see a penalty there. #IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This plays into Ireland's hands, so frustrating last time with stoppages #IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rubbish penalty! How is that a penalty he hit him fair and at he chest. #IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_KitchenWitch fuck them, youse are so beautiful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_KitchenWitch that's balls. I am sorry that is happening]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just earned the 'Cheers To You! (Level 2)' badge on @untappd! https://t.co/TefZhVhcKE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just earned the 'Wheel of Styles (Level 8)' badge on @untappd! https://t.co/HqR3zZuxBK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bradleyzimmer suck that your office is back today. My wife gets TWO days off.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>