<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Really @RedCross ??? https://t.co/9zJvroJ9Q5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lyft Happy to be back!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Uber too little too late. You've made your stance. For me- it's never been "pleasant" being a customer of yours- I gladly #deleteuber]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Uber has always been a terrible company- unfair to its "partners" and "riders". Never on anyone's side but their own #deleteuber]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's completely erroneous and disrespectful that it's been 6 hours since I've placed my acct deletion request w/ @uber &amp; it's not deletedðŸ˜¡ðŸ˜¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fact that you have to request to #deleteuber shows just how horrible @uber really isðŸ˜¡ðŸ˜¡ðŸ˜¡ Put up a delete button and make it easy!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DNC Where were you? ðŸ˜¡ðŸ˜¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm donating and I pray more lawyers volunteer to help these cases-  https://t.co/s9t60bGJ2J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love this!! "No human being is illegal" - #resist #MuslimBan THIS. IS. WRONG. https://t.co/kkbPow9VBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Twitter then block the hate accounts who stand against them!! Help #resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Banning innocent people based on their religion is WRONG!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let the Hunger Games begin... https://t.co/gIyPOni9X4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is insane!! https://t.co/IqBa5eyxNE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this China? I guess this is what he meant by "America first" - Constitution, Freedom of Speech...life...secondðŸ˜¬ https://t.co/U0uAndTSd3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what #maga standing up for rights ALL HUMANS deserve &amp; globally leading by civil example. https://t.co/6FF16fu0cv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday THE PEOPLE showed leadership, not the leader.ðŸ˜† Sorry had to laugh about this- but it's not funnyðŸ˜³ it's quite sad #WomensMarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And this is your legacy... First impressions are everything #trumpadministration #trumpadministrationlies https://t.co/AWpTXzsUYD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To offer ppl money for their support (celeb) yet they came out in numbers FOR FREE in opposition to you- HA!ðŸ˜† #WomensMarch v. #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@businessinsider Um an episode of Narcos could've told you that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WomensMarchOnWashington Donate your unused metro cards!! Don't throw them away!! #WomensMarch https://t.co/G2oRE4Uaos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[âœŠðŸ¿âœŠðŸ¾âœŠðŸ½âœŠðŸ¼âœŠðŸ»âœŠ #womensmarch #strongertogether https://t.co/c7OaO1Dq4P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheAtlantic And this my friends is Propaganda 101]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ardell_Lashes like seriously- please tell me the replacement to #206]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ardell_Lashes why did you discontinue #206ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜© I am legit dying in @ulta WHYYYYYYYYY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FLOTUS No- thank you from the bottom of my heart! I now have to unfollow this account.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlaskaAir Your Alaska/Virgin mileage welcome email propagates a mileage number automatically- but produces error on submit? Help?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a huge fan of @marcorubio actually! Bravo! https://t.co/Sbp2D9ky55]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isn't the whole purpose of a background investigation is to prevent situations of blackmail #NeverTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a federal employee why does it seem like my background check was more thorough than @realDonaldTrump?? I'm not even at the highest level]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol @facebook (In my Mean Girls voice) "Stop trying to make 'Live' happen!" https://t.co/0FtuJPGb1k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thedailybeast @mtomasky Well if you want to destroy a country of course you eliminate the most obvious barrier!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MGMNatlHarbor Stayed at a MGM 3yrs ago, just signed up for card- couldn't win plays bc MGM automatically enrolled me in #mlife - not fair!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WTH @facebook IDC about ppl going live!ðŸ˜¡ðŸ˜¡ How do I turn this god awful feature &amp; the notifications off?? It's so lame and unwanted...grr!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a sliver of hope that the greater good may prevail today. #dec19th]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Uber_Support I kindly decline. I'd rather not follow a complaint protocol each time, that's disruptive &amp; it's a horrible cust. experience.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@uber It's not fair to riders. Period. I've watched drivers go in circles; yet I can't cancel bc I get charged. It wastes my time &amp; $$.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Uber I believe location services will prove ineffective. It's the drivers. They can be 100% clueless most of the time. Enforce knowledge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why aren't Americans more outspokenly outraged over the #russianhacking of the election?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Internet is slow again! Another Ddos attack?? This Russia hacking is getting scary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going for the #javascript30 - let's end this wretched year on a positive note!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DJNeekola you're changing the songs too fast. Everytime you vibe...vibe's over...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now Standing Rock needs to sue the pants off #EnergyTransferPartners &amp; #NDSheriffsdepartment for inhumane treatment #NoDAPL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[50 Retailers Were Named in a MASSIVE Anti-Trump Boycott https://t.co/T4LPTTfNoj via @TeenVogue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pamtaro @gotechnica Wasn't it amazing to witness?! I was so humbled myself to even be there and help these young brilliant women!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Code girls code!ðŸ¤“ðŸ’»ðŸ’ªðŸ¾ðŸ’…ðŸ¾ #Technica16 #womenintech @gotechnica https://t.co/utyLTXQEuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At @gotechnica and still going strong! Great ideas and talent from these young women #womenintech @UofMaryland https://t.co/l9uh4ZGL7v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gotechnica Excited to help mentor other #womenintech at @UofMaryland #technica16 this weekend!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Evernote, Evernote, @evernote Why the hell did I wait so long to jump on this wagon? Who cares- glad I did! #6yrsprocrastination #impressed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WixHelp Thanks for your response. It says we are using the "slide deck gallery" and that is not listed in the chart of gallery options?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WixHelp Hi,I turned on SEO widget &amp; now the alt text for img shows on slideshow.Workaround...besides removing alt text &amp; reducing SEO rank?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wix Hi I turned on SEO widget &amp; now the alt text for imgs shows on slideshow. Workaround...besides removing alt text &amp; reducing SEO rank?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@refinery29 Excellent strategy to get your message out! Offering licensed images with @getty ðŸ‘ðŸ‘ðŸ‘Œ I #SeeThe67  https://t.co/dAay4Rnpxl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nick_sibilla Hey! It's Lia from Street Boutique. I have a question for IJ on an issue that I am just now seeing gain traction- let's DM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheAtlantic I've always raised an eyebrow about this https://t.co/J17idkBlGB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cloud9IDE Thanks you guys are awesome!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cloud9IDE I'm patient...ETA when the site will be back up?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Noto- universal font will be unveiled by @google tomorrow #cantwait https://t.co/XvI9DtMtE7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am can do more scoring with my BF than the 49ers right nowðŸ’ðŸ¾ðŸ™„ ðŸ˜‚#AZvsSF #tnf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#tnf #AZvsSF @twitter I freaking love you guys for streaming live NFL games, as a Californian on the east coast...this is DOPEðŸ™ŒðŸ¾ðŸ™ŒðŸ¾ðŸ¤—]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These #nfl REFs!!!ðŸ˜¡ðŸ˜¡ðŸ˜¡ðŸ˜¡ðŸ˜¡ #AZvsSF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nfl #AZvsSF NFL is now "No Fun League" ... Taunting...give me a break!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Current Mood: https://t.co/CwlRzb8q8L #MondaysMadeBetter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GEICO_Service please- no! No one contact me I've just ended our 11yr relationship. So over #geico too late to be helpful now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GEICO Completely ridiculous that it's taking 20+ minutes to cancel. If you cared so much you should have respected my concerns before nowðŸ˜¡ðŸ˜¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How freaking awesome!!! https://t.co/OAuzpRBO8y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shmorgan85 I was just thinking about her and then I remembered this RT I did last week: https://t.co/GjkJMSoXCt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Airbnb I received your letter. What a positive, sustainable solution to a poisonous problem. I appreciate the sincerity &amp; implementationðŸ‘ðŸ¾]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Throwback The B.Coming + @BallersHBO this week= Yes! Just YesðŸŽ¶ðŸ™ŒðŸ¾ðŸ™ŒðŸ¾]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sandwich never smelled so goodðŸ˜‹ #joseandrespepetruck @JoseAndresFoods https://t.co/6Xp8AlYNeN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kaneshow I don't see the humor in that?? It's hip-hop culture. Oh wait- my bad bc everyone feels included in it these days "it's funny"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok, @Spotify you're right #discoverweekly does know me more than I know myself #impressed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LogMeIn @joinme What's up with your server requests?!? Been stuck here for a week now- no reset email arrivedðŸ˜¡ðŸ˜¡ https://t.co/X4NOOjYaJ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flying @Delta today- their professionalism &amp; attn. to detail puts @united to shame. Yesterday's experience was the worst! ðŸ™„ðŸ˜¡ #flydelta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@united The flight was 2 hours late. Everyone inconvenienced- Staff nonchalant. Super unprofessional! Ever thought of "on-call" employees?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@united Sitting on flight. Pilot never showed up- forced to get off plane. Boooo!! #fail ðŸ˜¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Entrepreneur #senatoralfranken, focus on #gunviolence in the state of Missouri, not Pokemon #publicresponsibilityfail #congressfails]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpotifyCares My account still says free. But my card was charged yesterday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wix Server 500 error when I try to pull up my account- support page is re-directing...need to do work on my site HELP!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Humans are humans. #StopTheHate It's time for real solutions to address systems that enable this behavior https://t.co/PHNh1yOL4g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the heck?!?! @Uber #dc https://t.co/dgxDIPYiwM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coolhunting @sofitukker I've been listening to this song all Spring- great share- all of their music+remixes rock!ðŸ’ƒðŸ’ƒðŸ’ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shmorgan85 @Airbnb tweet it to Airbnb. Would be nice if @Innclusive was more functional]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eatbasicburger Now this is loaded fries!!ðŸŸðŸŸ #nomnomnom https://t.co/YWnJWFjiey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hopper (2/2) Uncertain you got my message. Limbo is not fun...not a great UX. Thank god I'm not traveling &amp; need immediate assistance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hopper I already did so. As the message stated repeatedly while I was on hold. There are no autoresponders, or email acknowledgements (1/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hopper Great App. Your support is horrible :-/ #noonelikes30minuteholdtimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@311DCgov @DCDPW @DDOTDC @dcdmv or I'll Uber/Lyft. Which #DC civic authorities see $0 of that revenue. I guess that's what you'd prefer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@311DCgov @DCDPW @DDOTDC @dcdmv I am not calling anyone. Nor registering. I will simply stop spending my money in #DC this is very greedy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dcdmv @dcdpw Show your proof that I've indeed been parked for "30 consecutive days" This is a failed, flawed initiative #DC #ROSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dcdmv @dcdpw Every DMV, city/traffic authority has the power &amp; means to run a plate. This is unnecessarily extraneous #dc #civicfailure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dcdmv It's ludacris, that you're demanding me to waste my day to go to a #DC #DMV to show you I am not a resident.ðŸ˜¡ https://t.co/nAPPaxXMeY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DCDPW I appreciate it. Yes I frequent DC. This ticket flagged me for it? Should I no longer support DC businesses...I can stay in Arlington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is by far the dumbest #DC ticket I've ever received. It's clearly says VA tags- run a plate lazy pplðŸ˜¡ðŸ˜¡@DDOTDC https://t.co/irOe7KNJSM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bethanyflannery Just curious, do you know Jill Spaeth?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be thankful for any type of food, you are privileged to consume today: https://t.co/iqB3psLzVJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@18f This is pretty amazing! https://t.co/cESer2J8SV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DCFemTech Any women-owned agency on the 8A list or GSA schedule- DM me! The NSF is looking!ðŸ’ƒðŸ¾]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YASSSSSSSS! I hope they capture the show well
https://t.co/U9pfo2hx1Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ObsoleteDogma In regards to your article on Venezuela, do you know of any reporters on the ground there? How can you get supplies/money in?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ATLairport Whyyyyy does TSA have "are you ready for this?" On repeat today at sec??ðŸ˜’ðŸ‘ŽðŸ¾ #stop]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>