<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Dave Armstrong: Trump slaughtered the TPP dragon. Why won't Lefties applaud? https://t.co/2TnWx5q6IJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who was our worst ever Minister of Justice and Corrections?
https://t.co/dcz3aYpUI9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hudsie42 Agreed, though bear in mind that generally teams don't throw games, individuals try to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hudsie42 Imagine the odds on Bangla losing when they were 500 odd in the first innings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dave Armstrong: Don't leave sex education only to parents https://t.co/y2wjkSalMI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coming up 'Hard case 20th century pub quiz'. https://t.co/woy6Zxb9cz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dave Armstrong: It doesn't matter what kids read, as long as they do https://t.co/eT4G1fdS3W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheLazyWriter4 Possibly. Wowsers pretend to get drunk and break bottles so police and council will shut Sevens down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's that time of year where everyone meets in Wgtn for the annual 'Who killed the Sevens? inquest. 'Fun Police' or 'Drunken Hoons' or both?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How valid is that Maori person's argument? Get your Boagy Skin Tintometer from any Mad Butcher outlet - free with every load of tripe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Wellington I hate you.!" From Glide Time" by Roger Hall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not a good sign for the runway extension https://t.co/8X3j0ItyJl via @dpfdpf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wouldn't venus and julian vs artie and serena been a more interesting match? #sibiblingrivalry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep. A great broadcaster and her kakapo book is an absolute delight. https://t.co/K0oRy3DKhz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RFStew Perhaps an unseasonabiy large flock of native birds flew down from Nick Smith's electorate and polluted the water.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jetstar quits Wellington-Melbourne due to lack of demand. Longer runway anyone or shall we just subsidise another airline to come here?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so glad that the Cold War's over.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovely stuff from Denis Welch
https://t.co/wXsdFLFIJA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@five15design do not need crayfish when the rig at gutties is so good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dave Armstrong: The Basil Awards for 2016 https://t.co/iq6xVTpVLm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mwyp unless gareth brings in a LGBT  (Lego gains and benefits tax)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mwyp I'll stick to land banking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mwyp Yep. as for the meccano set I had god knows how many years ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewjsmith411 Make New Zealand Great Again could be a good slogan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CnrJoe And arctic ice has melted under their feet despite environmentally friendly diesel usage by Kiwi Rail and NZ Bus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Santa announces that sleigh will be diesel powered this year as it's more efficient and better for the environment. #yeahrightkiwirail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Richie's retired but we've got a great team and an easy test against Ireland coming up #natzeitgeistdec2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NCEA Blingish: How many errors can you spot in this headline? Housing Minister and Broadcasting Minister support Mt Albert Nat candidate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClintVSmith And a democratic political party would;ve consulted with Mt Abt branch. Tho I'm sure Joyce/Bennett/Brownlee etc were consulted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dave Armstrong: Time to park this failed experiment https://t.co/0p0WSf1BVj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking: Yay, Gerry retains Minister with Special Responsibility for Swearing on Television.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Resign 11? GK Brownlee Defenders: Smith Upston Shearer Cunliffe Midfield: McCully Lotu-Iiga Key Goff Fwds: Burrows Parata. Coach: Merrick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoForMayor maybe. Read on!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@craigireson No! Blingish. What is it about politicians who suddenly embrace social media only when their advisors tell them to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dave Armstrong: We learned a generation ago not to build piles of affordable housing in a hurry https://t.co/5ysqXhuyMK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent article. At the heart of it all - why you shouldn't privatise public facilities then expect private owner… https://t.co/JyAcfoPoU1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VictorianPurple So did I but not sure it takes long to get to Honolulu CBD from airport.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NCEA Maths: Johnny travels from Auckland to London then Paris. In which of the 3 cities will it take the longest to get from CBD to airport?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[English was Australia and Coleman and Collins were the NZ pace attack.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenRoss_AKL Whoever wins they'll be snoring to victory.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShakingStick @thomasbeagle Though would have every right to call election. Would be in similar position to Shipley after Winny stormed out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're all wrong about Collins. She would be an amazing (Labour caucus) unifier.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThomedySci @Knhannah Andrew Rodman Little]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nat MP most resembling Shipley says she can work better with Winston than Nat MP most resembling Bolger. #cloudCollinsland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting in learning how to write for television and web series at Victoria Uni? Applications close on Dec 10 
https://t.co/S64aZr2lut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking news: Donald Trump has contacted John Key and wished him welll for future. 'He is a man of whom all of Newfoundland can be proud']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@5WinstonSmith5 @mcquillanatorz And shrek and hobbits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MorganGodfery 'The reluctant keynesian fundamentalist']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a wit I am. https://t.co/8mF7bSuMZN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vincristine Have always believed he's harder right than he makes out and hates having to 'sell out' on soft centrist policy all the time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking: Key will vote for English as PM and Bolger as deputy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ellipsister Good point. Bill could work with Win, but Paula, Joycie or Collins?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's hard being a pundit. Once we convince all we knew Lab wld romp home in Roskill we have 2 explain we've known Key would resign for ages]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenRoss_AKL Managers are quite good if they manage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenRoss_AKL Will Bill English be the Jack Marshall of NZ politics?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Cameron, Hillary Clinton and John Key walk into a bar...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isn't Key resigning and endorsing English a bit like Kane Williamson throwing it in and endorsing Ross Taylor?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a well-kept secret. Only non-Mp who know was Nick Leggett. #keyresigns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toby_etc Making Kim Hill roving overseas RNZ ambassador to anywhere she wants until late 2017,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@stevenljoyce will be coaching the Phoenix. Someone's got to sort out the defence and the penalites' #PMpressconference]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does one call the Italian crisis? #ciaoeuro #italianjob #Renzexit #pastalavista?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CTrevettNZH @toby_etc I can't see the Woods, Woodhouse Wood for the trees.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brycepearce And notches on the satirists belt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JennyWi18628806 @transparency_a1 All Black victories?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@citizen_parable Absolutely. One of the few advantages of GST, which is essentiallly a flat tax.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pamcrawford2 @FoxyLustyGrover I should point out the satirists just love it when their satire is taken seriously.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a really good review of a really good book. https://t.co/a4Ni8kmufb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dave Armstrong: Let's catch tourism wave with a city levy  https://t.co/HoUOnykwxK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cameraman accidentally tapes publicity stunt : Result: RNZ offices raided. Massive abuse of children in state care. Result. Nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking: 'We need to get over it and move on. It was over 100 years ago and serves no practical use.' PM calls for abolition of Anzac Day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nmjyoung Bles$$ you my child. #religotourism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricCrampton @SirWB I blame polis making regs that didn't fix issues in mining and ag but made life hell for many others. #killerminigolf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClintVSmith @TheNationTV3 Everyone knows Lab polluted Wgtn water supply which brainwashed peeps to vote 4 candidates with housing policy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After the break, why Labour's massive lurch to the left and Little's leadership spooked 64% of the electorate into not voting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justin_lester Dasher Dancer Prancer and Lester.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael Wood gently tugs the pony-tail of all the smug politicos prediciting an easy Nat victory next year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remind me whose leadership this by-election is a referendum of?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["After losing Mana Leggett slated National as being too wet and out of touch with heartland NZ. Rumours abound that he may defect to ACT."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dave Armstrong: Just how 'walkable'  is our city? https://t.co/tTz0x6UIOS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking: Govt to set up disaster service to alert ministers to potential PR disasters. GerryNet is expected to be fully funded and run 24/7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dave Armstrong: While we're in crisis mode, let's solve state radio's funding shortfall https://t.co/koGhuZ3f2A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tax cuts still on the table despite Kaikoura, Nat Radio, Women's Refuge, growing poverty, inequality, underfunded DHBs, schools in need ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tmurphyNZ @NZMorningReport Is the survey online tim?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Jamie_Scott And let's not forget the massive untaxed capital gains certain liberal churches make on all their land. They are truly blessed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sits vact: Geology teacher for Destiny Charter School. Must have quals in creation, pestilence, &amp; lewd homosexual acts. No BSc's please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Yeah nah, The Geonet guys can't afford to work weekends cos they cost 2 much but we give big tax breaks to Brian Tamaki for his good work.']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@secondzeit @edmuzik @tmurphyNZ True but not inconceivable for Peters to hit 15% of popular vote and hold balance of power.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dave Armstrong: A decent salary for making important decisions https://t.co/kWEVWX6fUq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArthurMeek Even messier than usual. even C's feather duster displaced in lounge. J very disturbed but not farting ... yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FELT Report . Things all over floor in office. Boxes, pens etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@flyerskies1 @CircaTheatre Cheers Anthony. Glad you enjoyed. You are obviously a man of great taste!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last night of Central tonight. book now@ https://t.co/kZfqz8qgsq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Terrific mix of erudite writing and emotional tension" Only 4 more performances of Dave Armstrong's Central to go. https://t.co/fSwQPBpF5w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dale_Warburton The tyranny of a Friday deadline. Phoenix win, All Blacks lose.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marksparkdaly Cheers Mark, no I haven't read it. Will check it out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dave Armstrong: Progress in war on drugs won't come by locking more people up https://t.co/y86y4etYdd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['sizzling denouement' Theatre Times reviews Central.
https://t.co/qz6hl0Efra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dave Armstrong: Breath-testing, death-testing checkpoints  https://t.co/A3PiavKadJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrickmorgan @metlinkwgtn Will try that one in summer. Another goody is train to Petone, along the river to Upper Hutt, then train home.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 fantastic speeches from 2 fantastic aussie unionists. #riphelenkelly]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>