<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@amyandcolour Bawl-ton. Or Bowl-ton. That's how everyone in Linenhall says it anyway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 episodes in to Peaky Blinders and I'm hooked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alensejkic that's exactly what I thought... like I was hoping it's "fake news" cause that sort of carry on is dangerous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stellar try from George North! Think he may have aggravated his injury though with that run #RBS6Nations #ITAvWAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wouldve been interesting if Italy actually managed to keep ahead and win. Would make for an interesting six nations #RBS6Nations #ITAvWAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think Italy lost their lustre after Wales got a few panalties. Heads dropped and Wales got two tries after 60 minutes #RBS6Nations #ITAvWAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lot of hard work put in for that try but Italy really deserved it! #RBS6Nations #ITAvWAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jones and North getting seen to 5 mini into the game ðŸ˜³ #RBS6Nations #ITAvWAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know this is real but it seems so surreal... https://t.co/PKa0BrloRc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fearganainm because money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some real flare from France in this game. Great to see #RBS6Nations #ENGvFRA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bolandjohn3 shite play altogether]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ireland had the opportunity to get a bonus point and start off the Six Nations good and work on winning a grand slam...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy to see Scotland play well and win but not at our expense #SCOvIRE #RBS6Nations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jackson is playing a blinder #RBS6Nations #SCOvIRE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great stuff from Earls #RBS6Nations #SCOvIRE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was just laziness. Letting in soft tries #RBS6Nations #scovire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the fuck is going on? #SCOvIRE #RBS6Nations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really wish I was in Edinburgh today! #RBS6Nations #scovire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whelan_cian @Kearnflakes that is sickening haha Town is just a no go zone cause of the Luas works]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I saw a Guinness Rugby poster on my way to college and words cannot describe how excited I am for Saturday! ðŸ‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love when the Guinness Rugby ads start creeping back on to tv coming up to the Six Nations. It's like the Coca-Cola truck ad at Christmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kearnflakes a 13km journey for me takes about 45mins to 1hr. In London a 23km journey would take me 25mins....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Considering every other news story or tweet is about Donald Trump...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I usually hate when news websites scrape a story out of a funny poster in a shop or something stupid but it's kinda refreshing now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know how I am going to put up with four years of Trump's administration doing stupid things and everyone complaining about them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lauren_mcentee at least you don't have 4 months to find a full time job ðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dillon_O_Neill can you bring a bag with you? Just say you had to do something before or whatever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love how the media mention that there's gonna be a Penneys in a proposed shopping centre but they won't mention the building designers...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@farmer12994 you're just a sound guy. Probably made the door's day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fargo_Farrell it was brilliant all the same]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fargo_Farrell it was hard to stomach, I saw a play of it in Edinburgh. The smell of Bovril stuck with me for the night]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like the episodes of Black Mirror that are the most realistic/believable are the best]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The White Bear episode of Black Mirror blew my mind...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously not looking forward to going back to college on Tuesday to start my last semester... https://t.co/iyw3pCFvzG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ciaratheimpaler ahh grand. Sorry, in that case no I didn't see anyone in the public crowd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ciaratheimpaler I meant on the dignitary side now, not the trump supporter side?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone else thing when Trump said "America first, America first..." followed by a pause that he was trying to start a chant? #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ciaratheimpaler yeah there were an odd few]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never thought in a thousand years that "your man from The Apprentice" would've been president of the United States]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I remember watching Obama's inauguration and I was stunned (in a good way) but I'm even more stunned watching Trumps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope Ryan Gosling in La La Land sparks a new trend of people wearing suits all the time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thought this was a parody account for a minute https://t.co/vMwfTgnDLr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@archicathal even though there's no need to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@archicathal I only started it yesterday so I'm on season two. I've watched bits of season three already but I'm watching it in order]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dream https://t.co/zn1DSYEhE0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or maybe I'm reading too much into it...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black Mirror is like a modern day Aesop's Fables.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanimusPr1me it's a good show. Some of the themes are a bit heavy haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first episode of Black Mirror is grim...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanananbatman I know how thick I get when I see people stoping security to rummage for their liquids. So I pre pack mine to be sound]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanananbatman I always pre pack my liquids in a clear ziplock so I just have to walk through security not hassle. Just a tip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wizanyay it truly is a blessing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ciaratheimpaler @todayfm that is actually sickening]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sale vs Toulon was a cracking match! #ChampionsCup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marktallshort yeah, England in Lansdowne is ideal. With the travelling and the home crowd Ireland will do well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marktallshort if we want to beat England then I reckon a grand slam is in order]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marktallshort England are the team to beat this year I reckon. If everyone underestimates them they'll get steamrolled]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You certainly wouldn't miss Sale Sharks anayway... ðŸ¦ˆâš«ï¸ðŸ”´ #TLNvSAL #ChampionsCup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marktallshort same ðŸ˜³it's gonna be an interesting series this year if the autumn internationals were anything to go by.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marktallshort yeah BOD said it just there. It's not pretty to watch but it's effective. Should've got the laptop out for Scarlets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marktallshort snapping I didn't watched it. I opted for Clermont Bordeaux... sloppy, dull stuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just watched Seige of Jadotville, billiant film surprised it wasn't seriously hyped up in the media. An amazing true story as well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally a try courtesy of Saili! #GLAvMUN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Murray too some elbow there #GLAvMUN #ChampionsCup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wasps are back in it #WaspsST #ChampionsCup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tough to spot that Huget try. Ref didn't even hesitate to award it. Lovely play from Toulouse #WaspsST]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Highlight of the match last night https://t.co/vXQ9C69Pws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wasps and Toulouse fighting for second place in their pool makes for interesting rugby! #WaspsST]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ciaratheimpaler don't know how people can just smash glass and not give shite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ciaratheimpaler even when I'm in a building where there's no animals ever I always thing "ohh a dog or a cat might swallow that" pick it up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Leinster game was savage tonight! #LEIvMON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did a weird jazz step on the ice and now my knee is in a jocker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It started snowing as soon as I walked my dog and stopped as soon as I got back... got drenched in the meantime too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deanvannguyen I saw on Euronews today that they're advertising their neutral stance on global affairs. Maybe more outlets will follow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conomolan where are you off to? The airport to go to Trumps inauguration?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I saw a weather warning that I shared last year about snow. Didn't really happen then so I don't think it'll happen now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who made this?!?!?! https://t.co/nk03siW7S0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YourMa I still think either way you have to sign up to a "private" one. The company just offer the private one to you cause they have to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YourMa if you work for a U.K company they generally offer them because of the mandatory workplace pension in Britain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fearganainm it seems such a juvenile thing to do. Like when you did something wrong as a kid but ignored it so you won't get in trouble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fearganainm I don't know, everything just seems like a mess in general]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Than investing money in some curtain that makes booze disappear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like I know excessive drinking is a problem here but surely the money would be better spent on health services/school education programs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read about the whole motion to hide alcohol in shops. I thought the government would know that hiding something doesn't solve a problem?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016 being a horrible year just isn't confined to 2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm spending my Sunday reading about Irish and U.K. construction  law... probably wouldn't have to if Brexit didn't happen...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only saw it there, absolutely stellar stuff from Munster this evening #MUNvR92]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_M_egg like mine is a fecking mouthful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_M_egg I found writing my thesis that you can't using anything remotely funny or abstract. It has to be painfully to the point and clear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Singing wrap songs or John Snow reading a news report about the years biggest hit or Charles Dance in general haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love when the Big Fate Quiz of Everything/The Year do stuff with otherwise traditional groups/people. Like the London Philharmonic Choir]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wizanyay you were wrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lauren_mcentee @Independent_ie could have just said they were deliverin a "salad" would have been less conspicuous cause no one likes salad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlisonSpittle I stopped reading it over plagiarism allegations (material taken from freelance journalists) but this takes the biscuit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rosariee_ no, blanchardstown is corduff and blanchardstown village supposedly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rosariee_ in some cases mulhuddart might be accepted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rosariee_ his address is actually in Clonsilla]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conomolan what are they doing it slowly so planners don't notice?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A few letters are missing above the old The Quill pub in town. Kinda looks like vandals are slowly trying to turn it into "tequila".]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>