<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@CiaraNiFhloinn I'd just like to reiterate the importance of an overall approach when facing the challenges of increased workloads.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harris is a weasel who is committed to privitisation. His politics inevitably leads to disaster when it comes to health care access. #cblive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This programme is reminiscent of I, Daniel Blake - a damning indictment of a government with a disregard for its people. #RTEInvestigates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tvcritics @ger_mccann @SimonHarrisTD And deflect the blame and make it look like we as a society have a problem to deal with, but not him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our government prioritises appeasing tax dodging multinationals over investing to make its health service fit for purpose. #RTEInvestigates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[James Reilly lying to the public on RTÉ news in 2015. Two years on, nothing has changed. Shameful. #RTEInvestigates https://t.co/oE4nmhfaMr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simon Harris will talk about collective responsibility &amp; maybe blame mgmt in HSE. What he won't do is accept responsibility #RTEInvestigates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gastro_Celtic That robana though...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great win by Monaghan and the perfect way to start 2017 after a disappointing summer. #monaghan #AllianzLeagues]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We may not have the big things" says the woman in the Liberty Insurance ad who has a spacious house and a car.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taxidermists are about as interesting as taxidriverists #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tubridy is pretty smug towards Russian athletes given Ireland's record of drug cheating at the Olympics.  #druggyhorses #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This guy just keeps on going. We know what you did in government. We saw it happen. It was only about a year ago. https://t.co/aTehVioy6O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AodhanORiordain @gocleircin @detlin808 Oh Aodhán - searching twitter for your name again? 😂😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Schroedinger99 The thought of having to cross two EU borders to go to school/ the shops is crazy. Haha - I just di… https://t.co/rvBD5YvM5I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's the Drummully Polyp - it's quite unique, I can't think of any examples like it. https://t.co/KcYIwx6BgV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stephen Donnelly when SocDems falls apart and they all follow into Fianna Fail after him. https://t.co/RYfegSjWzl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@detlin808 @gocleircin Aodhán O'Riordain - sure didn't he make a brave speech against Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[😂😂😂 Look at your darling now, liberal Ireland. 😂😂😂 https://t.co/x8vJjSktAQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DublinFilmFest Is 'I am not your Negro' sold out?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's happened again. https://t.co/QfZAoiKrB9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm necking bottles of Cavan Cola today - it tastes rancid but I'm doing my bit. #boycottUSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colm Tobin and Donal O'Keeffe. These men are angry at Trump and are busy writing virtuous tweets so you can understand their fury. #liberals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Serious https://t.co/O1aMLQwhGN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intergalactic Gary tonight... Hoping for the like of this. https://t.co/5RImljeuik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Philomena Cunk can bring Eurovision glory to the UK #EurovisionYouDecide]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Claire Byrne has a simple question this evening, now watch as Leo Varadkar does what he does best and not answer it. #cblive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Edwina Curry thinks she speaks for the working-class of northern English. Oh dear. #Marian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markgkeane Conor Hourihane has been the best midfielder in England (with the exception of Ngolo Kante) the past year but does O'Neill care?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markgkeane What does Ryan Manning have to do to get a game? O'Neill hasn't a clue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which makes you question if it is appropriate for Tommie Gorman to push his own agenda on the news of the national broadcaster.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm far from a Sinn Fein supporter but it's worth noting that Tommie Gorman would never speak about a Unionist politician in that manner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DublinFilmFest Can I buy a pass for multiple films or anything like that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go on Istomin - nearly there. #australianopen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are the general public really as right wing as thejournal.ie comments section would lead one to believe? 🤔🤔🤔]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Yahynzy Really interesting. It's kind of like a football Miracle on 34th street with Ally McCoist in the role of Kris Kringle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AtBirdTwoSwims @LovinDublin He'd write a piece about how single mothers ruined his sea view brunch in Ringsend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They even tried to use it as clickbait. Standard lovindublin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And there we have it. A video which has a central message about discriminating attitudes towards the working class… https://t.co/ruLk9Xm5PT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to lovindublin/Harbo inevitably sharing Emmet Kirwan's latest video and not seeing any contradiction.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I expected Dundalk to kick on &amp; dominate for next few years. Not a lot they can do to hold on to talent but they are a lot weaker this year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conor Clifford was a Boreham Wood sub recently. Good luck to him getting back on track but Dundalk aren't making hay with the UEFA money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Needlessly epic but great song. https://t.co/4iRjs1e2NM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#OurYear https://t.co/qVV3MrCIPc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rovers shaping up very nicely to lose 3-2 for about the 10th time this season. #BlackburnRovers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes @DavQuinn, you should be worried about the 'hard left'. They'll ensure sexist bigots like you will be challenged https://t.co/ZahBgGAAtb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TommyTiernanShow was popular last week because it wasn't the Ray Darcy Show. This week's first guest.. Ray Darcy. Sigh, where's the remote?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PTHosford Your correct to an extent but no socialist wants to see people earning sums like £250,000 a year, never mind a week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PTHosford A socialist model of football would be salary caps, reduced ticket prices, no transfer market and replacing it with a draft.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PTHosford There's nothing socialist about footballers' earning £250,000 a week - it's lunacy. You're well off the mark here Paul.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AgentDave_ Translation- "Heading to my Mum's frontroom this weekend to watch a stream of the football on my sister's laptop. Should be fun"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wasn't it Richard Boyd Barrett who starred opposite Meryl Streep in the River Wild?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tony Cuddihy from Joe.ie 'You won't believe what this Irish lad said about Neo-Nazis' #cblive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a really shit debate. #CBLive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I wrote it"
"The sub-editor wrote it"
Nick Pell took less than a minute to show himself to be a complete moron. 
#CBLive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I agree with no platforming. Nazis had a platform before and we know how that went. Also, no platform for Brenda Power just because. #cblive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next time someone says 'loony left' or 'fantasy left economics' ask them to justify the examples of capitalism raised here. #selloff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice to see Johnny Logan get a mention. https://t.co/lLqUgENlHJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Classic Simon Harris move, deflecting responsibility away from his and his party's failures. https://t.co/u2mJ5LHIq3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ffskennz A little from column A...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be fair this is actually an interesting discussion. #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm trying to stay off the gargle and out of pubs for January but Ryan Tubridy is making it hard. #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like something from the kid's news programme.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a boring interview this is - it seems to be pitched for an audience who have never heard of Donald Trump. #latelateshow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheKavOfficial Whereas Ian O'Doherty on the other hand is...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT'S HAPPENED AGAIN. https://t.co/GIm2kLDyR8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LolaKicks Either way, the documentary made for grim viewing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LolaKicks Aye. Tbf I wasn't saying anything about Leitrim - more the people involved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LolaKicks Why not? There was art class, dance, sport, performance art (stripping) and more besides. It felt like an afternoon at the Louvre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cultural tour de force. The Florence of the North West. #CarrickOnStag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CarrickOnStag https://t.co/8CGSEucZ6w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jomograd Boom! Tickets in the bag. The Belfast show is already sold out!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zaza is leaving West Ham early. Funny how his career at West Ham is encapsulated by his penalty just before joining. https://t.co/FJ7iKAYcm9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brought in Eriksen, made him captain, points in the bank. #OurYear #FantasyFootball https://t.co/2eJ9XojdQB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shane Duffy doing what he does best - scoring against Blackburn Rovers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[O'Riordain was right to ask why Ian O'Doherty was on but he gets plenty of airtime himself for a man who couldn't get elected in a 5-seater.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Luckily I missed #CBLive last night, it sounds like it was the live version of TheJournal.ie comments section.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[boards of canada - roygbiv https://t.co/glqLSX1kRM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bertie, we've had decades of your opinions and the conclusion most people have come to is that you are a crook. Can you just go away now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does anybody know why the mainstream media are so keen to rehabilitate Bertie Ahern. Top story on Today FM news today is an opinion he gave.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tubridy explained. https://t.co/hyd6jBC5RY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Ah Christmas, not the time to be thinking about Bord Gáis Energy."

Who thought this ad was a good idea? An ad that people could relate to?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRobsonator93 Right on cue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRobsonator93 Yeah he's on the bench. Wouldn't be surprised if he was misbehaving behind the scenes - he has form.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRobsonator93 There's still an equaliser in this - Anthony Stokes off the bench I reckon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That time Mr. Mulvaney misjudged the office Secret Santa. https://t.co/nyHjSaPGOb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You've got to sweeten the man."
One year ago today.
Hughie McElvaney.
Timeless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something not quite right about this. https://t.co/e7UBYKDs0Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jacknealonspub Hi Jack Nealons, I was thinking of coming in for the quiz this evening - does it start after the football?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a helicopter low hovering around Stoneybatter/Phibsboro/Glasnevin all afternoon. Anybody know what's going on?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see the Liverpool we all know and love return to action this afternoon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tubridy is struggling out there IMO. He resembles a Butlin's redcoat trying to drum up enthusiasm from a bewildered crowd. #LateLateToyShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bglendenning And I just stuck a tenner on Forest who for some reason were priced at 11/2 in the bookies at half time. GAME ON.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/hng43XFHab Exclusive report on the Virgin Mary appearing in Limerick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeterBradshaw1 It'd be nice if you sent me some of those films that arrived Peter, the ones that you have already seen. Cheers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Richard M. Pender's Christmas window display returned to Stoneybatter this morning after two years. T'wud warm even the coldest of hearts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice review but the band only lost their hold of the crowd because the venue is a dump and loads of people couldn't… https://t.co/oJqlEaqfSu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very good fun at the @hindsband gig tonight... pity the venue wasn't great but still a very enjoyable show.  https://t.co/oR7OYI6Ioa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great day for the parish. #stoneybatter https://t.co/oNjIoU6RLu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When u can't move on because you refuse to accept it's over. https://t.co/jVl71xFTE7]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>