<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@EXYUaviation why do they continue to go to London over dublin?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dublinbusnews 83a at stop 1618 just drove byb3 passengers with their hands out at 21.16 with the driver clearly not giving a shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EXYUaviation any new routes going to be announced from osijek?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RascalsBrewing if you happen to have 2 passes to alltech id happily take them instead and buy your beer there ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RascalsBrewing how many are left?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beerhousedublin @RascalsBrewing @thebeernut @Sean_Conlan bah, can you tap her now? I'll come if you do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RascalsBrewing @Sean_Conlan @beerhousedublin @blacksheepdub is it on yet at either?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onthebackpage please get a few kegs of Vacuum Boogie by @RascalsBrewing in. Its so fresh its a crime not to. Excellent beer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irishbeerdog review some beer you fecker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OHarasBeers @HomebrewClubIrl I'll talk to you again april 18 then. Can't wait for that hoppy taste.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OHarasBeers @HomebrewClubIrl so you will stand by its quality in April next year i presume]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OHarasBeers are you doing 18/24months for BB? For a dry hopped pale ale? Jasus! @HomebrewClubIrl https://t.co/BZX6xG2OyM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lostinskylines @galwaybeer @whitehagbrewery some of the best breweries in the world are there...........]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeavertownBeer @BeerRambler very small serving size!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EXYUaviation any zagreb dublin flights in talks?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EXYUaviation wtf? Why this route? Anymore osijek routes rumoured?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@inizzagip @GatwickExpress @Gatwick_Airport how busy was it Michaela?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@John_Kavanagh he must have been wearing a towel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EXYUaviation surely they will have sold all those flights already &amp; its not going to help them assess the demand as xmas is different]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EXYUaviation are we likely to see any dublin to osijek flights next year ftom ryanair or croatian airlines?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Urban0yster anyway to avoid the shipping price ie collection option?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LightHouseD7 no frozen sing along this year :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thebeernut in a good way? Its an great cider!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MMAjunkie what happened with the update of the app on Android. It hasn't worked since.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@icbshow @chopandbrew @YouTube where is his episode from brewcon 2016 in ireland???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thewasherwoman1 @majakristek usually the online menus aren't acurate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fraz1001 @Tom_Noc @SevereMMA @UFCFightPass Yeah but we aren't given the option to pay for it. virgin customers cant get bt sports!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SecondCaptains that was a truly terrible piece on mcgregor yesterday. The 'journalist' you had on was a disgrace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MMAFighting @shaunalshatti how does buffer not know that's a majority draw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kenearlys not staying up for ufc205?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kenearlys have you read john kavanaghs book yet? Any opinion? Looking forward to the sports book of the year pod #sorryitsnotabouttrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@northerncuisine well that could have been said a few days ago]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shane_ltfc @WYFC @WexfordYouthsFC wow you got me there!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shane_ltfc @WYFC @WexfordYouthsFC ha says the man with a profile pic of drinking alcohol illegally in a car!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dublinbusnews ah the ghost bus just arrived!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dublinbusnews stop 181, when is the next 83. It dissappeared with 8min to go and not another for 17min now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eric_heilig @KevinAherneChef @northerncuisine @GavinDonagh I emailed yesterday and no reply...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@northerncuisine where's the tickets?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewmcgahon_ fair play. You will be a success. Enjoyed the podcast and interviews for a long time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarryProf either do I want them. Where does it stop, should every item for consumption have a warning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NovaRunda just the weekend. We will be bacl for xmas and staying in zagreb for 1 night 30th dec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NovaRunda its awesome. Hides the alcohol well, a proper IPA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NovaRunda if it is available i will]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NovaRunda i hear there is a beer festival in osijek this weekend. I will be in osijek the 21st weekend. I hope there will be kegs left over]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Celticwhiskey @57theheadline @Upstairsat57 enjoying the gin! @Daniellelong88 https://t.co/UFDrOhMOGt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@57theheadline @gg_pizza thanks guys. Great beer and pizza https://t.co/mw8ZEO5qQz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dublinbusnews great! Ive been waiting at the stop since you sent that! What are all of these operational issues?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dublinbusnews it says 25min for the next  us on the app]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dublinbusnews another gigantic wait for the 83 at stop 181,whats the story?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dublinbusnews it would have been better to  operate the 6.50 instead of the 7.00. Now you have the 7.00  and 7.10 just a few minutes apart!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dublinbusnews whats up with the 83 route this morning over 30min wait from 7am at the 181 stop? Bus leaving every 10min my arse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeerPadawan @jokekoky @RossaONeill @irishbeersnob it isn't fair to the little good breweries to give terrible breweries nice reviews.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irishbeersnob what do you think is the worst irish craft beer?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TruCraft_IE @IndBrewing im trying to make them homonyms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TruCraft_IE @IndBrewing your all idiots, its one of the true awful beers out there #suckups]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@metalmanbrewing are you just using your own beers then? :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShaneSmith_ @IndBrewing you shitting me, its rank!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone any suggestions for the best European beer festivals in Q1/Q2 of 2017?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I take it at this stage there will be no london osijek winter route? @Ryanair @EXYUaviation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishBeerFest plastic glasses and rip off prices, last year cuming here https://t.co/U4aQlYSOT9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@norman_parke @MMARoasted sure just tout a bunch of tickets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@57theheadline ditch gin sounds gross]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryanair when will the stansted - osijek winter scedule be up for sale?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@basquelandbrew we are in san sebastian now, where can we go to get your beer?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kenearlys man he was so drunk/high at the start i thought it was going to be terrible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryanair when will the london-osijek winter scedule be added to the site]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@basquelandbrew any other suggestions for good places to drink?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EoinMcDevitt @saveciaranmurph eoin again ruining more of talented mr. Ripley again this week, this time hockey scenes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@basquelandbrew any brewery tours to be done?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@big_ern12 @billburr what are the drink options like?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GerTGWTC @billburr what time did he come on stage at?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@big_ern12 @billburr what time did he come on stage?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyanCullen90 @billburr what time did he come on stage?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billburr an example of some of the dickheads who got your tickets and others like myself are without #billburrows https://t.co/XAzw13JtkH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SevereMMAPod @andrewmcgahon_ i am and want a naked one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EXYUaviation really strange the winter scedule for london-osijek isn't out yet.  Any idea why?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@basquelandbrew we will be in San sebastian for 3 nights 18-21st of August, bilbao for 1 night 22-23rd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@haloheadbanduk can i buy your headbands anywhere in ireland?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nonlinearsoft just sent you one playing from a download]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vineyardltd strange question mayhe but would you consider a group buy? A bunch if us in dublin would be interested.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vineyardltd Cheers, my missus just bought 4 of the Imperial browns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the best public water fountain ive seen in dublin @DubCityCouncil https://t.co/47IQuHJpoA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chopandbrew where is the dublin episode?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RapSheet wow Americans don't really care about drug cheats, 4 game ban?!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nonlinearsoft nope, ill try play some downloads and send a report]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nonlinearsoft screen is off yes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@basquelandbrew hey guys, we are visiting san sebastian and bilbao next month. Finding it hard to get info on craft beer places/breweries]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nonlinearsoft let me know if you want any more. Happens every pod i play.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nonlinearsoft I just reported it and sent the email.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nonlinearsoft middle of the podcast streaming or playing a downloaded version. Happening last few months]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nonlinearsoft hey guys love the app but it at least once per listen it will just stop playing even though im not interacting with my phone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vineyardltd cool, going to be visiting next weekend. Any chance of getting in the Imperial brown, its something special]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vineyardltd what kernel beers do you have?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryanair no answer?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kenearlys @danjbrady @SecondCaptains dismount and walk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EXYUaviation are london osijek winter flights going ahead for this winter?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryanair when will the london-osijek winter scedule flights be available to book?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ufc fucking horrible, worst event ever to trial it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arielhelwani @mcconnellj its fucking horrible, my eyes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishRail no help at the station, they said to go back to where you bought them?!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>