<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The privilege and power of the police and county justice dpt is staggering and frightening #Netflix #MakingAMurderer #Wisconsin #Manitowoc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@huwr Their batshit is less crazy than Aus sometimes... but Canada is less cray AND their visas are cheaper. We're mugs #immigration #aupsol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking into Canadian visas as we speak.  Sick of this bollocks #auspol #Trump #TurnbullMalcolm #Trudeau https://t.co/Cq377kZwF3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shut up, stop that critical thinking, you bleeding heart SJ types: our deputy PM. #InvasionDay #NotMyAustraliaDay

https://t.co/bVBBEfPVmN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never forget what this day represents. 
#InvasionDay #AlwaysHasBeen #AlwaysWillBe #NgunnawalLand #NeverForget… https://t.co/RsaBDTzaIh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck off, @Barnaby_Joyce. *Median house price*. Includes Mt Druitt,  Richmond, Blacktown. Not just Mosman. #auspol 

https://t.co/NgOtKbWPD9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So far, parenting seems to be mostly just sending each other funny pictures we've taken of our child and laughing at her facial expressions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaoTunq You seem to have a lot of opinions. A bit of actual knowledge might stand you in good stead to be listened to in future.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can only assume @DavidLeyonhjelm has been trawling Twitter looking for mentions &amp; blocking ppl. Glad he's keeping busy over summer. #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How I know I'm doing well in my leftist, feminist quest for a better, more progressive Australia #auspol… https://t.co/Xndc07RDO8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wtf is actually happening in #auspol today?? Is it the heat?? #Leybye #Leybuy #OneNation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ecec #earlychildhood #skilled #sjiec #TheProjectTV https://t.co/65NKKmkeoS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obviously Leyonhjelm missed out on crucial brain dev b4 5 years old, but he shouldn't stop others from receiving quality care and education]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$800k apartment is not an impulse buy. A box of Smarties at the checkout is an impulse buy. @sussanley is so far from average Aussie #Leybuy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baby wearing at North Beach, #Wollongong on New Years Eve #babywearing #illawarra #visitnsw #cloudy #nye2016 https://t.co/oNdgfoae07]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy New Year. Catching up on #2016PubQuiz on @abciview with the family. @TomTilley's chiseled jaw is a thing of beauty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't think of anywhere I'd less like to be than at the shops today #BoxingDay #shopping #capitalism https://t.co/cdobmNpAyv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Patrickavenell It's socially acceptable to start drinking as soon as you wake up on #Christmas!! 😊 #Cheers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No tweets for a while. Have been busy learning to parent a tiny babby, born shortly after my last tweet. Merry Xmas… https://t.co/7kQVtF8Qzt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving this montage but not the music #insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh the awkward horror of Pyne and Marles #insiders #mattpricemoment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't. Unsee. Christiansen. Photo. #whip #insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@murpharoo always has the most amazing shoes!! That's why they always put her in the front chair, so we can admire… https://t.co/TgTinrIBsJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rabbitandcoffee Huw Parkinson has outdone himself... that was stupendous. #insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think it's time for many of us to admit that... #insiders https://t.co/tjx3SysYfK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul would've fucking loved to be a part of this. #CrowdedHouseLive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish I tuned in earlier. But Distant Sun is my very favourite, so at least I got to see that. #CrowdedHouseLive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blerg. Rather than listen to Cormann's monotone, I am going to get ready for my post-insiders Galentines brunch date! #insiders #galentines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KelMayo Really???!! You'd better not be yanking my chain. I might cry. #insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh no I had a feeling this was the last episode 😢😣😦😕 #insiders https://t.co/170qRSfYIy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice Seinfeld reference in next week's @triplejHack ad. Watch a few of those episodes to know that dating has ALWAYS been complicated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the best thing I've ever seen #talkingpictures #insiders https://t.co/nSnREeRj38]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[18C is talked about constantly by The Australian &amp; the Liberal Party. NOBODY ELSE cares, except to report on this fascination #insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen to the rest of the panel, Stutch. Stop singing the praises of low corporate tax - so many companies in Aus get around it #insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backpackers aren't coming over here to make a mint picking fruit. They're doing it for an adventure, to supplement their holiday #insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How many of your fucking children or grandchildren are picking fruit, @TurnbullMalcolm???!! #insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just last night I was chatting at a party about how The Herd's track "77%" is still so relevant and how fucking depressing that is #insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cathywilcox1 But then we realize that the brown people have jobs and white people don't.... INJUSTICE!! Privilege imbalance!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop fucking demonizing 457 workers. Most of them do shitty jobs that Australians reckon they're too good for.  #insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She always seems like she wants to be SHOUTING EVEN LOUDER but is barely reigning it in... I'm scared #insiders https://t.co/rNaEfuJw1p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The "double dipping" rhetoric has made ppl policy toxic &amp; uninformed voters are of the opinion that it's bad #insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love the word "feckless" in politics #auspol #insiders https://t.co/wDWasHm8Pt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[30% corporate tax rate, and yet we have all these multi national companies paying hmmmm NOTHING in tax?? How does that work?? #thedrum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Albo point of order: "On weirdness..." #insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not allowing bigots to say whatever they want is not a "crook law", it's fucking justified #insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop equating centre-right with "sensible".  "Sensible" is subjective. It does not mean what you think it means. @TonyAbbottMHR  #insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty sure most of us have changed some of our opinions in the last 25 years, Henderson #paulkeating #gulfwar1 #insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would be interested to know the percentage breakdown of talk time on today's #insiders - seems like Hendo is talking an awful lot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business people don't automatically make excellent politicians. Case in point: Turnbull #Trump  #insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe they should've made a booking...? #insiders #sarcasm #omfg https://t.co/JZNi4A8ZRg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barrie: "You could argue it's not unlawful to seek asylum" BECAUSE IT ISN'T!! OMG stand up to Hendo, Barrie, he's fking INCORRECT! #insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The beat-ups of visa rorts make my English hubby's life a fking nightmare as we have to repeatedly prove our relationship is real #insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because "trickle-down" principles always work. /sarcasm  #insiders #ciobo https://t.co/K5pyyhof6U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We love foreign people coming to Straya - as long as they don't want a job #ciobo #immigration #backpackertax #insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And no further discussion other than in relation to Trump? Central Western farmers have issues that run deeper than… https://t.co/oEXDzVMTIc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why ask Hendo about Turnbull being banned from Mardi Gras??! He will not give an understanding or sympathetic opinion #insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huge swing towards Shooters-Fishers-Farmers in #OrangeVotes but hardly surprising #nswvotes #auspol #insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia will always be America's lap dog #auspol #insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shame, Fraser, shame
#november11 #1975 #dismissal #whitlam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America has today told us they would prefer a misogynistic racist with money to a qualified woman with political experience #Election2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the fucking shit is going on, USA?? You got some serious explaining to do... #electionday #electionnight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Journalist: "Senator Roberts, just a question about something real -"
Roberts: "My home planet needs me"
#auspol… https://t.co/THARyqYtjP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've just discovered that @Lindt discontinued their Peanut Butter truffles earlier this year. WHY WASN'T I CONSULTED?! #devvo #crushed #sad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Malcolm Roberts doing Incy Wincy Spider? #ecec #EarlyChildhoodEducation #bigsteps #auspol https://t.co/h356KlpowB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do Americans want someone who isn't a politician doing the work of a politician? Why do they dig the unqualified angle?? #insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bob Dole looks like a prehistoric man that was frozen in an ice cave for ten thousand years, then dug up &amp; trotted out by the GOP #insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeftyMatt It still sounds horrifying when she says it. #insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People keep asking if Turnbull is "Abbott Lite" because he's not defined himself as anything else #insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indigenous Affairs??? Really? Oh heaven help our First Peoples #insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Susan Ley keeps a fixed gaze on Malcolm Turnbull as he speaks at the presser, willing him to not say anything stupid #insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@damienpbuckley Just sneaky fuckers who hope that nobody else checks or notices?  #insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cullerton is a politician that makes me embarrassed to be Australian. Just listening to him speak makes my ears bleed #auspol #insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danielbowen I'm not sure @billshortenmp is capable of speaking any other way... #insiders #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How many other countries are prioritizing "people smuggler deterrence" in these times of huge population movement?? Just Aus? #insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AT LEAST CANADA AND AMERICA ARE ACCEPTING GENUINE REFUGEES YOU HEARTLESS SHITBAG #insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop saying Unity Ticket #insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish I had a tv in my shower so I could watch #insiders while getting ready to go out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[J Howard defends Bill Leak, uses phrase "creeping political correctness", loses credibility w/ anyone w/ a brain, sense of empathy #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IKR. I'm an early childhood practitioner and know how crucial family is to a child's development #ppl #insiders https://t.co/HY1pOJK1yi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expecting my govt to support me through times of limited earning capacity (eg studying, raising chn) is NOT bludging #insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a pregnant, employed taxpayer &amp; so glad that these privileged white men are so carefully considering my survival w/ a newborn #insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still can't fathom how cruel punishments for desperate asylum seekers will "send a message" to people smugglers  #insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fucking freeloading fuckstick. Fuck off and pay for your own shit.  #joehockey #doubledipper @JoeHockey https://t.co/tbXfRxEYWA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not watching #insiders this morning. The mall is so quiet this time of day!! I should do this more often!! #shopping #misanthropy #belco]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the actual cunting fuck?! This muppet is scraping the barrel for ppl to blame for unaffordable housing #auspol https://t.co/JW1Ufn86Th]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And apparently that's all there is on the matter. Gerard's opinion, Malcolm's opinion, discussion over. #insiders https://t.co/lsln9G8QbS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am really feeling Fleur's red shoes today. Very nice. #redshoes #insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh please, Straight White Old Man, tell us how young gay people should feel about being subjected to a plebiscite  #insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel a bit sorry for Malcolm Turnbull. Stuck between a rock and a National Party #insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol, O'Dwyer's fuck up... classic  #insiders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And here comes Andrew Barr!! #actvotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like this @ABCNews24 host. He actually challenges Zed's negativity and propaganda. Quite rare in our media of late #actvotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@giddeygirl Don't be silly. Then we'd have to judge men on their looks and support role alone. Who would do that to a person? #actvotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bitter Southsider (probably) Zed calls fastest-growing town in the country a "small part" of Canberra #actvotes #gungahlin #lightrail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ANTI_UN @wattletree56 @Brentus88 OMG what??!! People are tweeting about OTHER THINGS??! Inconceivable!! #actvotes #feedingthetrolls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zed concedes it's hard for Liberals to win support in a progressive, highly educated place like Canberra #actvotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And now that we have federal politicians on the panel, it's a lot less civilised #actvotes #abcnews24 @ABCNews24]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shane Rattenbury's speech makes me happy and optimistic about politics again. #actvotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Antony Green "can't see how the Liberals have a path to form govt" at this stage @AntonyGreenABC @ABCNews24  #actvotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Must be the old people. They don't do electronic votes and don't like light rail, because of reasons. #actvotes https://t.co/5r3WejDdtQ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>