<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[BERKELEY, Calif. (AP) - Officials cancel Breitbart News editor talk at UC Berkeley after protesters throw smoke bombs, flares at building]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Latest: Ivanka Trump visits Chinese Embassy -  https://t.co/jGRkxuCEQY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@IvankaTrump the life of the party at Chinese New Year party at embassy https://t.co/A1V3ED9dVR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spotted at the Chinese New Year reception at the Chinese Embassy: Ivanka Trump and daughter https://t.co/2jw1xaeSwJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump threatened in call with Mexico's Pena Nieto to send US troops to stop "bad hombres," @vmsalama reports: https://t.co/Yr2HMItptp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (AP) - GOP-controlled House passes measure to scuttle Obama regulation protecting streams from coal mining debris]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichLKosinski But instead we get a Capella version of Bonnie Tyler's "Total Eclipse of the Heart"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be it resolved: All journalist schools should implement a seminar on the first day of classes in how to mute your phone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DOVER AIR BASE, Del. (AP) — President Trump makes unannounced trip to honor the return of fallen US Navy SEAL killed in Yemen raid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OKnox Sometimes you can keep a Baghdad trip secret by telling reporters you're going to Kabul. CC: @justinsink @mikememoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (AP) - President Trump has left the White House on Marine One on an unannounced trip, White House has not disclosed destination]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (AP) - Senate confirms Rex Tillerson, former CEO of Exxon Mobil, to be President Donald Trump’s secretary of state]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (AP) - Trump tells GOP Senate leader to "go nuclear" if Dems block Supreme Court pick, in apparent reference to rule change]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEW YORK (AP): @AP NewsBreak: Clinton will reflect on 2016 race in new book]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama fights back: the former president's orbit is now actively resisting #Trump - https://t.co/rNaCIUaU0E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Al Gore urging senators to vote against Trump's EPA nominee --&gt; https://t.co/ZCpEtVbNEj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (AP) — Senate committee approves Trump Treasury, Health nominees without Dems present after GOP changes panel's rules]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump having private lunch today with his secretary of state nominee, Rex Tillerson, the @WhiteHouse says]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New this AM: Former VP @JoeBiden launches nonprofit foundation to promote equal rights/opportunity - https://t.co/kugANg42RZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's secretary of state pick Tillerson headed for Senate approval -  https://t.co/uxER9utH1u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a Pyongyang car dealership, only the logos are local -  https://t.co/4enU0LpX3A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like there is a metaphor in here somewhere https://t.co/2S8MVstnlk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BISMARCK, N.D. (AP) - North Dakota senator: Acting Army Secretary directs Army Corps to grant easement to finish Dakota Access pipeline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it ok to eat tacos for every single meal in a given day? Asking for a friend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama aides applying "Romney test" to Trump: Only criticize Trump on things Romney/McCain would deem beyond the pale https://t.co/I6U1SmnI51]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Latest from @AP: Trump nominates Neil Gorsuch to Supreme Court -  https://t.co/xBJgBmOhzb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (AP) — President Donald Trump nominates 10th Circuit Judge Neil Gorsuch for associate justice of the Supreme Court]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Obama fights back: Former president's orbit resists #Trump -  https://t.co/I6U1SmnI51]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Early #FF @AP's @acaldwellap, who is killing it on Trump immigration and has literally not stopped working in four days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hundreds of US diplomats defy White House warning, sign memo criticizing Trump temporary travel ban - https://t.co/IFxwRTQQlv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAN FRANCISCO (AP) - San Francisco sues Trump over executive order on immigrant-protecting sanctuary cities, calling it unconstitutional]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (AP) — US official says 872 refugees to be admitted to country because of hardship concerns, despite ban]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LONDON (AP) - British government pardons thousands of men convicted under now-abolished anti-homosexuality laws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Philly Dem @Michael_Nutter on CNN says there may be "mental challenges" with Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (AP) - New acting attorney general directs Justice Department to defend Trump's executive order on immigration and refugees]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justice reporters: How is it OLC approved EO if there wasn't a legal rationale clear enough that Yates would have been forced to accept it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump fires Justice Dept. head over executive order defiance (from @AP) https://t.co/9Ypm9ML3g7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (AP) - Trump fires acting Attorney General Sally Yates after she orders Justice Dept. lawyers to stop defending refugee ban]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CC: Rex Tillerson DALLAS (AP) - Boy Scouts of America will allow transgender children who identify as boys to enroll in scouting programs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (AP) - Acting attorney general says Justice Department, under her watch, will not defend refugee executive order in court]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump courts #Jordan's King Abdullah II amid Israeli embassy, refugee concerns - https://t.co/Ti6zh9ma5s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abneufeld Yes, I've read it in full, of course]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House, US diplomats clash over travel order. "Get with the program," Spicer says. @AP story by @APDiploWriter: https://t.co/gDcQL7hSjS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@GWtweets President Knapp says Trump order 
"directly threatens wellbeing" of students, faculty, GW seeks answers - https://t.co/ZeE6CeeUNK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking silence, #Obama speaks out on #Trump immigrants order  - https://t.co/HTrM9qBlwt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joining @ShepNewsTeam on @FoxNews now to discuss the fallout from #Trump's #immigration order]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama statement praises 'engagement' around US over Trump immigration order, breaking his post-presindecy silenec https://t.co/dghPVdsuFV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Evergreen memo from wire service reporters to all flacks. The answer to "when is your deadline" is always "right now"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blast from the past https://t.co/bcooUuHoJr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inbox: MVVA, Site Design Group, and Living Habitats selected as landscape architects for #Obama's presidential library &amp; center]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait when did it snow I am so confused]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BAGHDAD (AP) - Lawmakers: Iraq parliament approves 'reciprocity measure' after Trump's travel ban, to apply for Americans entering #Iraq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QUEBEC CITY (AP) - Quebec City police confirm fatalities in a shooting at a local mosque, 2 people arrested]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Danielle1239 It's true Obama admin identified those countries as of concern, but never intended that designation be used for visa ban]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting messaging from White House this AM, arguing it was Obama's admin that identified the 7 countries that Trump used for visa ban]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (AP) - Trump imposes lifetime ban on administration officials lobbying foreign governments, 5 years for other lobbying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TEHRAN (AP) - Iranian state news agency: Iran to 'retaliate' against order limiting immigration from Muslim-majority countries]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (AP) - Trump signs executive action for 'new vetting measures' to keep 'radical Islamic terrorists' out of the US]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DALLAS (AP) - TransCanada has quickly filed a new application to build Keystone XL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (AP) - AP Sources: Trump, Mexican President Pena Nieto held hourlong phone call Friday amid dispute over border wall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justinsink oh, yes. Duh. How quickly those ex-WH reporters get rusty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Trump's plan to pay for Mexico border wall would work - https://t.co/d91vu4jTDk w/ @joshboak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About to join @ShepNewsTeam on @FoxNews live from the State Department to discuss British PM Theresa May's upcoming meeting with Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No no no let's not do this please

Inbox: "News Alert: Scientists for the first time have created a part-human, part-pig embryo "]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (AP) — Current, former U.S. officials say Border Patrol chief Mark Morgan has left the agency]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomgara Yes, but hyping up/sensationalizing a story to get more eyeballs is not how we roll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MEXICO CITY (AP) — Mexican President Enrique Pena Nieto says he has informed the White House he has canceled trip to Washington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has anyone tried the stretch dress shirts from Brooks Brothers? Yay or nay? Looking at you @EricSchultz @joshearnest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MEXICO CITY (AP) - Mexican president says he regrets and rejects the US decision to build a border wall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this statement from @TulsiGabbard. She met with a whole bunch of people, yadda yadda, oh BTW also Bashar Assad… https://t.co/ZPMwMSkZAA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#MEXICO CITY (AP) — Official: Mexican president 'considering' canceling trip to Washington following Trump border wall order]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slow down please, Wednesday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (AP) — Trump administration mandating EPA scientific studies, data undergo review by political staff before public release]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This -&gt; https://t.co/naHrTx5GP7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (AP) — Draft order shows Trump plans to suspend issuing visas to citizens of 7 Muslim-majority countries for at least 30 days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEW YORK (AP) _ Dow Jones industrial average closes above 20,000 points for the first time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (AP) — Draft order shows Trump intends to stop accepting Syrian refugees, suspend broader refugee program for 120 days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEW YORK (AP) — Actress Mary Tyler Moore is dead at age 80, publicist says]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (AP) — Trump signs immigration actions to build border wall, says, 'We've been talking about this right from the beginning' .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eating yogurt with a fork is just so unsatisfying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump draft document says U.S. laws should be obeyed at all times and explicitly rejects 'torture.' https://t.co/szL5rCbaU8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (AP) - Draft White House order seeks review of interrogation rules and if CIA-run prisons outside US should be reopened]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LINCOLN, Neb. (AP) - A Nebraska legislator has resigned after tweet implying women marchers were too unattractive to be sexually assaulted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (AP) - Police: Protesters disrupting work, climbing crane at construction site blocks from the White House]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (AP) - Trump tweets he's asking for a 'major investigation' into voter fraud; says may strengthen voting procedures]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BANJUL, Gambia (AP) - Gambia's new president will return to the country on Thursday, official confirms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COLUMBIA, S.C. (AP) - South Carolina Gov. Nikki Haley resigns to become U.N. ambassador; Lt. Gov. Henry McMaster is state's new governor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@felschwartz Sigh girl why you make me feel so old]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So yes, the official White House position is that millions of people in the US illegally voted in the 2016 election]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LANSING, Mich. (AP) — Michigan environmental agency says Flint's water system no longer has levels of lead exceeding the federal limit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COLUMBIA, S.C. (AP) - Rep. Chris Corley, accused of beating his wife bloody, resigns statehouse seat rather than be expelled]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (AP) — Trump bans EPA employees from providing updates on social media or to reporters, bars awarding new contracts or grants]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (AP) - Senate Foreign Relations Committee votes overwhelmingly to approve Nikki Haley as US ambassador to the United Nations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (AP) - Trump says he'll announce pick to fill Supreme Court vacancy next week]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (AP) — Trump signs executive actions to advance the construction of the Keystone XL and Dakota Access oil pipelines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaredRizzi Guilty. Also I am locked in a broom closet please send help]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WASHINGTON (AP) - Senate committee approves nomination of Elaine Chao to head transportation department]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of websites, switchboards and logistics: Important to remember  any incoming administration has a ton to get up and running in little time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Curious whether anyone who was upset about Lynch-WJC meeting is upset about appearance of Trump-Comey bro-hug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know what this means but sounds cool LONDON (AP) - Formula One CEO Chase Carey tells the @AP he wants to add a street race in the US]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>