<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[A clear demonstration of why data matters more than what one believes. @NotAltWorld @washingtonpost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the world has changed. Communist Asian countries are showing leadership, while the west regresses into mediocrity. @business]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much for draining the swamp! @ReclaimAnglesea @guardian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ultrasupercritical is another way of saying it's 5% more efficient but still less than 50%. More marketing BS. @GeochemOz @WAtoday #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Clean coal' would push up power bills more than wind, solar or gas: analysts https://t.co/doRGzcX8VP via @watoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overpopulation &amp; environmental destruction are real issues. Abortions could be far lower by promoting harmless contraception. @PeteBaklinski]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is exactly what the policies of @votesustainable are about. There is already such a party. @macro_business #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why @VoteSustainable is the only option if you're concerned about population for sustainability reasons. https://t.co/OWYyLoWyxJ #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clean Coal doesn't exist. After CO2 there is still the toxic fly ash and acid mine drainage to worry about. @ProfPCDoherty @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["sustainably grow"...now there's an oxymoron. This philosophy is flawed and needs to be phased out. @1petermartin @ToniHassan @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[State considers appealing order to reveal Roe 8 plans https://t.co/UjMheU37Vj via @watoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A State election coming up perhaps? - Ellenbrook rail link back in transport plan but maybe not until 2050 https://t.co/D6Gmgt0WGh #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[India freaks out over U.S. plans to change high-skilled visas https://t.co/gJjSAu2kzq via @CNNMoney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No prizes for guessing why the more pristine rivers are in Northern Canada, Alaska and Russia, almost nobody lives there. @conservbytes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's not get hamstrung by policy or principles, after all this is politics! @hughriminton @Dehler45 @PaulineHansonOz #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Peter_Strachan dead horse flogging is becoming a national pastime. It doesn't matter whether it's a nickel mine, coal or the TPP. #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Peter_Strachan these issues keep coming up in elections, yet are brushed off as populism. No wonder mainstream parties are sinking. #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CBA: Housing affordability looks set to worsen (via @BIAUS) https://t.co/IBoG7jWlQb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Trump approach to the judiciary has striking parallels with that of Robert Mugabe. @Reuters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is why voting right-wing to deal with immigration is a disaster in the making. Better to @VoteSustainable. https://t.co/7ObqCnn3kN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loophole will allow donations made in dying days of federal election to stay secret https://t.co/EnKRzkK5Xk via @watoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@William_Bourke Like with everything else moderation would have kept a modicum of sobriety. The immigration binge i… https://t.co/8RZmmNsNHr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Climate deniers blame global warming on nature. This NASA data begs to differ https://t.co/qGvEBkmbAg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Peter_Strachan @AngelaSmithWA True but it's also a blight on the Libs that they have so little respect for heritag… https://t.co/Yvxsbw3sIb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tourism overtakes coal exports as services drive growth https://t.co/EiODMb4E2V via @watoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteylG True but there are also issues with currency exchange rates, cost of living &amp; regulation that require adjus… https://t.co/IzD8hc1jpZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump filed for re-election 5 hours after his inauguration and it may matter - https://t.co/N1lzojqw5v via @Shareaholic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1petermartin @smh @theage If it weren't so, it would be almost impossible for the average person to move house; it… https://t.co/Mf7koViYW4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WSJ This doesn't bode well for the long-term health of high-rise communities. Another way our current economic mod… https://t.co/hGrfoTE3v5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@macro_business Immigration is like nutrition. A healthy diverse diet improves vitality, too much of anything is to… https://t.co/H5yvCrSyEt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is absurd! - 'Worthless' hairdressing qualifications leave tens of thousands 'unemployable' https://t.co/pgRBrsxHMk via @watoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Howard Has Billed Taxpayers $1 Million Since 2013 https://t.co/xaEzYEopj8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[lf multinationals and immigration had been better managed, populism would not have succeded. Australia will be next. @wef #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump's Muslim ban excludes countries in which he has business ties https://t.co/2i2kRjnxol via @watoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The role of capitalism in the rise of populism https://t.co/qaxp1cCFzI via @wef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Reasons to Like the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency https://t.co/vqML6sZyi7 via @NatGeo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PopnMatters @Peter_Strachan That's almost the population of Australia in one year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New map reveals shattering effect of roads on nature https://t.co/UJrBecveUF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RogueNASA @p_hannam All scientists and Engineers should go on strike for just a day. When nothing works because of… https://t.co/dsbdvY2a7v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Suzuki on Exponential Growth https://t.co/K5iyfMO4S6 via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a cop-out. There's no such thing as a guaranteed return; subsidised property speculation is wrecking Australia. https://t.co/PX2bjUemEZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technological progress alone won't stem resource use: No evidence of  overall reduction in the world's consumption. https://t.co/orHfJoqE9L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How ironic that "Capitalism" is ending up exactly the same as Communism, which was the system George Orwell had in mind. @washingtonpost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. government scientists go 'rogue' in defiance of Trump https://t.co/No6NpNduPz via @Reuters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AltNatParkSer @darylgibson @BBCWorld They have a lot more in common with the Taliban and Boko Haram than they thin… https://t.co/qrz9bpqvyx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@macro_business "Tackling supply-side issues" is another way of saying quash NIMBYs &amp; the environment to double dow… https://t.co/Q9zPw5BXQg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netherlands moves on abortion funding after Trump reinstates 'gag rule' @CNNPolitics https://t.co/OLkrZbuqvL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not much use if the slack is taken up by foreign buyers and investors. #auspol https://t.co/5untQaRxOK via @newscomauHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BreitbartNews Local Sioux officials must be very tired, since the same paragraph is cut &amp; pasted twice. https://t.co/w6vfFA88no]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JacquiLambie The refugees are not the problem. It's doubling the intake of other migrants (&gt;90%) that has maxed ou… https://t.co/45ymaRRJWb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AustralisTerry The fossil fuel lobby will use increasing political pressure to impede renewables, especially now t… https://t.co/zLXUddKk1h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still no train station 15 years later: angry South Perth council hits back  https://t.co/eE2p6NAe3f via @watoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Peter_Strachan There we go, "it's not rocket science"! Either our pollies are terminally stupid or (as many suspec… https://t.co/BSvpTRPdqY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adele_ferguson @theage Corrupt corporate leaders suck in their weak-principled underlings as well and victimise ot… https://t.co/6O9oN3jOtx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@canberratimes Instead of putting out mindless corporate engagement surveys, business should fix this. It's why so… https://t.co/vPulpQof9L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanielWickham93 @MichaelWestBiz @guardian This sort of governance is reminiscent of the last days of Apartheid. Th… https://t.co/PUNpK6eSiy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AustralisTerry That would mean admitting that fossil fuels are not the future. We'll have to wait for another gove… https://t.co/YH8IWUSaUU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen up, if we're married or plan to have children is none of your business https://t.co/DEKcY76xaa via @watoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyNewsAust @Luke_FoleyNSW 25% of NSW property is sold to overseas buyers. The govt doesn't care about affordabili… https://t.co/EDbqzibUu6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pauline Hanson channeling Trump to become WA's kingmaker https://t.co/YzDumLCDZM via @watoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@CNNStyle Increased efficiency is all very well but we had better start paying attention to the fact that people n… https://t.co/y0mUnDNH3y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will the world's next megacity come out of a 3D printer? @CNNStyle https://t.co/t0wNhU4O4j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GuardianAus @guardian The budget emergency is all but forgotten when it comes to winding back tax rorts on propert… https://t.co/52jlhIXxey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GuardianAus @guardian When 30% of property sales in Victoria are to foreign buyers, then the problem is not supply… https://t.co/2y7uEpS8eg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GuardianAus @guardian The desperation to keep the #Ponzi going is palpable. It's simple logic that house prices ca… https://t.co/rpAFO89Tp5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SimonThomsen @m_jns @BIAUS @bengrubb Downgrading to a dumb phone is becoming an increasingly attractive option. It… https://t.co/dTVGdoY0Av]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Locals furious as state approves unlimited heights in South Perth  https://t.co/my82uNV9CI via @watoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@macro_business This government will flog the property horse until the vultures are chewing its legs off. #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jouljet @deniseshrivell @SBSNews A healthy return on 'impulse buys' is a much higher priority than affordable hous… https://t.co/RiRaUnXAM8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lenoretaylor @BoomersAreEvil @guardian Is the government planning to build high-rise park benches to sleep on or i… https://t.co/KKIWyj3moY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoomersAreEvil Spot on @BoomersAreEvil and we will probably have to work longer too. We can't have increasing long… https://t.co/sdXoPAfPg2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@guardian We have to start accepting that population growth is a massive part of the problem. Climate Change is ac… https://t.co/LQBkkRKrdx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global warning: Australia and Asia predict climate cost of Trump's agenda – live https://t.co/XpTAlN3CAI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perth sprawl continues as industry, councils, state play blame game https://t.co/EEJyA4I4mV via @watoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With Sydney finally dead, Mike Baird's work is done https://t.co/hMtAyNHttN via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EnviroNews @NASA So we're back in the Middle Ages after one election. The Earth is flat and anyone who disagrees w… https://t.co/3kwWVcGGHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnWren1950 @GregHuntMP @smh This is why #Mediscare worked, it conforms with the underlying philosophy of Coalition policies. #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High immigration masks Australian economic decline https://t.co/4w6rwh1l9m via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@p_hannam China has the upper hand, which makes protectionism understandable. Throwing away a leading position in r… https://t.co/IJCPHN0GjH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not really a surprise if graduates can't get a job. - WA's report card: University drop-out rate increases https://t.co/CwALVWHIYh  @watoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PopnMatters @William_Bourke Notably overpopulation isn't limited to nations, all countries need a population polic… https://t.co/xQtrsMaGhM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arch criminals "parking on verges" - Council slammed for facilitating 'illegal' Roe 8 protests https://t.co/DgA3J2QE9X @watoday #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@William_Bourke What happens when foreigners 'rotate out' of Australian property eventually? Not only will it kill… https://t.co/pgcCtkZ2aW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uranium mine consent in face of extinction threat 'is God Clause at work' https://t.co/EbauEV60kO via @watoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aggressive bank bonuses risk mis-selling: Sedgwick review https://t.co/vQBs3IENed via @watoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poetic justice if only it weren't billed to taxpayers. - Asbestos riddled through Roe 8 site  https://t.co/fRR20KdtWb via @watoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ipsos survey: Australians want a strong leader to take country back from rich and powerful https://t.co/jGdvUtTufA via @watoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoomersAreEvil 30% in Victoria! This is how xenophobia starts... #auspol @VoteSustainable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fitch revises outlook for Australian banks to negative https://t.co/mWvQVwOFFg via @watoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wyoming Bill Would All But Outlaw Clean Energy by Preventing Utilities From Using It https://t.co/cto4vcAezc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congestion happens through infrastructure lagging population growth. This is another red herring. https://t.co/CxTgfWReoB via @smh #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - The yoga classes helping prisoners in South Africa https://t.co/JH0Ug7zt3I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too expensive: Concerns for the future of private health insurance  - Yahoo7 https://t.co/gOyHbt0E11 via @Yahoo7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@macro_business No wonder when property speculation is rewarded with #NegativeGearing, CGT discounts and minimal te… https://t.co/DJJqTXho2l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fed up doctors threaten to bill time wasting bosses who demand worker sick certificates  - Yahoo7 https://t.co/4cjFnfaixf via @Yahoo7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@William_Bourke @mclaren2gb @michaeldaleyMP Great to see @BenFordham gets it! Lower immigration is a common sense s… https://t.co/Z9LkIfPT4C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One would have to wonder about the infrastructure job prospects under Labor for the company that does this work. @watoday #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WA environment minister 'comfortable' with bulldozing bushland for Roe 8 https://t.co/nmkVSJljXF via @watoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why open offices are bad for us https://t.co/kAZ69lOqSG via @BBC_Capital]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1petermartin @smh @theage What happens when EQ is the sole criterion for a management position. Qualify by pub att… https://t.co/oqyzHhigcT]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>