<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@celticsancowboy - You're absolutely dishonest and lack any ethical standards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@celticsancowboy - More meaningless rethoric. https://t.co/jDJAaFTUsE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@celticsancowboy - Nice attempt to misdirect the discussion away from the fact, the pause i.e BAN..You're intelligently dishonest..Good day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@celticsancowboy - Yes, you should stop listening to the MSM. Educate yourself before it's too late.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@celticsancowboy - It's a temporary freeze to re-examine the policies surrounding nations were there isn't proper vetting. Note - Temporary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@celticsancowboy - Do your research. Obama banned Iraqi Refugees..What you think, I pulled it out of thin air?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The intolerant left in action...

https://t.co/0cVeb5YKl0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JacksonNewton_9 - So, we're not allowed to be proud of our school? Take your intolerant uneducated ass elsewhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WilliamJMiller @DLoesch @alexa_lebron - Usage of rape in such a manner is offensive. removed the Tweet, lacks courage once  tweet was known]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's talk about California seceding from the United States... I guess they can depend on Hollywood to continue to make their bombs...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh the outrage! Liberal racists are upset the Trump White House is honoring Black History Month https://t.co/K5jjAOJR85]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Melon_Daddy @SECNetwork @AlabamaFTBL @UA_Athletics - Tell your friend GA is still an outstanding school with a rich history in SEC Football]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics - But, Islam is a religion of peace...right...?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxNews @POTUS - Sure beats a beer summit or golf outing @BarackObama
That's how a real POTUS acts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SECNetwork @AlabamaFTBL @UA_Athletics - But...Who won the championship....?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicholeo5145 - Best to you as well..Enjoy your day..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Portrait of an uneducated, intolerant left-wing hack. https://t.co/StnRrzVs5U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nancy Pelosi Caught On Hot Mic: ‘Tell Them You’re A Muslim’ [VIDEO] https://t.co/KnCmAn2ySw https://t.co/fvrhmqUG6w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheLeadCNN - ‘Totally-Not-Senile’ Nancy Pelosi Is Blaming Donald Trump For A War That Began 2015 [VIDEO]
https://t.co/zF19Sx3las]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN - Apple doesn't have a leg to stand on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheLeadCNN @BenSasse @NancyPelosi @CNN - The intolerant left criticism of Judge Gorsuch is rehashed standard democratic talking points]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Totally-Not-Senile’ Nancy Pelosi Is Blaming Donald Trump For A War That Began 2015 [VIDEO]
https://t.co/zF19Sx3las https://t.co/6sIHqihBYq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a criminal act. The @SecretService should investigate this CEO immediately https://t.co/z25QKguVNR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrentBozell - @maddow is in constant melt down mode. She's bitter and just so biased it blinds any reasonable chance of coherent thought]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DLoesch - It's beyond insulting to see ppl act that way. But ppl feel embolden to act like idiots hiding behind the keyboard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN - After the whining press demanded to know where POTUS was going. Shut them up real quick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@newsmax - No fan of Brady, but this is just ridiculous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics - You missed the obstructionist democrats being childish. Getting personal and whining.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kaitlancollins @DailyCaller - Sick of the arrogance of some of the press.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man who claimed mom died in Iraq after Trump's ban lied, Imam confirms: https://t.co/KKGeqqjCo9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@celticsancowboy - What's unlawful?  The EO is constitutional and enforceable. Much like Obama's ban in 2011 of Iraqi Refugees.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cclucas99 - Far too long Republicans have been sitting back and ignoring personal attacks. It's time to get proactive and fight back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cclucas99 - Well, when DT goes after an individual or subject, suddenly things happen. It's his style. So far the ppl like it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@austin_hall - End of free lesson...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@austin_hall - It’s been standard practice over the last 80 years to not confirm Supreme Court nominees during a presidential election year,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics - Who the hell cares about Al Franken. Democrats are hypocrites and obstructionist. Let'em continue to implode.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theblaze - I wouldn't even offer @CNN a seat in the press room or aboard air force one. Freeze CNN out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelEDyson @TheView @WhoopiGoldberg @sunny @JoyBehar @JedediahBila - Dyson another race baiting liberal hack.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nancy Pelosi defending illegals over honest law abiding citizens is absolutely absurd. https://t.co/p9yLjFiIpE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill - This just in, no it won't. Thanks Harry..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewDay - Apple better watch out. We're watching what corps say and do concerning the lawful temporary ban.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN - CNN is still pushing their Anti-Trump agenda. Unbelievable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some People Wrote ‘Resist’ On A Beach In Maine, And CNN Is ON It https://t.co/mgLbuXZhg3 https://t.co/lPNbdNzFmD https://t.co/ynQnJxsMJ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[German and EU taxpayers will pay nearly $46,000,000,000 to deal with problems caused by Muslim migrants… https://t.co/U2JTo0tiHI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DailyCaller - Democrats further cement the fact they're childish. The intolerant left is imploding right before our eyes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Chicago's Violent Crime In January Matches Bloody Start Of 2016"

https://t.co/x2YXV5muVU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disfunction is the only thing democrats are good at.... https://t.co/qBLY7eIrGr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JedediahBila - I suspect Barbara is lonely and lives in her daughters basement watching cartoons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JedediahBila - People feel embolden when hiding behind a keyboard to act in such a childish manner. Note 'Bully' in the Twitter handle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If democrats are going to continue to play the obstructionist role, then use all options available. https://t.co/N6yxSg6wow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad to see the number of bogus accounts designed to just spread hate towards others like @TrumpLies247 who offers nothing of substance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrumpLies247 - Enjoy your parting gift. You're a sad individual with anger issues..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MuleorAstromule - Yawn..You're absolutely so focused on bashing Cruz and Trump, you're giving Franken a pass..I se… https://t.co/5IOF701J2D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@newsmax - Will some one tell @DangeRussWilson his opinion is meaningless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MuleorAstromule - too bad you couldn't address Franken childish behavior. Good day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MuleorAstromule - I'm saying it doesn't matter. It's between Ted &amp; Trump. They've spoken since, one can assume it was discussed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DailyCaller - The sheer stupidity of @WhoopiGoldberg never fails to deliver. Hateful, intolerant and disgraceful best describes her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MuleorAstromule - Thanks for the 'Alternative Facts '..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@newsmax - Here comes true 'Alternative Facts']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyRiddell - Nancy Pelosi is one of the most dishonest and uneducated individuals to hold office. She's just plain unintelligent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics - Ted Cruz needs to go punch that chicken s**t Al Franken in the mouth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hateful, intolerant and disgraceful. https://t.co/CLi8eYZM7E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theblaze - Nancy Pelosi is one of the most dishonest and uneducated individuals to hold office.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN - Al Franken @alfranken is a disgraceful human being. The people of his state should consider finding another representative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democratic party is literally imploding in front of our eyes https://t.co/c4TQZXtuR1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things that make you go, hmmm... https://t.co/axcjvOSMrG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch the circus act... https://t.co/EbdbrUHjii]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NancyPelosi is heartless and puts illegals over U.S citizens..She's disgraceful.. https://t.co/NwtTj5HO5d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics - Here comes the loser..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Oh_That_Stung - They're given a platform you or I don't have access too. Unbelievable you're defending rich out of touch often hypocrites]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Oh_That_Stung -I'm not an hypocrite nor self improvement enough to be my opinion is better than everyone else because of my stature in life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Oh_That_Stung - I'm not given a mic, stage or have the MSM behind me pushing my opinion as if its more important than the average American.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Oh_That_Stung -,Celebrities are paid to act, simple. Their opinions aren't in more important than mine. That's what the MSM seems to forget]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@townhallcom - Jail the gang bangers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cclucas99 - No matter, he's there at least 4yrs. I see positives so far, but it's early. Time will tell...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Erin16795743 - Poorly written. Poorly executed. Shoved down the American people throats. Then to level fines etc, ridiculous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Erin16795743 - Trump just announced the willingness to work to lower the cost of meds. Unlike ACA which has increased the cost.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Erin16795743 - Pharmaceutical a business. Yes, it's capitalism. They invest millions, wait yrs for approval.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Erin16795743 - That's the problem. Role models aren't what we elect them for. They're elected to do the ppls business. Role models, nope.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicholeo5145 - See we agree. We see the world differently, Common ground.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mhardison1965 - Is that all you have egg? Dismissed. I don't have time for such nonsense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Erin16795743 - Pharmaceutical companies do provide millions of FREE medications to low income Americans and other countries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Erin16795743 - Find this hard to believe. You're spouting democrats talking points endlessly and defense of ACA is a clear example.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicholeo5145 - I love how personal ppl get instead of focusing on the subject. We're done. Enjoy your day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicholeo5145 UR blind to the fact we have to work within the system to bring abt change. Screaming for change with no action is meaningless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Erin16795743 @CNN - You're scared of a real businessman, not a political hack in the office now. 8yrs of rethoric and we were left weak.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Erin16795743 @CNN -What's ironic you seem to lack the facts abt our presidents not being poor, but it's another strawman. Come on be honest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicholeo5145 @CNN - Pure political rethoric. The same ole tired rehashed democratic talking points. No ones right has been taken away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxNews - By any means necessary...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By any means necessary... https://t.co/xuNoWzNwAE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iran launches another ballistic missile. The Obama Legacy of failure comes back to remind us. https://t.co/utQP5CYBsJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Erin16795743 @CNN - Have a good day. Keep complaining, we're moving forward to restore America.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Erin16795743 @CNN - You're not listening clearly. Great thing abt this country, you're entitled 2 ur opinion. Even if it's basically wrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Erin16795743 @CNN - You're offering nothing but democratic talking points based upon nothing be rethoric. Hard to take an egg seriously.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Erin16795743 @CNN - He actions say differently. This WH is moving forward to restore economic growth and development of jobs, quality jobs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Erin16795743 @CNN - ACA is an absolute failure. Hard working ppl lost providers, coverage and premiums in some cases doubled or tripled.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MZHemingway - It’s been standard practice over last 80yrs to not confirm Supreme Court nominees during a presidential election year. Fact.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MZHemingway - I didn't support Trump or vote for him, but he has impressed me with his ability to stay on track and adhere to his promises]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intolerant left is in full create egg accounts on Twitter to harass anyone that disagrees with dems, celebrities or special interest groups]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN - Well qualified.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>