<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Our new house is now unconditional! So exciting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So @jemyoshioka suggested Olivia Coleman for the new #DoctorWho and I am so behind this suggestion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Megapope @Styla73 @insopherable I've sorted this fyi :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@insopherable @Megapope oh god can you dm me where your new job is? You should have proper colour booklets not poor quality B&amp;W photocopies!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And this is why it's so important that fascism is never allowed a platform. https://t.co/fTHHT8sm7p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes a lot to get all the different Jewish congregations to agree on something. Zionists are the outliers. This… https://t.co/0cTjq3ZON9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dimsie @meganjwhelan that would be my best guess too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look at this amazing card that @jemyoshioka drew for my work farewell morning tea! So wonderful. https://t.co/rvzlXhb3Dx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disgraceful and spineless stuff here from English. I'd call him a joke, but nothing about this is funny. Just pathe… https://t.co/VW1PkLpHRb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaronincognito yep if you join online at https://t.co/s5k43PyWeW you'll get the info you need :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Megapope @aaronincognito @NZPSA @bootstheory hope that helps!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Megapope @aaronincognito @NZPSA @bootstheory which may end up being an easier way to join if they're being problematic about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Megapope @aaronincognito @NZPSA @bootstheory but if they can't work out processing (which they should be able to) you can do an AP instead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Megapope @aaronincognito @NZPSA @bootstheory if you call 0508 367 772 during office hours, they'll be able to give you more specific advice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Megapope @aaronincognito @NZPSA @bootstheory if the latter then the former might not be able to sort it. But you can still be a member.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Megapope @aaronincognito @NZPSA @bootstheory are you being paid by the agency you're doing the work for, or a recruitment/placement agency?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shit this is tense #NZvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go the mighty @BLACKCAPS! Great start #NZvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sitting at my desk insulting guinea pigs to @jemyoshioka but apparently not loud enough to get a reaction from @bootstheory. Will try harder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gtiso go to https://t.co/vLnWPK69ip and register an account. When they ask for credit card, instead at bottom input code &amp; then you're done]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pseudony_Ms the benefit of having two screens!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free Sky fan pass for the cricket today! Use the code BLACKCAPS. Work today has improved significantly. https://t.co/CRTlBMaHyW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is simply wonderful. Bravo! https://t.co/3O30SsG47f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brave Smudge was very excited to see us on our way to work this morning. First time we've seen it this year! https://t.co/dFNMApxxEe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Techius @grumpybirb @Pno_nwa oh do fuck off. Blocked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hidden Figures is really bloody wonderful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laranitaNZ up a valley from Owhiro Bay, at the start of the Red Rocks trail.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went back to our favourite South Coast spot, possibly for the last time before we move to the Kapiti Coast. So pret… https://t.co/dRNNj97t5C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@manateeidle you know our story if that's the sort of thing you're looking for?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elsa found a little comfy hidey place in the corner of the spare room https://t.co/XNPWIlirG6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS 25 Oct 2006, in the Dom Post. Before Prosser was an MP, though given 'wogistan' hard to say new job tempered his beliefs much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kumararepublic there is absolutely no chance that he'll succeed Winston.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@verbscape yeah for sure. Cheering is great though IMO - but it's quite different from the sort of bravado which I'm also seeing a lot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alans_world their current incarnation (right wing resistance) is still many of the same losers, still failing to make new friends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alans_world yep they were. Thanks to several things (inc. lots of antifa activity online &amp; offline) they mostly went away after a few years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gurrlwithacurl thanks. It's a long time (10ish years) ago now, I don't think back on it much. But with recent news...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gurrlwithacurl oh that's barely even scratching the surface. It was a time. Not a fun time, but a time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But nazis will build their response based on the threat they think they face. And it probably won't come back on you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But I, for one, have had enough of people talking like they're already regularly punching nazis. Most of us aren't, won't, can't. That's ok!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not saying everyone should dedicate their lives to antifa action.We've all got to live &amp; there's plenty of other issues worth working on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So either put up and do your best to make sure fascists can't organise, or stop talking about it as though you are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a Jewish lefty who has had neo-nazis literally piss on my mother's grave (and send me photos of it), &amp; try to run me over, it isn't fun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm all for punching nazis, but also think about who is gonna feel the worst of the blow back if you're talking a big, but empty, game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alans_world as well, I also cut out this page from that day's paper, handwrote the date on it, and took this photo. But thanks anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alans_world Hi Alan. No, it wasn't. This letter is from 2006. I would know. I was one of the organisers of the anti-fascist protest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearMama_ Steven Universe is wonderful and heart-warming and beautiful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Eliana0Buchanan ugh. I've never met the dude but know a bunch who know him and thought he might be ok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tui_talk @MsAnna_Jane Anna do you want to book now? I'm a little preoccupied with beer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tui_talk maybe! @MsAnna_Jane do we have time for this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making beer on a sunny Saturday afternoon https://t.co/Ge2s9Ku9PU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pr0gger @reckonsemoji yep that's right, just after the National Front's march in Wellington on Labour Day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's the 3rd ranked NZ First MP calling a National Front march a "demonstration of nationhood &amp; pride". Party of… https://t.co/xtrdtmjBEx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsAnna_Jane @beckeleven one of my many turns of phrase just biding their time before they gain worldwide popularity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@uniquelikethem @MsAnna_Jane they're pretty good from here too, to be fair https://t.co/AWDU5IbmN5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@saniac I had forgotten about this! Thanks for reminding me, it really is very good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessEtheridge that is outstanding]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My last Friday working for the @NZPSA #coffeeselfie https://t.co/NNfyMpOaJY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@genuinelygreat @simonjtapp @thelittlepakeha @MsAnna_Jane but it's so far away! It's a completely different state highway!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonjtapp @genuinelygreat @thelittlepakeha @MsAnna_Jane there's more than one? I'm amazed already]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@genuinelygreat @simonjtapp @thelittlepakeha @MsAnna_Jane this sounds like my dream]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dimsie @MsAnna_Jane thankfully no.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thelittlepakeha @MsAnna_Jane remember who? What's twitter? Who am I? All I know is home ownership. Leverage. Mortgage rates. Sub prime loan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So @MsAnna_Jane &amp; I have had our offer accepted on our new house, and we're moving to Raumati Beach in around a mon… https://t.co/nTCA2pis5Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorJeph @ShakingStick oh woops missed that bit. I stand corrected]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorJeph @ShakingStick it's more pay, isn't it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gtiso @mstevnz interesting! I'm not sure where I picked it up from tbh but I've used it for years. Looks the neatest to my eyes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gtiso @mstevnz my preferred style is semi-colon after each, full stop after the last.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scoutriver @jemyoshioka @Megapope I did 3rd form art (I think I got a C), no higher education required, just good instincts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jemyoshioka @Megapope We had to make a new group join form in your absence, Dan. Jem and I worked really hard, hop… https://t.co/Qe7qQx31WI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The awesome @LI_politico talking to the awesome @SusieFergusonNZ on the awesome @NZMorningReport. So much awesome! https://t.co/8C8MbqQcyA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smudgey is very sad that we're going to work today, she did her very best to try to convince me to stay at home. https://t.co/jxRgSn085x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@runningwhio @MsAnna_Jane ordered online from https://t.co/5nhTcZ615r. Hope it works for your kitty!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thelittlepakeha I'm so confused right now. @MsAnna_Jane is uncontrollable laughter next to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatthewHootonNZ no, I avoid proto-fascism on principle. Besides, you of all people should know the difference between rhetoric and reality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is possibly the reachiest reach I've ever seen Hoots reach. https://t.co/NoUTvQlXhv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_kellydare @MsAnna_Jane nice to see you too! Have a great day 2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsAnna_Jane @gurrlwithacurl I was curious as to why you'd tweeted us with nothing but our own handles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raena In hindsight, it's interesting how huge those albums were amongst people my age despite the fact we had no idea what Triple J was.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raena oh I had the album from that year's countdown! So many great tracks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quote is from the Conservative Party announcing their new leader, who wants you to know he likes his family. https://t.co/L1b5aeBj1g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["His philosophy is, if it isn’t broken, don’t try fixing it, but if it is broken, then fix it." Now that's inspiring politics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wrote (most of) a thing. https://t.co/dWqyhLDQzL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonpnz @MsAnna_Jane @Styla73 had lots of help from great mortgage advisor &amp; lawyer. Feeling pretty confident but will have to wait &amp; see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pepperraccoon @MsAnna_Jane @simonpnz @Styla73 nope, there's at least one other.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonpnz @MsAnna_Jane @Styla73 deadline private treaty, which I'd never heard of until late last year but seems to be very common now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Cat(an) is looking pretty settled now. https://t.co/EWNXVv5Zpo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elsa is scoping out the board, trying to decide on her opening move. https://t.co/6BE2bNCcCi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurieFleming @Katieshould @jgmccl whereas everything I've tasted at Beach House (probs about half the brunch menu) has been outstanding.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurieFleming @Katieshould @jgmccl yep it's my new favourite cafe. The last time I went to The Bach, I couldn't finish my coffee or my food]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jgmccl @Katieshould so many dogs! Also Queen Sally's Diamond Deli is really worth trying for deliciousness. Owned by same folk as Maranui.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Katieshould @jgmccl (I've lived in both Kilbirnie and Lyall Bay, both really lovely communities)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Katieshould @jgmccl Elements have new owners now but it's still pretty decent - the old owners &amp; chef now run Beach House in Owhiro Bay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@insopherable congrats on both of these things!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found this excellent kitty waiting for a bus in Kingston. I hope it knows public holidays mean Sunday timetables! https://t.co/UAyBwZz9qJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thebibliophile9 it's ok, the good politics have always been on my mum's side of the family. That's the side I'm closest to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thebibliophile9 it was my father's. I think he was given it but not sure who by. He did vote Act in '96 I think though, unfortunately.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CnrJoe only by Richard Prebble unfortunately, so nope.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzdodo @MsAnna_Jane @KaroriBee I don't like any part of it, but then I don't really like lamps in general so I'm not the target audience!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you the sort of person who wants an autographed Richard Prebble book? Then there's something wrong with you https://t.co/jzdwzvcthR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsAnna_Jane @KaroriBee Unfortunately one of the things that's easier to see in the dark when the lamp is on is the lamp.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>