<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bolt_RSS newsflash: protests are democracy in action.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@navyblue_8 @Bolt_RSS Protesting is a fundamental democratic right. It is democracy in action]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rodsav Cat out of the bag #westlondonsfinest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which EPL team will be the first international side to play at the new Perth stadium? Clue: best team in the world. #wanews #sundaytimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My story in today's The Sunday Times on Bradley Edwards #wanews #Claremontkillings https://t.co/mVMr1jhw0j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrSophieHenshaw @7NewsSydney yes it is. Sorry for not responding sooner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WA Speaks results in tomorrow's paper. Warning: there are a few surprises. #wanews #sundaytimes #waspeaks https://t.co/OkREJH0lTY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrJM_Fernandez The legend Saxon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MB_Donaldson I just said the same thing in the office]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChelseaKelv @Kingcanners I bought the book from the Megastore a few years ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kingcanners Sorry to read this. You are a legend. I bought your book from the Megastore on a trip back to the UK. Great read.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[USA TODAY's Editorial Board: Trump is 'unfit for the presidency' https://t.co/wwH4IpR1op via @usatoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1RobBeasley Is he still talking to you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CecileOConnor same happened to me not long ago. i hope nothing was stolen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My update on situation confronting families in High Wycombe ‘Fumes so bad I kept passing out’ https://t.co/U0wKWzeNgi #wanews #perth #toxic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KaitlynOffer It was a great paper, hey.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KaitlynOffer Yes, it might be the last midweek paper. Definitely the last under News' ownership. I recall working on the first.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This one might be a collector's item. Grab it. https://t.co/170KoE6uOd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nightmare on Adelaide Street: meet the residents with justified worries about what is blowing in the wind  https://t.co/WOxJFheSvN #wanews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nalder quits. Full story in tomorrow's The Sunday Times. #wapol #wanews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Real_KerryDixon Good luck with it Kerry. I'll definitely order. All the best, from a Dunstable Blue, now in Oz.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chelsea's 'oldest fan' buried with Blues merchandise after death https://t.co/rcwqvtN6DK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1RobBeasley heart says yes, head says...go on then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fears over recycling ‘deadly’ waste https://t.co/CJKn6uv0RV My yarn from the weekend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liam Bartlett's great column from Aug 7 worth reading again in light of developments this week. https://t.co/NAMPyag7vj 
#wapolitics #wanews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Sunday Times, PerthNow record strong growth https://t.co/u6eLj8jrOG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ABSCensus Are you down again?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kara_vickery I'm getting the same]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kante signs | News | Official Site | Chelsea Football Club https://t.co/7RdWcWzjn0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ALJB1982 @jasoncundy05 @ManUtd he's right though, collective amnesia from all those who used to give jose abuse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ManUtdUpdates_ collective amnesia then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top front page https://t.co/2sMPrrCAjI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our front page...interesting night #ausvotes #wanews https://t.co/Yt1my3qHEc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shorten delivering a non-victory victory speech #ausvotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WA to save the day for the Turnbull Government. Can we have our GST proceeds now? #ausvotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations, Chelsea! In Conte, you’ve hired a miracle worker https://t.co/qzDUiF0lji]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@surfnturfRP @HistoricalPics The people in the pic weren't rockabillies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@surfnturfRP @HistoricalPics Rockabilly is alive and well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another strong newspaper tomorrow #sundaytimes #wanews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prawns sold in Australia contained trace elements of cooling water from a nuclear plant https://t.co/W4O8szEQZz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My article on food fraud in Australia https://t.co/W4O8szEQZz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WeAreChelseaFC did he actually say musty smell and pants instead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danlevene Scarier than the Exorcist. It just doesn't look right. Come on Conte, help us to forget Jose.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ACCC reviewing sale of The Sunday Times and PerthNow to Seven West Media https://t.co/vAQ6GUOqEJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stakeouts can be tough assignments https://t.co/ntSASzV4h4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like a Spring day in England #PerthStorm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MUA official Chris Brown dumped as Labor candidate https://t.co/6Ytq9FXfcZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bio-Organics inquiry: WA’s environmental watchdog failed to sound alarm https://t.co/1lnUS7NLAn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was at this game. Great day out, when Wembley still had terracing. First trophy I saw the Blues win. #KTBFFH https://t.co/Qxmsm3tEjC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How a Perth SAS soldier’s message from beyond the grave changed lives https://t.co/Tsh2JMIkXH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cracking paper tomorrow #wanews #sundaytimes #bestinthewest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recycling old news https://t.co/HwT5SJ8H7r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ErinParke2 Nothing springs to mind, other than: crap. You mean where no news is news?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The night's big result. Chelsea 2, Arsenal 0.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The real football about to start. Come on you Blues. #CFCvAFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NineJamie who buys these scarves? just tourists i hope.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@M7mmd13 I think he meant we had more corners. Problem is we did nothing with them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarefreeTVCFC Agreed. KTBFFH.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@M7mmd13 No, definitely not. But he needs to dispense with loyalty and see that some out-of-form players have to be dropped.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Astronaut @StationCDRKelly’s stunning picture of Perth from International Space Station http://t.co/nOvHs83gNT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[News chief renews attack over ‘digital theft’ http://t.co/6SGZAY7KqW via @NewspaperWorks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[walkaway campaign has a familiar ring to it. http://t.co/T1aFhkyrni]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@TrumpInsulter says: "Hokey garbage that journalist John Flint" http://t.co/koRJFWZCqh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Definition of a scoop. Never-before-seen footage reveals Russian-backed rebels arriving at the wreckage of MH17 http://t.co/WvrrLhlx86]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Highly recommended show https://t.co/TkWmaUuYLn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fair dues Sinead...Sinead O'Connor's rant over Kim Kardashian's Rolling Stone cover  http://t.co/kLH3vivKB2 via @DailyMailCeleb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God bless #TheFew #BattleofBritain https://t.co/RNzjHMUelY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good luck at Brentford @JMcEachran20  https://t.co/lv6RADddih]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian politicians should learn that improper conduct doesn't boil down to what is legal or illegal, but what is right/wrong. #shorten]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why it’s time for FIFA to reinvent itself - http://t.co/tTGqzbA0v0: http://t.co/xsefTAvQLt via @virgin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dorries_cmail Obviously worried about football's growing popularity in this country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kyle Sandilands: the rotten core of our nation | Perth Now http://t.co/OaQkHZcrMG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former boss attacks ‘lost’ RSPCA http://t.co/ZpkboKDuVM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terrific story, well worth a read. https://t.co/KuQUonW4N5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow's jam-packed newspaper #sundaytimes #wanews #bestinthewest http://t.co/QtYZIWEg12]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cathy_Crawley I'm relieved her life was spared.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[why save one, and execute the other eight? #bali9 #balinine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope she turns okay. Feel sorry for Nepalese, loveliest people http://t.co/zsjCRZYqKb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perth doctor joins ISIS medical team in ‘jihad for Islam’ against the west http://t.co/lXDB2T5X8X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hipsters and snobby staff are ruining our inner-city cafes http://t.co/tlS4Q7OqNm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarlHopley I worked it out Carl. Took me a while though...sorry. The Banbury Post, now that was a long time ago. Hartley top fella.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarlHopley Hi Carl, where did we work together? The mists of time and alcohol...All good with me. You?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chelsea’s first cup final – a century ago | News | Official Site | Chelsea Football Club http://t.co/LesRpirGT4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fans won't be happy tonight? http://t.co/HxyaU64BX8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top notch journalism here: Home truths of Perth’s property investment pitch from the homebuyer seminar circuit http://t.co/blJSLDUz5A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social media - home to the angry, the vindictive and the self-important | Perth Now http://t.co/3W794nElbg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@perthnow Ridiculous OTT fine; I feel sorry for this guy and no spent conviction; legal system in WA is topsy turvy.#wanews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bio-Organics scandal: Inquiry over dumping of industrial waste in Perth’s outskirts | Perth Now http://t.co/KLUdUbnPbc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Support for Socceroos-England clash to open Perth’s new stadium http://t.co/k9C2wBmkUD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alan Jones made sense on #BaliNine executions http://t.co/HWLm4xTaOp Also right about AFP's hand in this atrocious situation #bali9 #AFP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see some AFL noses out of joint at suggestion the Socceroos open the new stadium. Insecurity/inferiority complexes at large. #wanews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Ashes series for football. Would be epic.  http://t.co/0d3oBLKfgX #socceroos #football #perth #wanews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An epic curtain-raiser for the new Perth stadium when it opens in 2018? Check this out: http://t.co/0d3oBLKfgX #wanews  #sundaytimes #perth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For those that have forgotten the Kennedy royal commission was compromised by the state's treatment of whistleblower TL. #wanews #perth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colin Barnett is kidding himself if he thinks the CCC was a wasted exercise. Of course corruption existed and still exists. #perth #wanews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Diego Costa is a monster - that's why I love him | via @Telegraph http://t.co/rGmZmYylDl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow's front page. Giving the Socceroos due credit #wanews #asiancupfinal #Socceroos #football http://t.co/TDIQax47V2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How is that Hull player still on the pitch? #EPL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done Perth Scorchers. Who'd have thought a cricket tweet from me, #perth #scorchers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BroadcastMoose @Cfcaway papers trying to get him banned]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>