<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Off to the back garden to grab my gumleaves... https://t.co/pMBIkuNMfi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facts matter: exploring sabotage in a research lab HT @RetractionWatch  https://t.co/3E98dT1gH7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent choice @CScienceEditors! Issues in this book in many cases still ongoing. https://t.co/OyLtNfWKlT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For those who participated in the Women's March - yes, we can have a positive impact on the political disaster we s… https://t.co/lxUwr9fiNe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Survey for those who use iPSC cultures or are interested to use in future @ECACC https://t.co/fmVU78ikLv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Culture collections hold science history! A look back in time to Australian Sir Howard Florey. https://t.co/wKY8bDbKU3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does science have a reproducibility problem? It's complicated...science that is. @juliaoftoronto HT @ProtocolsIO https://t.co/3wqAnyCzLM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for the recognition @JAByrneSci - cancer research needs #BetterScience to give #BetterCures. https://t.co/SgVtiy4Tk5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SH-SY5Y as a "cellular model of Parkinson's disease" - long way between cell culture and the patient with the disea… https://t.co/Fap07Id9KK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Striking similarities between papers using human cell lines - great detective work @JAByrneSci HT @RetractionWatch https://t.co/yEJWavIV5N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This "PCR dinosaur" (I manually did waterbath transfers before PCR machines) is excited to see new technologies! https://t.co/WJOGshzaNf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Stem cells cannot be safely franchised” - once treatment happens it cannot be reversed #safety #BetterScience https://t.co/WgByRkQMzN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spotting science quality is an essential skill ... said as I disappear under an avalanche of #cellculture papers https://t.co/LJcKcsMdqO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice job with the hemocytometer @Nats_lab! So begins many years of counting :) #biology #biomedical #cellculture https://t.co/hDgY76Prys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some very good points here on dealing with the “rejected” manuscript. RT @ClausWilke: How to reject a rejection https://t.co/u4qoUKJS9W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool video showing #HeLa overgrowing another culture.  Fast-growing cells = cross-contamination if one arrives in y… https://t.co/d6se7eAbSm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helpful article on Conflict of Interest and the broader context of "Interest" - in my view, non-financial interests… https://t.co/V7xBCr0N17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is automated post-publication review helpful? Lack of curation + courtesy are both concerns @nature #reproducibility https://t.co/45v5OyhoM3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheCesareLab congratulations, well deserved!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ICLAC list updated: 451 misidentified cell lines with no known authentic stock #betterscience #cellculture… https://t.co/XYOEodfDZ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have a strong view about research job security in Australia? Take @TheASMR1 survey! https://t.co/6FR1gP4hRg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For correct link to #cellculture article @Leibniz_DSMZ_en see https://t.co/ya9mlK1AU4 or https://t.co/KkFvuKUE9P - thanks @hildabast!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hildabast thanks for pointing out the problem with the link - correcting now :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gorgeous data @Leibniz_DSMZ_en on #cellculture problems: risk of misidentified cell lines 1:6 from secondary sources https://t.co/tIZoTtjx0f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah, the joys of growing cells #CellCulture #MyChildren https://t.co/qGESU0IBrv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Broad-ranging discussion of cell culture core facility work from Tari Parmely @LabManager https://t.co/p0ppOsvtZa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The foundation of community resilience is proper planning." True for the research community too! #standards https://t.co/yOSBrK3nbX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some good thoughts on the switchover to #GHS - crunch time is approaching for #LabSafety compliance! https://t.co/oJGL8dwe94]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Growing cells faster is not necessarily better.  Sometimes long-term culture gives a closer model ... fascinating s… https://t.co/MuBPh83vGu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lteytelman @PLOS It's often assumed that those who need journal access have research funding - entirely untrue from my own experience.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[100 years of cancer research, but the quest to cure cancer seems like it's just beginning. Easy to take past advanc… https://t.co/YkX7EMKuvM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The quick A-Z guide to social media for academics, very handy @andymiah https://t.co/AMmOvktTmA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This article @MyBioTechniques beautifully sets out the challenges of rare disease research &amp; funding #LaforaDisease https://t.co/uU7roiOp3i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great recommendations for reproducibility @DanielJDrucker e.g. panel discussions at scientific meetings https://t.co/nwAEBXaZbO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fascinating story of how kuru was discovered - prions make history through the PNG kuru archive. https://t.co/IlNa2tjwvs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done @dcapslock, hope the wind is beneath your wheels - a great cause! https://t.co/Ym2j4pokeB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CancerMoonshot is an international initiative for #betterscience https://t.co/8q5wrz9K8D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[United States, welcome to the world of the becquerel. Metric units reduce confusion when dealing with radiation. https://t.co/9DJdWHIXj6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disappointed to see no #reproducibility provisions in #CancerMoonshot report - #betterscience needs #betterquality. https://t.co/TCjPq94naN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What to do with mycoplasma contamination? Helpful comments and further reading @j_perkel #cellculture #betterscience https://t.co/y1xbVL98Rg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many thanks @promega @gsaldanha for highlighting problems with cell line identity #cellculture #authenticate #iclac https://t.co/JTGbdIrLfG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for the link @NancyScience - great that the originators able to share data from donor tissue and STR profile. https://t.co/7brohmD6N9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strange inhabitants of the #cellculture world: #Bat costumed amacrine cell @Thepurplelilac https://t.co/Cuoikpmqup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you know that the EU assigns specific database rights independent of copyright? Me neither! https://t.co/oy6UclAmYK via @NatureNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sample problems suggested by male/female discrepancies, but is this due to loss of the Y chromosome? Hard to know... https://t.co/hiO0J451ku]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Editors @nature: nothing beats reading the journal article. Journal impact factor slowly declining in value? https://t.co/H8si89o2dJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why it's hard for journals to challenge fraudulent science - kudos to those who do! @bmj_latest HT @RetractionWatch https://t.co/yr5cWIbscp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Even if this was one bad batch": cell lines come from cancer so they are heterogeneous by definition. 3/3  https://t.co/3MDStSD9ZD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The test suggested that the cells were genetically identical" but actually looks at donor origin, not heterogeneity https://t.co/3MDStSD9ZD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some inaccuracies in this press release regarding #cellculture #reprodubility 1/3 https://t.co/3MDStSD9ZD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science as a collaborative enterprise encounters hurdles when assigning accolades: case in point, CRISPR @NatureNews https://t.co/hDKCPX3Tyi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The challenges of #cellculture in zero gravity. Feeding and passaging cells in a super-snazzy environment @ISS_CASIS https://t.co/2OUzheHsyk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @ivanoransky @armarcus for writing re misidentified cell lines in publications. Goal = continued improvement. https://t.co/7jzLukw21r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#retractioncon cites @realDonaldTrump: data reveal he has been misidentified as a politician but this is incorrect. https://t.co/fM041rAnZG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see more visibility for retracted articles in PubMed, kudos @hildabast @PubMedCommons https://t.co/axgJ5NkfmS via @RetractionWatch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NancyScience Thanks to you and your collaboration partner for the reply! Some journals moving to #authenticate but many still to decide.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exciting to see new Human Cancer Models Initiative building better cell-based models #cellculture #BetterScience https://t.co/uktXwYRboi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A 30 year perspective on peer review urges more data and training - fascinating. #reproducibility #BetterScience https://t.co/4wFwgG69nE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any journals out there require authors to #authenticate cell lines in submitted manuscripts? Please RT and let me know #cellculture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reproducibility relies on understanding our reagents - important for both cell lines and antibodies #authenticate https://t.co/1b3qgS6Bi3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drawing a (safety) line in the sand: thoughtful article on radiation safety lessons @Tim_Jorgensen https://t.co/elWANQnazu via @aeonmag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful images from Art of Neuroscience competition - particularly impressed by 3D cortical spheroid #cellculture https://t.co/0tzKx7p3F3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ethical reforms needed, but proposed changes will slow research with little gain: approach should vary with the risk https://t.co/0a0QMGJWef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@biochembelle Thanks for sharing our cell line authentication primer @PLOSBiology: lots of challenges &amp; solutions! https://t.co/o4WAHpjqjt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the "digital cell" @quantixed to where it all began: Cells on Film from #cellculture pioneers @scoopit https://t.co/9uYqZPtFgw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A modern day take on imaging and analysis of cells - the "digital cell" @quantixed #cellculture @scoopit https://t.co/f9uHNYW3SM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lteytelman Interesting! Huge no. #cellculture issues also e.g. seeding density can affect reproducibility, see https://t.co/FccgZQeXLF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greatest contributor to #reproducibility? Vote and RT much appreciated! https://t.co/cJJVUDyOEA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Appreciate the comment @theWinnower - publication has costs and someone must pay, but funding not always available. https://t.co/KbzgYbmnQf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spent yesterday looking at lab safety incidents so this article is topical! Laboratory Hazards and Risks @LabManager https://t.co/iKlY3ELTBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#reproducibility means many things to many people - clarity needed for better science, but is one meaning possible? https://t.co/HUNaPvbu81]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An easy way to print @Trello information, code shared via @dcapslock Linked In post. Could be useful @clathrin! https://t.co/dGXehhCHzF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remembering a woman inspired to make the world better - #JoCoxMP now inspiring the world #courage @ITVAllegra https://t.co/ov2nta24KU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using a biosafety cabinet @LabManager - how and when to use it will determine safety #cellculture https://t.co/uNUaKarJ1Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clathrin @quantixed Topic for future would be great, your thoughts on what works and what is a work in progress would be helpful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@quantixed @clathrin Analysis workflow v interesting - would also enjoy your thoughts on reagent databases (and Trello is great resource).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thoughtful perspective on iPS cells and their impact. Therapy has a long trajectory but research is powering on! https://t.co/OOSAj2hv6Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And what does it mean to #authenticate a cell line anyway? Primer @PLOSBiology with cartoon = reward for reading :)https://t.co/UZeQsKHj9E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why use standards when testing cell lines or reagents? Great perspectives @usnistgov @plosbiology #authenticate https://t.co/d6dn6yZIfm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Alexis_Verger Thanks for the link to our list of known misidentified cell lines, much appreciated! #ICLAC #cellculture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MathCancer @lteytelman @PubMedCommons Great to learn about @MultiCellDS! Reproducibility relies on testing to #authenticate cell lines.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lteytelman @MathCancer Retraction or correction can be appropriate depending on situation: agree decision belongs to authors/editor/journal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lteytelman @PubMedCommons Kudos to authors &amp; journals for correcting the record. Post-pub review = improved transparency, much appreciated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating interview with Patrick Soon-Shiong on the need for a cancer "discovery engine" #CancerMoonshot https://t.co/hzTELSEnit @medscape]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clathrin is this your lab sharing morale boosters? Brilliant idea! Need an international #CakeClub competition :) https://t.co/IYh7LPiZHt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful images from breast cancer research @BCRJournal! MDA-MB-231 3D culture is a deserving winner #cellculture https://t.co/xlUnqJU8Zr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thoughtful article @theWinnower on practical measures to enhance #reproducibility - verification funding is needed! https://t.co/iF6QpzVbdq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Browsing open access Lab Resources at Stem Cell Research, great to see stem cell line info published! #cellculture https://t.co/P0SirkIXIv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The internet can be a wonderful thing: 2001 FDA document brings some clarity to origins of HEK-293 #cellculture https://t.co/oewsyuBenJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What can we do to ensure #CancerMoonshot is effective? Focus on #reproducibility will help: https://t.co/jo2Sxmsgvi https://t.co/RiAd3XkMqO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EscoCO2 while the incubator is important good #cellculture practice is key. No guarantees without careful handling. https://t.co/CoXrtKdWTk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good quality data need good quality materials: important to #authenticate or validate #cellculture https://t.co/gUH5IWYFUi HT @kyleserikawa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So true @kyleserikawa - important to authenticate/validate cell lines, mouse strains etc. Worth the time and effort. https://t.co/iTBvcmZGUP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating data here e.g. 26% had #reproducibility procedures in place early, 33% in last 5 yrs. Publicity helping? https://t.co/pIjG9ClXRj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thattai @clathrin Forward yes, steadily no. Effort spent on debate can be better spent (my view), but understanding the words does matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EscoCO2 Good points - also important to #authenticate your culture. Is it the same cell line or is it overgrown by #HeLa/other cells?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thattai @clathrin So true!  Words can be a hot topic of debate e.g. "cell line", "cell strain" and "transformation" https://t.co/IObTr4CUHz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fun look at the microbiome and its possibilities @usnistgov https://t.co/v5kNPI6DdC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Challenges of Cell Culture ... helpful summary of common cell line problems and what to do about them: https://t.co/pHaimmOwUm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ISSCR Thank you for these beautifully detailed guidelines. Massive amount of work, well done to all involved.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>