<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I was not chosen by whim but by Your predetermined Will in all eternity before the beginning of time. You sought me… https://t.co/aMCr3SNQVp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Focus on the goal, not the obstacle. ( Anthony Morrison ) #. https://t.co/TFGKIA2FZX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi Oralia, nice shot. I'm going there on my way to Italy in May. https://t.co/qLDep4Nxc2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unless they are mulims. https://t.co/dSXzG7txdX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm with you Mike. https://t.co/IHyuE8ZkL0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's a reality TV actor. He does not even make a politician's little finger. I thought The USA was great but now ju… https://t.co/dSqURqWZSK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cacti are found only in American deserts. Tallest R SAGUAROS reaching 50 ft tall. Live for 200 years. Weigh 7 tons. https://t.co/HYfOI0M8QU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The muslims are evil. Now every'one is calling Europe EURABIA. That bastard Angela Merkel has got to go. https://t.co/8kCwN9STGF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You become what you think about. ( Anthony Morrison ) #. https://t.co/g7OfrED1yO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The two most EVIL men that were ever born on this planet. https://t.co/U262RIAy3v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmyDaniel212  Hi Amy. Your TWITTER wallpaper and account are awesome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Christ is with me, then nothing be against me. https://t.co/os8TRnghZz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If bacon grew on trees I'd be a vegetarian. https://t.co/8EyUyF2nUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She always has been and always will be a totally boring disaster. https://t.co/ZPV8N8DdZ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AngeliaHubbar14  I really dig your TWITTER wall'paper Angelina.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had the blues because I had no shoes, when upon the street I met a man who had no feet. https://t.co/gflzwGCUVK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pebblesnwood  I will be in my home'town Munchen, 15/5 to 15/8 Alles Beste.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi Claudia. Yes, sleep long, live long. Sleep is the best medicine for every'thing x x https://t.co/F1f90z3szV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donaldo tramp is to Politics what Liberace was to pumping iron. https://t.co/YcFbnZnOtT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even the grated big stones @ the center are good for you. https://t.co/thM9u4iOB7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I look @ this I know we have a Great God displaying his immaculate handiwork. But showing us drops of his Merc… https://t.co/DKX6TsOD21]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is a great deal easier to do that which God gives us to do, no matter how hard it is, than to face the responsib… https://t.co/4PmPvBMnJu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The awe of The Lord is the beginning of knowledge but the morally deficient despise wisdom &amp; discipline. ( Prov 1:7… https://t.co/xvQqH9GXY1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eat sparingly and @ regular hours. https://t.co/G93phvYtYu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And if a door does not appear, build one. https://t.co/YBvp23cOPo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Sahara Desert in North Africa is The World's largest @ 8400000 sq km. https://t.co/oxI9bJvK1X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Fed mints / prints money out of NOTHING. That's why The USA economy is known internationally as The Casino Econ… https://t.co/vCHaRdUrHO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You might be a dick'head if you think The Stock'market has a fence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have always known you &amp; loved you, from the moment of your existence and before the beginning of time. ( from Psa… https://t.co/RBsi94WZXf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life does not get any easier, you just get stronger. ( Anthony Morrison ) #. https://t.co/EQGysKtoNq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May you always do what you are afraid to do. ( Anthony Morrison ) #. https://t.co/aV2jqn7d9h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sooner we see the end of these has beens the better. https://t.co/ebQ4k0sEIg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Christian in his right mind would want to go to Iran any'way. These bastards have so much blood on their hands. https://t.co/gPgEEz719K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fo5tered  I really dig your TWITTER wallpaper Ed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TOE = A device for finding furniture in the dark. https://t.co/8BQ3ltWI78]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deserts cover about 20% of The Earth's land surface. Sand accounts for only about 15% of our desert regions. https://t.co/lFkrjU2xSL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never lose interest in life and The World. https://t.co/OKQoTFZhx4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cancer can not survive in an alkaline environment so eat as much yogurt &amp; drink as much milk as will agree with you. https://t.co/lNbS0qWAug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What'ever a man seeks, honors or exalts more than God, is idolatry. ( William Ullanthorne ) #. https://t.co/R8KfqAbFZt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I started jogging to keep in shape but soon gave it up because the ice cubes kept falling out of my glass. https://t.co/gZRCQNQ49c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, a million times better than that rap crap and punk junk. https://t.co/wqSQrKeOL3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In all your ways acknowledge Him and He will make your paths straight &amp; direct you. ( Proverbs 3:6 ). https://t.co/CerjClRqvl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If they can make Penicillin out of mouldy bread, surely they can make some'thing out of donaldo tramp ? https://t.co/3J6nz5Zw8r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you are a loveable one of a kind with lasting personal worth; unique in The Universe; complete in Christ, headed fo… https://t.co/bGHspRV5gq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You never fail until you stop trying. ( Anthony Morrison ) #. https://t.co/OiXKgbHPMi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Belgium can not be worse than the horrors in switzweland Daniela. Even those arrogant french are not as bad. https://t.co/qPYE30BLjO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The key to success is often the ability to adapt. ( Anthony Morrison ) #. https://t.co/2qVCx3O65Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NADIANASREDDINE  Hi Nadia. Thinking of you. I trust you are well and thriving. x x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do you say you have APES all around you ? https://t.co/1pPZbRdbgv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where are you now Daniela ? Still in the land of brussels sprouts ? Why do you say you have monsters around you ? L… https://t.co/fOOxfjvRhM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She looks like a total incompetent; like all tramp supporters. https://t.co/adqxa8UdYW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donaldo tramp has no more back'bone than a chocolate eclair. https://t.co/mZqKxefylP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who does not forbid sin when he can, encourages it. https://t.co/o4O35aDaBI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trust in The Lord with all your heart and lean not on your own understanding. ( Prov 2:5 ). https://t.co/Yj1jXfUnoJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rap crap. No melody. It's worse than punk junk. https://t.co/mUdYZJ2iBe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What one does OFF the job is the determining factor on how far one will go ON the job. https://t.co/Wlqx8jN6BZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rice is the only grass that grows in water. The main food of more than 50% of The World's population. 90% grown in… https://t.co/xgOG4gIO2m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There were two people walking down the street. One was an artist. The other one did not have a job either. https://t.co/ZQsZzhmJwx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are a living testimony to my creative handiwork. There is no'one else like you any'where in my creation. ( from… https://t.co/DLTUCZYUNK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fear regret more than failure. ( Anthony Morrison ) #. https://t.co/YcIZ5tDPSb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not limit your challenges; challenge your limits. ( Anthony Morrison ) #. https://t.co/1rvGt677C2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do council workers &amp; sperm have in common ? ..... Only one in two million does any work. https://t.co/X4mp8MajML]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The largest wheat'field on The Planet is in Alberta, Canada, covering an area of 55 sq miles, ( 20000 football fiel… https://t.co/eiW6y95juD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A goal is a dream with a deadline. https://t.co/ZFZKCkqpZg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How beyond golden is the Faith. https://t.co/JQiveu87ZY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God does not call the qualified; He qualifies the called. ( George Barna ) #. https://t.co/lqqKqmoTH8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our society is not a community radiant with the love of Jesus but a dangerous network of domination &amp; manipulation. https://t.co/LeFWFlUqKI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let love &amp; faithfulness never leave you; bind them around your neck. Write them on the tablet of your heart. ( Prov… https://t.co/6HMAqXl42S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donaldo tramp is the same old sausage fizzing and sputtering in his own grease. https://t.co/aUHsFUaoVm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donaldo tramp has the attention span of a bolt of lightning. https://t.co/rHNx2TXmtD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donaldo tramp is the type of man who will end up dying in his own arms. https://t.co/Vr9MJiRkqM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our Lord is He who goes with us to fight against our enemies to save us. https://t.co/toRW3hUi25]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have over'come The World. I have deprived it of power to harm you. Fear not and do not tremble. https://t.co/rw33UlQ41e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In me you have perfect peace. In the world you have trials and distress but be of good cheer. https://t.co/VCuaOSy7qN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can not improve what you do not measure. ( Anthony Morrison ) #. https://t.co/w9Z55K6KRi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May you always do what you are afraid to do. ( Anthony Morrison ) #. https://t.co/D4jpSBEK4T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are more than 5000 species of frogs and toads on The Planet. ( David Attenborough ) #. https://t.co/kUqIdGKXxH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learning is a gift when pain is your teacher. ( Anthony Morrison ) #. https://t.co/IKJjuAHJkX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Work hard; dream big. ( Anthony Morrison ) #. https://t.co/vZX2Km8Sws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is fattening as it will give you the crunchies. https://t.co/KFar2B1BfT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Save The Planet and be buried in a plywood box standing up, ( unless You tire easilly ) or be cremated &amp; have your… https://t.co/ZTmRicjvgA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi Rose honey. Gosh he looks an aweful lot like Frank Sinatra. x x https://t.co/h6d84BJ0hD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kinky is when you tickle your lover's bum with a feather. Perverted is when you use the whole live chicken.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ability will never catch up with the demand for it. ( Confucius ) #. https://t.co/R1pu0R13f9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exactly. No'one in their right mind or an OC ignoramus would have the audacity to ring you @ ungodly hours. https://t.co/l3MgPhsGTD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right now it's Thursday, 26/1. Time is, 0115 am. https://t.co/xzbmWap8Uw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, for sure Daniela. I turn my phone off when I go to bed.If my land'line rings in the middle of the night I do… https://t.co/tvD4rIPIwU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If some'one tries to shoot donaldo tramp ..... will his body'guards shout, " DONALD, DUCK " ? https://t.co/1NqaKzJPh7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanielaSmits   My landline from within NZ is 04-9340880 and my mobile android is 021 045 0066, ie : 0210450066.The prefix for NZ is, 0064.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[75% of accidents are caused by people &amp; 95% of people are caused by accidents. https://t.co/aUY4K8TUiF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JUST REMEMBER DANIELA. YOU &amp; NADIA ARE GEMS AND YOU KNOW THAT GEMS ARE HARD TO FIND. x x  :-) https://t.co/RJUtGVd9xf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exactly Daniela. YOU &amp; NADIA are my favourites. YOU ALWAYS CHEER ME UP WHEN I AM DOWN x x  :-) https://t.co/cXgvEcRdF6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHEN YOU COME TO NEW ZEALAND, YOU CAN SAVE HEAPS IF YOU STAY WITH ME IN MY NICE APARTMENT IN THE SKY DANIELA. https://t.co/yJnyND3zm3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello cheeky face Nadia. Luv, cheeky face, Nicky. https://t.co/K5EzMgkMnV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow u sure get around dear Daniela. Brussels sprouts fried in sesame oil is one of my favourites. https://t.co/eDtN5nh2KF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You and Nadia are both my favourite favourites dear Daniela x x It's Thursday, 26/1. https://t.co/1NqaKzJPh7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks Daniela. I am so busy working; Proof Reading for Government I will be up all night working. The upside is a… https://t.co/9wX50yXEld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@osacay Gr8 to be on'board with you Osa.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eldiablo0786 @DanielaSmits @MitsiGiorgis @BluesignV @NADIANASREDDINE  HERE IN NEW ZEALAND IT IS NOW WEDNESDAY 2345. ALL THE BEST.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Top 5 Followers: @DanielaSmits, @MitsiGiorgis, @eldiablo0786, @BluesignV, @NADIANASREDDINE. Find Yours Free at https://t.co/kiAYs7a35p]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>