<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[This level of fubar usually takes weeks to develop :( https://t.co/pOSuxG21sb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We don't say thank you enough, thanks to everyone that did :) https://t.co/vHaef8iPrs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see that more and more people are reading New Scientist and the Economist https://t.co/rnqTJ9ba7y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WGladstone Nobody talks about because we're busy living it :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simongarlick Apparently Musk thinks a compromise is possible. He's dreaming, as always]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simongarlick I count 3 female managers. It certainly looks unbalanced but I'm guessing they recruit from outside, or the policy is newish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PVickers "strong likelihood ... would violate their rights ... as guaranteed by the Constitution". That's as strong as a judge can make it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FluffyMcduff @kmesquire @jason_pontin That means he's ignoring 1/3 of your constitutional bodies. So he's unconstitutional whatever he does]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ktwolf @AymanM it's a sad day when you have to ask that :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simongarlick Human? Mostly white &amp; female but some diversity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it possible that following Trump's plan would be an improvement for Australia? I know it's a bullet train wreck… https://t.co/aVyojueMAm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would gone for excessively pro-active alcohol harm reduction officer but Nanny State scans better https://t.co/bps1b8U8hx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brycepearce @nzherald I for one, welcome the new super power based on surfing, movies, and computing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarristerNZ We shouldn't've been helping them for at least the last 15 years :-/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wendy_nm @joshrogin @washingtonpost You Yankees are so cute, thinking that you actually have left wingers in the Government :-D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnDiesattheEn @NewsfromScience traditionally a back-down means that they'll wait 6 months and then do it a little more subtly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ctOSLeader @GeorgeSaysHi @EduardoLattes @Daanm19821 @Ty_A_Rutherford @HamillHimself Haha! I got caught with Muphry's Law :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeeganNYC Who was the author? Online magazines can be 99% blog, and 1% journalist contributions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MorganGodfery and objectively wrong. Let's hope they don't need the original study replicated before they'll believe it :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tanepiper he'd probably just say: "you're so right, completely false. Like the lies from the media, so false. Nasty media" :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gandalf with a Dr Who scarf and a Star Trek meme. Presumably he’s representing for Princess Leia https://t.co/UuyOFidkPx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jacopo_della_Q Always relevant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnDiesattheEn  You have to speak to people in a language they understand. Sometimes that means Spanish, sometimes Elbownian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm glad that Trump quoting the Bee Movie is fiction. It was hilarious but ultimately too ludicrous :( https://t.co/NM31q2v2Q0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katystoll not The Manchurian Candidate?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been wondering if the ephemeral nature of Twitter would clash with the presidential records legislation: https://t.co/N3hUQBvXtq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamieRoss7 @nushyb to all those people: QEII herself has made our feelings clear already https://t.co/VkUnsd3XLG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Women's March is now the definition of a successful march https://t.co/YVOyCCtUK4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What else can we con Trump into plastering large pictures of in the WH press briefing room? https://t.co/VXXwgFb5BF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jtacket33 @mulvihill79 They couldn't call in sick to see their glorious victory in person? They're not very committed to their cause :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@the_under_score @mulvihill79 What sort of grand social movement is so ambivalent they don't turn up to see their leader take power?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@the_under_score @mulvihill79 This is a silly statement: they think Trump is awesome but they can't take a day off to celebrate his big day?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can see the grass, it's a small crowd :-D https://t.co/UW53gRF6qA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeorgeSaysHi @EduardoLattes @Daanm19821 @Ty_A_Rutherford @HamillHimself He's secretly keeping the the market for 4-door cars alive? Odd.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonrosenberg @piersmorgan Does Piers not know that the Million Man March has already happened?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simongarlick @newtgingrich that's some impressive sycophancy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KnightWing19 @PNtlhophi @keithboykin Mate, you're talking to everyone and arguing with someone that agreed with you :-D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KnightWing19 @PNtlhophi @keithboykin whatever dude, you picked a fight and then refused to front up. Up your game or stop playing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KnightWing19 @PNtlhophi @keithboykin Mate, I agree with your initial statement but now you're going to have get some sound bites :-D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Movie advice: don't see @LionMovie , just go straight to https://t.co/wfd5TfmRhA and give them all your money. It's easier...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fibbyccino For Cake Club? https://t.co/gfIkfIJkgz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brycepearce @BicycleDutch Hills? Where? Just ride around the volcanoes! Sheesh...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenDohertyCorro @BarristerNZ @DIBPAustralia @guardian truly a spectacularly stupid policy and implementation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ianapperley @ScoopWellington Killed by the anti-fun brigade :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MorganGodfery Agreed. On the upside at least it wasn't Mel Gibson and a poly version of Braveheart :-/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys! Actual instructions on how not to be creepy: https://t.co/GrpzxKNAOb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's lovely living in a modern society with a functioning health system, Yanks should try it sometime. https://t.co/Ygq3jXI8xN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tanepiper you may be confusing England with Britain but that's understandable :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's writing prompt is for a dystopian science fiction novel: https://t.co/rtcJAmpJi8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katystoll @guardian So, it's a dead issue already then?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simongarlick @EricCrampton I propose a national morning celebration followed by an national afternoon of shame and excuses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johncheese Mitchell's angry rants have their own playlist on QI's YouTube. Worth a watch for his insight &amp; elocution while being klaxoned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonrosenberg we can never return this genie to his bottle, all we can do is watch and try to stop him :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johncheese I have, but Maoris are much happier about Honkies than your POC are with Yankees and Dixies :-D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dtaylor5633 @mungler Ahem: "first they ignore you, then they laugh at you, then they fight you, then you win". "They" are apparently at #2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free skate, for the falling off of. https://t.co/A3KE3TKl0n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#strawberrypocalpse https://t.co/IPJ4xSg6wr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ParburyWill @WingsScotland Umm, Don't Know is winning in 6 out of 9 issues. You guys really need to fix your political parties :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the Nicky Nicky Chocolate Bickie Spot, enjoying the view #Wellington https://t.co/roCyifSE2w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Wellington has dinosaurs at the botanic gardens. Come walk the dinosaur :) https://t.co/5Aiw9Yz2zh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Classic @RtHon_JohnKey, only missing the "well that's contested" https://t.co/h2olloEoj7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tanepiper at that point, irony and idiocy with merge to form "irdiony": A new element similar to Kryptonite but for intellectuals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tanepiper @ManusBlessing @PaulBrannenNE hmmm, optimistic ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ManusBlessing @tanepiper @PaulBrannenNE isn't that actual treason? Excluding the head of state from the most important thing in 20yrs?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me: bill please!
She: let's put it on Housekeeping
Me: cocktails are groceries? This is an awesome relationship #marriage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wannabikkit Yepsh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone needs to go to The Juniper just off Featherston Str and ask for The Hulk #greenandproud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Salamino15 Manners Str, next to the hairdresser that does African braids (Pigeon Park)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WGladstone E.g. "Only sissies threaten Putin by stockpiling nukes, a real man just rips his shirt off and punches Putin's face"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mungler tho shalt not use ActiveRecord?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice to know that someone else does this :) https://t.co/IzvlP9qvWN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada winning on the appropriate ministers in cabinet: https://t.co/rldOpIKWcw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We subjected a 40 year old Kiwi male to DNCE's Cake By The Ocean for 5 hours, you won't believe what happened next!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep: "through-out the 5500 year history of our planet". Egypt has over 6000 years of history. Science has 4.5 billi… https://t.co/8LpgP5SNu6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jacopo_della_Q "... trapped forever in the moment of asking 'turn people to dolls? Is that really a thing you can do?'"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonrosenberg WWSGD (what would squirrel girl do?)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dat1cinnamon Sanders, Rubio, Jeb seemed like the nicest Bush. HRC is just the last in a long line. You need less "bad" and more "better"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dat1cinnamon Mate, we've been sitting here watching you crazies toss good people aside so you could vote for an ugly Kardashian. "So sad"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dat1cinnamon The policy he hasn’t done yet, which will cost $9T, and will give him a 7% tax decrease?  Or some other tax policy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dat1cinnamon Yeah, nah, I’m good mate.  If you can’t think of anything off the top your head, I’ve got better things to do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rnz_news @BarristerNZ I'm very sorry to say this but, Damages &amp; Costs is not a victory. It's a price to do illegal policing :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dat1cinnamon @MyLoveUntitled @CandaceSmith_ in the interest of learning, please name a good thing Trump has done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cjsbishop Disgraceful? You mean like fondling little girls' ponytails or giving millions of taxpayer money to Saudi princes? Silly man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PluperfectNemo @JRRParker Dude, we've been mocking Tom Cruise's height for 2 decades. Good argument, bad example]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarristerNZ "like" as in "similar to, but not actually"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Whiner In Chief? https://t.co/9CGfTiuevc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was excellent walking along Lambton Quay Sunday &amp; people managed to survive w/o their cars. Can you make it permanent @WgtnCC ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was excellent walking along Lambton Quay Sunday &amp; people managed to survive w/o their cars. Can you make it permanent @Wellington_NZ ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fibbyccino LOL! No, I did not :-D Serves me right for not checking :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Soozn79 @NewYorker Were they more feminist than Nancy Drew? Cos she was awesome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bclevinger never seen Moonstruck, are there many explosions or laser swords?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bclevinger I agree as my wife just viewed it for the 1st time and declared it "a Xmas movie". Jedi are obviously Force Fundamentalists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wannabikkit we could fix that too :-D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wannabikkit most of them do, but that's just routing issue. Besides, w/o cars, it would be possible to have walkers and buses: Amsterdamish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was excellent walking along Lambton Quay today &amp; people managed to survive w/o their cars. Can you make it permanent @Wellycc ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarb @saniac it's a start, and then they need to arrange studies that measure the effectiveness of the implementation. Knowledge is power]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@saniac @sarb maybe they believe in delivering policy that is shown to work?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the company owns your hobby, get a better company. https://t.co/Iwm0OArKY4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nick_Craver @YouTube is that, is that a good Vulture? OMG!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HORansome @MorganGodfery @toby_etc I am lucky enough to live in a country where my premier can have 3 terms before I discover his religion]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>