<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing says a Saturday afternoon off like re-installing audio editing software!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DocNaismith @ShelAlexander @ChallengeMTV Setting up my PVR now. I think MTV has a Rivals 1 marathon on right now if you need a fix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@criseyde Heyman, Dudleyz, RVD, Jericho, Bam Bam, Sabu, Storm, Malenko, maybe Douglas, Raven and Dreamer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@criseyde He'd be my headliner. Outside of Vince, he's the most influential person in modern wrestling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@criseyde Personally I think they should do a class that is 100 per cent ECW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@criseyde Lance Storm, maybe Cornette or Mysterio? Outside chance Chavo? Malenko?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@criseyde I was so happy when they started selling Owens gym shorts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Curt_Magurt1 @ChallengeMTV @ShelAlexander We can negotiate guest spots]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As any of my friends know, I'm obsessed with @ChallengeMTV. Me &amp; @ShelAlexander are putting that love into a podcast https://t.co/YWKrgF9qrb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally watching NXT TakeOver from San Antonio. I love that the Authors of Pain's names are an Occam's Razor pun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you ready for the 29th season of @ChallengeMTV? No? Then listen to me and @ShelAlexander's new podcast https://t.co/YWKrgF9qrb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me and @ShelAlexander have come together like Voltron to do a podcast on the new season of @ChallengeMTV. Check it: https://t.co/YWKrgFr1PL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WEMovement @CaraGeeeee Excellent Q&amp;A and Cara you're beautiful in those pics!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone at the New York Times is not feeling the Super Bowl https://t.co/XaSQHRdJkl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blade Mann-Dixon is the best name in all of junior hockey, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@criseyde @eatspecialk I was trying to explain that the New Day are right up her alley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's that time of year where I catch myself saying things like "Man, the Lethbridge Hurricanes are really rolling right now..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VictoriaAhearn GIF game on point]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And one of Canada's best amateur golfers! https://t.co/pRgx1gHNw6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@criseyde "that time he did a moonsault off of a fat guy"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdrianKLee so soon? Wasn't yesterday Black Tuesday?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ADeMeltCTV Yes. It's ruined my life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@siomo in fairness, they are considered weapons of war]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm about to get my first-ever filling but Sukhinder, my cab driver, was very reassuring. He said I shouldn't be scared]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too real. https://t.co/27chwcXQQw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShelAlexander Do it for Vethamany!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm collaborating on a project with @ShelAlexander for the first time since OAC Law. Can't wait for you guys to see what we're up to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love that they continue to call him Handsome Rusev #Raw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theory: Braun Strowman is secretly Dewey Foley. It's why @RealMickFoley keeps giving him what he wants #Raw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great work by my colleague @GregoryStrongCP speaking with @EppingJohn about the support he received after coming out https://t.co/OLhNFwjqrt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That said, thoughts and prayers only take you so far. It's important that we fight intolerance in all forms and learn to love our neighbours]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just this weekend I was talking about how much I love Quebec City. My thoughts and prayers are with those affected by last night's shooting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chekhov's folding chair pyramid #RoyalRumble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaddyGurks heck yeah!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can I please watch the WWE in their promo videos and no the one that's on Raw every week?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm rewatching trailers from the @ChallengeMTV and I'm getting so hype for the next season to start. It's going to be incredible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats @ScottyMacThinks! One of my favourite guys in the press box. https://t.co/D0moH61YJI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@s_findlay Spend that money you earned working for free on more expensive envelopes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyanBMcKenna They're both from my constituency! Premier Wynne's kids went to Wanless and she ran the PTA, Mayor Tory attended Bedford Park]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kathleen Wynne v. John Tory. Battle of North Toronto! John Wanless v. Bedford Park! https://t.co/BoUvWB7PT8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@criseyde Hopefully some day they'll pull out of it. Until then... NXT!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@criseyde It's that damn 50-50 booking they use on Raw! NXT gets it right and stays PG. Owens and Joe were/are both effective heels on NXT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@criseyde Can the WWE bring back a competent heel of any kind on Raw? I'd love the Chris and Kevin run better if they were more devious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My mom just made a "cash me ow side" joke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ric Flair your entire life has been lit. https://t.co/vxo5cVhh0l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How mild is this winter? A woman in a halter top just walked by me at King and Portland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaraGeeeee Thanks cuz! Not just for the tweet, but all the love and support during some tough times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Christie_P83 Thanks Christie! I did the thing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaraMcK I was scared to share this because I do feel that stigma, that it will be held against me. Thanks for sharing your story too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mich_mcq There definitely is a stigma too. I had one (now former) friend mock me for seeing a therapist. Being open helps end that stigma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mich_mcq Thanks Michelle! I hope the tweets inspire someone to seek help themselves]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@siomo Thanks SioMo! I appreciate the kind words. And confirmation that I'll always be the only Chud in your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marygazze Thanks Mary! I appreciate the support. I was hesitant at first but my hope is that it helps someone else out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyway, back to jokes about wrestling, rap music, 1990s pop culture and bad puns.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emathieuStar Thanks Emily! I appreciate the support. I was unsure if I should even post it but then said "what the hell!" and went for it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobsonDan Thanks Dan! It also taught me that our writing can affect people's lives in unexpected ways and that what we do has a real impact]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's lots to learn from my story. 1) Talking helps. 2) There are lots of resources out there 3) It will get better #BellLetsTalk 8/8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With her help, I've made incredible progress. I'm good 98 per cent of the time. The other two per cent I know how to deal #BellLetsTalk 7/?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But because of that book I saw how unhealthy, how toxic, I had become. So I started seeing a trauma counsellor #BellLetsTalk 6/?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But I hadn't told anyone how much it affected me. I told myself I was just grieving. I soldiered through. #BellLetsTalk 5/?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Y'see, my dad had dropped dead of a heart attack in Feb. 2013 and I had found his body four days later. It fucked me up. #BellLetsTalk 4/?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I reached out to my therapist from when I was getting divorced and, in Dec. 2014, I was diagnosed with PTSD myself. #BellLetsTalk 3/?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As I read Malarchuk's story about his struggles with anxiety and PTSD I realized I had some similar symptoms #BellLetsTalk 2/?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back in Oct. 2014 my buddy @RobsonDan wrote a book w/ Clint Malarchuk called The Crazy Game. I bought a copy at the launch 1/? #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThrowinSmoke I'll talk only if it's with Maddux]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nickacoates I can take your game to another level]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nickacoates I could have told you that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoePack Things that make you go hmmmm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is an interesting move from the IIHF. https://t.co/SS4DMp71n0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm catching up on the Bachelor and here's my only question: is Corinne a sociopath or a psychopath? I'm leaning toward the former.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jackie_Redmond It's a good look for you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@s_findlay I just can't get over the guy's look. THAT was the most attractive teenage male in all of Ireland in 1998?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm teaching @eatspecialk about the wonders/horrors of B*Witched's C'est La Vie. That guy's belt is cinched SO tight https://t.co/a52Iess7no]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@criseyde This article is what convinced me to change my habits About halfway down he starts explaining things https://t.co/NsSdISMnPY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@criseyde Squad! Squad! Squad! (do people still say that?) But, yeah, the no screens policy has made a huge difference for my insomnia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marygazze If @Twitter wanted to make real money they'd let people edit their tweets for a monthly subscription fee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@criseyde Also, thanks for following me back!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@criseyde I've made a point of not looking at a computer or TV screen for at least an hour before bed. It's made a huge difference]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrBrandonStroud @sundownmotel @YouTube I don't remember it at all and this is the first I've heard of it. But I kinda like it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marygazze that makes sense! It's just weird to me because it's the worst time for Hollywood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't tell you how badly I wish their theme songs played https://t.co/xlhwx2Bayn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Serious question: why do they announce Oscar nominations so damn early?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Whatever you do, make sure Roman looks really strong," - CM Punk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jphoornstra It was custom made! Has MEXICO stitched on over top of the Vick paint letters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elrines it was a gag gift where someone had made me a Ron Mexico jersey https://t.co/JQMAta1kCc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@the_Zubes pretty sure they're deployed whenever I'm running late for work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The good news is I own an Atlanta Falcons jersey. The bad news is it says MEXICO on the back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@the_Zubes Queen's Quay streetcars are going to take years off my life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is, officially, the most I've liked the Patriots. Ever. https://t.co/PNPqYmPK8Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tweeting this is the best thing I've done today. RT it and make it the best thing you do today. hoodclips's video https://t.co/2yqaIqbjxL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tyler_harper could you please at least change your team name to the EDM Oilers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tyler_harper This is the darkest timeline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@s_findlay most importantly, Just Blaze retweeted it himself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Started my day at work with a phone call to @erik_read. Here was the result https://t.co/2ve2wGnYD8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tyler_harper Team Rocket tho https://t.co/ejUA8GIZAf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This was really cool! Can't wait to see more https://t.co/qYLAcEioOo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WongSN590 too bad it's overshadowing the Revival calling TM61 tilapia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@siomo I'm pretty sure if more than 50 people are together one spontaneously appears]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are rumours the Oilers are going to experiment with cloning. They're going to be Letes-tube babies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got to speak with @JDufourLapointe, @MikaelKingsbury and @andi_naude this afternoon after their banner day on the… https://t.co/taCTbWjB8r]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>