<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@lisasetepenre Yes! Take all the encouragement you can get :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deedot255 Neighbours is known for its verisimilitude]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Alicedkc That is... insane.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haha! You win. This is true. But only 12 years before him :) https://t.co/5YJhttCvZ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cheprin Hilarious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cheprin His real-life mother is white. That said, I am mostly annoyed by the age thing. She's only 12 years older than him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fifail Hahah, yeah, I just checked. Stupid Hollywood.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Equiatic_Bind Face/Off, Barton Fink, Fire Walk With Me, CastAway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fifail Yeah, she's really not. That's a Hollywood trend - any woman over 40 can play any guy under 40's mother.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cheprin Oh, interesting! That might have made slightly more sense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#BatesMotel Season 5 trailer https://t.co/RWiwPAhqM0 We all go a little #psycho sometimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which casting director looked at Nicole Kidman and thought "yeah, she could be Jason Momoa's mum"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@likeadeuce Totally. And I'm seeing it being shared on FB as a "reasonable argument" and it just isn't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jetgirl78 Shout-out to all the Americans who have finally done the same]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, let's stop pretending that publishing on Medium means anything. https://t.co/qN7EK7NRRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Anotherfilmnerd @RDudle You leave Sam Elliott's voice out of this!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mvddm Need photos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RDudle Watch Shawshank. The rest you can skip.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jazifer ARGH, this makes me so mad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deedot255 That article is from Dec 2015, although I'm sure it's near the top of his agenda.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@euro_trashed Oh lord, that's awkward.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter eggs haven't evolved much past this. https://t.co/VxDTHNJX7d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcterzakis Still a better movie than The World Is Not Enough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deedot255 People who get paid to spruik things on Instagram.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jazifer Trump: Bringing Families Together since January 20. 2017.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not always easy talking about politics with my parents, but thankfully we all agree that Trump is batshit insane. So there's that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deedot255 The burden of watching torrents/streaming 😉]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deedot255 No the Sheriff killed him. I had forgotten that too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time for a woman. https://t.co/jEGovg0d5p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jazifer Show him photographs of stairs!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, I'd like to say I'm surprised @TurnbullMalcolm but this is the least surprising thing you've chosen to ignore. https://t.co/O7baiRkEqp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dylanjakemorris The angel in you, the devil in me. Kinky.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Anotherfilmnerd @Equiatic_Bind I have not seen Django Unchained.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Anotherfilmnerd Wait... what is this referencing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brocklesnitch Gritty Hot Tub Time Machine reboot?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@P_Hendrickson But also you don't say doctress or authoress, do you? I feel like awards shows are the ones keeping actress alive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@P_Hendrickson I know. Such nerds we are 😃]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@P_Hendrickson I guess they invented the word because women weren't allowed to be actors for centuries?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@P_Hendrickson This is definitely something my female actor friends have noticed is more prevalent in the US. Here they are actors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@P_Hendrickson No, it isn't redundant because actor is not gender-specific 😊]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@P_Hendrickson You could just use actor. But if you must specify gender, female actor is the same as female doctor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's a pretty fatal flaw when it comes to musicals. https://t.co/NvnBYksrdB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Season four of #BatesMotel was its best season. I am very reason for season five now. Bring it on. #Psycho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any day now, hopefully. https://t.co/Fh7jVPqCDV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump has already declared his candidacy for 2020. This is madness. Read the thread. https://t.co/7lPVhYgO83]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4x08. Another piece falls into place. Heartbreaking. #BatesMotel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robwillb I'm watching ep 8 now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robwillb Where did you stop?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robwillb I was wondering if you'd managed to finish it yet. I'll probably get through it tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freddie Highmore has been great this whole show but he's really kicked it up a notch in S4 with the recurring Norma/n split #BatesMotel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Impressed with how focused this show has become this season; very little feels redundant unlike previous years. #BatesMotel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nearing the end of season 4 of #BatesMotel and... the oddball tone is slowly giving way to tragedy and the pain of inevitability.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@likeadeuce That's where they moved to after being born in Kyrgyzstan, which is not long before they went to the US.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They were born in Kyrgyzstan, which is not Russia. Kyrgyzstan is also not on the list. https://t.co/LL7cz1vemN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do you sleep at night? And I don't mean upside-down in your cave. https://t.co/sw0toUoh8D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Equiatic_Bind Yeah, it boggles my mind that sort of ignorance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia and the United States have a lot in common, including their woeful, abhorrent treatment of refugees. https://t.co/W06pgETtEx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tara_Calaby And she has her beautiful wife back :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robwillb This is a nightmare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmilyJackCO Yes, it crossed my mind after the alt-gov't feeds popped up. But now it feels like a state of emergency.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robwillb A friend of mine who lives in NY on a green card traveled back here for Xmas. She'll get back in because she's white.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robwillb There are people with green cards who traveled and aren't being allowed back in. That's insane.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@squideye It's not but we've seen armed police forces mobilised against US citizens and protestors before, even recently.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jazifer Yes, that's a great point. Our leaders need to be better, but I'm not sure they are. Ours don't like refugees either :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xfkirsten Yes, I can already see how difficult this must be from the other side of the world. Living there it must be terrifying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xfkirsten Yeah, the GOP narrative that the East &amp; West coasts are out of touch belies the fact the interior is so insular]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xfkirsten It's not. And it's great to see Americans resisting. But it fills be with despair that this is happening over there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And because most of my Twitter feed is Americans, I feel like I'm at the centre of it - and I should be, because I'm scared for them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm seeing lawyers in New York gather on Facebook to triage arrivals at airports. And the alt-gov't Twitter accounts trying to get truth out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right now it feels like American citizens are using Twitter &amp; Facebook the same way it was used in Egypt during the Arab Spring of 2011.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tara_Calaby Welcome home, Tara! @fifail Glad you've arrived safely in the US, Fi :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PJSActor The best 😭]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's an episode of Sliders not Black Mirror so I'm fine with it. https://t.co/42anLDs7bJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Maizysgrrrl I dunno, I think accuracy is pretty important even though the bigger picture is also important]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Hurt in The Proposition https://t.co/pGY5ybE1Ql]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@euro_trashed Ha! I've always heard the opposite. The characters of Company are already a chorus, why not an orchestra? I don't agree though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@euro_trashed Yup. He did the same thing with Sweeney Todd which I think would have been more egregious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Hurt played Winston Smith in the film version of 1984, so of course he couldn't have lived through what's happening today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crediting John Hurt as "Harry Potter actor" in the headline of his obit is so ridiculous. Also, every Brit actor ever will also suffer this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jadegrrrl The internet is wrong. Good lord.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deedot255 Holy fuck. And why has she decided to admit this now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@P_Hendrickson They're delicious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ben1283 I already had no interest and now... less than none]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Try to enjoy them while your country becomes a fascist state, America. https://t.co/yzbOmkUPvX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ben1283 Where the hell is that extra 40 minutes coming from? That's an extra 50% of the original's runtime?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deedot255 Oh sure. They'll be fine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deedot255 Well, sure. I think all the credits are at the end of La La Land but Pasek and Paul are in the fine print. Seems wrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deedot255 Admittedly, in theatre the opposite happens. The lyricist is best known and the script/book writer is less known.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deedot255 ... Pasek and Paul are left to get credits when the songs are listed, which are right near the end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deedot255 Classic MGM musicals credited the screen writers and the music/lyric writers up front...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#LaLaLand is credited as "Written By Damien Chazelle" which, as a musical, should require equal billing for lyricists Pasek and Paul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Anotherfilmnerd They should make a movie together]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Anotherfilmnerd But also every Richard Curtis movie ever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robwillb Thank you for the perfect setup :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Anotherfilmnerd WELL, ACTUALLY...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@P_Hendrickson @theerinmaher Well, actually... you're right 😉]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robwillb I was about to Google fringing. It sounds sexual.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robwillb ...but apparently now, some people use it to encompass more than that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robwillb Well, also mansplaining doesn't really mean making corrections. It's a specific patronising "know it all" kind of thing...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robwillb Also, in this day and age of "alternative facts" I feel like making corrections is important. Esp. when mistakes are retweeted]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>