<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[US judge temporarily blocks Trump’s travel ban nationwide - The Washington Post https://t.co/SCXuPNU9xq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump said he’ll ‘totally destroy’ the Johnson Amendment. What is it and why should people care? - Washington Post https://t.co/cw7mco2Pn3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Australia does not put  America 1st, like in Rio, a crooked Aus basketball team almost beat Team USA. Not good!' https://t.co/mMF7eommpS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gold. 
"It's about time someone attacked Australia. Thank you, President Trump." https://t.co/mMF7eommpS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge:  "There has been chaos . .without any kind of actual hard evidence that there is a need" for the exec order  https://t.co/jyyqQvpNa2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Normally, outlawing a voluntary contract b/w private parties is what Republicans consider government meddling  https://t.co/klLeMKe2WZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great piece then.  More so today. https://t.co/s8HboBvo4C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exactly. https://t.co/X54Qsb9G5V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's remember that US refugee deal is only to assessthe people on Nauru and Manus, not to take them.They aren't getting on planes tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And @latikambourke nails it, and gives credit where it is due. #auspol https://t.co/T3MYZ1WzAc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What guff that @TurnbullMalcolm isn't beholden to anyone because he donated his own $. Plenty of other donors to the Liberal Party. #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Botany Bay had a plebiscite, and overwhelmingly voted no to merger. They since been forced. Now what @GladysB ? https://t.co/jhGaNlSCu5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read this. Very good analysis of the PM's speech. 
Malcolm Turnbull oblivious as world moves on https://t.co/Y0B5cbYIYp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not officially public disclosure.  It's not real time. It's not accurate. https://t.co/07mPMs719z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually no one knew about it. That's the point. https://t.co/dB3PSRdCSP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is textbook losing your cool @TurnbullMalcolm - and BTW, it's Peta Credlin who called you Mr Harbourside Mansi… https://t.co/dExeqUoAjF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, it seems like a good time to point out that #CredlinKeneally will be back on air in 6 minutes on @SkyNewsAust #mrharboursidemansion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonvandore Thanks!  Fixed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great profile of @edhusicMP by Jana Wendt
https://t.co/wOYtYBPzxc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In order:  Top 10 highest taxing Aus govts:  Howard, Howard, Howard, Howard, Howard, Howard, Howard, Turnbull, Howa… https://t.co/jjiGd59EZ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or many of my Cabinet colleagues. https://t.co/26iu4AI1PW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull: I'm not a political hack. I'm not a political animal. I'm into results. 

Wishing the camera panned to ScoMo at that  point. #NPC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember in 2010 when @TurnbullMalcolm threw his support behind 100% renewable energy supply within a decade? #npc https://t.co/HDNJ6WLJPc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now that @TurnbullMalcolm puts such stock in ALP economic modeling, will he also consider the Opposition's case for negative gearing? #NPC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations @mymgsm - ranked #1 business school in Australia again!  3 years in a row. And top 50 in the world. https://t.co/BVILYHQEo4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We don't have an agreement the US will resettle refugees on Nauru &amp; Manus. It's an agreement that the US will assess them. That's all.  #NPC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My column today https://t.co/oDYMp7XIx3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@don_pretorius @smh that's a fair point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exactly.  Let's save the self-congratulations until people are off Nauru &amp; Manus.  https://t.co/cxmxvLFFWw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama rejects comparison between Trump’s immigration policy and his own, encourages protests - The Washington Post https://t.co/hwdV4kZP4s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dissent memo circulating in the State Department over Trump’s policy on refugees and - https://t.co/0FUysR5Vun https://t.co/tdM0rqO0yb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No. My position has always been safe, legal and rare. https://t.co/YWTbJ3FNCv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Matthewjw1978 It is perfectly legal to hold two passports. I do not. But many Australians do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Julie Bishop instructs diplomats to ask President Trump to exempt Australians from immigration ban https://t.co/9y3kqhLFp2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is brilliant. Highly, highly recommend. Long, but worth it. 

How Jokes Won the Election - The New Yorker https://t.co/vpxNRXc3aD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['The illegal migrant comes like that ‘stranger’ in whom Jesus asks to be recognized. To welcome him is a Christian duty' - John Paul II]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“A person who thinks only about building walls..and not building bridges, is not Christian. This is not the Gospel." https://t.co/EHuCgENQoD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This kind of misses the point. https://t.co/HkeIXig5xt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Milwaukee Bucks concerned for Australia's Thon Maker after Trump's travel order enacted https://t.co/mKdRqP0qIZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hence @ThonMaker14 can't come home, can't play in Toronto. https://t.co/wR3e8c4wnd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope pro-life marchers in DC also back universal healthcare, access to reliable contraception, paid parental leave, &amp; affordable childcare.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @TonyAbbottMHR read this -
Pope: You can’t defend Christianity by being ‘against refugees and other religions’  https://t.co/mRpKjx1M9A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shouldn't the question be - how many childless men become premier?  In NSW, it's 2 of the last 5.   https://t.co/OYw5Mho8Sx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kiwi press reporting confusion on what the new Trump rules might mean. #waitandsee  https://t.co/OEZp1zq1IZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interview required: Trump may dump visa-waiver program for Aussies https://t.co/boECHV2ZYT via @TravellerAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump wishes us well on Australia Day - and apparently, wants us to stay out of his country. https://t.co/vjc27X5a2f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netherlands welcomes Trump in his own words. Gold. https://t.co/fouSynZnSj via @youtube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thinking don't make it so https://t.co/DcufDQk77i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep. I bought it for him in Atlanta. https://t.co/bQ780d2nL9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My childhood feminist TV icon 

Mary Tyler Moore, TV and movie star, dies at 80 - The Washington Post https://t.co/M6pMs41Yv1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exactly https://t.co/GcOrAGzav4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Refugee deals. The TPP. The Turnbull government is apparently living in an alternate universe.  https://t.co/rqYDMyiOBJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia Day: let’s shift it for a truly national celebration - by Ian Macfarlane  https://t.co/rcZzKbriYK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How ugly and cruel is Trumpism going to get? Today we get an answer. - The Washington Post https://t.co/rOiIPbeGPO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Daily 202: 11 stories from President Trump’s first 100 hours that deserve more attention - The Washington Post https://t.co/4K4746IDtd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That seems a bit OTT https://t.co/ElGp2lGfj5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually we already had it - Keneally &amp; Tebbutt https://t.co/D3Yc3jTOul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My column today. https://t.co/ig3BXh2M2J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenYHomeBuyer @samdastyari @PaulBongiorno Get your history right. The Coalition approved the Packer casino.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Belligerent 
Lying
Threatening 

Also, Spicer reads his notes like a year 7 student doing a book report. https://t.co/Ox3ObALXZs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I read all the tweets first, and thought 'surely, it couldn't have be that bad.'  It is.  Shocking. https://t.co/vp5OWp6ETc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's only a flesh wound. https://t.co/rssect7QEl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Women's Protest in Miami, Florida. Overflowing crowds. They've had to shut the venue. #lovetrumpshate https://t.co/KlQdZ7JnlU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Miami Women's Protest.  Been going 3 hours &amp; still too full to get in. Yet it fills my heart w/hope.… https://t.co/awVQUDOu5Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A most dreadful inaugural address - 
By George F Will 
The Washington Post https://t.co/XEPO5THLls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recommended https://t.co/XYldOQknBu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoying some rare &amp; close up sightings during my trip to Florida https://t.co/ig4EIYqZjC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Malcolm Turnbull’s ticking clock — Newspoll noose around PM’s neck https://t.co/aCahqkjkIc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went to the Jimmy Carter Presidential Library (it's v good) in Atlanta today &amp; saw this. 
Doubt Mike Pence will be… https://t.co/UsvvUdVt9m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to remove Donald Trump from office https://t.co/uFO7CVsFtQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Obama is a Muslim, is Trump a Russian spy? - The Washington Post https://t.co/isIdJttxFn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Skaroyo Not by a uni and a year 11 student. They can buy their own lollies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean, this bag of lollies is an 'unexpected purchase.'  An investment property? Please. #sussanley https://t.co/8VAkXF3Mqd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did a federal minister even have time on a work trip to buy a property? #sussanley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure my family appreciates the endless @Indigo_Girls tracks on my iPhone playlist, but we are driving through Alabama &amp; Georgia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just don't use all three (middle name is Kerscher) and we'll be fine. https://t.co/9kYmhTySSH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our family voted them very good, FWIW https://t.co/EKDlY6ZOi7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man, @AlboMP has some amazing branding operation going on.   Found in a gas station near the Mississippi/Alabama bo… https://t.co/3FbQAk4Qa3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump's trade policies become more shocking by the day https://t.co/ummH4nyFi5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[However, AEC has no plans to make us wear shirts or pants while voting. https://t.co/acjzvr1CQQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Innovation and agility. https://t.co/ye9UCtURB4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me. 1986. Huge Wham! fan. Loved @GeorgeMichael https://t.co/5YpP08rFyp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NSW road fatalities up - but not due to P-plate drivers. So why is the @mikebairdMP Govt taking away their maps app… https://t.co/4NPInshJVW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The response to this tweet. https://t.co/gSQ55bFb7Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas!! https://t.co/y3uXlouKdJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, canon law never did anyone any harm #paedophilePriests #denyingbirthcontrol #denyingcondomstopreventAIDS https://t.co/luUXljoeVm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In that contest, I'm backing Chicken Little (Tony 'debt and deficit emergency' Abbott) https://t.co/Rdf7fvDaqO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does anyone know if @corybernardi is familiar with the story of The Boy Who Cried Wolf?  Just curious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like upgraded every hospital &amp; electricity infrastructure &amp; built M2, M7, CCT, ED, M5, &amp; new rail lines?

Oh that's… https://t.co/ozkpLvjVLV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually our 'Christian' laws derive from Abrahamic laws &amp; covenants. You know, Abraham - the 'father' of Judaism,… https://t.co/lTI8Yhoq4S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Replace 'Muslim' with Catholic &amp; it's a near perfect description of the Protestant view of Catholics for the first… https://t.co/FtmRxR6xrt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stupid comment. There is Catholic law. It's called canon law &amp; co-exists with Aus law. Ask any divorced Aus Catholi… https://t.co/NVv1d0KmmQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrowningInIt1  You can blame the O'Farrell/Baird governments for the casino. 
My government put the ferry hub there without a casino.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another Keneally Govt decision, next step in transformation of Barangaroo 
#FerryHub 
#NoCasino  https://t.co/BAB5TIBbZz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because @ljayes can wear whatever the hell she wants. #procape https://t.co/qhwfSbrLVi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kumitaguchi @PatsKarvelas it's really quite frustrating.....you give me some hope PK!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day 12 of laryngitis &amp; respiratory virus. 
And it's my birthday. 
And MYEFO. 

Yippee.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@domknight @EternityNews in the Catholic Church- no coincidence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I attended Catholic high school &amp;  uni, worked as a dorm supervisor, school teacher &amp; youth worker. Anglican or Cat… https://t.co/GcZl0hk9us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fr Mike is 100% spot on. The culture of the Catholic Church actually encourages young women to choose abortion. https://t.co/7wLnpA0Xt8]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>