<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElizaJBooth @reaDonaldTrump well appreciated that we have a president that is fighting for us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElizaJBooth @reaDonaldTrump really go to work get over it!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealDJTrumpTeam @realDonaldTrump @samsung @seanhannity @axios Samsung will HELP make America great again together united we stand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gatewaypundit @reaDonaldTrump arrest her!! Slander is very easy to profe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnFromCranber @larrykah14 I don't want my tax payers money going to this!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump lock them up riot's ten years min]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump call for feds and national guard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealDJTrumpTeam @POTUS @realDonaldTrump American people standing with you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump tillerson will be great for America]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Karmatella @justinhendrix @realDonaldTrump there was no media have respect!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump prayers for the family my heart hurts for them as my own son serves USA army]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@POTUS @TeamTrump @VP our country is in danger of corruption beyond]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@POTUS @TeamTrump @VP I pray for your hard job ahead of you. Our country is in very bad shape. #maga!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hunterswogg @reaDonaldTrump call feds and national guard in now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Iran is the swamp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JimmyEarlWard @BreitbartNews call feds national guard in now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redsteeze @reaDonaldTrump call feds in now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump what ever Obama wanted to do go the opposite way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump don't let them in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump yes. So Isis could take over the united States of America]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lrihendry she needs to be fired!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RexTillersonSOS prayers for you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RexTillersonSOS thank you for your service]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@POTUS @VP honored to have him serve our country]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GorsuchFacts @EastBayTimes #maga you will be awesome prayers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealDJTrumpTeam he will be awesome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Plaid_Tillerson it's really great to see with humbly honored to serve the united States of America proud of you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealDJTrumpTeam @realDonaldTrump @POTUS @DonaldJTrumpJr so glad to see rex humbly honored to serve his country]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@foxnewspolitics @CDerespina America safety first]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxNews @BasedMelGibson go nuclear on all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@foxnewspolitics @AdamShawNY go nuclear on sessions rex tillerson ASP Ben Carson ASP all cabinet pics quickly approved]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDennisLynch about time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: GOP changes rules to approve nominees after Democrats boycott (video) https://t.co/1D6yiPa3Zh via @realDennisLynch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reaDonaldTrump hope and pray for your cabinet pics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump thank you president Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealDJTrumpTeam @POTUS a man's word is the soul of him forever. Thank you president Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GorsuchFacts @marc_lotter @POTUS congrats proud you abide by the constant and a godly man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VP it's an honor to have such an awesome Christian man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VP @POTUS great man proud of my president Donald j Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seanhannity @RealDJTrumpTeam @mcuban America first]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reaDonaldTrump @PressSec @POTUS thank you!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @USTradeRep need rex tillerson ASP Ben Carson ASP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpeakerRyan we need a Republican to vote on sessions rex tillerson devise Ben Carson ASP 51 votes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Republicans have the house at 51 votes so vote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BretBaier our safety of our country is fist. Thank you president Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer need sessions ASP rex tillerson ASP Ben Carson ASP ect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxNews @POTUS what about the family that lost life's in terrorism thank you president Trump for extreme vetting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls @PressSec @netanyahu @AmbDermer drop sacition on them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@100PercFEDUP what about Isis attacks on American soul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katywithawhy @reaDonaldTrump prayers for life's lost in Canada.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealDJTrumpTeam thank you president Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@foxnewspolitics @JuddBerger thanks for keeping American people safe president Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@foxnewspolitics @FoxNews #drain the swamp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need extreme vetting look what happened in Canada due to terrorism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealDJTrumpTeam look what happened in Canada due to terrorism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AgendaOfEvil @larrykah14 @MoneyJihad thank you president Trump for extreme vetting we don't want what happened in Canada terrorism here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reg1776 @BreitbartNews we don't need what happened in Canada thank you president Trump for extreme vetting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAm2skilled we don't want what happened in Canada to happen here, thanks to Trump for extreme vetting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@foxnewspolitics @HowardKurtz @FoxNews media swamp report for Canada life's lost due to terrorism thank president Trump for extreme vetting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump where's the tears for life's lost in Canada due to terrorism!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump thanks for keeping us safe. We don't want what happened in Canada.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dcexaminer we want extremely vetting. Look what happened in Canada!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DBloom451 thank you president Trump!! We don't won't what happened in Canada to happen here!! Prayers for Canada.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Extremely vetting much needed, example look what happened in Canada!! Prayers for Canada!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealDJTrumpTeam thanks for your hard work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bookgirl8 @reaDonaldTrump it's like illegal immigrants are trying to take America over.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think if anyone voted and are illegal immigrants they should be deported.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@watchdoggy yes thank you Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealDJTrumpTeam @FoxNews milliary waters also]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealDJTrumpTeam @FoxNews not far to people living there that voted Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealDJTrumpTeam @FoxNews we would have to have a wall to keep illegal immigrants out they also couldn't vote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealDJTrumpTeam @FoxNews monument there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealDJTrumpTeam @FoxNews then they can form there own wars against us.we couldn't send any taxpayer money to them. There is military]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump good for Mexico and Americans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Trump2016Chi @KellyannePolls offer adoption in all other orders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Trump2016Chi @KellyannePolls also only allow abortion under extreme rape harm to mother life with there choice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Trump2016Chi @KellyannePolls partial term abortion should be out law ed also law against abortion passed six weeks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump illegal immigrants voting in California!!!I stand with Trump...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let me say,we must not allow commonest, evil, terrorism take over our country!! Proctor of my children.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza @Trump2016Chi Chelsea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TEN_GOP @pele_my and my son scutes when he crawled.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TEN_GOP @pele_my so sweet ,I remember when my daughter first crawled she rolled her whole body]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CronkiteSays @reaDonaldTrump proud of this man!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealDJTrumpTeam @POTUS tax payers dollars shouldn't be spent on welfare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealDJTrumpTeam @FoxNewsInsider he's great for America]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealDJTrumpTeam build the wall!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DebAlwaystrump this is against the federal law]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My uncle drawer 670.00 per month @89 years old . Ate peanut butter cracks. What do dems eat steak??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would like for those in Washington DC to live on what our elderly people live on!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reaDonaldTrump there's 24 hrs in a day what do they do for the rest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reaDonaldTrump our vets deserve to die in there home max tax free money for caregivers 1700.00 per month @$10 hr that's 7 hrs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reaDonaldTrump we worked for our social security Obama care is in Medicare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reaDonaldTrump hard working American people pay. People on social security living in poverty, haven't had. Raises]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reaDonaldTrump people miss work from blocked roads. Some people have to work unlike illegal immigrants getting welfare that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reaDonaldTrump sick pathetic  lady can't get her cancer treatment for another three month]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reaDonaldTrump new York bombs,mall shooting ECT riot's blocking traffic women misses her cancer treatment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VP @POTUS awesome let the healing began]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NolteNC @reaDonaldTrump leave this child alone!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JudgeJeanine @realDonaldTrump our country is back, let the healing began.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @romoabcnews @DavidMuir @POTUS @ABCWorldNews @ABC2020 what about DACA and Johnson law]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>