<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[How can you call someone a moepi when you're a moepi yourself? ðŸ¤” #cringetweets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never been so stressed over trying to find a fricken house ðŸ˜“viewings after viewings after viewings! Zzz just want my own place again ðŸ¤žðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheCLASSYKiddo can't deal reading all his wife's tweets ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't think my kid looks 3 months... ðŸ¤”ðŸ¤£ https://t.co/9H9XoP9ASQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cajeyduzit this is so yuck Cajetan ðŸ˜‚ #bungeye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can the next 4 weeks go by really fast please, I'm ready to drop ðŸ˜…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deborah_tuitama leave him here or hair? ðŸ˜‚ðŸ”«]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're broke the same day you get paid ðŸ™„ #moneycome #moneyalwaysgo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&amp; super excited for babyshower.... Mainly just to eat my nutella cake ðŸ˜‹ðŸ˜‹ðŸ˜‹ðŸ˜‹]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Out of all places I only get stretch marks on my arms ðŸ˜’ guess I can't complain about a clear tummy tho ðŸ™‚ðŸ™‚ðŸ™‚ðŸ™‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woke up to the sound of guns shooting ðŸ™„ soon, very soon, the PS4 is gonna go 'missing' ðŸ¸ðŸ¸ðŸ¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deborah_tuitama my bf reckons it's the same and it's driving me effing nuts!!! ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CAN SOMEONE PLS CLARIFY THIS FOR ME? Is 'here' and 'hair' pronounced the same?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone elses bf turn them into an uluka'e? Just tore our room upside down then cleaned it again ðŸ˜‚ðŸ”« ffs. Hormones on ðŸ”¥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just over a month (or less ðŸ™ðŸ½) to go till mini landchief arrives! Mummy and daddy can't wait to meet you fat boy â˜ºï¸â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love this guys' confidence it literally amazes me ðŸ˜‚ðŸ‘ðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Va'a: Can mice shrink?

No babe, those are baby mice ðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dyyying to sleep on my stomach!!! #pregproblems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stretch marks are coming through... â˜¹]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thinking bout where my life's at &amp; I'm so grateful ðŸ™ðŸ½ especially for my boys who I get to spend my life with â˜ºï¸ #feelzat3am]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baby is posterior ðŸ™„ and kicks 24/7 fml please go to sleeeeeep baby ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(Even though when my pay runs out I'll be hoping baby daddy tops up my acct so I can go out for dinner w my girls this weeknd ðŸ˜‚) #priorities]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honestly feels so good being able to buy things you need for your child without having to rely on anyone else â˜ºï¸â˜ºï¸â˜ºï¸â˜ºï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things that make me happy these days: Finding out I get 18 weeks not 16 weeks of paid leave cos of policy changes â˜ºï¸â˜ºï¸â˜ºï¸â˜ºï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&amp; then comes out of the shop with door knob covers so his nephews can't open our bedroom door ðŸ™„ My baby gon' be smarter than his dad ðŸ˜‚ðŸ”«]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went baby shopping &amp; Vaa puts some dummies in the basket... Got to the counter and I pull out pink dummies ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜© but we're having a boy fml]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nerisa01 lmao he was still repping his gears and flags around ptown ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nerisa01 haha baldy guy? Wearing the hurricanes flag as a ie?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I literally go from ðŸ˜Š to ðŸ˜¡ to ðŸ˜¢ in seconds and usually stay ðŸ˜¡/ðŸ˜¢ for hours!!!! Ffs ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being hormonal has probably been the worst experience I've come across throughout my pregnancy ðŸ˜’ðŸ”«]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am I crazy for keeping tabs on Vaa thru my netflix acct while I'm away from home? ðŸ¤”ðŸ‘€ ...Nope! ðŸ˜‚ #icanseewhatyourewatching]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spending two nights away frm Vaa for the first time. He's tryna act like he's not sad but i know hes crying inside ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #girltime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baby shower planning in progress ðŸ˜ðŸ£ðŸŽŠðŸŽˆðŸŽ‰ðŸ‘¶ðŸ¾]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@niaasseaso omg i had a fit when this happened ðŸ˜‚ðŸ”«]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wish I knew how to drive manual so I could drive myself to the shop for cake â˜¹ #wakeupvaa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just spent $200 on baby clothes online... I think I'm obsessed with buying baby gear ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry but... I can't stand people who drive and snapchat... Not sorry ðŸ’ðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeeceGodinet idk, who comes up with stuff like that tho ðŸ™„ðŸ”« hahahahahahaha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just want these last 12 weeks to hurry ðŸ˜´ #3rdtri]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have the fobbiest bf ðŸ˜­ðŸ”«sends me this from downstairs while I'm upstairs sick in bed. #looksyuckanyway ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/LZZoRMAWK7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MAYLYN_26 omg I did an IP man marathon in the weekend haha pt 2 is so kaea lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went for a walk this morning. First exercise since being preg and fark I don't think I'll be doing it again anytime soon ðŸ˜…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never take loved ones for granted. Rest in love Lisa and love to all her family and friends ðŸ˜” sad to hear the loss of anyone!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally got cot and new bedroom suite tomorrow ðŸ‘ðŸ½ woohoo! Can't wait to set up room. Now can this baby hurry up and come out now ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We'll see at 5am if it was a good idea that I happily let Va'a go out tonight ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stopped playing pokemon go as soon as I realised I needed data to catch em all outside my house... Fuggg dat! Save my data ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting sooooo impatient!!! Just wanna pop already ðŸ˜© #sleeplessnights]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Va'a thinks I bought him yeezys for his birthday.... ðŸ˜ don't be too ambitious m8!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sherridaan im still waiting to play too ðŸ˜¤ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@etanahlalau omg meeee toooo ðŸ˜‚ my bf's like 'who is this' ðŸ™„ðŸ™„ðŸ™„ ummmm im like 'who r u' ðŸ˜”ðŸ˜‚ðŸ”«]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fainted in the warehouse ðŸ˜‘ this pregnancy getting me good!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Literally emptied out my bank acct today buying Vaa's bday present. He better be grateful or imma cut the wires to his ps4 for his bday ðŸ™‚ðŸ™‚ðŸ™‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sleeping is almost impossible!!! ðŸ˜¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing makes me cringe more than ppl who put others on full blast on fb and insta.... Fuuuuck up noone cares ðŸ˜´]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@__irma20 ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ i wanna push this baby out now! When are you due to drop?! Exciiiiiting!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished reading 'Me before You' now I'm lying here feeling grateful to hear Vaa snoring next to me ðŸ˜‚ got me right in the feelz ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 more months ðŸ˜“ almost there baby boy ðŸ¤˜ðŸ½ https://t.co/xbrg7N0qOw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you get dragged into drama by insecure bitches sticking their noses into your relationship when theirs' is jitty ðŸ™ƒðŸ™‚ðŸ™ƒðŸ™‚ #wegood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I have a spending problem... It has now become a bigger problem with baby on the way and I think in one week I've bought 10 booties ðŸ™‚ðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@T_Nonu why fi?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@T_Nonu why not?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could not care less about the NBA finals ðŸ™‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those girls who have 'Samoan/German' in their bio's but be looking Fijian... ðŸ¤”ðŸ‘§ðŸ¿ðŸ˜‚ðŸ”«]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Despite all the anger... I don't think reposting the front page is necessary.... Couple ppl on fb posting up just makes me cringe ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually stunned that the Samoa Observer would even think that posting about suicide like that on their front page was ok ðŸ˜”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FSeaso fark liveh caught me at chicken shack tonight... I'm getting too masagi with ptowns food places ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@niaasseaso tell him to get a life plz ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CAN THIS BABY HURRY AND COME OUT PLZ SO I CAN STOP EATING LIKE A AIKAE ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Romeo Santos - Promise ft. Usher https://t.co/rNJYi4MKuB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 roti butter chicken wrap, 2 pork buns, 3 pork dumplings and 2 chicken kebabs later ðŸ˜© this baby is so hungus!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@petaia_tiai i'll let Va'a know, he works for spark ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And about to break the fuckin ps4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About to lose my shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woke up in the middle of the night and went baby shopping online ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Makes me cringe at the fact that he needs to have a go at EVERYTHING!! #okayidontwannastartatweetwarplz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Random tweet and no idea why i follow tbh but Eliota Sapolu's tweets are so unecessary and just plain eye-rolling material ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... And so killing 50 gay men is ok cos he 'got angry'? 

What the fuck!!! ðŸ˜” RIP #PrayForOrlando https://t.co/XDIN19lsmM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I reckon if I never got pregnant, I'd never be able to stay sober for longer than a week ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worst thing about online shopping is waiting for your things to arrive ðŸ˜‘ðŸ–•ðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One more month then I'm officially a Ptown resident ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­

ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@debbietuitama should be worth it in the end hahaha. Yuppp mummy's boy on its way lol xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Craving pears so bad my mouth is watering ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This was me answering the ph after 9 missed calls in 5 mins ðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got the ph call I've been expecting for awhile... 'Sorry lissa I'm gonna be that fuckn uncle but who's your baby daddy and what he do?']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasFretton fuck i bought it anyway ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pleeeease hurry up October!!! I can't wait to meet my little boy ðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I have to justify everything I buy online cos apparently I have a spending problem... ðŸ¤”ðŸ¤”ðŸ¤” https://t.co/Z2I2gH096l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every year I've gone out to watch State of O. Tonight was first time ever I watched the full game.... Not cos i was sober or anything... ðŸ˜‚ðŸ”«]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait to catch up with my 4sum tonight â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't contain excitement about finding out baby sex tomorrow!!!!! ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ #plzbeagirl #wedontneednomorevaas ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yuna - Crush ft. Usher ðŸ‘ŒðŸ½ðŸ‘ŒðŸ½ðŸ‘ŒðŸ½ https://t.co/8m4BEtWu10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tea_Muaiava well shes lucky she has you looking after her hahahahaha always laugh at your snaps of her lmao! Palagi's aye ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tea_Muaiava fuck she's hillarious!!!! Where do you work? Haha don't ever paint the poor girls kigilima's like that again ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tea_Muaiava is this the chick in your snaps? ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ did you paint her kigilimas? ðŸ˜‚ðŸ”«]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just looked down and felt this pain in my heart... I have kankles ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been awhile since I've worked 5 nights in a row... Night number 2 and my eyes are cryyyyyyaaaaang ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ #saturdaycomequick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plz god give me a girl ðŸ™ðŸ½ðŸ˜‚ so we can gang up on daddy who thinks it's funny to constantly piss off mummy ðŸ˜ŠðŸ˜ŠðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get to find out if I'm having a girl or a boy in two weeks â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&amp; then Va'a tells me to stop wearing my nice clothes until I'm 'skinny again' cos I might stretch them... ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tea_Muaiava beautiful? ðŸ¤” I feel like a walking whale ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ but thank you thank you haha â¤ï¸]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>