<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[when someone in Australia returns @PhilipRucker and @gregpmiller's call https://t.co/OoeyvXyack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Unsilent 
Coffee?
Beer?
C-O-
B-E-

(me too)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia's PM declines to comment on conversation where Trump berated him https://t.co/oQ1By6nT23 https://t.co/XJzzoNROgo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this is gonna end with a booting and @gregpmiller and @PhilipRucker famous in Australia https://t.co/i9cdkwFsmw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[oh god I just realized where this is going https://t.co/lQPbm4qybc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[False claims about a big electoral college win or inauguration turnout aren't just for us, but for world leaders to… https://t.co/vrapF4bUpS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worth remembering that historically speaking, @realDonaldTrump had among the smaller electoral college wins on record (46th out of 58)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pres. Trump, on a call with Australia's PM, badgered him, bragged about his electoral college win and bailed early… https://t.co/dFz2lTe8xq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here are fatal terror attacks in the U.S. post-9/11. More than half the jihadist death toll occurred at Pulse in Or… https://t.co/nrGF0RQKHo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump admin wants counterextremism program to focus only on Islamist extremism, not white supremacists, per… https://t.co/XCx9k84aiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe it'll be good?
[RON HOWARD V.O.: It won't be]
https://t.co/zKLN2stHJE https://t.co/01iYdxKkNu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abbyohlheiser who knows what else will escape I guess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[well, this dream is dead https://t.co/crGMlnw0CL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why was @stevekerr tweeting about subscribing to a news outlet today? Here's how #presson got started https://t.co/1abYeUz5qi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ollie the bobcat, who escaped the National Zoo on Monday and had a grand adventure, has been found (...at the zoo) https://t.co/M1sX3V6mtt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ME: We have captured the bobcat, so all is well-- [trips, falls over, accidentally opens up the lion, bear and zombie enclosures]

uh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UPDATE: They found the bobcat! OUR LONG BOBCAT-RELATED NIGHTMARE IS OVER

https://t.co/uOMWK1Wo4F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gbrockell @alexlaughs gonna need to bring in more people here @abbyohlheiser @ElaheIzadi @slarimer @pepsi @jfdulac]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexlaughs but isn't beyonce enough magic for us all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexlaughs what if it's one of those accounts that tweeted 90 things and deleted the wrong ones tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scotusreporter Bob is this a joke tweet or a real tweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Murray plagiarized question to DeVos, who later plagiarized an answer to her, via @danmericaCNN https://t.co/whH5MK14X8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jdelreal the hell you can't]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The U.N. has not been shy about ripping into President Trump's travel restrictions, which it says endangers refugees https://t.co/hBYvk0JgOf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BEYONCE: HAVING TWINS

THE WHITE HOUSE: [clears throat] We accidentally burned down the East Wing. Hello? Anyone?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rsemmel @washingtonpost the owl got hit by so many vehicles, I just can't handle that again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_cingraham @CaitJGibson you're telling me we should be reassured because a missing bobcat and ghost owl have teamed up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Trump: I did "substantially" better than other GOP candidates with black voters

The facts: lol cmon 

https://t.co/D1GDltC5Uq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaitJGibson oh god I can't handle that again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I tweet very bleak things all the time and even I think "There's a bobcat on the loose in D.C. and nobody's looking for it" is a bit much]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The zoo is suspending its bobcat search, which means there's a missing bobcat in D.C. and nobody's looking for it https://t.co/nakEIBo8w7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This #PressOn thing, wow. If this keeps up we can finally get @Fahrenthold the gold suspenders he keeps mentioning https://t.co/Q8FAX5iepn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erikmal I stand by my prediction man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DUBS IN FIVE https://t.co/PtJU3CB1II]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump transition email shows effort to boot all inspectors general https://t.co/LJcIQKp4tu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.N. experts say Trump's immigration order violates U.S. human rights obligations https://t.co/d9Z06jxuan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeSoulinspired oh it is most definitely real https://t.co/3abLAGPKR2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Black History Month https://t.co/r7nUlIlW1Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a good thing President Trump has never gotten any facts wrong so he can keep assailing a reporter for a mistake https://t.co/aST140OkUd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Again I thought there was some kinda separation thing going on here https://t.co/dmecAlejIV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Trump, six days ago: The media "is very, very dishonest."

The White House, today: Please read these stor… https://t.co/jLyPVgYo3o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The worldview and ideas of Steve Bannon, now President Trump's chief strategist, are becoming U.S. policy… https://t.co/kjWPzM9SOl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Trump is motivating a LOT of Democratic women to get more politically involved https://t.co/c0bMvB7273 https://t.co/BT4LbxsCVF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Update to this thread: Turns out that was the last time @KellyannePolls appeared on CNN, which the WH is icing out https://t.co/Pz0XBS3H2P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Newly-minted Supreme Court nominee Neil Gorsuch's mom once ran the EPA. It didn't go well. https://t.co/dTb7u1h1oH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attorneys general in NY, Mass., Virginia and Washington state join fight over constitutionality of Trump travel ban https://t.co/pj3PFrkFOC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aren't these guys at the WH for a political event...running the business entirely separate from politics/the WH? https://t.co/hJFzub8ORC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ff @scotusreporter, a Florida man and a fine Supreme Court reporter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before the Supreme Court nominee was announced, the court declined to stay an execution in Missouri. It was carried… https://t.co/AlzEtNYWHz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House statement on President Trump's nomination of Judge Gorsuch to the Supreme Court https://t.co/cK1CPj3Gsy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Since Pres Trump keeps mentioning Justice Scalia, a reminder: he discussed a conspiracy theory around Scalia's deat… https://t.co/u3Lab6hp1x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT if you're the Supreme Court nominee, fave if you're not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AGs in New York, Mass., Washington state and Virginia are getting involved in legal challenges to Trump's ban https://t.co/GUIOIjwCUV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[States are joining the legal battle over Trump's immigration order, with four AGs filing or seeking to join lawsuits https://t.co/GUIOIjwCUV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you pick a twitter fight with Blade you get what you deserve tbh https://t.co/YJaoV2bbR0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[whoever finds the bobcat gets the robe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[who did this? I'm looking at you @daveweigel https://t.co/J2oxWCzh5H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York's attorney general has joined the ACLU's NY lawsuit against the Trump travel ban https://t.co/sgkRgMgpgW via @Reuters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Trump administration says 872 refugees "in transit" will be allowed in the U.S. this week https://t.co/fMqoAdeNYt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[alright now I'm just rooting for an asteroid https://t.co/9cd35kmSaY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While complaining about the media getting things wrong, @seanspicer gets something wrong while attacking @acosta… https://t.co/eVvmtuMiRO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[well this seems like a sentence we would revisit (if words still had meaning, that is) https://t.co/OLCnBf7767]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[congratulations to President Obama on serving four terms in office https://t.co/hpjqyrjHUa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@seanspicer says the media's reporting has helped cause confusion surrounding the travel ban, because literally why not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During the raid in Yemen, "almost everything went wrong," says one senior military official. https://t.co/ZcAozLQFLd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reminder that a day ago, @seanspicer pointed to San Bernardino to justify the ban https://t.co/NrIPlBV5mK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess if you wanna be technical, it's an entry ban, since it governs entry into the U.S. https://t.co/MaLvxgDJLk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@PressSec just said "numbers don't lie," so here are President Trump's daily poll numbers via @Gallup: 51% disappr… https://t.co/H6Mni26cP4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“What’s going on in the world?” is an objectively embarrassing thing for Tom Brady to say to dodge questions https://t.co/wE30mD5BWk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Trump administration says it will allow 872 refugees into the United States this week https://t.co/u5mj0KFKbu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JUSTICE #1: So how'd you get picked?
JUSTICE #2: Got a call at home. You?
JUSTICE #1: I got a rose on national TV

https://t.co/ZeYbs9Q8Tq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a lot of other stuff going on but it's important to remember Taylor lies to you https://t.co/bbqqneC7Jy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @wsj's top editor would like reporters not to refer to Muslim-majority countries as Muslim-majority countries https://t.co/pG6vDtTwlB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this tweet is a journey https://t.co/IPfWcr2nLP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Trump's repeated comments about crime and "American carnage" range from misleading to incorrect https://t.co/5QYi0ij7af]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ISIS has apparently cobbled together an armed drone program https://t.co/ETVtMPEpAI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Trump's firing of Sally Yates "sets a dangerous precedent," writes former DOJ spokesman @matthewamiller… https://t.co/wtebvLMmyF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Washington Post's database of people shot and killed by police in 2017 is here: https://t.co/fG3CvmLY7R

Will be updated all year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[damn I should've waited to tweet this until I got this gif https://t.co/6dGzjhWilB https://t.co/fDKJy1gLMt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidCovucci you seem to know an awful lot about bobcats for a guy who claims not to have stolen the bobcat, Dave]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh that's right, there is still a bobcat roaming Washington right now, waiting, lurking, preparing (or sleeping idk) https://t.co/cL22tf54EV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House: The travel ban really only impacted 109 people

Reality: The travel ban could impact 90,000 people

https://t.co/ruX1lAGicL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the perfect burn, top to bottom, because everything LeBron says is 100 percent accurate https://t.co/UYUVCcwUg2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Washington state's AG filed a lawsuit against Trump's travel ban - a suit that has the support of Microsoft + Amazo… https://t.co/GrV5ZvX7Rl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattzap the good midwest or the Ohio midwest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're 11 days in and the Trump White House is already a hotbed of disorder and tension https://t.co/rrtzJPS6fH https://t.co/IgTtjJQ4VC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[hooks up IV of whiskey] ah, time to check Twitter dot com to see what is going on in the world https://t.co/SoNXtNERUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The House Oversight committee has 43 items on deck this year. None are focused on President Trump.… https://t.co/SNQwyAmwSh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When President Trump says something blatantly untrue, it spreads like a virus https://t.co/6dGzjhWilB https://t.co/ctgB8uIEkR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What makes what he says credible? Because he's on TV?" LeBron speaks the truth https://t.co/Z3g7fWzjDS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The White House says it will keep Obama's LGBT protections for federal workers in place after all https://t.co/mGDFLXA8cC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump appoints new ICE director. Dept. of Homeland Security says acting director wasn't fired and will remain on… https://t.co/Yv4Xbi4FfN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The White House releases its own statement announcing the new ICE director https://t.co/OocyE2KtZT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobL777 these are all very good and I appreciate every one of them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Dana Boente, the new acting attorney general? https://t.co/KNkd86gnwS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Sally Yates? Meet the acting attorney general Trump fired and accused of "betraying" the Justice Department https://t.co/CQm2aHnEdr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For anyone still seeing reports that Trump fired the ICE director, according to DHS that is not what happened https://t.co/qm5GVdnVca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@journodave maybe people need to chill for a second]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Again, according to DHS, Daniel Ragsdale, acting ICE director, was not fired but will remain in his role as deputy director]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DHS says Ragsdale, the acting director, was not fired, will remain deputy director of ICE after serving as acting director (2/2)]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>