<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlbertLeRoi haha twitter's sarcasm filter is down! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, now that you sent me THREE copies of your pitch, I will definitely talk to your Obamacare expert.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gorsuch fulfills Trump's pledge to appoint "pro life" justices to the Supreme Court https://t.co/EHLhBudtR7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anti-abortion groups say Gorsuch pick fulfills Trump's campaign pledge to appoint "pro life" judges https://t.co/EHLhBudtR7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shocking that the SCOTUS announcement is 20 minutes away and the name hasn't leaked yet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The bobcat-- must be the bobcat. https://t.co/Ccc7AhHzDf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rep @DaveBratVA7th says "the women are in [his] grill" over Obamacare repeal https://t.co/8O4jktJitO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dem boycott of Senate Finance mtg means there is no quorum to advance Tom Price's nomination to be HHS secretary. He's in limbo now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conservative health policy expert @DeanClancy is betting GOP will balk on repealing Obamacare and settle on "fixes" https://t.co/llZGf1Bg2h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This really should be the biggest news of the day https://t.co/NfCrVGtESM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pretty big issue, for sure! https://t.co/WpwAILgnAh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rs have introduced a draft of their pre-existing conditions bill but no overall repeal plan: https://t.co/XIAW3PPRJ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steveabowden I'm not sure it will-- but health won't be the topic du jour for a few days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every high school that did March for Life is at Pentagon City mall now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlennThrush but I doubt the Piano Man did]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice scoop from the WaPo - recording from inside GOP retreat's health care session. Clear pic of the chaos https://t.co/U4sdY8MXz7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jenhab Reporters are repeatedly TEEING THIS UP for May!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiting for a "Love Actually" moment between Theresa May and Donald Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump administration abruptly pulls Obamacare ads that had already been paid for - from @pauldemko https://t.co/F1yL0GEVQX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freshman Republican introduces bill to eliminate "Members only" signs from Capitol -- does it include members gym? https://t.co/sMu9o9vObN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump on his search for his CIA director: "Where the hell is Pompeo?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump: "Tom Price is going to do a phenomenal job"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[way to set expectations https://t.co/6ixz4EN8lr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VP Mike Pence will address the March for Life on Friday, a coup for the anti-abortion movement]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't expect a White House health plan to sail thru Congress, where even GOP allies want Congress to write bills https://t.co/FAldWRRXmw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ASlavitt Serious question: Doesn't the same apply to all the pro-ACA ads over the years and now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sen Alexander on a Trump health plan: "Just because he recs it doesn’t mean we have to do it, but it’s very helpful" https://t.co/FAldWRRXmw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm still on a Trump robocall list. I can report Obamacare will be repealed and I can be added to a FAX to pressure Congress to support it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conservatives balking on Ocare repeal? "There is always the danger that this could go catastrophically wrong." https://t.co/uskdWjQdlL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's new Mexico City policy is massively bigger than earlier GOP versions -- reupping my story from Monday https://t.co/DxUpbdnG8F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rshawnm woah i am a horrible fan for not watching!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It pays to be a packrat when 5-year old quotes are relevant again. https://t.co/tUgU0K9FOI https://t.co/lf0wic4Kgn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sen @RandPaul tells me he is introducing his Obamacare alternative bill this evening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tom Price throwing major shade against both Politico and Talking Points Memo for, um, quoting him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eight Senate Democrats asked the SEC to investigate @RepTomPrice over insider trading allegations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump appears to have reinstated "global gag rule" that blocks federal $ to foreign aid groups that do/support abortion but text not out yet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federal judge blocks Aetna's attempted purchase of Humana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of Trump's first official acts was to tell his government to do all they can to waive Obamacare rules https://t.co/cNdK5CucoE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The order itself changes nothing right now, but makes clear that his administration wants to/will undercut the ACA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump issued order to his administration to roll back, waive, exempt as much of #Obamacare as they can before Congress can repeal it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This vote has been scheduled for Tuesday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is on tv signing orders but what are they?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JakeSherman Isn't that her in the left side of the picture?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BresPolitico how does it compare with Eisenhower? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sangerkatz @jrovner @sarahkliff @JeffYoung @CitizenCohn @sam_baker @aawayne lots of home remodel references, particularly from Sen Harkin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JakeSherman Kasich is in town to talk with R lawmakers about O'care repeal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tom Price's HELP Committee hearing ends at nearly 4 hours. Next up, Senate Finance confirmation hearing on 1/24]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["That's some good staff work" -- Price with some sass, I think, for Sen @ChrisMurphyCT on serious stock questions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@burgessev congratulations!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Important to note that Republicans and Democrats have/will have far different definitions of what is adequate health coverage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two hours into Price confirmation hearing, he says that the goal of his health plan would be to cover more people than Obamacare did.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sen Bennet jokes that he showed his injured knee to HHS Sec Tom Price, now he is railing against GOP health plans. Kind of theatrical]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rant: Please, stop bumping your Tom Price react in my inbox. I got it the first time (and the second and third).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just announced: HHS secretary nom Tom Price will go before the Senate Finance Committee on Tuesday 1/24. Tomorrow, the HELP Committee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[House to vote next week on a bill to prohibit taxpayer funding of abortion and ban abortion coverage from subsidized Obamacare plans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sen Ted Cruz gets a big laugh when police dog barks in front of group of reporters in the Capitol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a good summary of HHS nominee Tom Price's health care bill: https://t.co/pIhF4AjrLx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HHS .@SecBurwell disputes GOP claim that Obamacare was already in a "death spiral" before repeal efforts began. https://t.co/iGghLEpdm0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SecBurwell, who led Obamacare for two+ years, will soon sign her family up for one of its health plans https://t.co/iGghLEpdm0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ddiamond You're the best Dan! thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republicans are taking a major step to show they are committed to a smooth transition from Obamacare to a new plan 
https://t.co/kMeO7iPZBI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republicans took the Obama White House to court over Obamacare's cost-sharing program -- now they plan to fund it https://t.co/kMeO7iPZBI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEWS: Congressional Republicans plan to fund Obamacare's cost-sharing subsidy program -- before the kill whole law https://t.co/kMeO7iPZBI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jenhab No Democrats joined the GOP in the vote. Nine Republicans defected for various reasons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The House has now approved the first of many steps toward repealing Obamacare. The Senate approved earlier this week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not getting carded at Harris Teeter was too harsh of a blow this evening]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senate voted to start the Obamacare repeal process last night; House planning to pick up the baton tmrw https://t.co/qxnXBY3aHu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump team starts talking with the Hill on maternity leave and child-care policies -- from @rachaelmbade https://t.co/vmWz6LIois]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Latest vote-a-rama count: 187 filed amendments.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Trump intro'd "an actual specific [health] plan, that would be a much easier starting point than taking 6 plans" https://t.co/71f3in8Kzf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's health care plan would either help the GOP coalesce behind a plan or drive a wedge with the Hill https://t.co/71f3in8Kzf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're up to 126 (mostly health) amendments filed for Senate vote-a-rama this evening, but there are some repeats and some won't get a vote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spotted on Senate side of the Hill: HHS designee Tom Price, who did not answer questions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's drug comments could make tonight's (likely and nonbinding) Senate vote on drug negotiations a little more interesting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump: Obamacare repeal and replace "on the same day... could be the same hour"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump on Obamacare repeal. "We are doing the Democrats a great service" I suspect Democrats would disagree...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump: After Price's HHS nom is approved, we'll be submitting an Obamacare repeal and replace plan - "very complicated stuff."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's call for a quick Obamacare replacement didn't really clear up the morass on the Hill https://t.co/95eOQyS3f4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder why Americans strongly detest Washington? https://t.co/bfvzK1LOZJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vaccine skeptic RFK Jr. will lead @realDonaldTrump's vaccine safety panel https://t.co/ErP8u1BG0C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump meeting today with HHS secretary pick Tom Price and CMS pick Seema Verma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@burgessev is really interesting in hearing this story: https://t.co/Nv5ziknH9N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOP running into a lot of problems on Obamacare repeal, but all comes back to this: What Republican will ACTUALLY vote against repeal?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SenBobCorker and four moderates try to slow down the Obamacare repeal train https://t.co/Nv5ziknH9N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonder what these people in white coats are at the Capitol to talk about? https://t.co/pkNrlUoIi3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So this is interesting. https://t.co/BlbFcBqEDA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't think they're at the point of "breaking ranks" -- yet. Any R who opposes repeal gets immediate primary https://t.co/uzRaT1KkgC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[throwback #tbt https://t.co/wG0CubFxhH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[House @SpeakerRyan says Obamacare repeal bill will include defunding Planned Parenthood. Prior version of bill did so for one year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senate Dems demand ethics investigation into HHS nominee Tom Price's stock trading before confirmation https://t.co/zridMqZgmJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republicans are considering delaying instead of repealing some of the taxes in Obamacare - w/ @burgessev https://t.co/HJjxNbPfIa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Covering Obamacare sometimes feels like running a circular track. https://t.co/zLt7BaO6fW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOP airs Obamacare divisions in meeting with VP-elect Pence - w/ @burgessev https://t.co/HJjxNbPfIa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dems will blame collapse on GOP's repeal. Republicans will argue it was going to happen anyway because ACA was already collapsing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is Trump trying to get ahead of the blame game on the insurance market collapse that is likely to happen in 17… https://t.co/zlpCWX2F3a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats admit they can't really stop GOP from repealing Obamacare. Now the goal is maximum political impact https://t.co/n9lLt3iZuz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republicans aren't worried about preserving Obamacare's "universal coverage" -- they are pledging "universal access" https://t.co/w8scgOEJfe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Capitol Hill has a strong First Day of School vibe today -- people lost, big crowds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArmstrongDrew @ddiamond There is a summer 2013 CMS printout on my desk that promises exchanges are ready to open on time!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ddiamond perhaps the most 14th street thing ever!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>