<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Great video from @ericfitz7 about what he feels @jciireland is &amp; thanks for the shout out! #BeBetter #WhatCouldIBe https://t.co/RRekxheNhp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @MovemberIreland for my #Movember compass! I'll never get lost again. Proud to be a platinum member on the I… https://t.co/X8KHZojPnb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How beautiful does this #cinema look in #Shanghai Excellent work @neriandhu https://t.co/hniIgehBa9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The early bird catches the worm. Up and just hitting the road for a day delivering training @jciireland in Mayo. #BeBetter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing change of use for the #GPO this evening for the @dublinlionsclub #EricsParty Amazing sense of community. We… https://t.co/AjY6NO4eze]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the way to volunteer @dublinlionsclub annual #EricsParty in the #GPO. Looking forward to a great evening of service to the community]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Leitrim and #boxty making on #greatrailwayjourneys now @BBC 2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giddy-up! Guess who's listened to audiobooks for 7 days in a row?  Join in the fun with a free Audible trial.: https://t.co/QqmhUcdPKQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New year, new you? I really like our latest TV ad. It's as simple as what and where. #insideindeed https://t.co/NdK8sj5f3C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm confused &amp; hungry with these similar logos #celebritymasterchefIRL Red with a dash of colour along the bottom… https://t.co/yCCoHO7DAC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying to figure out how the @didelectrical clock works because it looks like it's flying around! @tv3ireland #celebritymasterchefIRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice touch at work in the Indeed office Dublin from @ArtizanFood with an energy boost smoothie. #insideindeed https://t.co/fWx5VdEDLn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting, @Activehours which makes every day a payday, just raised $22 million in Series A funding https://t.co/H1dTZcXMSf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not enough anymore just to have a mobile career site: https://t.co/SUfnLMHNI9 by @Lars via @FastCompany]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Guest Blog for @ThePanelDublin: Christmas Crackers - 3 #Networking Tips to remember this time of Year  https://t.co/pcrjNxZ96Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatKennyNT Virtual Reality #PKNT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really interesting read. The Future of TV isn’t apps https://t.co/Ln9ypghypl via @techcrunch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016, a year in job searches. How the different events over the year shaped how people searched for jobs. https://t.co/GleerniQc5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @ElectricIreland for my gift. Just in time for Christmas! #ElectricIrelandRewards https://t.co/DAu9R7wben]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best of luck to all @indeed Dublin running in the @Aware 10K today. Our running gear may be a little competitive fo… https://t.co/J0ThblxnBj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Irish Company Using NASA Technology To Create "World's Coolest Beer Glass" https://t.co/dOMVYJjZXO via @TheEffectDotNet @IglooGlass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really informative Twitter Hour this evening hosted @jciireland as part of their Active Citizenship Week  #AutismAwarenessJCI Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was in @CineworldDublin yesterday, saw they didn't Autism Friendly Screenings, so I did some research… https://t.co/Ob9bPGZyWy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Pay app just appeared on my phone. Does this mean it's launching in #Ireland soon? @Android #AndroidPay https://t.co/bNHU28BsAk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome to the future of work https://t.co/2TIICoXaLA via @techcrunch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for the #Movember cake and cupcakes @indeed @MovemberIreland #insideindeed https://t.co/PSUfd3bfBs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[War veteran, 89, posts ad for job to stop him 'dying of boredom' https://t.co/rRT05rp6Gh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Update 5 of 5. Final few hours with my mo. Thanks for all the donations, still time to support.… https://t.co/fWro9rqvnN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On my way to @TescoIrl Sandymount to do a shift with Dublin Lions Club for our annual food appeal in aid of… https://t.co/iVX1XvbYz6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need your support. Help me reach my target this Movember, and your donations will help men live happier and longer
https://t.co/bjxU2GsYtZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Culture Fit is Critical in Startup Hiring - Indeed Blog https://t.co/qmbPnYZpdM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The midway point. Thanks for all the donations so far and if you haven't done so yet, a little will go a long way.… https://t.co/9Y61QMzcfb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 flights in 2 days with @KLM and I have to say thank you for your excellent staff and great service. A pleasure flying with you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to the Annual @jcimayo dinner next Saturday. Who's coming? #BePartOfIT https://t.co/ynWdl4SNDS https://t.co/saS3hWAScB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great first days training with over 60 local JCI board members from around Denmark. That me rabbiting on at the top… https://t.co/ZnRTYBuK17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off to work with @jcidanmark local JCI organisations for the weekend in Billund, Denmark this afternoon. #BeBetter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great day volunteering with @indeed Dublin planting trees for @TreesForIreland near Marley Park D16 @InsideIndeed… https://t.co/e4Wzp4UK7A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're celebrating hitting 500 Indeedians here in the Dublin office with some nice treats @InsideIndeed #insideindeed https://t.co/3u1pRdMtzk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Update 2 of 5. Couldn't control the growth of my mo! Only kidding, thanks to those who have donated and more to com… https://t.co/xdfkLRfvVB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GMurnaghan @LeeCPhillips @InsideIndeed Thanks guys!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only 5 updates I promise, I'd really appreciate your support for me to look even more stupid https://t.co/bjxU2GsYtZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The history of innovation in recruitment technology and services https://t.co/sek9LeZFnl via @techcrunch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Passionate about sales? We're passionate about helping people get jobs... at @indeed! Meet our UK Sales team 3/11 : https://t.co/kM835YiJth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should You Require a Cover Letter? - Indeed Blog https://t.co/qlWVeeHivz #jobfairy #Indeed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Busy 3/11? Why not join the UK Sales team for some networking and frosty beverages in @indeed's Dublin office?: https://t.co/kM835YiJth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you or do you know a great #sales person? We're looking to grow in our #Dublin office with lots of roles! PM Me https://t.co/743HTsD7fN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheers @dannycagney @jciireland @JCICork I need the support... Let's see if I'm featured in this debate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a great residential board meeting with @nycinews in Wicklow, now heading to the @jciireland National Conventi… https://t.co/Y1zc2vWgT4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice mention in the @IrishLegalNews -  Cleaver Fulton Rankin hosts networking seminar for younger staff https://t.co/vGVSxEMLQw @CFR_Law]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your CV is probably missing this killer piece of information https://t.co/xyqLTxGInv via @jciireland #volunteer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 Hiring Lessons the Tech Industry Can Teach All Recruiters - Indeed Blog https://t.co/IZOS9Av0c2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The importance of science fiction to Entrepreneurship. An excellent piece by @BNarasin https://t.co/zrYIFDQBqW via @techcrunch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited to be speaking @CFR_Law this evening in #Belfast on the topic of "Sparkling Conversation" and the power of… https://t.co/eTsFCCfdA7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may be watching too much @NarcosNetflix on @NetflixUK as I've just caught myself speaking Spanish to myself and I don't know any Spanish..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this epic, expertly executed $77k Indiegogo backer troll https://t.co/OLgNMcdtCz via @techcrunch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honoured to introduce @SaskiaTidey @DFitzy23 @CianCowley and @vincentbrowne for the @BOIbusiness Enterprise Town… https://t.co/2E7Ysugunf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to MCing the Bank of Ireland Enterprise Town event this afternoon in Dun Laoghaire @dlrLexIcon… https://t.co/IORDl09P7x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, amazing building, time lapse video and Norwegian scenes. Reminds me of the West of Ireland https://t.co/7Lj4UXxQM0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 1% of the Indeed Dublin office flying the Green and Red of Mayo for the football replay tomorrow @indeed… https://t.co/pKSRFKqjTL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just heard my first Christmas ad on @NewstalkFM for Kube interiors! In September.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Innovation is in all the wrong places https://t.co/bz0zJqz6ih via @techcrunch One of the best articles I've read in a long time @tomfgoodwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @IndeedUK CV gives you access to millions of candidates. Join us at 2pm to reach the talent you're looking for https://t.co/sw0oRCuvYn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 Examples of Great Organizational Culture You Can Learn From - Indeed Blog https://t.co/vZwBwvxoff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gender pay gap in UK won't close until 2069, report warns https://t.co/bWqezX90XN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having much first burrito from @ZambreroIreland and loving the concept of #Plate4Plate Hidden away on Hatch Street… https://t.co/4v9ifgT0ZX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see @alexisohanian co-founder of @reddit giving a shout out to @MayoGAA on his Snapchat for the match next… https://t.co/Sz6TO4iVLk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're growing in our Dublin office and looking for Account Executives. Send me a message if your interested https://t.co/YGEo7Y7VsF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @martimurtagh and @NewryJC for a great evening. Although this looks like I'm telling someone off.... I actually may have been...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to speaking with the members of @NewryJC this evening on the topic of #Networking in the @pkffpm offices]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We'll score 3 own goals the next time for the Dubs so they'll win....we might hear the Hill at the next game 😉 #Mayo4Sam #DUBvMAYO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would red jeans be too much? @MayoClub51 @MayoGAA @HSmayo @MayoAssocCork @MAYOMAD @MayoDublinAssoc https://t.co/L651cC1nJ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Survey results are in as to who the other counties will be cheering for today.. Independently verified #TheToughest https://t.co/093Z3s5zjl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having a great afternoon volunteering at the Blue Fire Street Festival in Smithfield #LoveSmithfield #BlueFire16 https://t.co/ffp1CNj4Qk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sun is shining and looking forward to volunteering at @CultureNight later on! Come along and say hello! #LOVEculture https://t.co/z2VUGlST49]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who ever thought 50 chairs in a room could be a work of art or should I call it an installation? Beautiful https://t.co/1t9QI4vao2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great board meeting this evening for the @nycinews and thanks to @AmnestyIreland for the use of the boardroom!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this the future of working in an office? https://t.co/MyZJzusFJc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had a great evening MCing the @JCISouthside Friendly Business Awards. A room full of local friendly businesses is hard to beat! #FBAs #JCI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look at me there... Front row. Nothing at all to do with my aging eyesight.. Ha ha https://t.co/IExMinJlgy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just out of a room full of volunteers receiving orientation. Looking forward to @CultureNight this Fri #LOVEculture https://t.co/dyzmO6TXWE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman after my own heart @AoifeCoop regarding time keeping. Totally robbing "Don't be late, there's no debate!" Love it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We’re Expanding Our Team Dedicated to Studying Global Labor Market Trends: Here’s Why - Indeed Blog https://t.co/ZksiK1i8WA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have a great day @ronanmooney and @barrybkkelly on your big day! #RBWedding16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've just volunteered for @CultureNight have you? https://t.co/JjtLwJaR3x #volunteer #CultureNight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Passionate about sales? We're passionate about helping people get jobs... at @indeed! Meet our UK Sales team 9/8: https://t.co/S8EjbGm9mR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of our offices here @indeed Dublin. We're all about results! #insideindeed #OscarWilde https://t.co/VsZp508kfB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Directors @ericpryan, @ColinBohanna and members of our UK sales team are looking forward to meeting you on 9/8: https://t.co/S8EjbGm9mR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give me a follow @jesskellynt and I'll DM you my direct one. Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @jesskellynt I'm working with @indeed The World's No 1 job site, and I'm sure we can help if we can.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most dangerous job on the planet. Sad to hear of this loss. First in and last out. https://t.co/IUGQQ6GOD3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How 3 Companies Use Mission and Purpose to Inspire Top Talent - Indeed Blog https://t.co/e2GrWyhKtM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My dad calls me up, all excited that he just spotted my new work sponsoring a match he's watching! #insideindeed https://t.co/LwHLDrRwpY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sun breaking through for my first day with @indeed @InsideIndeed #insideindeed https://t.co/bbuNSeQY3l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiting for the right professional network https://t.co/MrrkDPzYe2 via @techcrunch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blue astra travelling the wrong way on the N4 dual carriageway at junction 11 near Mullingar @aaroadwatch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Next Step" as today is my last day with BNI and FireCloud365. Read my post here https://t.co/AFOVMqAjVa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Dubai fire: Blaze engulfs more than 30 floors of Sulafa Tower https://t.co/CkOZJqCTiL Glad to hear of no casualties @firecloud365]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for super customer service from sales consultant Shannon in Carphone Warehouse in Carrick-On-Shannon. #TopNotch @CPWTweets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks Martin from @fit_funds Glad you enjoyed it! #Learn2Earn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["5 Business Snapchatters I follow" https://t.co/5z8nOCdW1m @garyvee @msuster @alexisohanian @WeAreBrave @justinkan #Snapchat #Business]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>