<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump is done with Kellyanne Conway, hands her off to Mike Pence’s office https://t.co/YYplO1N6cU via @PalmerReport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Budweiser’s Super Bowl ad is a moving immigrant story. It’s just not Adolphus Busch’s: https://t.co/Y69rYO2eoI via @BrowBeat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senate subcommittee to launch Russian interference probe https://t.co/ICTcyYmZDH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Memo to the White House on the Contributions of Frederick Douglass https://t.co/mrpoCdqJyw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After the March, Recriminations? https://t.co/nu1za4owZf via @WeeklyStandard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dr. Seuss political cartoons re-emerge amid criticism of Donald Trump https://t.co/wPmoWkY5CX via @USATODAY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senate confirms Tillerson as secretary of state https://t.co/f4ywjG0DGG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mayors to Trump: ‘Don’t Punish Us’ https://t.co/3xbO05FJw7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kal Penn turned a hateful troll's message into $500,000 for Syrian refugees: https://t.co/EdlwO3efnM via @BrowBeat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scientists Baffled by McConnell and Ryan’s Ability to Stand Upright Without Spines https://t.co/7T5TcqHrdT via @BorowitzReport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russians Charged With Treason Worked in Office Linked to Election Hacking https://t.co/7mLohUJNir]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DA: Man kicked Muslim woman at JFK airport, said 'Trump is here now' https://t.co/K6RdsgkZ0Z via @USATODAY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Preparing for the Next Epidemic: A First Step  https://t.co/jTr7afEbVi via @billgates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lpjasper63 fact is, NO growth in federal work force. There's the lie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lpjasper63  let's not call these facts, really. Alternate truths, perhaps. Get with the program.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lpjasper63 Did you happen to notice Tump gave an invalid reason for freezing federal jobs? But I guess it doesn't matter-he doesn't need 1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Protest Fails https://t.co/pTkJDLqckR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Via @NPR: Republican Plan To Replace Obamacare Would Turn Medicaid Over To States https://t.co/KKWLJHohQF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It sure looks like more people showed up for the #WomensMarch than inauguration https://t.co/sv5zSzhCAw # via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BergDog_69 way to finish strong! Way to go!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - The Guyana tribe in search of a lost identity https://t.co/xtDXZwPBwp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Julia Roberts Taught Me More In Less Than 2 Minutes Than Anyone Else Has Done My WHOLE Life! https://t.co/IyoRTlocbO via @Dejanscode]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prosecutors, Justice officials sign letter criticizing Comey decision https://t.co/4BZNau0NMA via @USATODAY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mental Illness Is Not a Horror Show https://t.co/ku912ZQ6o1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Meaning of Bob Dylan’s Silence https://t.co/b5o0OEHnjd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report: Burberry and Coach Could Be Merging https://t.co/04Hogzp6sM via @thecut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clinton wins ‘Trump Bingo’ on ‘Saturday Night Live’ https://t.co/Sf7HwEe1iI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump uses out-of-context line to hit Michelle Obama https://t.co/qX0XlrkBmZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salma Hayek: Trump planted story about my height after I denied him a date https://t.co/NDV4L8HMZn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ana Navarro’s One-Woman Revolt Against Donald Trump https://t.co/pq9O13Bxke via @newyorker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Price I’ve Paid for Opposing Donald Trump https://t.co/KxIvXYvg2O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's 'rigged' election talk echoes former segregationist George Wallace https://t.co/VpEA84iQM3 via @USATODAY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016’s Manifest Misogyny https://t.co/l5nmyy0DFv via @newyorker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forget this “Hillary is unlikable” stuff. Hillary is downright inspiring. https://t.co/eLYlZortVh via @doublexmag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MedImmune looking for a contact in Gaithersburg.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump once fired 'Celebrity Apprentice' contestant for 'locker room talk' https://t.co/arK7v7JYCi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch Fred Flintstone and Barney Rubble as Donald Trump and Billy Bush https://t.co/yvyccYXNus # via @HuffPostComedy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For Many Women, Trump’s ‘Locker Room Talk’ Brings Memories of Abuse https://t.co/JtgwrHgVrV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Goes to the Dogs https://t.co/MA6yhyI9kf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arizona Republic gets death threats after endorsing Clinton https://t.co/8T6F9kUFp2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['how I Met Your Mother' Star Ashley Williams Reveals Miscarriage: 'i'm A Survivor' |  https://t.co/aBLG1XRZuw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Sound of Science -  https://t.co/GOzbYPuS6f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First African-American, woman to lead Library of Congress sworn in @CNNPolitics https://t.co/OX8Z8DD8dz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Morell and Vickers: An open letter to Donald Trump https://t.co/H3DEtX4hKu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Donald Trump retooled his charity to spend other people’s money https://t.co/bVD6yW413v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Researchers Confront an Epidemic of Loneliness https://t.co/AHHhoN6Bsr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9/11 Miracle: The Little Chapel That Survived https://t.co/XSCDu61J8J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 things I learned from falling in love after divorce @HuffPostBlog https://t.co/n0XLZmNLOG via @HuffPostDivorce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 essential trips for 'Game of Thrones' superfans, organized by house https://t.co/Egx3aVK9R5 via @mashable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Pipeline Fight and America’s Dark Past https://t.co/Y6JgJVTUQX via @newyorker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Via @nprmusic: Hear Jack White's Acoustic Take On The Raconteurs' 'Carolina Drama' https://t.co/cChEyTEAsw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here’s a smart way to reduce gun deaths that many gun rights people actually support: https://t.co/OCNPWNhNKV via @slate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Hillary: How Very Dare You! https://t.co/kjEK2j2MbQ via @RBHSOregon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alphabet plans to deliver Chipotle burritos via drone at Virginia Tech https://t.co/xXUMfUBITK via @technology]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, Seriously, Chelsea Clinton and Ivanka Trump Are Still Friends https://t.co/RKoDeCsJky via @thecut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Associated Press has deleted that 2-week-old Clinton tweet https://t.co/8BiNefCBIC via @poynter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dabney Montgomery, Tuskegee Airman who safeguarded Martin Luther King Jr., dies at 93 https://t.co/ACuWMpS2b7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Ann Coulter jokes at the Rob Lowe roast? They really were that brutal. https://t.co/3Tmu3AuY2S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Female genital mutilation needed because Egyptian men are ‘sexually weak,’ lawmaker says https://t.co/14ps2r5CLb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's history of corruption is mind-boggling. So why is Clinton supposedly the corrupt one? https://t.co/UsED0CSVZy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Morgan StanleyVoice: A Green Bond Revolution With A Social Twist via @forbes https://t.co/NPgml8iJGT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surfing in Nixonland https://t.co/oKs82hZ9RB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Longtime Republican consultant: if black people voted Republican, voter ID laws wouldn't happen https://t.co/EIa4B6b0pD via @voxdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guess which candidate's foundation was caught in an illegal campaign funding scheme? https://t.co/Lpuo09Z28p via @voxdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just saw a snow plow on 70N in PA....wha?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump Jr. Retweets the ‘Neo-Nazi Movement’s Favorite Academic’ https://t.co/ROFD9zUMGH via @jdforward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump to show up, not speak out at black Detroit church https://t.co/imrP72pgsp via @USATODAY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Medal of Honor Recipient Has Some Choice Words for Colin Kaepernick About the Meaning of 'Sacrifice' https://t.co/bD5QihZwS2 via @TheIJR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AstraZeneca agrees to pay $5.5 million to settle alleged bribery probe     https://t.co/rBDhtweQP5 via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North Korean vice premier executed, south says https://t.co/u863OmtAnU via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michele Bachmann: God picked Trump to be the GOP nominee https://t.co/ZylRfrJ3nt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[USA TODAY analysis: Rich Democrats surge past GOP in political giving https://t.co/CMmoWRYToa via @USATODAY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[POLL: 31% of Trump supporters actually support an Atlantic ocean wall to keep Muslims out https://t.co/ixRz2gZE6k via @bi_politics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Criticize Colin Kaepernick but support Donald Trump? Think again https://t.co/NYCt2P4fej via @USATODAY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gene Wilder rejected James Corden's 'Late Late' invite in an email as sweet as a Wonka Bar https://t.co/e4ssXkTJIx via @USATODAY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple Found To Have Received Illegal Tax Benefits, Ordered To Pay $14.5 Billion In Back Taxes via @forbes https://t.co/cMjsLVzjmj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lightning strike killed 323 reindeer, and this is the ghastly aftermath https://t.co/PL3mNLMmh6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers targeted Arizona election system https://t.co/yTKBYNdQXr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 Reasons Why Trump Would Hate Being President https://t.co/kykWUmqN7m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michelle Obama's ship has come in @CNNPolitics https://t.co/HLDXVpucXk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alleged California sex offender found in Louisiana with 4 missing kids https://t.co/ng07v8dFQB via @nbcnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missing spring breaker was raped, shot and eaten by alligators, FBI agent testifies https://t.co/0AsEVG79vX # via @HuffPostCrime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lessons Learned from The Demon https://t.co/FiMcK6pzpV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump was accused of destroying email evidence in lawsuit 10 years ago https://t.co/Iy9NPE4lPm via @USATODAY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton Has Been ‘Finding Her Voice’ Since 1993 https://t.co/RboxZcHZwH via @thedailybeast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are female CEOs and senators disproportionately blond? Blame sexism. https://t.co/mYKKuOW9tD via @doublexmag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump: Media has missed 'the whole point' on immigration https://t.co/1gfkDEyUJA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Rob Lowe's roast, Ann Coulter gets burned hardest https://t.co/eepH878gYV via @USATODAY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump risks enraging his own supporters backing down on immigration https://t.co/yTgGWkTzkQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump fights breaking out across college campuses https://t.co/fKpUPbymRu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. intelligence says Islamic State is weakening after series of defeats https://t.co/9VSTGr9ohk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Yoga Teacher Has a Great Message for Her Critics https://t.co/8Gu94xKDcD via @thecut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Father of slain reporter rails against ‘orange-faced Fuhrer’ https://t.co/W9NdZSl844]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bannon's ex-wife: 'He didn’t want the girls going to school with Jews'  https://t.co/bLC31lYoY9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michelle Obama Knew at Age 10 That You Don’t Need a Man to Be Happy https://t.co/jRz6XySbek via @thecut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maine governor: The 'enemy' is people of color https://t.co/x4f0e3pWnV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a liberal professor, and my liberal students terrify me https://t.co/Jbbaplb1ra via @voxdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is he trying the Pontius Pilate role?  https://t.co/aSPI2KSpBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stumped on Immigration Plan, Trump Gives Mob Rule a Try https://t.co/ZRHq7F0l8I via @intelligencer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Incredible possibilities of 'invisible' wood @CNNStyle https://t.co/ruKuJQD4go]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>