<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[With more than six months to the election, can Schulz sustain (honeymoon?) bounce to dethrone Merkal? https://t.co/FIM5YqRtA7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very nice blogpost here on the complexities of income equality in the UK, most of which also applies to Ireland. https://t.co/JalFizrvgy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HmsGerlach My point: govts target poverty and deprivation metrics, but don't target inequality metrics. I (respectfully) stand by it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HmsGerlach No, they don't, as - err - mentioned in the column! No country targets Gini Coefficient]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ireland has traditionally been weak entrepreneurially. Column #2 on the spectacular exception of aircraft leasing 
https://t.co/TSL2Sa2HBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My column on Ireland's falling inequality levels and why no country explicitly seeks to reduce income inequality.
https://t.co/7OaVFOPceM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanKay_Rocket ...being as dumbly confrontational as DT with his administration only plays into the hands of those him who want crisis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanKay_Rocket We absolutely need to respond, but as issues arise, not with blanket "opposition to the 45th POTUS and his government"...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surf's not up: a strong take on the campaign for California to exit the US https://t.co/NIWAn9Yym0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanKay_Rocket if DT puts US on par with Russia, not a matter that requires a European response. There will be many fights. Keep powder dry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NChildersMEP Trump is a disaster, but his election was not a "coup". Nor is there evidence he wants to "wipe away" UN, EU, NATO, WTO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Europe needs to be calm+calculated if/when Trump threatens interests, not do as this hysterical Spiegel piece urges
https://t.co/hVVh5WhvSp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sinead_ryan Ignoring trolls is the response. reacting in any way just encourages them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eosfuturedesign Can't be much. Singapore's total tax revenues equal just 14% of GDP. Up to 50% in some European countries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ronanlyons Like most things in Singapore appear to be, but don't think most Brits want to abolish NHS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK public spend on health is 4 times that of Singapore. Cutting taxes to Singapore levels wld make post 2008 auster… https://t.co/MtrtkM1JvP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worth noting that Singapore's healthcare system could hardly be more different from NHS. Nothing is free, at point… https://t.co/WoiS1Olx52]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LarryPDonnelly don't let it get to you Larry. You've been a great, non hysterical voice in all this. Serious times, serious people etc...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@siliconbarry post tax, and includes welfare payments.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Latest figures show income inequality in Ireland has fallen below the EU average. More details here… https://t.co/rVynsA68gJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MartinDoyleIT Great to hear Martin. Many congrats.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 years on, household wealth is still below peak. But falling debt+rising asset values helping rebuild households'… https://t.co/1WIgOboPvX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's column assessing the health of democracy, along with some of the data cited. https://t.co/3oKRYZoRrL https://t.co/9uyNR7Brfx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomClonan @sarahcareyIRL @Independent_ie Don't see one Tom. Nordics all have big populist/anti-immigrant parties. They haven't been immune.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Urban deprivation rate has been higher than rural rate for every year bar one since records began in 2004. https://t.co/Cvlcv1sIAV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GerardBrady100 interesting. havent seen this source. is it from revenue?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consistent poverty rates broadly similar across the country, though with some strange looking temporary spikes. https://t.co/zmnKWaLM8F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HmsGerlach 46k  IT jobs in Dublin, 1/12 of total. also, increase in housing stock in Dublin during bubble was lower than many other places]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HmsGerlach wage inflation highest in tech sector, which is concentrated in Dublin, and more general indicators point to stronger recoevery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Convergence of disposable incomes across Ireland's regions since recovery began. Surprisingly, Dubliners have not b… https://t.co/aK9TREpIcC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those with 2nd level education only were the big losers in the crash. Tertiary and primary educated experienced sim… https://t.co/15AnGJjBjO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EI_55_ Not from today's trawl through data or from recollection.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While older folk have never been better off, real disposable incomes of working age people are still below the pre-… https://t.co/UJ41BF0lSS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@r_o_farrell Good point. Any data on homeless households as % of all households?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinHigginsIrl Economy was still contracting in 2010-12. Recovery only kicked in in 2013. All measures better since then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New figures show deprivation rate, consistent poverty and income inequality all fell in 2015. Suggests that economi… https://t.co/LkV5FBwksl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Polarisation of US politics in recent decades has been more a phenomenon of the political class than the general po… https://t.co/ENlos0X3tT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@POLITICOEurope's description of today's Oireachtas committee hearing with @vestager is not flattering.… https://t.co/DvwENk0u4p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MayorMontague they give me an occasional week off - all work, no play etc. normal service resumes Thursday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dsmooney BTW Derek, I'm not having a go. Always read your stuff because I respect your views. Just (respectfully) disagree on this occasion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dsmooney I felt the piece was overly critical. This govt not up to much, but a challenge like brexit plays well to the system's strengths.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dsmooney I'd be careful not to conflate system's capacity for statecraft with EK's capacity for statesmanship.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating comparison of Europe's 1848 'springtime of peoples' with 'Arab spring' by @FukuyamaFrancis https://t.co/ng47VbjK6A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dsmooney haven't heard officials complain about resources, human or otherwise. I could be missing something. Have u heard anything?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always ask my non Irish contacts about Irish role in Brexit at EU level. Yet to hear any say it's passive or behind the curve. @dsmooney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very interesting take on Ireland-UK relations, and the common travel area in particular, by an ex Irish diplomat. https://t.co/Dism5MX6Gt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Diplomacy North Korean style. U.S. simply can't be the lynchpin state in world affairs if it's leader acts like thi… https://t.co/U2pNjxp0i5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best essay I have read on the rise of populism - erudite and balanced. Also highlights what is not known/understood.
https://t.co/JCyaqBlZWA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cartoon shows a certain small island being sunk/run over by new man at helm in U.S. https://t.co/i3yCIO7Nte]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calm, sensible analysis of EU free movement issues, with some modest proposals on reform. https://t.co/CjrUH4MDrA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK exports more to EU27 than most EU members export to UK. For most countries UK market is not v important. This pu… https://t.co/YDznEddmqR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Germany exports to China 5x more than the UK. Both are in the EU. Why do Brexiteers blame EU for UK's limited exports to emerging markets?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If this is construed by Germany/EU that European companies are being leaned on re location of investments there wil… https://t.co/ku6Z28E1Rk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nationalists don't make good internationslists - they dislike and distrust foreigners too much. https://t.co/XNo9VWeAlK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discussing #Brexit and implications on @TodaySOR after 11. Yesterday's column on what Ireland's interests are here… https://t.co/fo4QSVw6Rj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My column on Ireland's stance on #Brexit, and the views of @PhilHoganEU and ex-diplomat @ray_basssett on same.
https://t.co/CJo6t1jhBU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huge swings to the sane, internationalist centre in both UK by-elections today. The west may not yet be doomed. https://t.co/esL2BNqczL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mario Soares was a giant among post-war European leaders, playing a huge role in Portuguese democratisation and dec… https://t.co/6BxiIZaVgV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Brexitologist" - must be first contender for new word of 2017 https://t.co/zdi07cm3QG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could even the wildest conspiracy theorists have dreamt up such a scenario just 20 months ago? Much stranger than f… https://t.co/VAwSMBU8T8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of food for thought here. https://t.co/xOW6nfSiDZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahcareyIRL Everyone manoeuvring and pursuing their interests. Information and views flow thru all sorts of channels. V complex and messy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahcareyIRL There are lots of differences among the 27 but agreement not to make them public to maintain appearance of unity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@centralbank_ie The link above is to an excel spreadsheet!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnOBrennan2 I fully agree with you! Your analysis is spot on, on all counts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There has been a lot of ill-informed nonsense spoken about Ireland's position on #Brexit lately. This is an all too… https://t.co/Z5pShCPFnp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My columns on very good foreign investment story and much less positive public finances news
https://t.co/ZJk0KBz87T
https://t.co/m8SFquz8iy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the books below are discussed/reviewed here by @fromTGA. Well worth reading.
https://t.co/LXzuScy5HQ https://t.co/2vJph8uxEm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnOBrennan2 he's  been downbeat for quite a while. This is from volume one of 'political order' in 2011.… https://t.co/kBTcHizOOj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating piece on Calafornia underscores just how much diversity there is across US states
https://t.co/dXxNmp3cjp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Extremely unlikely scenario admittedly - President Le Pen loses a Frexit referendum she herself calls https://t.co/m8OhJoW77Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: December tax data are weak. Pattern since mid-2016 suggests a slowdown in the economy in the second half… https://t.co/yptWKctIjM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US election didn't lead to a change in Americans' views on whether their country is on wrong/right track (although… https://t.co/DhPYuKsMem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex political insider on why simple solutions don't work for complex problems.
https://t.co/ERFxdLjfjK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poll shows a Varadkar-led Fine Gael would enjoy a surge in support (+8 points) compared to current support levels. 
https://t.co/jFDmZK2MLo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A book that is definitely on the list for reviewing in 2017... https://t.co/Gs7tTD2s3X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/2 All the main sectors added employment with the exception of IT hardware https://t.co/rn0aR8Wg2n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/1 Today's @IDAIRELAND figures on foreign investment in 2016 are really positive.1/8 private sector jobs accounted… https://t.co/3YCxwd9skx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great. Must look them up. https://t.co/D61eqcGHCN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GerardBrady100 @siliconbarry thanks. can you share the dataset?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@siliconbarry totally fair point. Have you any data series on start ups?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If this is a good measure of entrepreneurial dynamism, doesn't suggest that start-ups have played a big role in rec… https://t.co/hMd09OleCB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A continental perspective on how Northern Ireland will be affected by #Brexit. https://t.co/FOqxADHsHa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Edmund Burke's words here are more relevant than ever.  https://t.co/BYcyPn98o0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wide-ranging, if slightly anglocentric, view of Europe's year from Brussels https://t.co/ph85rmS3aB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Among 15 European countries, just 1 in 3 people on average believe their country is headed in the right direction.… https://t.co/APd1RgLzxz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The complexity of the modern world has fractured the old left-right ideological spectrum. Good research/analysis he… https://t.co/4uMs27NU1g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's column tries to take stock of 2016 (can't remember a harder one to take stock of). 
https://t.co/ZPMAGDapau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This (excellent) oped on globalisation underscores how rarely the upsides of openness are made in Irish media.
https://t.co/LtHLtUREYe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brought to mind: my column on why Trump is not Reagan, and related matters.
https://t.co/2Cjsl1UKk7 https://t.co/i0CgSu5CmE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/1 Great essay on journalism in Trump/post-fact/truthiness era
https://t.co/vDh0hdiTFB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/2 including this advise against sounding angry https://t.co/v4SyUfyt6Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The brilliant @JonHaidt gives a social psychology perspective of economics, politics and history. It's a powerful a… https://t.co/YEMXqJArwr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The collpase in support among Italians for all aspects of the EU is a stand-out feature of latest @EurobarometerEU https://t.co/Cv1imQk52I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of good things kept happening in 2016, in Ireland and globally. Today's column https://t.co/AD7njKyL4R https://t.co/wmNujHBEqt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EU_Commission wins final legal stage re states aids and tax. A very important precedent.
https://t.co/h0lpGgsLcc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The modern state has three broad functions: security, redistribution and regulation. The last is most complex AND m… https://t.co/HHle0bT3s2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smomara1 Strange that the report makes no mention of the changed i context, particularly after the Trump Carrier intervention.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A major risk for the Irish economy is whether Trump leans on American companies based here to relocate jobs, functi… https://t.co/CFFlTzVibg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US legal scholar from free market Hoover Institution is harshly critical of #Apple in tax case.

https://t.co/k7tlOABXxZ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>