<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@CitizenActionIL keep posting pics! #Marchinto18]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamseanbaker @IndivisibleIL_6 @IndivisibleKane @IndivisibleTeam keep posting pics! Keep up the good work! #Marchinto18]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saturday morning inspiration. Dems on offense--&gt; https://t.co/LlEOSRFkGR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is disturbing. https://t.co/t4t597duQV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, "class" and "grace". Thanks for being such a role model. https://t.co/sSmsgH35rp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is so offensive https://t.co/F6qVMsDaab]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure awkward is the word, but it's a potential disaster for the people who live there &amp; a political nightmare f… https://t.co/eyGjJWK59u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[House GOP running scared--&gt; "Rep. Roskam's office cancels ACA meeting when reporter shows up" https://t.co/QTB7IdIAW8 #IL06 #ACA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's almost like Erickson isn't on the level... https://t.co/1Sc3uWT8TG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[House Republicans are still sucking up to him with rosy cheeks! https://t.co/pbkBsJbB9I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why would you say this? https://t.co/1m2v2RLij0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Spicer guy seems on the level. https://t.co/3DFLaglwqP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks Sheldon. #stayinoakland https://t.co/Ktj8tttaYy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One ethics debacle after another with this Republican-led Congress. Americans cannot trust Republicans to ethically… https://t.co/Q72SXx3gHP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bye Felicia! https://t.co/X9RyzOV2ji]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yup I'm pretty much right here--&gt; https://t.co/qmy4P5km8m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He knows--&gt; https://t.co/kyQnyvMgMg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WilsonWPA @KatyTurNBC I consider continuing to support someone "playing along". One would need alt-facts to draw a different conclusion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WilsonWPA @KatyTurNBC really? It's not? Republicans declared they would never vote for Trump en masse when these things occurred? Stop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@KatyTurNBC is speaking a whole bunch of truth that needs to be spoken. The GOP has become a party of the spineles… https://t.co/zjqhxixumE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This. This. A million times this--&gt; https://t.co/qamlhlv0sj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cc @SpeakerRyan. The world is looking at you and the silly little pamphlet won't do. https://t.co/C07nY1M98V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In which it's pointed out in detail how @repgregwalden has absolutely no idea what he's doing on the #ACA. In. Over… https://t.co/AYZZCC4Zfk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amen. House Republicans must be held accountable at the ballot box in 2018. https://t.co/Cjly9XKlXB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just google "Paul Ryan on voter fraud" and you will see how shameless he really is. No backbone at all. #BetterWay https://t.co/Q9O9NRVpDB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Speaker Ryan folds like a cheap suit, but hey, he's got a shiny little pamphlet! #BetterWay https://t.co/0x4rHEhNqT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ohh wuuuuut? Fox &amp; Friends is going to get holier than thou on opining?? https://t.co/A5OKQl8jSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History won't look kindly on Ryan's #betterway or his silly little pamphlet. https://t.co/mgKUTtE9Hs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warms my heart that you'll be sticking around for more Chris. https://t.co/Cq9XcSv8Vq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overshadowing GOP retreat--&gt; "Trump begins his term with a negative 36 - 44 percent job approval rating" https://t.co/N2rB5xCgi9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump in bad shape on key indicator--&gt; "53 - 44 percent that he does not care about average Americans" https://t.co/N2rB5xCgi9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why? Why wouldn't he keep calling out for the CIA director? https://t.co/ad0JdOW3b5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This was truly bizarre. He doesn't know how any of this works, does he? https://t.co/eF90yhpTex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These are definitely unusual times, but this definitely in the danger zone. https://t.co/lDH4fwSLvq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like the "we are more than a shiny little pamphlet" retreat was stomped on by Trump--&gt; #BetterWay https://t.co/wJsaSqDP5w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Speaker Ryan just exposed himself in a major way. Apparently, the deficit is not a Republican priority anymore. https://t.co/c65g1fzrUJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty clear already that this absurd American taxpayer funded wall is going to cause House Republicans a lot of heartburn...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@dccc statement on Speaker Paul "shiny little pamphlet" Ryan's 1st 100, no I mean 200 day "plan"--&gt; https://t.co/BPYSGC2DwE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndersonDrew Yeah I think they've replaced the clock with "wrong number who dis?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phew, thankfully Ryan just gave us that explanation for why they made it first 200 days instead of first 100 days.… https://t.co/GJz4axFxgA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But yeah let's totally cut PBS to end the national debt. https://t.co/uIp0DViHIY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[REAL HOUSE GOP 200 DAY PLAN: More Unpopular &amp; Fringe Policies That Hurt America's Middle-Class https://t.co/pxbZvfCXTd #BetterWay #ACA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DippinDots = fake ice cream. What is wrong with normal ice cream? Who asked for these dumb things? https://t.co/Vu8Up3fo7G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#priceiswrong--&gt; "Donald Trump’s HHS Nominee Failed To Properly Disclose Purchase Of Discounted Stock" https://t.co/y08mo6GPAV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@MSNBC just replayed @RonWyden taking @RepTomPrice to task for his super shady financial dealings. Bravo Senator! #priceiswrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I went through HS not knowing "based on studies I've been shown" excuses everything. "No mom, based on studies I've been shown..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CORRUPTCONGRESS WATCH: @RepTomPrice's Shady Stock Trades on Full Display in Today’s Hearing--&gt; https://t.co/BGQMwqBzKP #priceiswrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We learn a lot from reading you. https://t.co/QrQyb4MIxh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta love @clairecmc taking apart @RepTomPrice for not understanding how big of a tax break for the wealthy repealing ACA is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Important read--&gt; "Obamacare repeal would also affect your employer health insurance" https://t.co/zqDujjknTi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's clear that @RepTomPrice's stock scandal is not going away... #PriceHearing
#PriceIsWrong cc @RepChrisCollins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[uhhh I'm just flabbergasted that he said affordable healthcare is the wrong issue to focus on. There's no evidence… https://t.co/VUXtJqwEyw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making things up...like this? https://t.co/KZWtdgLhSd https://t.co/bQ7bA8WDo2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First we get participation trophies and now this: https://t.co/QL97jHB9CF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wow, wow, wow...are you saying he lied after promising he would not lie? Why would he do that?! https://t.co/qI9DQS1NIL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warriors coach Steve Kerr clowned on Spicer as well: https://t.co/hkyBwvvPhn https://t.co/rQkD8MbGqx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I found my love for organizing &amp; Time Kaine in the beautiful city of Richmond. Read this via @JesseFFerguson --&gt; https://t.co/itAjRlBY2M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please clap. https://t.co/dzdACnL0Fs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#mutemonday -- I already unfollowed @POTUS and never followed @realDonaldTrump but I'm urging everyone to follow @splcenter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whao if true, heard Trump and others as well! https://t.co/lLDkpLJVQ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heilman teaching important words... https://t.co/Dy0kV0uDqg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yashar has done the steadfast work of reminding people what the CIA &amp; FBI does and how to refer to them. https://t.co/tndYsJWC6x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only a true sick man lies and denigrates the CIA in one tweet. You're a Senator, sir, and this is still American. https://t.co/sh9LkA0rZU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thought you were good at the number facts Neil. This is too low by gametime barring any bad Pats injuries in this g… https://t.co/0cAoZLjQ9O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's cut the cute cliches every time something outrageous pops. Dude, none among us. None among us. https://t.co/3hwo85TnHD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seeing this game makes me think even more about what #raiders could have been without devastating Carr/ Penn injury]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cestephe you trolling my hate on Trump? I def don't support him or the patriot Trump sycophants]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone should pay close attention to Spicer here. We now know he does nothing but lie. Makes this story even more… https://t.co/s4Lb98rMDS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strongly agree. Media is biased towards facts and critical thinking. https://t.co/My57YHfgmv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And zero NFL fans are surprised that the Trump sycophant cheatriots got an erroneous call in their favor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's...a #hottake if ever seen one https://t.co/8vVnQDDGvl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LeBron's whining might be worse, but fair comparison https://t.co/ccjtNsSudZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why his suit fit terribly? https://t.co/bLq3i6WUoE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Important reminder: the Patriots are Trump's team. Go #Steelers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He is very, very far from being a moderate. https://t.co/59lybkBupm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There should have been some coverage on the Sunday shows of widespread grassroots backlash to ACA repeal vote https://t.co/jtaRo06x9F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THIS IS TOTALLY BANANAS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does Conway think attacking John Brennan is going to help Trump's relationship with the intelligence community? Hint: It's not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wow, of all people to declare war on, why Chuck Todd??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didn't take long for Conway to become unhinged...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here we go...Kellyanne Conway time!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@MeetThePress featuring the smaller marches across the country as well as the big ones. This is important.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Critically, these marches were featured on A1's and local evening news broadcasts across the nation. This was not j… https://t.co/dMKvgeTFjS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woke up inspired. Reading stories of smaller marches in towns all across America has the GOP as shook as the big ones.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This one really didn't age well https://t.co/En7SeaCc1K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fair, but not okay to lie out of RNC either. They do regularly but not okay and not productive. https://t.co/XjHdPElvke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is sick. Think of all the House Republicans who have turned themselves into little more than his lackey. https://t.co/aPblMoKbs0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would be Baldwin style hilarious if it wasn't so offensive what he did and where he did it. He can't wrap his head… https://t.co/lSAjAmp5TX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is shook https://t.co/2LiVLp810x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raj gets it right on the most important part of that rant--&gt; https://t.co/grTkgSyiYV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd say the biggest thing to come from that was a brazen threat at our free press. The lil guy was hilarious before… https://t.co/SR2Pzmx1lZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sean Spicer just threatened the free press in a major way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHAT IS SEAN SPICER DOING RIGHT NOW?!?! I'm sorry this is hilarious. He's losing it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hahahaha Sean Spicer really isn't up to this. What an utter embarrassment this "presser is". Calm down little guy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today followed a week of widespread backlash to House Republicans voting to repeal the ACA. Just getting started. https://t.co/c67lgB9Zmi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[House Republicans will pay a heavy political price. We've already seen widespread backlash in districts across the… https://t.co/IB9SHntg5l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is obviously terrible. We need to move forward and hold Trump &amp; his House Republican lackeys accountable (aka… https://t.co/gZc20oCaYT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This about sums up the small gathering people call a crowd for Trump--&gt; https://t.co/uoWsXFPpzY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An important list to read today--&gt; https://t.co/qFFIHumSU4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leading @HuffingtonPost today: BUSTED: CHAFFETZ ETHICS SMEAR EXPOSED https://t.co/tsbxOaEovA #utpol https://t.co/fusXdj0Hfl]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>