<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[46. Mike Nichols: American Masters (dir. Elaine May, 2016) #52FilmsByWomen https://t.co/nMDIyQrMRy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sia @ACLU Thank you! https://t.co/bpuPFoFyeC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Squeezegutalley @charloween @dolly_clackett I remember when that came out . . . how badly I wanted it to be good, and then . . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanHF and a huge influence on the ending of the production code.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join me, @robertjesimpson &amp; @JMCarlsten for book launch and Being There screening: 21Feb QFT Belfast #HalAshby https://t.co/ta6DqqyPRh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scifizoe was watching some old Buffy the other night-fair bit of walk and talk around Sunnydale High]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[why do they keep saying "honest"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[45) Stories We Tell (dir. Sarah Polley, 2012) #52FilmsByWomen https://t.co/YcLGhMFtLS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog 13) Because that’s all we’re talking about here - living in a world where we take care of each other.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog 12) might bring them something akin to the calm you feel knowing your world is secure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog 11) and maybe, just maybe, consider that supporting them - empathizing with them . . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog 10) that you give a thought to other folks, less off than you, or who need more than you, who get it less than you do . . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog 9) and your heart is Grinching out 4 times too big looking down at that smile, basking in the glow of your family love . . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog 8) And that when you’re holding your kid in your arms, now safe from harm . . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog 8) And that when you’re holding your kid in your arms, now safe from harm . . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog 7)I wish you’d think about the subsidies, the insurance breaks, the externalities that let you get the health care you get]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog 6) So, first, I’d like to say that I hope everything turns out all right for your kid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog 5) And I know that whatever kind of dick you might be on the surface, you’re probably hurting inside.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog 4) And I know how it is to have your child’s health in the hands of medical professionals who don’t keep you in the loop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog 3) So I’ve been shitting on the bile stuff, but I’m also a dad of a sickly kid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaron_m_hunter 4) And I know what it’s like to have your child’s health in the hands of med professionals who don’t keep you in the loop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3) So I’ve been shitting on the bile stuff, but I’m also a dad of a sickly kid. https://t.co/4KcGMlFxXV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog 2) But you decided to drop your bile all over twitter tonight while your kid was sick. And that’s all kinds of fucked up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog 1) Look, I don’t know you, and you don’t know me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog Aha! you're on about condoms, not birth control. You're one of those "but baby, I just can't feel it" kind of guys, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog Unsurprisingly, you also don't know how to count . . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog nope, don't change the subject, dillweed! You pay for what benefits you, screw the rest. That's the case here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog Suppose you also drive on "not public" roads, breath "not public" clean air, too. Jesus fuck, who actually had kids with you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattWalshBlog um, maybe the irony of you bitching about one medical situation while maligning another? How daft are you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conversely, I pity the life your kids will lead, you hateful knob! https://t.co/e7vJrXiTdC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zacheney did it involve Joe Biden? a cat? the freest little kid you've ever seen? that dos equis guy? irony? emptiness you can't describe?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melikhovo Oh, also, S5 of Lost is fantastic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@waxbanks @melikhovo Just beat me to it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melikhovo Buffy mixes serial and episodic, and there's fan disagreements over season rankings, but S5 is definitely one of its best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[43. Miss Representation (dir. Jennifer Siebel Newsom, 2011) #52FilmsByWomen https://t.co/IDFCl4Lg1r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Event reminder - next Monday in Dublin. All welcome, feel free to share! #booklaunch #halashby #christianmetz https://t.co/FdGYXviqUW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[40) Laggies (or Say When - dir. Lynn Shelton, 2014) #52FilmsByWomen https://t.co/qiHbSizaGw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarthaPShearer (there was a cool Hungarian version from about '02 called iwiw, but it never spread)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarthaPShearer Damn! I think I didn't even know what MySpace was then!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarthaPShearer wow, that's as old as old school gets! Study abroad year?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A few thoughts on how even well-meaning work can perpetuate Hollywood sexism: https://t.co/4t7PFZb0TJ #womeninfilm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelenExeter Thanks, Helen!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy to announce myself and Cormac Deane's launch of our new film books. 9Jan/7pm/Dublin. Please share!… https://t.co/W85VQAEPTz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[38) Grace of my Heart (dir. Allison Anders, 1996) #52FilmsByWomen https://t.co/LlmklyM9PJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@obrienspeak @BloomsburyBooks btw, not sure where you're based, but there will be a Dub book launch on 9Jan, Belfast 21Feb, discount copies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FilmNerdDave @obrienspeak @BloomsburyBooks @halashbymovie really looking forward to the film. Any release date set?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@obrienspeak @BloomsburyBooks Not sure it's been reviewed anywhere IN academia. Did come across this recently: https://t.co/JNR1gDpIMC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@obrienspeak @AmericanNewWave yes, thanks! Working on my abstract!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@obrienspeak @BloomsburyBooks Thanks for the nod! Hear you on the price - love to see it in more hands (future paperback?) - library copy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Second half of my rambly take on the auteur paradigm - why it's still with us whether we like it or not: https://t.co/g9HXYmi33Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Short thoughts on purchasing some Polly Platt DVDs: production design and collaboration https://t.co/QBWYmWk9LQ https://t.co/TYne4PO9y9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rcolintait yeah, it was fantastic!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Conntec Since we seem to conceptualize non-facts as facts in this modern world, couldn't you just say 341 is actually 500 and call it good?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pauseforthejet Yup - it's like, just pick up the phone, dude! There's a ton of us out here who'd seriously love to help you out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[35) Obvious Child (dir. Gillian Robespierre, 2014) #52FilmsByWomen https://t.co/yp2PR6fKyE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pauseforthejet Totally! And that's his ONE example from the '70s???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@enortee Me too! Now I've finally seen them all at least once!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Squeezegutalley Know what you mean . . . I guess you've seen other Holofcener films - all so rewatchable!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pauseforthejet "mediocre" is a pretty kind description of that piece . . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Squeezegutalley You're so right, it was lovely!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@enortee Was so good, really really enjoyed it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[34. Enough Said (dir. Nicole Holofcener, 2013) #52FilmsByWomen (got some catching up to do!) https://t.co/oB9rGsyUf7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need a distraction? Rambly post on how the auteur paradigm came to dominate film discourse? https://t.co/9png7hE8Oz #LoveIrishResearch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pauseforthejet so much fun to teach!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rcolintait NBC seems to be the best of a bad bunch . . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bittersweet Chicago: Cubs win (yay!); #scms17 says 'no' (nay). As baseball taught me long ago, there's always next year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dublinbermia will def keep you posted as details become clearer . . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dublinbermia Thanks! Some great work being done on women in contemp. Irish industry. Planning a spring seminar to tease out connections.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A few comments re why my research project on women in US film industry focuses on the '70s: https://t.co/QWHdYM4DKk #LoveIrishResearch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TXFMDublin --&gt; and a great bonding experience with my 5yr-old, Otis. Otis says to say he's so sad you're going, too! Best of luck y'all!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TXFMDublin so sorry you're leaving-just moved to Dub 2 yrs ago and txfm has been my go-to station from the start --&gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pauseforthejet so much ugh!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My essay on performance and authorship in #BuffyTheVampireSlayer S6, latest Journal of Film and Video (JSTOR):   https://t.co/Ny6gZTcgiu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pauseforthejet also, great Dylan song, so . . . Synergy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great read about a great filmmaker https://t.co/XmGpvBSYmk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for the RTs this week: @pauseforthejet @Squeezegutalley @mariaprama @zacheney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A few thoughts on auteurism and the new De Palma doc. https://t.co/uSoRzqE875]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've started a new blog for my IRC sponsored postdoc project, Women &amp; New Hollywood: https://t.co/5InSgUfU9v #LoveIrishResearch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlasgowsDA @kinowords Exactly . . . it's a scam, just like quantitative easing and student loans!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kinowords @GlasgowsDA and even that doesn't work! It's like that scene in Mad Max, when the water's released-most going home w/nada.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlasgowsDA Also, "quantitative easing" drives me nuts when so much is being cut. The nerve of them . . . "hmm, let's give it a fancy name!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlasgowsDA was hard to imagine disliking anybody more than I did Osborne, but this lot now . . . yeesh!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlasgowsDA sort of amazes me how blatant they're being about it, and how easily they seem to be getting away with it. Smug. Grim.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ohmeara Yes, reminds me of Northern Exposure in that way (without the fish-out-of-water, but with way more snark!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ohmeara I've just started my first time, abt 1/2way through S1, loving it even more than I'd thought I might.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rcolintait ha ha . . . I've been singing random bits of it out loud all week!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matt_boyd_smith @rcolintait yes! and plays so well and unexpectedly off every image, action, line of dialogue in the min. leading up to it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rcolintait Yes! 1st time I liked it but hard to see through all my cringing; teaching it this week opened my eyes to much greatness in it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matt_boyd_smith CT brings so much depth and pathos to what really could have been a 1D role.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Charlize Theron's facial expressions from a scene in Young Adult. Amazing performance with a spare bit of script. https://t.co/WEEoPOOgDH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NowWatching Young Adult - no matter how many times I see it, the naming ceremony brings on the mega-cringe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaron_m_hunter a bit interesting, then sad, then really, really gruesome . . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[31) Hot Girls Wanted (dir. Jill Bauer &amp; Ronna Gradus, 2015) #52FilmsByWomen https://t.co/pnZJCLIyiJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harsh incongruity of the twitter feed . . . https://t.co/1pyKPKyMno]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Started #GilmoreGirls for the first time last week. Loving it. Dialogue as great as promised, but Graham's delivery is killer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pauseforthejet some of it fried, I hope!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pauseforthejet ha, been there. At least in C/E europe, even the 'vegetarian' restaurants have meat! Hopefully you could compromise!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pauseforthejet 've met plenty who wholeheartedly believe if there's no meat, it's absolutely not dinner, can't be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chutry Ha! yeah, that was a few years early! A definite mess, might be interesting for the place/people involved-if you like an '80s vibe!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chutry Yes, so much talent. Sadly the leads bring it way down, and it's a tonal mess. Looks good, though (Deschanel's work is great).]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>