<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Stupid Affirmative Action douche https://t.co/xIohWrNX9x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Civilization. Only muslims creating havoc. We must destroy this ideology. https://t.co/kPjCiXtmvE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[California is lost. Dynamite the Andreas Fault https://t.co/gw1mbenyHC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes it is. Majority want to kill me https://t.co/yV256vFoSo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How ever did London elect this dipshit? He talks out both sides of his mouth. Fucking hypocrite.  He hates Britain.… https://t.co/FGWevQnDpi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck Maher. He is shallow but thinks he's deep. Narcissistic sob. https://t.co/gXVCX3IVtC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TouchMyTweets to me life is hard. But the courage to press on is what sustains me. I don't believe in heaven. So today is all I have. Peace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a start https://t.co/iY61xptK16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chris Hayes is a two timing b___t__d. https://t.co/cG6wfAmYJO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. Did they ask Hillbot why? https://t.co/Q2QfJwWayf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trevor Noah. How did he get any job in USA?  Simpleton with no skills. Junior high humor and intellect. My, my. Wan… https://t.co/BnlXI1C84S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There has to be truth. Muh feels don't cut it. So many have copped out from life. We must win. Truth must win or th… https://t.co/bTQ1iNJAbc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gooood chocolate. Yummy https://t.co/pr4OZptQB5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teacher, hmmm. Idiots. The Renaissance is dead. Revive the Renaissance and Latin/Greek tradition. Our Western herit… https://t.co/8ojeSuGqmb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But, yes, we do need a national standard for right-to-carry and national reciprocity.

@ThomasJefUnit99]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eliminate all of them. https://t.co/6WPmox5DII]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's retarded and doesn't know it. No one at CNN will tell her the truth. Ass Clown. https://t.co/0i8jPjNEBM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If people can threaten DJT then why can't we threaten to kill Soros? https://t.co/yHLVUHl91s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs. No fear of being violated. Imaginary https://t.co/mLZGHp62TQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally.  Bring it. #MAGA https://t.co/8RS78tchWl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marrow is a cretin in classical sense. How do idiots get a platform? Just fire her lying ass. #MAGA https://t.co/6ZyFM8wu4H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another retard who thinks they're an intellectual https://t.co/7FeUcmpvFF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheaper to deport than pay for their sorry ass no skill no brain selves https://t.co/DSJDLbaJcQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Send in the Legion https://t.co/rtztcdfVOZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fire them https://t.co/x6LErjwAxM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck BK. Cancel all subscriptions to Weekly Standard. Out if touch rag. https://t.co/i4XIWv1fbl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh yeah. Bunch of losers in cubicles https://t.co/XlGAIxBJTM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kill them before they kill us https://t.co/eR7kSy3mWz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's called English https://t.co/IwSv3Lw5sh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can have her https://t.co/gIHCUKiYty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck them. Buy an Audi https://t.co/CVBueifpD9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proves he doesn't know shit https://t.co/AygVeKAbQb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Speaking of trash. Leave the idiots behind and let's #MAGA toward an awesome regeneration of the American Spirit.… https://t.co/7Qqi33Iiam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agreed. He's right. Islam is not a religion.  A political, controlling, manipulative, violent, stone age cult https://t.co/qzgFVjmSDW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cuck Daily News. Spineless. Cruel to make light of murder https://t.co/gMH6DdCn4D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never had it and never will. #MAGA https://t.co/0mzrbVpkus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good riddance. Always choosing the most damaging course leads to a life of failed dreams. Join those moving on/forw… https://t.co/CIokL7MN2I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just send them back in 40 days. Saudi Arabia would be first https://t.co/7o2MY9vEO3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could give a crap that any follows me. I hate Twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[95-Year-Old WWII Veterans To Obama Is BLOWING UP The Internet: “I Can’t Figure Out What Country You’re The President Of”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worst place to live https://t.co/VYp17ZO4A4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Old and sleepy https://t.co/nmTY6b5OZ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 things to know about James Mattis, Trump’s defense secretary pick https://t.co/bzbxLvETTu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clinton: 'Fake News' Puts Lives at Risk https://t.co/bg9RJxyzvO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Nuclear Option: Trump Cures Insanity in American Politics - Breitbart https://t.co/6jrScpHBlD via @BreitbartNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Johnatsrs1949 his business's interests are congruent with our interests.If good for him then good for our economy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HoustonWelder totally agree. I love my friends even if we don't see eye to eye. We argue all the time and it makes us like brothers. #MAGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@syqau but why so cucked ? No machismo to keep aliens from destroying their country. No more Thor, Valhalla?  We want Vikings!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyday commonplace event for a Muslim. No big deal. Why the angst? Pfffftt https://t.co/0vCKY50qo9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She killed so many without a thought. So sad. So....
Weapons sales, Libya, etc. She is out of touch https://t.co/yaWw5SCuEL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Incompetent with no design https://t.co/dMU18scLUh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bet all those cucked Swedes..less than 5 inches. Oops. 12.5 cm https://t.co/haq41scuny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really? My god. Such insight. Who would've thought? Bunch of nincompoops. I say. Jolly,good https://t.co/enzYOyVKZt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump please why puzder? I don't expect much for my $3700 from you. I gave it freely. Don't let us down #MAGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cernovich @AAAauto willing2listento his side?  There is no reasonable argument.Any pedofile should be scared.We will hunt u down#PizzaGate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What? They already OWN us. We be property. So nice https://t.co/sr9TlUXBdq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So many imbeciles and simpletons on TV https://t.co/iZpW9ixJ6v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uhhhh??? He's an apologist for Islam?  Okie doke. If if if if if if if etc #TheDonald https://t.co/puPUTpKTip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG. That simplistic wearer of magic underwear is the village idiot. No clue. Like "Being There" gardener Peter Sel… https://t.co/64k9Yayrck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LouDobbs @SpecialKMB1969 @realDonaldTrump 
Oh yeah. Already doing myself. Only bought bolt cutters made USA. Lowe's didn't have em. #MAGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why so many wish to return to the stone age is mystifying. Left screaming about rights etc. These guys will make u… https://t.co/2sPep8lSAY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No Trump made Trump and made Bannon relevant. Breitbart had been somewhat fringe but rode coattails of DJT. All good https://t.co/Bcib3vAoA0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such a consistent boob. So predictable. Schlepping his shit about the country. So sad. Never really relevant. #MAGA https://t.co/4KagOEIWf5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isn't it about talent? The NBA is certainly about talent and not about quotas https://t.co/Un60aE8frZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hopefully DJT will rescind any idiotic measures. We love legal, American loving peoples. They come here because we… https://t.co/Q6UurcmeAf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No problem. He's irrelevant. An actor who was on show not that popular in his day. Kinda sad. Getting stuff off his… https://t.co/8W28mUIIHz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not so sure. My humble opinion, we make choices to hit rock bottom. Then cry "Help". Man trying to finagle out of t… https://t.co/CMrueR7L4x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ablebody4 humbled]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HRH Is fake and a shill. Why she had any credibility at any time is a mystery to me. https://t.co/gsMT3zziyz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That dipshit nerd/pussy in class who always made u cringe when raised his hand https://t.co/8EDijw4buj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barbarians no longer at the gate. We let them in. Why are we committing suicide? Sad. Mystifying. Bring more Greek… https://t.co/TjssuzeNAN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some Christians corrupted byPC.Over years some liberal, some conservative.Whole gamut.Wasting time on nuances.We al… https://t.co/e3WQynFdh0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_AltRight_Anew @genophilia_anew I am pro-American. Why some think loving my American heritage is anti-Semitic I'll never know #MAGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pamela_Moore13 @YahnelE and not 20 years later]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaGodfather907 she's an idiot pol.Why other idiots keep electing her bespeaks of the insanity of let's agenda in face of human nature #MAGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When a man is incompetent u can't fall back on racism. There are tendencies w/ cultures but any intelligent person… https://t.co/pQNmPlaM4L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We honor the men of PH. You, a cuck. Traitor to their sacrifice. Suck a lemon. DBag. #MAGA https://t.co/RulAXGuHmz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black Americans luvd JackieRobinson. I loved LarryBird. I'm the racist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer Scott Pruitt is completely in touch with the American people #MAGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's a man's man. We need men to be men. War is hell. Being dominated by an inferior culture is a more terrible fat… https://t.co/bjSBpowNzB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No humor? GB is lost. Punch was famous. So sad. Legacy extinguished. Take back your culture the world envied. They… https://t.co/j4iPj2zyFS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Show no mercy. Annihilate them all. https://t.co/8bayFAeWQ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wtf? Hopefully only Gray and butternut crayons https://t.co/t0MHTBFgLj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hopefully Russia will poloniumize him! #Putin https://t.co/wIplIIXxN4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TYranny of the majority. Only not so long ago minorities defended this concept. So sad. #MAGA https://t.co/9doIYILTLG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be a Brit and be Great. #MAGBA https://t.co/46oQmZWcW5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So now it's an issue? Shithead. Go Hahvahd https://t.co/JxrJLu8v6Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally out of touch #MAGA https://t.co/aBGMfrZBGF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's new https://t.co/H82AJ1axBT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never Come Down [PRESIDENTIAL REMASTER] https://t.co/ZQua8aQwDo I enjoy the tune with Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't worry. No common ground. Just a signal of respect even if not deserved. It will influence the idiot left. https://t.co/gAjyUhLyoD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stein is who we all know takes advantage of American Freedom. She exploits it for own advantage. Not like true Amer… https://t.co/cu61eksUyQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sanctuary for crime/ murder.We should invade to protect those who deserve peace/safety as US citizens.No American s… https://t.co/d3gGHJRvII]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@manny_ottawa @johanvanwyk999 omg. Is he real? What a vacuous human being. He seems so retarded in intellect and reality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@littlrdragon @vivelafra @DrJillStein @BernieSanders @TheGreenParty typical hypocrites, abandon principles for $.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NonnaLovesMe @trump2016fan @SpeakerRyan I don't get PR.He seems duplicitous and slimy.Why does WI keep electing him? He's so beta andweenie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Withered old c_nt. https://t.co/VOBLHsAZOF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidJo52951945 @TheSun GDamned pols giving away their peoples £. Make UK great again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sanders. Pseudointellectual. Moron. Agenda is hate on whitey. https://t.co/Q7UgP6uN0g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phil200269 @karenmcallier Go DJT. Fuck the Mainland Chinese. Nefarious two faced bastards]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>