<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomwfreeman nothing remarkable about it with the budget they have! Hearts just signed 9 new players majority never played in Scotland b4!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomwfreeman it should not matter what season back it is that's a pathetic excuse recruitment and tactics have been an absolute shambles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomwfreeman average Rangers player earns almost 400k a year the average hearts player earns 80k nothing ridiculous about the expectation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@86christie better than holt, graham, keats and arguably Cummings maybe not needed for league but perhaps there thinking of cup?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johncrossmirror @domfifield @potty_9 this guy rates ivanovic a bit more highly than Yursel lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AgentScotland hates being pulled up on any his 'facts' 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grahamruthven lol @KThomsonAcademy aswell?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grahamruthven McDonald's never a red games ruined if that's a def red]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@potty_9 am shite at both tae]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@potty_9 mental! Snookers Nae easy game either]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@potty_9 was a cupl o yr ago mind we wondered why he ws continually overlooked for awards whether it's all time greats or sports personality]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@potty_9 see Ronnie O'Sullivan still winning major tournaments at 41 year old]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrewanmurray who cares]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrjakehumphrey made a right Noel hunt of yourself with gerrard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love corbyn! If only labour was one labour and not have dugdale leader in Scotland https://t.co/VfNjRhKR2P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CELTICGLASGOW_7 @ScottGShore @StaceyDevlinxxx well if that's u attempting to take the pish that's even worse 😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CELTICGLASGOW_7 @ScottGShore @StaceyDevlinxxx ooffttt banter fucking horrendous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CELTICGLASGOW_7 @ScottGShore @StaceyDevlinxxx he's a die hard hibs fan he bought shares in the club and is mates wi mickey weir]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CELTICGLASGOW_7 @ScottGShore @StaceyDevlinxxx he had a Celtic top in his hands and the point is??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_Tman10 @HibsNews1875 @Brez01 his agent all but confirmed that was his last game for hibs his goal v Falkirk was a pivotal moment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hucks6dh6 @n_lumos the English league is massively overrated and full of foreigners it's total toys out the pram stuff now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hucks6dh6 @barryhillis the English game hs bn riddled with greed for the pst decade it's hugely overrated also now the toys r out the pram]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@guardian he said this weeks if not months ago can u not print something recent at least 😫]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@potty_9 aye if it's no better than what's there then what's the point eh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@potty_9 can win u a cup though mate without stokes or Henderson last season hibs would have never won that final]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kenny_Millar same! Seen some highlights of guard and a run of games seemed to have done him the world of good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kenny_Millar school playground stuff! What's the bets he's not eligible to play v sporting in this deal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kenny_Millar might be short deal Kenny there next game is versus Sporting!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@74frankfurt good photo but it is 100 percent at ravenscraig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@74frankfurt my da said it's not bilsto glen they were picketing the steelworks at ravenscraig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WeeRascal2 that's ma old man in the Tammy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeebBrown @74frankfurt elate has to be different! Nowt changed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No every day ur old man pops up in a photo when ur scrolling through twitter haha! Nice Tammy da 😂 https://t.co/n2YwGn9LCx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@74frankfurt where did you get the photo from bilston glen do u have anymore?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeebBrown @74frankfurt hahaha quality and the hat haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@74frankfurt @JeebBrown hahaha that's ma dad in the Tammy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grahamruthven watch it every week! Can't beat a Jeff Saturday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andy Murray might not go on to win this but saving 3 championship points then winning the set takes some mindset he is an absolute machine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WingsScotland more referring to workload of staff etc I work days and nights the pressure on most departments is unreal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WingsScotland why do we always have to accept 'operations will be cancelled' and compare to elsewhere can't we strive for better? And I was]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WingsScotland I'm an snp supporter and also work in the NHS in Scotland and can't see much wrong with what's said in this article]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boyle is the most frustrating player in that hibs team! If only he had an end product! Time and again touch gets away fi him or loses ball!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pureraygin @Euan23 @BBCTomEnglish @BBCSport Hahahaha shadow? When did u last beat us? Who is the Scottish cup holders?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bbclaurak any public apology about ur treatment of corbyn?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeartsThough a pathetic wee stadium that holds 16500 😂😂😂 hibs have had the biggest crowds in edinburgh 3 years running FACT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fucking Hate MVG no giving a fuck how good he is he's a prick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@potty_9 can't stand him mate what's the shouting and fist pumping after every good throw all about]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm no even playing and MVGs celebrations after every decent throw he has gets right on my fukn tits!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrewanmurray and if Scott brown had a two footed lunge it would be a harmless dig also aye?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McIverTheMark so have a wee think before u say nothing is the managers fault the manager as he 'claims' picks the team himself!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McIverTheMark zidane should take flak for that! Cathro playd smith with rherras on the bench ultimately this decision as u say cost 2 goals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McIverTheMark aw come on don't be so thick! Would zidane play a rookie and leave an experienced left back on the bench? If so then yes...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McIverTheMark hahaha whys that? Explain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McIverTheMark haha only one who's stupid here if u can't get the logic of the manager picking the team that fails then U don't have a clue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McIverTheMark who picked Liam smith to start??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McIverTheMark course he does team blew a two goal lead against a shite Dundee side]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_Tman10 @bmann04 thought I read he had £25mil release clause?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nickybhoy1888 I've no heard the song mate but don't think so think it's the fact a rangers player song could beat the to Xmas no. 1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nickybhoy1888 top of I tunes chart but hundreds of little mix fans are gon mental about it lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nickybhoy1888 the green brigade campaigned to get some song to no.1 so Huns countered it wi a joey garner song and it's shot off and is...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrewanmurray @McGregorDerek everything has been going great on the pitch big tests to come when things not going so sweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@86christie sites are horrible places to work especially the amount of fannies with bad attitudes u come across]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Johncockerell9 @Jasoncummings35 @garyoliver7 we're u one of the thousands of fans booing at final whistle today John?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still goals change games hibs more than capable of going in at HT one up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hibs have been poor first half hour Morton probably should be winning! Yet to see shinnie do much in a hibs shirt and Cummings should be on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MCATEER4 @guardian what a crock of shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pistol147 coming across as a total knobend on twitter today it's almost as if he wants to be controversial deliberately]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@potty_9 what a prick eh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has CR7 been better than Messi? Has Messi been better than CR7? It's a question that has divided opinion for almost a decade no dif this yr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@potty_9 psg no great shakes mate expect both to go through comfortably]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_Tman10 @LMairzo batters a bit extreme tam city failed to batter them twice recently despite the millions of pounds playing squad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Roy1Batty @NickKayFEN just need to look attthe guys timeline to see how much pish he tweets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[James tavernier is no bad going forward but is easily one of the worst full backs defensively in Scotland. Woeful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrewanmurray @Johncockerell9 jobs for the boys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrewanmurray @The_Tman10 anyone who knows the man within football or played under him knows it has plenty substance!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garyshearer1  @Spanner_Rankine @Stenbizz that popular Barca teams must park the bus myth busted again https://t.co/yZG1Imz8Uv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Young male raf man in Suffolk still missing and French male student in Edin also still missing said it b4 those disappearances cd be linked!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We don't know how lucky we are that we have Andy Murray as one of our own the guy is phenomenal and an absolute animal physically]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gerrymcculloch1 come on he's a bit part player just now with tremendous potential but potential is all it is at the moment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@psmythe72 @Mid_Advertiser in the meantime snp msp Colin Beattie brings motions about toblerones to Parliament]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reckon sfa r penny pinching not sacking strachan or his team predict Scotland rally finish 2nd in there group but don't get a play off spot!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@uartlach totally ashamed to have Colin Beattie represent Midlothian after that embarrassing toblerone motion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pietros1 trust me a man in your walk of life knows nothing about the real life struggles of the underprivileged]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Higginbotham05 @1_royle @MCATEER4 that's enough to turn u off football for good to many know it alls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pietros1 @afneil @ONS many have chosen many don't have a choice! A company director, stock trader, tory knows nothing of the real world]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pietros1 @afneil @ONS so 3 percent of how many million? Com on then smart arse how many people is that in a round figure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnAshtone @Megashelley @afneil 0 hrs contract may suit some but not majority someone can hav 0 work for weeks but b classed as 'employed']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If this was ronaldo he would be getting abuse left right and centre https://t.co/mgh4kmpxqL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@afneil and how many zero hour contracts? Absolute sham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@potty_9 shows u how players mature he comes across really well plenty experience and hasn't just jumped into top level management]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@potty_9 @BBCSportScot football was the boozegate and fingers up to media incident bet he would love to make amends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@potty_9 @BBCSportScot I'd actually like him to make a good career in management and manage scotland one day he said his biggest regret in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robertthomson55 @FitbaHacks absolute pish county have been bankrolled for years easily in that top 6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Massive if but IF MESSI was to leave Barca for somewhere else and be successful it would be wonderful for the claim he's the best ever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missing military man down south still not found missing French student in Edinburgh still not found both similar age! Serial killer about?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Record_Sport @The_Tman10 is it bumper or on the cheap?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somecunt somewhere should be freezing messi's mums ovaries and his dads sperm now! Once he's gon we're likely never to see the likes again!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PathheadAmateu9 @Darren1979 @Anthonywalker81 cranks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some folk wnt appreciate what scotland has in Andy Murray until he's retired greatest sportsman we've ever produced consistently world class]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HibsOfficial #hibeefamily https://t.co/fGfwAKL80x]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>