<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Single #Garage in #Leichhardt, very close to the Light Rail Station. https://t.co/5KQdCV2YgK #Sydney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am a man of many ideas and very little time for them. Maybe working less will give me the chance to fulfill some of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Voter's Family Deported https://t.co/gRgfQ1UUBl #TrumpTrain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@AnaKasparian it is not helpful to criticize third party voters. Democrats did not appeal to enough people. https://t.co/GU9af8TGdP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zlatford this is not #auspol or #maga]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If this is true, the US gov is implicitly strengthening #WhiteSupremacists https://t.co/Q8uInoxhHx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WinstonsWrath @cjcoop2 true. It is important to separate the religion from its followers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cjcoop2 substitute a few words and you can make a similar case of US invasions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cjcoop2 @TEN_GOP sure, but so is freedom of religion and civil disobedience. I hope we can agree on that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TEN_GOP maybe, or also the reason Trump will loose. But I am hopeful the 2018 elections will reduce his power]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jlizza1 @TEN_GOP you cannot do that Ju. A lot of them are your fellow citizens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Pamela_Moore13 the US has a history of civil disobedience, so this is quite 'American']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Pamela_Moore13 do you mean this ban? https://t.co/010kLMZ125]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope other #Muslims, #immigrants and sympathizers join and close their stores in solidarity https://t.co/YzndMdNRY4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like this, my kind of protest is one that will immediately show effects. #BodegaStrike https://t.co/YzndMdNRY4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has anyone experienced a lack of help from @fairwork_gov_au? #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@NatJamesFWO is there a way we can rectify this? We checked @fairwork_gov_au rules for internships and they were not being followed #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@NatJamesFWO @fairwork_gov_au said she accepted the unpaid internship, even when she explained it was not valid and she was in fact working]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@NatJamesFWO my partner asked for help because she was in a sham internship, but @fairwork_gov_au did not help. #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@strahlen read the article, good at making me think. What do you think are effective ways to bridge that divide?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coooeeeeeimback look, it ended up hurting more https://t.co/PHttwy8P2W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@RealJeremyNolt don't generalize on the whole Left, we disagree constantly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonWolberg for the sake of fairness, what was the original topic? I will be happy to check it as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hi @JonWolberg, yeah, sometimes @SydneyAtheist gets like this when you are making sense with your argument.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@FoxNews Forced To Apologize And Delete Tweet. #Canada FTW https://t.co/xfrymhis9E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@flyingmonkeyair Nigel, the problem is that those generations lived and died to protect the dysfunctional electoral system the US has.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For picking fruit/vegetables, or pruning, you should be paid at least $22.13 an hour as casual. #Australia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is serious and legitimate concerns. If they are not addressed #NewZealand risks being tempted to swing to righ… https://t.co/c8WfsWIGBk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[60% did not report the crime to the police, saying they felt it was not interested in rural crime. https://t.co/Ft9nNkSC8n #NewZealand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewfaith not at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@andrewfaith in Argentina it is impossible to renounce it. You are Argentinian for life, including by naturalization.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is so much vile in David Archibald words. Sexist, ignorant, elitist. Please do not elect this person. #auspol https://t.co/ly7PL5jxbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IamCatyI no need to insult me. I can see you just want to assign imagined blame on an innocuous act. You are not worth my time anymore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I agree, and I lean left. #auspol should be for Australia's policies https://t.co/rF1x1pdHug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@WilliamFosterAU you are being unfair. I support a watchdog, but it should check any fake news. #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@IamCatyI there is no relation to what are you saying, it was a cover because it was news. Like this https://t.co/ZhewS2p4fF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@realDonaldTrump not today motherf*cker https://t.co/6nOMJI0sVo #TrumpTrain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@coooeeeeeimback I am not concerned about my own self interests, since I am not affected by the ban, but I can empathize with others]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coooeeeeeimback 2) the order can be used to create resentment and breed more violence, which might endanger US more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coooeeeeeimback 1) not all from those countries are evil, and evil comes from other parts, including the US. The order does not protect you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coooeeeeeimback I see we are not going to agree, which is ok. However, consider the following:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am very glad people cared. https://t.co/JmhtHvyoKB #auspol https://t.co/a8RtfIFQmt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am very glad people cared. https://t.co/vFUxguxkTP #auspol https://t.co/a8RtfIFQmt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coooeeeeeimback there is no world liberal dictatorship, but if you have the evidence I am interested.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coooeeeeeimback I am not a troll, I am a concerned human. You don't have to listen to me if you don't want though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coooeeeeeimback you are talking about a dictator, not a president. We will see if congress and the courts validate what the president wants]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gov_Girl76 agree with Congress and SCOTUS speed, but remember Congress can override a veto.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gov_Girl76 to be complete, Congress can also overturn an EO.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ @Gov_Girl76 but her actions seems not to be against rules, thought she can be removed, true.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/ @Gov_Girl76 ok, I understand. Seems your issue is with the AG acting as a check when she should not be doing that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gov_Girl76 and to repeat my question, isn't it part of the US a system of check and balances?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gov_Girl76 the EO has actually been partially halted by courts. Why do you think she is not upholding US laws?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheCoffeeQueen2 why do you think Tillerson is not part of the swamp?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Gov_Girl76 the AG is supposed to folliw the law, not just follow the president blindly. Do you support a check on Trump?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems #trump supporters voted for a very hypocritical person. I hope we can bridge the differences and work for com… https://t.co/nxCa5NjciW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vic schoolboy 'gutted' over US visa ban https://t.co/CPIgCWy5w0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hi @littlecaesars, your ordering in #Australia is very confusing, the online deal does not work. I am going with another pizza place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Your challenge is to prove that you belong in the same tribe as them" https://t.co/SdNhYJzMuC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Québec mosque shooting: five reportedly killed in gun attack https://t.co/kkyAPXU49H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Standing up for what’s right https://t.co/WQ2pWBM06G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@georgiedent @deemadigan lets hope she can be helpful in closing offshore detention centres and bringing refugees into #Australia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am glad I avoid @Apple @Microsoft and @facebook. And so should you. https://t.co/QxOfFuZacA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With a green card? That means she is a resident, how can they turn her back? https://t.co/w8OyZynuXf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#boycotttrump and do not give money to the US gov https://t.co/I4zoMTppDj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@amazon rejected me for Mechanical Turk without a reason. You risk losing a customer. #Amazon #mechanicalturk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not surprising, but a constant issue that affects immigrants and youth. #auspol https://t.co/qYWA49CTjH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We #Programmers are in a unique position to whistleblow on unethical and illegal things we’ve been asked to do https://t.co/royBmWXp1B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ But, if the far right see that people are prepared to defend themselves, in many cases they back off. #auspol https://t.co/X82mGlv4Zr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/ The far right have shown that they are ready to use violence against those who they see as vulnerable. #auspol https://t.co/X82mGlv4Zr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope the alt-right movement in #Australia gets more under scrutiny to reveal its even more hideous side. #auspol https://t.co/YTPoX0o2hq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pakistani mom promised her daughter a wedding reception. Instead, she burned her alive. https://t.co/NBOJve9MG8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why I Only Work Remotely https://t.co/VS1MMx1f99]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True, but then #Australia should resettle the refugees in Australia. #auspol https://t.co/g3Nfr2kWvh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the point where we should start planning for a #Boycott and Divestment from most of the US, except perhaps… https://t.co/78k5OzQT64]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good example, the world needs to look for leadership to other countries now that the US is entering a worrying era.… https://t.co/m0YYypthCA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@PeterDutton_MP please help this woman. Forget politics and use your humanity. #auspol https://t.co/hmXzj3ghCa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Snowden I hope we can fight this with other non cabled communications systems, like satellite internet, FireChat or similar, etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kudos to @GoCatchApp support, I left my backpack in a ride and they help me contact the driver and recover it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ That is the #Australia we should all have. https://t.co/BspeXpeXGM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/ Today I left my backpack in a @GoCatch, and the driver returned it. He is a Muslim who came as a refugee. #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ @leftrenewal if multiple meetings are held, livestreaming is a great tool #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/ @leftrenewal to solve the issue of time and place for meetings, perhaps use a communication platform to coordinate #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@leftrenewal aims to be a faction that emphasizes the outside party movements and orgs for change #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Greens emphasize nonheirarchy and decentralization @leftrenewal #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Criminalising flag burning is very bad. It takes nationalism down a dangerous road. #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@leftrenewal is true that some right wing politicians use 'others' as scapegoats, but what about the voters who believe that? #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @leftrenewal makes the case that just having Green MP's does not mean Greens' policies will happen #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @leftrenewal wants to foster social change from the bottom up #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems like @leftrenewal wants to emulate the @SenSanders movement #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People look to the left as a way to righting inequality @leftrenewal #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The idea of no single federal leader is interesting. @leftrenewal #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learning some history of Greens at  @leftrenewal meeting #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It seems @leftrenewal membership is only open to Greens. Perhap a broader coalition could be better #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ If you fought for AU, you also fought for the right of people in AU to have opposing opinions # auspol https://t.co/X0aCii7tpG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/ Though not fatal, this is another case of nationalist violence or threat of violence. #auspol @SydneyAtheist https://t.co/X0aCii7tpG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@adammichaelwood @codinghorror the world is not ASCII, it is Unicode. My cv is andrés-proaño-cv.pdf and not andres-proano-cv.pdf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JeremyTravers @stephanieando I would rather use @GoCatchApp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@duncanbourne where did you read/heard it was not ok for unions to support labor? Or is it illegal somehow? #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/ @AFPmedia so I then use an alternative spelling, and mark it is not correctly spelled. Again, I cannot continue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/ @AFPmedia trying to get a police check, but your system will not accept the spelling o name.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>