<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The irony.
https://t.co/N1nve6Mqj8
https://t.co/GqzgTeLoZS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2017 Story of Stuff Community Survey https://t.co/z76LkXnD2o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nucci_erika @joceynuptse @JustinTrudeau @liberal_party This was a no-brainer. Search for best practices, adopt and move on to next policy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Policy fail. Shame, @JustinTrudeau https://t.co/jrLhSG6lxm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@karensmyidol @_Allyria My 3yr-old great niece recently had an ear infection. Screaming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We gave you hummus. Have some respect." https://t.co/gs3sWsQw7S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Team_Barrowman You in that, too?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Early Modern English &amp; the Mob? Whoa Thanks, @PaulBudra (The Province actually printed something worth reading for… https://t.co/ClzoE4XWCn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nils Bohlin, a hero. https://t.co/plXFORuwTi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aye, I do love what my eyes can read! https://t.co/LIQslpy9ud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spod1000 @Jenkins100Rose @WomackChris @the_dooIio Nice, but can we wait until after S10E12 for this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phil500 @Jenkins100Rose That gives planking a whole new meaning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@karensmyidol The detail in Big Ben is amazing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't believe this, then BITE ME! #NotAWhovian https://t.co/OM46c754ed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bbcdoctorwho @WarwickADavis HBD, Porridge!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch Kilauea Volcano spew lava into the ocean
https://t.co/MnjpEdesEN Blood of the Earth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CosmicWhoNerd With you in spirit from the other side of the Pond.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_27th_Doctor Gotta find that story.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter Capaldi Wants a Story Where the Doctor Wakes Up to Find Himself Starring in Doctor Who https://t.co/JaOyO7gwvw via @io9 Let's do this!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can run from this, JT, but you can't hide. https://t.co/SAeigR30Jm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, that's precious! https://t.co/AnatNLiZXw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Statement by Ed Broadbent on Liberals' Abandonment of Electoral Reform Commitment https://t.co/grFGvoSAB4
Policy fail!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is why Peter Capaldi will always be The Doctor to me. https://t.co/dRjk3jYAB5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@0hMySt4rs 8pm? No bloody wonder! The show is in the wrong time slot. At least where I live it runs at 6pm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Team_Barrowman Welcome back!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HuffingtonPost That's because she looks like a dalek. No, sorry, that's an insult to daleks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man Who is the living embodiment of dreams come true. https://t.co/2oAsRfcj8Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pinkwaldd Can you say "Torchwood?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Slfriend79 @uncy14b Me neither. There's always the chance of a multi-Doctor ep in the future, but this is just 2 soon considering the world]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abimaclean @CuriousCatMe Too early for this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SAVETHEDWE @GeorgeBaker26 In how many hours? We're not in the same time zone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jk_rowling Ya burned that fool, JK!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Slfriend79 Me, too. 😩]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhovianLeap Too early for this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@claraozwins @FrostWells Me, too long]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whouffaldi I'm down with this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whouffaldi Also The General in Hell Bent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Taylor_Bookout I'm sure he will. I'm pretty sure, in fact, he'll do more bc he'll have more time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@twelvegoogles Not the only way. There could always be another echo story. Bookends, y'know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrostWells That'll depend on Victoria filming. The S10 Xmas ep will probably start filming in summer, with Victoria about mid-way through?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@avonlealetters That happened to me when Jenna announced she was leaving.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CosmicWhoNerd @Lanaismyperson WE SHOULD BE HAPPY
WE SHOULD BE HAPPY
WE SHOULD BE HAPPY
WE SHOULD BE HAPPY
WE SHOULD BE HAPPY
BUT... 😩😩😩😩😩😩😩]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorF0rever You know this moment will eventually come, but I'm just not ready for it. I wanted one more season with PDC/12.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@0hMySt4rs In the back of you know this days always coming - like  the Veil in Heaven Sent - but it still hurts. I wanted one more year. 😩]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dutiesofcare Bookmarking this for later.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jenna_Stans 😄 Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@doctoorwho Well, he is a Time Lord]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And out of nowhere comes this... https://t.co/l7O7gSlwK0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jenna_Stans I have. She's awesome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jenna_Stans 3000? That all?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amjoyshow @Slfriend79 @csdickey 'Think' he's lost his mind? We're way past that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Slfriend79 @YouTube Strange. I can watch this now without wiping my eyes. Don't know if I should feel good about that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheresaMayPM You are not Churchill. https://t.co/QHNSjZA5Ty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They know. They remember. #muslimban #internment #neveragain https://t.co/Hm8cCXfJKs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sadly, this is how a lot evangelicals see the world. 'Pro-life' they are not. https://t.co/3veuUQysaB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brinatello @time_soulmates Who would even question this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will they step up to the plate? https://t.co/GuqZ0ozCIk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pinkwaldd You sound like my niece. She's an RN.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And don't forget the bar of soap in your bathtub you thought you put away. https://t.co/Dphqc2lMlA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@karengillan Of focking course not! (me, in Malcolm Tucker voice)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JustinTrudeau I support this, but do not forget our long-oppressed First Nations while we open our doors to the oppressed from elsewhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pinkwaldd Join the crowd.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome back to the 1930s https://t.co/Kz847Atsro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jenna_Stans Didn't get a ticket in time - each local cinema running TDOTD sold out. Watched at my sister's - she got me into Who long ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo https://t.co/U935fL1Ukm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AltBadlandsNPS @YouTube "...refuse to keep our mouths shut."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@usgov France would like the Statue of Liberty back. You've renegged on your part of the deal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrWhoWorldwide @Jenkins100Rose Everyone raise your sonics in honour of Sir John]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So uh, Governor, for what price did you sell your soul? https://t.co/R6OdtqJvAA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have we gone mad? https://t.co/AjeYfXJWOW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My sonic raised in your honour, Sir John.
@WithJohnHurt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cbcian John Hurt also recently played the War Doctor in @bbcdoctorwho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously, translink, WTF? "The new 95 B-Line no longer stops here." Have you ever heard of… https://t.co/cJHywqqPfO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone please say it isn't true. https://t.co/t1XLGmuovW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This film could've been made last year! https://t.co/8J6Ihu5Im5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBCStephenQuinn @YouTube I needed that after this sh#*e of a week!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why @Carole_King is just now re-releasing a song she first wrote in 1982 https://t.co/kQKn4JYrOT via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonRiley7 @Slate And learn psychometrics. The other side used it against you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read. This. Article. https://t.co/1wqTgcxioD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And everywhere else! https://t.co/RcTtRK7seW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘What a City Is For’: How We Can Find Our Way Home  via @TheTyee https://t.co/K4BxjKDBA8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/aIl4h3SErB
Growth is a disease.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Petition: @JustinTrudeau Welcome those fleeing from deportation under Trump into Canada.  https://t.co/C0OKe2iiHo via @leadnowca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stingray cell phone surveillance is irresponsible, and invades our privacy. It’s time to #stopstingrays https://t.co/QtplccoO36]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dinasteria @madeleine Okay, so we agree on something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dinasteria @madeleine Then you'll agree the deaths of hundreds of 1000s of Iraqi and Afghan civilians in the last 15yrs was equally wrong?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jenna_Stans Premonition, then. Remembering forward?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jenna_Stans Theory, probably wrong, but: the red beanie as tribute to Mary Tyler Moore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lzbthmlnck @JonRiley7 I think we're past kool-aid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@atruedrwhofan Phone books are cool. Criss-cross directories are awesome!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reflecting current events, Doctor? https://t.co/vMdOhRCAAT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If anyone wants to really understand the Canadian oil pipeline debate in one succinct article, here it is. https://t.co/D43MdfgzzU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AstroKatie He's copying CDN policy under Harper.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dinasteria @madeleine 1 was strategy by one state to change another's foreign policy. The other: unapologetic, premeditated mass murder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Amazing_images @Thelnteresting Doctor Who SFX in the 60's.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Amazing_images @Thelnteresting Look! It's a catalope!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating. And kinda depressing. https://t.co/x8nCnBnIDp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dinasteria @madeleine Maybe because she hasn't forgotten. It's called learning from one's mistakes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Support the service that supports you. https://t.co/e6U6CgUvoI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could watch and listen to this all night. Probably will. 'night. https://t.co/0Mg2jFpB5r]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>