<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Flashback 2006: Senators Clinton &amp; Obama Vote For Secure Fence Act, Bush Signs Bill https://t.co/VnjOuHDYOt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AustLiberty @PaulineHansonOz It is still incompatible with our way of life regardless of what damn label is put on it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noAgendaShop @THErealDVORAK Things that make you go …yum!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulineHansonOz The reason for Saudis not being included, is money, money ,money. Afghan same deal - money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulineHansonOz The media in Aus is about as trust worthy as the US media unfortunately]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@THErealDVORAK Alternative facts………okay!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BasimaFaysal @KirralieS @lsarsour @MariamVeiszadeh Have a close look at the picture. It’s wrong at so many levels]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KirralieS What could possibly go wrong!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@THErealDVORAK It must be global warming!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AMDWaters I believe its called Political Correctness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OMGTheMess @KirralieS @Summersalt_55 And the main stream media proliferates the problem with BS to scare the sheeple]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewhorowitz What about NY Post as well??? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KirralieS @smh As opposed to.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NoAgendaNation OMG, this can't be right. Somebody do something. Lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cadoges Isn't the web wonderful. Have a great New Year mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adamcurry Just want to wish you ,Tina and JCD all the best for the New Year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@THErealDVORAK Just want to to wish you and Adam all the best for the New Year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning! British Airways e-ticket receipt malware arriving in an inbox near you http://t.co/thTvvcD2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leolaporte Good to see you having a day off. tWiT went well. Enjoyed John C and the crew.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@stephenfry: Sneak preview of the iphone10 … http://t.co/Ih3a9Nz6” Note to self, get bigger pockets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryan @veronica My best wishes are with you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephenfry It seems that we in Australia are not immune from this nonsense, Boystown is under investigation going back decades]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@io9 Different body every day? Methinks confusion in the bathroom ......to sit or stand???? :-)))]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnCleese suggestions? Why yes, a title and first line. But that's probably not what you meant :))]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryan an I what?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just looked at Google search home page. Very cool Star Trek theme.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SGgrc 
Thought this was interesting
http://t.co/uGurajqd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting article @grc  http://t.co/pwkgRy50]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to look at this http://t.co/YO8lBvv6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the world is so concerned about human rights in #Libya why don't the also look at Zimbabwe? Just curious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Factual info on Japanese Nuclear  Power Stations  http://bit.ly/eOjapE Updated daily.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@efa_oz @ashermoses thanks for the great article]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CDCemergency Your link in this tweet is broken.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rank alarmist who utterly discredits the UN Intergovernmental Panel on Climate Change http://bit.ly/gyEkjs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Highly recommended http://bit.ly/gV5NpV via @TweetSmarter Install HTTPS Everywhere to keep your Twitter & Facebook secure everywhere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it a lie or the truth. One has to ask. From @JuliaGillard http://bit.ly/f4omGe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The things that come to those that wait may be the things left by those who got there first.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My goal in life is to be as good of a person as my dog already thinks I am.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If at first you don't succeed, skydiving is not for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the moment I picked the book up until I laid it down I was convulsed with laughter. Some day I intend reading it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some days you're the pigeon; some days you're the statue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Light travels faster than sound. This is why some people appear bright until you hear them speak.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give a man a fish and he will eat for a day.
Teach a man to fish and he will sit in a boat all day drinking beer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Britain's service station rip-off - Fuel prices  http://bit.ly/hzrAIv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not walk beside me either. Just pretty much leave me the hell alone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not walk behind me, for I may not lead. Do not walk ahead of me, for I may not follow........  cont...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The journey of a thousand miles begins with a broken fan belt and leaky tire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It may be that your sole purpose in life is simply to serve as a warning to others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone has a photographic memory. Some don't have film.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WTF...  http://australian-politics.blogspot.com/ Little kids bombed out with drugs to save work for their government "carers" via @jonjayray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vexnews With google, try the HTTPS version for greater security.
Thanks for the article.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NonRadical Good article, thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NonRadical That's a bit of a worry right there!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrianDunning I'll have some of that lol :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FBI: Muslim Brotherhood supports terrorism http://bit.ly/evHgkQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beware the Muslim Brotherhood http://bit.ly/g5zQ67]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Is the Muslim Brotherhood, and Will It Take Over Egypt? http://bit.ly/eCIEVl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[National ID Card Scheme Bites The Dust http://bit.ly/esfktL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Dozen Bad Ideas for the 21st Century http://bit.ly/fV1UZD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@2GBAndrewMoore It may help to identify the idiots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GibsonResearch And on it goes. iPhone passwords succumb to researchers' attack http://cnet.co/i6tTex via @crave]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vexnews Hey it's a dog show for horses. The Arabs have one for camels too don't they?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jsnell 17C in Sydney Australia. Yesterday it was over 40C. And it's summer!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@canadafreepress I wish that more politicians would wake up to this unacceptable problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aus_media Good article]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LastPass Congratulations on 1million. Pity I don't use Facebook :-(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonjayray Another good article]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonjayray Good article.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NonRadical @ElyssaD I don't have a Facebook account,but if I did, would be concerned.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TweetSmarter Unfortunately this is business as usual for China. Constant censorship.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TweetSmarter 
Good stuff. Expert = a drip under pressure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PajamasMedia Good article]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hotdogsladies Are you sure about that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@calvetica Sure, why not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TweetSmarter Any privacy issues with this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IntelliProtect I think Noscript & Adblocker Plus block tracking without any fuss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TweetSmarter Guilty as charged]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has anyone noticed that "warmists" resort to personal attacks when they feel overwhelmed by reality?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@news_com_au  Yup, the warm beer does that to ya ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like another bot ( @TruthENess )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wattsupwiththat Hang in there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Twitter Worm Exploits Google’s URL Shortener http://on.mash.to/fAuHBn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonys3kur3 Good to know,spammers have holidays :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yahoo!7 acquires online voucher website. http://yhoo.it/gAbqo7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook backtracks on apps grabbing address, cell number. What next? http://t.co/GgLFjZF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@newscientist Looked like a good story. Not interested however, in having to log in to read it. You dont need my info for marketing purposes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here we go again! U.S. moves forward with unique internet ID for all Americans: http://j.mp/f3g7dh via @TweetSmarter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@efa_oz "Schools and hospitals"? - Greens propose $100 GST-free threshold for online shopping http://bit.ly/g0f2eH Greens = Lies and B.S.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cnet Interesting turn of events!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SGgrc via @dsilverman Chinese hackers on to a new IE bug, says Google. MSFT asked him to delay fuzzer release. http://bit.ly/gw2fij]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy New Year all, may it be good to you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good luck with that guys r/t @PajamasMedia 
Sarah for President? http://bit.ly/fHU3Bd #tcot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good advice via @TweetSmarter 
How To Avoid Getting Scammed When Buying or Selling Online: http://j.mp/i6xoJD RT @FunGiftIdeas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some good ideas via @TweetSmarter 
15 More Twitter Tools for Small Businesses http://j.mp/dStiIc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting article via @Ghostery 
"Internet Tracking May Not be Worth the Headaches" - TechNewsWorld - http://bit.ly/gXJTyw #privacy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent advice via @TweetSmarter 

What can you do when someone is being abusive on Twitter? http://j.mp/g9dGfD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaliLewis Norm? No. Prob started about 3-4 eps back. W/Beat stopped syncing to iPhone3G. OK on PC. Some 20+other p/casts incld G/Beat allOK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Scobleizer Robert Scoble
"Leo Laporte. Great to see this about him: http://nyti.ms/fukQSp"

Well done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas to you. Hoping that you have a safe and prosperous New Year :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A definite maybe RT@tan123
#agw earth will warm 2 to 20 degrees. Or it'll cool. Or it will repeatedly warm and cool:.. http://bit.ly/hF9kUz]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>