<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@HMRCcustomers It says I do, but I have not worked in the UK, nor am I resident, nor do I have any UK income. Which seems odd.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HMRCgovuk Hello – I have not been resident in the UK since August 2015. Do I still need to do a tax return?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HMRCcustomers Hello – I have not been resident in the UK since August 2015. Do I still need to do a tax return?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to make the Wellington Sevens booze free. That'll fix things. https://t.co/NuUoxMnmIl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of folk dressing up as yellow seats... https://t.co/5k9VySZblk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for deer, pigs, goats... anything really. https://t.co/y027GaV7tO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScottSimpsonMP Congratulations!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justin_lester Glad to hear you and JR are ok!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomTugendhat More importantly it delivers crap intelligence, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Makes Trump seem positively angelic... https://t.co/xLyGkuRxuu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nicola Sturgeon put firmly back in her box. Time for her to focus on more pressing matters, like getting Scotland's… https://t.co/n4hjcOlVrn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Intellectuals enjoy the surprising privilidge of being scandalously asinine without harming their reputation..." https://t.co/jho4J7vWpv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I want to see a positive before a negative. Indulge me." https://t.co/tGAjaRPF9n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A stronger, fairer &amp; truly global Britain"

Farewell to the dead hand of the €urocrats.

Hello world.

https://t.co/bbHgjKkACE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see Wellington business @ACMEANDCO taking Austin, Texas by storm. https://t.co/6lw3bR689m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@allanholloway @DanielJHannan Absolutely true. My grandparents felt similarly about Japanese cars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Starbucks Is there any way of buying your 'You Are Here' mugs online?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a disgracefully half-arsed road tunnel. Irreparable damage to a landscape of vital importance to British hi… https://t.co/NHELLY57ng]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Besides, if the SNP was serious about independence it'd be tackling Scotland's structural deficit with the rest of the United Kingdom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AyeAye111 Quite! Drove monetary union among other things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not holding out much hope that Sturgeon and her cronies will push for the Darien Scheme to be added to the Scottish history curriculum.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spend spend spend! The SNP has clearly forgotten that near bankruptcy drove Scotland to seek union with England in… https://t.co/HeZM1bixcK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The West has a hard enough time ignoring unsavoury dictators. How could we snub a democratically elected leader of a G7 nation?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surely the lesson of 2016 is to stop saying 'we won't deal with xxxx if they win'? Really dumb gesture politics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didn't we say this about Donald Trump? https://t.co/fOtEQ8yDZo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10% of the Alamo defenders massacred by the Mexicans were British, including John MacGregor, one of my distant rela… https://t.co/JpuEViqO6k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oliver blamed Sydney's licensing regime when he canned his Wellington restaurant. Extraordinary buck-passing. https://t.co/gALhjR5XdG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Austin's beautiful City Hall. https://t.co/tJbeLSLXfU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dpfdpf The real reason... https://t.co/gALhjR5XdG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great way to show gratitude to a country that took her in as a refugee. By her own admission she doesn't like New Z… https://t.co/l5PElsVdEg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found in the 'awkward' section of your local bookshop... 😬 https://t.co/RyrQ3jvmbf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tough gig being a puppy when everyone wants to take you for walks... https://t.co/z74loB7H54]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisBramwell I've paid my subscription but not sure I'm a member. Thanks for the suggestion – slight chaos because I'm en route to the US.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robot_ranger They didn't take the bags! Shocking lack of commitment to adventure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustyrake Thank you! Really appreciated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for all the retweets! I should have pointed out it had a brown leather saddle on when it was nicked. The police have been great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pukeko65 The police say there's been a big operation by professional thieves. The cops seem pretty on-to-it. Fingers crossed for you son!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thieves broke into my apartment complex on Boxing Day and stole my beloved Surly ECR. Beyond frustrating! Keep an e… https://t.co/7UGUSzwELT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Scilly season is very short. https://t.co/x7CDxerI4n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watership Down made me very anti-greenfields development at an early age. RIP Richard Adams. https://t.co/cb3vHbakYa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hunthillwill If only the Allies had been more pro-active on the canvassing in 1940. I suspect the response would have been 1997-esque.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hunthillwill This from Max Hastings' 'The Secret War' on the importance of campaigning on the ground... https://t.co/xWQHHANmWy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IsobelEwing I think you'll find that's referred to as a 'Reverse Werther's'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Britain couldn't spare a ship for @nznavy's 75th birthday fleet review – unlike Australia, Canada, Japan &amp; the US. https://t.co/qWziNDCtc5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Term limits are bad – Obama could easily have done 12 years as president. https://t.co/huY8muZAFP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lifeboat from MS Mikhail Lermontov, in Picton. https://t.co/WwBRknJ9Bo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Out and about on Christmas Eve... https://t.co/gQWqb7akYl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@malosilima Morgan will be bricking it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@malosilima Hopefully Lego fans in parliament would block that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@malosilima Gareth Morgan can't come fast enough for you! Perfect for me with my low value, high yield Lego portfolio though... 😉]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@malosilima I think the kicker is having to keep the cellophane wrapping on...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still kicking myself for not buying the Lego Death Star 2 (10143). $300 when released – goes for 10x that now. https://t.co/bPcZDVIBMm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off to the Sounds for Christmas – so long Wellington! https://t.co/Je4a24DyOk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@malosilima Flipside is Santa will be able to deliver presents to all the network, rather than just the small amount with an electric line..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hunthillwill Love Stockholm. Lived there for a year and a bit in 2005/06. Amazing place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I did say this last month... https://t.co/pqedM3V4Vq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IsobelEwing Bicycle Junction on Riddiford St in Newtown. https://t.co/64603JdsdJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IsobelEwing +1 for Topline Taylors. Good knowledge @jamespeshaw.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done @WgtnCC for producing a really good FAQ on today's Targeted Building Assessments, which include my office. https://t.co/8RqyvzovS6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't say I watch much TV, but Paul Henry's stuff was brilliant. Big loss for NZ broadcasting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BecaGroup @BillEnglishMP is a parody account...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wildantlers Isolated Saddle, Wards Pass and Upcot Saddle. 60km of road at over 800m altitude. You're familiar with the terrain?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rebuilding the coastal route is the only realistic option – an inland road would be at least $10bn and cross 1000m+… https://t.co/xBsXMYVxAC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you don't shape the world you will be shaped by it" – really powerful speech on the disaster in Syria by… https://t.co/5o3UnB39nk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alas this was many years too late for Donald Trump... https://t.co/UG4e6l1KtC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York ——&gt; Auckland non-stop can't be far away: it's a similar distance to this new Qantas service. https://t.co/1txXouCa9v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always good to see the Hikitia in action. Nothing quite as evocative as the smell of steam engines... https://t.co/HitzjjSydF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrickmorgan Still with the desperate shortage of decent locking points...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothy_stanley Time chickened out in 2001 – OBL was the standout candidate (in line with Hitler and Stalin). But it went for Giuliani.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JosephPagani And to be fair, Blair's work on things like Clause 4 got New Labour into shape for government.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JosephPagani No, that'd be John Smith, one of the best PMs Britain never had.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JosephPagani Very true! So Little is somewhere between Foot and Kinnock...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JosephPagani Neil Kinnock was an electoral failure; Andrew Little is a fair comparison there! No NZ heirs to Blair on the scene yet...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JosephPagani The Nats are in trouble if winning the next election is the height of their aspiration: Key was much bigger picture than that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JosephPagani Barely, and the Tories were out for a generation after Major's defeat in 1997. He was a weak leader who damaged the brand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill English is a pretty underwhelming replacement for John Key. A bit like going from Thatcher to Major.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IN WHICH Gareth Morgan Discovers Economics and Politics are Very Different Creatures
https://t.co/Y3KFOJ88nL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Must read piece from @franks_lawyer on GWRC's Centreport property investment. (Plot spoiler: ratepayers lose out...) https://t.co/ezkUxoosKK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We're going to build a cat-proof wall. It's going to be tremendous – nobody builds anti-feline walls like me." https://t.co/DMG5GN1S9Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahfreenz Perfect. Meet you at the WCC lobby?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["My party wants to hike the tax on your home and kill your cat. Can we count on your vote?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JudithCollinsMP Best of luck. Hope your colleagues give you the prime-ministerial gloves!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @garethmorgannz had knocked on doors in the local elections he'd know just how loathed his proposed 'Family Home Tax' (aka rates) is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This isn't mean in an unkind way, just a helpful 'don't double down on reheated septuagenarians' sort of vibe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Statistically Joe Biden is likely to be dead by the 2020 presidential election. https://t.co/FBTmklNWmD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prime Minister Bill English. What an exciting prospect. https://t.co/ErNnC1QFfB https://t.co/RZiLL8KJ0I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A steady hand on the tiller &amp; down-to-earth goofiness have secured John Key's place in NZ's pantheon. My take at https://t.co/oyZlfS6p9G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Key's steady hand doesn't make for flashy 'legacy', but he's been a terrific PM. My piece for @SpecCoffeeHouse: https://t.co/VBj4fGy8Vo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahfreenz Cup of tea?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanielJHannan Shock here in Wellington. Some offering conspiracy theories – most just see his supreme service &amp; desire for something new!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BGCraven It's a conservative estimate! But I agree – point is it could be the thing that saves Little's bacon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suspect John Key's brand alone is worth an extra 1-2% for National. Might be the boost that Andrew Little needs to get back on the list...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stability isn't a sexy legacy for John Key, but 2008-16 has seen major earthquakes, a global credit crunch – and the 2011 Rugby World Cup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Italy has had four prime ministers in the time John Key has been New Zealand's PM.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Short answer: don't hold your breath. Commercial fusion generation is still 50 years away. https://t.co/MiaOcieW3w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlyAirNZ Your route map is awful. Impossible to figure out your network from it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can we trust @UKLabour with the nation's finances when it can't even hold onto its #RichmondPark deposit? https://t.co/1UKCF9XkjR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zac Goldsmith has Olney himself to blame. #RichmondPark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was a dumb, arrogant promise. https://t.co/E5tVFdPEUk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a special place in hell for Tories who lose their seats to LibDems. Zac's by-election was deeply self-indulgent. #RichmondPark]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>