<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[A tax that could pay for Trump’s wish list is already dividing the GOP - The Washington Post https://t.co/lrjB5STUdw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former top diplomats, tech giants blast immigration order as court showdown looms - The Washington Post https://t.co/GP3afC8Gff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump and Staff Rethink Tactics After Stumbles https://t.co/alujxZu3of]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Romney: Trump has gotten off to a 'strong start' https://t.co/Lz5DvtC1uT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘S.N.L.’ Goes After Trump Again, With Melissa McCarthy as Sean Spicer - https://t.co/7HKoA097CI https://t.co/fDwtzkoB0d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alec Baldwin returns as Trump on SNL, where an evil Bannon is actually president - The Washington Post https://t.co/yuZtJZ5t1P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9th Circuit Court declines to quickly reinstate travel ban - The Washington Post https://t.co/WVhaq5IIL5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bush-appointed judge halts Trump travel ban nationwide https://t.co/g8WgmFibcq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Travel Ban Judge James Robart: A Soft-Spoken Jursist Who Minces No Words - NBC News https://t.co/CsBkaHB3XF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Kerr is extraordinary for reasons that have nothing to do with basketball - The Washington Post https://t.co/f5cZBqlCRT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump lashes out at ‘so-called judge’ who temporarily blocked travel ban - The Washington Post https://t.co/R70HGvF35b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s pick for Army secretary withdraws from consideration - The Washington Post https://t.co/TzqRGczvGi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back to reality: Obamas settle into DC life @CNNPolitics https://t.co/YfRvBKbZ3V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Trump approval rating lags behind past presidents @CNNPolitics https://t.co/5ujgW560P6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s Mar-a-Lago getaway could cost taxpayers more than $3 million https://t.co/1gGhRbxkLo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York Times Co.’s Decline in Print Advertising Tempered by Digital Gains https://t.co/9EtdyIn04V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senate advances DeVos's nomination, setting her up for final vote  https://t.co/FX5SN6c3al]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NYC Federal Judge Extends Stay on Trump Travel Restrictions https://t.co/fbjCuK97kJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Embraces Pillars of Obama’s Foreign Policy https://t.co/VY8LXiox3c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Tells Israel to Hold Off on Building New Settlements https://t.co/VY8LXiox3c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gutiérrez: Democrats now the pro-immigrant party | TheHill https://t.co/3SiJ7aAxWX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats plot protest for Trump’s speech to Congress https://t.co/4wXtsgZDW2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mexican government says Trump never threatened to send troops to Mexico https://t.co/K0Xv4jkrV5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No ‘G’day, mate’: On call with Australian prime minister, Trump badgers and brags - The Washington Post https://t.co/hszmrnJDSx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump to Mexico: Take care of 'bad hombres' or US might https://t.co/2HgsfBn8oB via @YahooNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(NYT) Neil Gorsuch, the Nominee for a Stolen Seat https://t.co/e4RXeC5hL5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mysterious intruder rattles GOP lawmakers https://t.co/kXU0lxqzxK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOP House chair: Maybe we should cut off part of D.C. and send it back to Md. https://t.co/Thcw8ZUay6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Upset in WSJ newsroom over editor's directive to avoid 'majority Muslim' in immigration ban coverage https://t.co/dOwePd9IPJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama backs alderman in first post-presidency endorsement https://t.co/SyXMAo9ZWd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats boycott confirmation hearings for Price and Mnuchin, blocking votes - The Washington Post https://t.co/MYp1L0b962]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Revisiting the 'Saturday Night Massacre' https://t.co/7B8UuXWQa7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spicer splits with Bannon about the press https://t.co/0dcsG3I2MU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spicer slams ‘pathetic’ criticism of Holocaust statement that omitted mention of Jews - The Washington Post https://t.co/naM05iqsTL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama supports protests: 'American values are at stake' - POLITICO https://t.co/Bgad5bS66E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Multiple people reported killed and injured by gunmen at Quebec City mosque - The Washington Post https://t.co/rb9WHZo2GV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. service member killed in Yemen raid marks first combat death of Trump administration - The Washington Post https://t.co/vYNPpnj1Ey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump signs order temporarily halting admission of refugees, promises priority for Christians - The Washington Post https://t.co/VTgwHZQU5v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. economy expanded 1.9 percent in fourth quarter, 2016 GDP rises 1.6 percent - The Washington Post https://t.co/YJg2giPd0V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump lays groundwork to change U.S. role in the world - The Washington Post https://t.co/N44oAnfG4W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump pressured Park Service to find proof for his claims about inauguration crowd - The Washington Post (Imparable) https://t.co/PPE0TobJg9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WH press secretary says border wall will be funded by 20 percent import tax on Mexican goods - (guerra comercial) https://t.co/rfLvI9BwLA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s flashy executive actions could run aground https://t.co/13f6yAQh7d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Press secretaries express sympathy for Spicer https://t.co/k5kDjJMP9c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pickup Truck Dangles on Edge of Sinkhole That Swallows Up Yards, Street in Montgomery County | NBC 10 Philadelphia https://t.co/TKNquArKna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dow Jones industrial average reaches new high, tops 20,000 level for first time - The Washington Post https://t.co/eQAeirN5tr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump dogged by insecurity over popular vote, media coverage https://t.co/7mfNUxrlcI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first days inside Trump’s White House: Fury, tumult and a reboot - The Washington Post https://t.co/SONlmw29VB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[D.C. cab driver calls John Elway his favorite QB, discovers Elway is in his cab https://t.co/46WK3fgoX1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recidivism Watch: Spicer uses repeatedly debunked citations for Trump's voter fraud claims https://t.co/9CLagfOITv #alternativefacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sean Spicer’s Stalinist apparition - The Washington Post https://t.co/ZLpYC1O5di]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There’s no evidence that Trump’s inauguration was the most-watched in history. Period. - The Washington Post https://t.co/OHexED2aiW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump repeats debunked voter fraud claim at meeting with Hill leaders https://t.co/3zipOfGDcL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sean Spicer at press briefing: 'Our intention is never to lie to you' https://t.co/JuY5Lh8IkM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ABC: MORE: President Trump also signs executive order imposing federal hiring freeze with exception of the military.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poll: Warren could face rocky reelection path https://t.co/qLnwYZJpRu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Diplomat’s Advice for the Trump Administration https://t.co/oIyNzMlVqO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The perfect meme for the ‘alternative facts’ era: #seanspicersays - The Washington Post https://t.co/I9hfCbti4M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Alternative facts:' Why the Trump team is 'planting a flag' in war on media https://t.co/hLWk36F4H2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Residente Chases His Muse, at the Genetic Level https://t.co/KZAwerIuLs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FACT CHECK: Trump uses bogus claim to knock media on reports #laguerradeTrump  https://t.co/8lYlgfjyR8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women’s marches: More than one million protesters vow to resist President Trump - The Washington Post https://t.co/0V3TXtVZVC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inaugural Speech Dims G.O.P. Hopes for a More Conservative Trump Agenda https://t.co/cqNLopVsRm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The campaign to impeach President Trump has begun https://t.co/niZieAhzfh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WomensMarch https://t.co/fqg4t1FN1p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women’s March on Washington shakes out to be a star-studded event - The Washington Post https://t.co/uioI4R54jX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A police chase ended with 3 dead and 20 others hurt in Australia https://t.co/nTUNCqTJmL via @nbcnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet Trump's spiritual adviser, televangelist Paula White https://t.co/B7DyQVZcJs via @nbcnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wayne Barrett, Fierce Muckraker at The Village Voice, Dies at 71 https://t.co/vQjT7n2Oe0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Source: O's, Trumbo agree to 3-year deal
Sent with @MLB At Bat https://t.co/lrW73SuxD2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kanye West not being invited to Trump's inauguration because it's "traditionally American".  https://t.co/zJd7NyX5Hv https://t.co/eTqxInh4W9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New survey shows how much Fox News dominated the 2016 election: https://t.co/ClIoDZ6E4S vía @AOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Dinner Honoring Mike Pence, Donald Trump Touches Many Bases https://t.co/hwaWUQt9sv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obamacare attack dog to lead GOP effort to replace it https://t.co/17eHBezasU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Earth Sets a Temperature Record for the Third Straight Year https://t.co/XBGWABRltF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump puts GOP in awkward spot on Obamacare @CNNPolitics https://t.co/sZgDEYWVqs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Cabinet will be first in decades without Hispanic member: report https://t.co/6W4kFOc0o9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump will pick Sonny Perdue to lead Agriculture - POLITICO https://t.co/SnceBszVfH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reporters have worked from the White House for over 100 years. Will Trump evict them? - The Washington Post https://t.co/LkKlh1cNc7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(NYT) Obama Commutes Sentence of F.A.L.N. Member Oscar Lopez Rivera https://t.co/zT5Ivid0NU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lin-Manuel Miranda says he'll play 'Hamilton' in Chicago for Oscar Lopez Rivera - Chicago Tribune https://t.co/k4bwNj3psr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama's Hesitation To Free An Elderly Political Prisoner Is Shameful https://t.co/PEfT51Hl1c # via @LatinoVoices]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Health Law’s Repeal Could Raise Costs and Number of Uninsured, New Report Says https://t.co/TbpZOYeP7y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump mistakenly tweets to wrong Ivanka, who tells him to use 'more care on Twitter' https://t.co/L7cXpFGoOG via @nbcnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Story of My Life | The Players' Tribune https://t.co/rMpMYqHh9U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In ‘Brexit’ Speech, Theresa May Outlines a Clean Break for U.K. - https://t.co/7HKoA097CI https://t.co/VPat1SuCow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ellison: I will not attend Trump's inauguration https://t.co/XWzukfiZkI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justin Trudeau's Bahamas trip being investigated by ethics watchdog https://t.co/geOvyDy5cT via @nbcnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Is Making Journalism Great Again https://t.co/czpkUqCJPv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama to commute hundreds of federal drug sentences in final grants of clemency - The Washington Post https://t.co/zlj5QThZa6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump national security spokeswoman Monica Crowley to forgo post amid plagiarism charges - The Washington Post https://t.co/XB8zKXe06L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[F.B.I. Arrests Wife of Killer in Orlando Mass Shooting https://t.co/r0GqmFNKUt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Samsung Heir Faces Arrest on Charges of Bribing South Korea’s President - https://t.co/7HKoA097CI https://t.co/G7RMA1HatP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With All Due Disrespect https://t.co/kWwCEy9TA1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump vows ‘insurance for everybody’ in Obamacare replacement plan - The Washington Post https://t.co/hWkeQ2w8kj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(Son 20 ya) These Democratic lawmakers won't be attending Trump's inauguration https://t.co/4wcboYwaLp via @nbcnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[News conferences could be moved from White House, Priebus says - The Washington Post https://t.co/zgzItRWTGT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Via @NPR: Pardon Sought For Prisoner Who Fought For Puerto Rican Independence  https://t.co/zE2BtR8jBz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHIP LIST: Democrats boycotting Trump's inauguration | TheHill https://t.co/K7x6EkPdiP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can Trump’s Cabinet save him from himself? - The Washington Post https://t.co/qtrgsDprwT]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>