<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@VanguardBears @STVGrant This guy! Obsessed with the champs as per usual.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wondering if there will be any in or out of Paradise today?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hearing 40m for the Moose from Chelski?! Take that shit if true âœ… Doubt it tho lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Record_Sport Yet it's acceptable for some zevco fans to celebrate a 5 game unbeaten run??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edbug29 Same here man - plodding on! Still enjoying the sweet sweet bucky lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really wish these clowns the worst of luck. https://t.co/VTaG3XQYcJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right in front eh me! https://t.co/HSbRUa0J7q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lynseymckeown @HannahB4LiviMP Buck up your ideas you useless talking head fucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClareWa25115331 @ChrispyGhirl  some amount of replies here! Do what you want at the games. HH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celtic, Fulham, Leeds and Man Utd and Leeds fucked my coupon against some pub team! Sakes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[KT is 100% on a different level from the grass, KT is worth 10 times that fud. https://t.co/FVLO0wurDv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerhouse performance by the history bhoys. @Daily_Record Did we stumble to the record today ya cunts? Just the 4-0. #NewRecord #coybig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Â£100 bet half time talk between Tanner and the rat will be "eh that was a pen tho eh eh"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gastro_Celtic Shite! Had him as first scorer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mon the hoops ðŸ€ðŸ€ðŸ€ðŸ€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parody account? If not this guy is hilarious HH https://t.co/N125aAXCms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scuj1 we've all sorts of records to break to bam up the Zombies!  Nothing personal.... Bet youz hump us now I said that. #fuckyoukarma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JustABhoy Where is that? Kyole Edinburgh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scuj1 I guess we can't be pals tomorrow ðŸ˜¬ not at least til 3pm HAHA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#justified series 1 episode 1. I'm fixing to watch me all 78 episodes in this here box set. YEE HAW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scuj1 shit hole full of Huns Scully..... Bad buzz mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scuj1 motherfuckers mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edbug29 Alright Ed! How u doin? Hope you and the fam are ok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck off Brighton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Slavelle90 *you're* fucking knucklehead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Slavelle90 &lt;---- crackpot https://t.co/jBHgVj5UCN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All sorts of dolce gusto coffees and coupons â˜•ï¸âš½ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paddypower exact same bet on @bet365 Â£200 more wings than paddy power - can you explain? https://t.co/43ni9tLGD8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scuj1 @onechord_js Yaaaass double the luck sir. Who do you bet with? Mines was an acca tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus titty fucking Christ. https://t.co/GZPdXaYWUj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TSBible @TheNotoriousMMA He is trying to take keys!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HOOP588 Hail Hail Gary, spark a few cans and get mad way it pal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[James Tavenier (who?) to Lyon for Â£6m @SkySports https://t.co/3TbpfAm301]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On eastenders 'I feel I just went 6 rounds with @TheNotoriousMMA' it's 3 or 5 rounds! Those judges at it again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DS1888 that's a cracker Daz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomasjrennie Baldy cunt, you look like someone drew glasses on an egg.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sure!! I won't hold the breath. https://t.co/f4uTNzrLob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rachel_Lynchx That country has a hidden deep embedded racism, it's escalating to sectarianism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Rodgers effect has spread to Boyata! âœ… â˜˜ðŸ€â˜˜ðŸ€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DRkneevil @danawhite Dana as JoJo's agent who she is unaware of, I demand that Anderson Silva money for the London card!! DO IT, DO IT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hate how you become a timetable expert by sitting in the first seat on a train, naw pal I don't even know where fucking Hyndland is ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some amount of French conversations on my feed. I had to mute some asses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because there will be zero bids for him. In other sensational news, water is reported to be wet. https://t.co/SXaawQ8waa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carolk23 @piersmorgan @mcgregor_ewan Ewan patched you piers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like writing a note for dogging school, this clown will sign anything he's told https://t.co/RhWyKAtxlM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chump change for the Bhoys https://t.co/JyiOisTcFJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chadmendes your friend is also called Chad? Is that a popular name in USA?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KyleFrancisFalc @LiamUTLR @viewofficial Kyle Spolier, its 2017 n The View are one year less relevant. Non tour coming up with The Automatic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClareWa25115331 @bridhe_mac some attention seeking wee wanker from what I'm reading. Sad bastard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's squeezing the bottom of the wrapper like offer a pal a crisp AYE ONE FUCKING CRISP https://t.co/C4Rpmb1etZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Literally though he died when a tree landed on his car? Jeeze that's sad https://t.co/YCCcXBeM2G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chillyzag That's a good ethos, thanks man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MMAWeeklycom Bellator is the home of insane flying knee injuries Semtex and MVP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chillyzag Hi chilly, is your tag line a scooter lyric? I like it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolute piece of shit. https://t.co/EGQ8VQgmxg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scuj1 I got Lynx Africa for days bro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@77MASH @COYBIGCMONHOOPS in 98 shows, not one bad guy got shot by this crack team of commando s hmmmm ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scuj1 she sure is getting to lay next to this hot piece of sexiness every night ðŸ˜˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scuj1 My lady is off to Iceland end of Feb!! ðŸ˜¬ðŸ˜¬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danawhite hey Dana how can you hold a UK card and not have 2 division ass kicker @DRkneevil on it? Come on man!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lynseymckeown check this owl out! https://t.co/91KQMFEwtD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Daily_Record its a whole row of letterboxes she can chew an apple through way thon buck teeth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Record_Sport @Daily_Record it was a chip shop munchie box, too much even for a fat cunt like him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1872ChrisKerr @Scotpatsfan @celticsyndicate Trainspotting is on Chris, that's what your mum was using whilst preggers with you. Poor lad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Scotpatsfan @celticsyndicate @1872ChrisKerr mum, why is dad such a scudbook?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NosaRenda @wes_foderingham @ThatWeeMan it would be better for humanity if you did not spread your genes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@celticsyndicate @1872ChrisKerr its the only chat they have, guy looks like a creepy bastard, bet you he is hiding a few secrets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NosaRenda @wes_foderingham @ThatWeeMan please, don't have children.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NosaRenda @wes_foderingham @ThatWeeMan Why would I colour in Lego then eat it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnnydowno1 Anybody know what this guys on about? Don't think all his dogs are barking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnnydowno1 That's a nice photo of a lamp post, you're a special boy eh. Go draw a fire engine with your crayons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NosaRenda @wes_foderingham @ThatWeeMan HAW HAW AHV NO GOAT A SISTER YA PURE MENTO DAFTY YAAASSSS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NosaRenda @wes_foderingham an ah wiz pure hinging oot the back eh yer granny like yaaaaassss @ThatWeeMan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robertmcc13 @1994NathanC @wes_foderingham Yes you clearly are the brains here aren't you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zombie admits that the SFA are helping sevco with home draws for additional revenue. https://t.co/5xyOKFv7aj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robertmcc13 @1994NathanC @wes_foderingham So you're admitting it now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robertmcc13 @1994NathanC @wes_foderingham Doesn't say either fixed or deliberate? Proving my point by circling it was a nice touch. Cheers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robertmcc13 @1994NathanC @wes_foderingham I know right! Your pal talks some amount of shite eh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robertmcc13 @1994NathanC @wes_foderingham you're wrong on both accounts. I watched it and never said it was fixed. Double fail.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robertmcc13 @1994NathanC @wes_foderingham Go watch it and see?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lukeu1234 @1994NathanC @wes_foderingham looks like a fat cunt to me. Another zombie with the only patter they have. Pathetic!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Completely obsessed with the Champions. Poor little zombie. https://t.co/1tlJk03jZx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gilchrist450 @1994NathanC @wes_foderingham ok lad. Zombie cunt oops auto correct error, that should have said have a nice evening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnnydowno1 I don't have a comprehensive list of storm damaged areas, perhaps try the council.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gilchrist450 @1994NathanC @wes_foderingham Will do lad, learn to spell before you next tweet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lukeu1234 @1994NathanC @wes_foderingham Who's that horrible looking bastard?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gilchrist450 @1994NathanC @wes_foderingham Dunno lad, never noticed anyone called Rod the time doing the draw.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ned_Stevens @wes_foderingham Never heard of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[State of this mess. Look how greasy his hair is.... All 4 of them. https://t.co/D95fRaGq8p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wes_foderingham I see you cunts got another home draw, The SFA keeping the crumbledome open for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanAFC97 @SDrever @Mr__JD It means someone is require to suck him off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MDembele_10 @celticfc Top man Moussa, you need to score with your other knee next week you goal machine HH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The bold Rod was pure blazing there! Wish he drew us way the zombies for some added hilarity! HH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_Hoops_Fan @celticsyndicate @KennyMiller17 @JLazzaro16 Kenny Miller ya dick. (I know you're not the Hun)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Leighgriff09 Take the week off mate and come back for the jambos! ðŸ˜· HH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fucking belter!! Though he skied that there HAIL HAIL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stuart_Mactier @The_Hoops_Fan More like looking for change down the back of the seat, junky cunt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wsc3 @BradyTrett I love how you can get a decent scrap going and you're left to it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCMOTD @emmamarieb89 buy a new couch, that one is shite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#womansmarch damn, these bitches be crazy https://t.co/U2SueJenLH]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>