<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@dannolan sabre rattling China for 1200 pre-vetted peeps. It's bargain of the century thanks to desperate bidder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dannolan uh, part of the mooted agreement was that Australia may take part in freedom-of-navigation exercises in the South China Sea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's almost as though Trump doesn't listen to 2GB.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also a reminder that Kenny is a terrible 'journalist' - Oz Pols have praised Trump policy all week. Made no difference.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump has a remarkable ability to make people self-cuck. Their dignity, their careers, their countries, their families.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new News standard is single line of half-hearted criticism of Trump while attacking everyone else for growing shitshow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing, nothing can ever be the fault of conservatives, conservatism or Trump, only the media and liberals. https://t.co/BydJdRwG5B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonathanvswan both Mexico and the White House have now denied the other half of this auricle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@illywhacker_ @MarkDiStef bit of both]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkDiStef @illywhacker_ but no doubt Tomi Lahren is generating a lot of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkDiStef @illywhacker_ the cliches are so thick it's hard to tell where they originate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Serious bureaucratic resistance to the Trump EO - hundreds of officers have reportedly signed this dissent: https://t.co/onodUA5YYj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Imresal quite right - Nazi comparisons should be reserved for Stephen Conroy, Safe Schools, SSM supporters and the Australian Greens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fakeedbutler @EX_V19 maybe. I don't know they'd even bother focus grouping it yet. Just have to be tough on borders no matter what.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EX_V19 @fakeedbutler prime-mover is wanting to cement refugee ban, welcome by-product is appeal to shock-jock set.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here is Murray Rothbard on anti-David Duke 'hysteria' in 1992. Sounding very familiar. https://t.co/nNp32CFrLb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This is why Trump was elected" has become the new "this is just what ISIS wants".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marrowing &lt;calls critics of this 'kids'&gt; &lt;RTs pasty incel neckbeard broadcasting live from parents' garage&gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chriskkenny @joeoarc @PrisonPlanet @jason_a_w do you even know what you're endorsing? Is ISIS an Israeli front organisation?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@John_Neidhart @mtaibbi @scottdools there's a podcast about it here: https://t.co/luCwfRUpl5!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@herandrews @robbykarol @MarkSKrikorian perhaps next time you can choose a moral exemplar who wasn't a rapist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@herandrews @robbykarol @MarkSKrikorian your ridiculous example might be pertinent if the UK had returned Koestler to Vichy France.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pleasedontatme you would think so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems CBP are partly making an Australian-style argument that the airport is not part of migration zone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow @damonsilvers for latest on the possible separation of powers crisis at Dulles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feature of today - watching people who support a Muslim ban angrily insisting that the EO is not a Muslim ban.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clothedvillainy what did that tweet say? deleted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had Burma, Iran, Sri Lanka etc in mind then. Did not think the cravenness would extend to the US, but here we are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've written previously that Australia's obsession with returning refugees means it will turn a blind eye to human rights abuses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not surprisingly, the legal language of the EO is a complete shambles: https://t.co/6oIHMMbd5A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@liamvhogan they collapsed on the first test of the manifesto - the Israeli bombing of Lebanon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RitaPanahi what separates you from people currently on Nauru or stuck in airports other than timing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RitaPanahi I hadn't read your column and thought perhaps I'd made a mistake. Couldn't be a more perfect illustration.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrayConnolly absolutely. Good radio show about this: https://t.co/BKbcKvxXWf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrayConnolly it is. But Catallaxy is supposedly Australia's #1 libertarian blog. Its readers don't seem to realise that, or don't care.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrayConnolly @RedState I strongly disagree - see https://t.co/DHqeftDHzX for eg. It's not just inconsistency.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrayConnolly Reason running thorough legal fiskings of Trump EOs. Catallaxy comments running 99% pro-wall and pro-tarrifs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrayConnolly @RedState maybe. but American libertarianism and conservatism is much more coherent. Compare Reason with Catallaxy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Extreme example - @RitaPanahi's family fled Iran. What does she have to say about ban on the same? 'Teh left - LOL'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many conservatives don't like Trump, publicly and privately. But 99% of commentary is about left hypocrisy &amp; protests.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's plenty of of conservative opposition to Trumpism in the US and UK - including former hardliners like @RedState. Almost none here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Compare the Australian statement here with the others. https://t.co/kDfXgjIIXV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dr_Tad your self-appointed role as turd-polisher-in-chief is going terrifically well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrayConnolly @KristianHarstad @HelenKennedy not true. In fact Hitler offered to let Jews leave Germany if accepted by other nations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkDiStef @fakeedbutler how often do boomers pick you up on points of grammar, but get it wrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomwestland everything is Communism https://t.co/cHqFmYvfO4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Fussy customer". This @jonronson article about Stanley Kubrick's archive repays re-reading.
https://t.co/uNzxzIql5P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chriskkenny He made the statement when speaking about imagery of the "in person" crowd.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chriskkenny “This was the largest audience to ever witness an inauguration, period, both in person and around the globe,” he said.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheDingoes Edwin? Is that you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dr_Tad still threading the needle between 'Trump is disrupting the elite order' and 'Trump is just like Obama', then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheDingoes Dingoes twitter, aka mainly slav-descended incels the Nazis would have executed at birth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@illywhacker_ Blainey kicked things off around 1985, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@illywhacker_ @historyben also a book that almost never mentions the indigenous, partly because they would invalidate its shit thesis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@illywhacker_ @historyben the fact that he is considered the apex of Australia's conservative intellectuals speaks volumes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@historyben this is flat wrong. Grant doesn't say it in the speech, and Dickens doesn't say it in the essay (which… https://t.co/vXUjVkMazS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FitToPrint @NYMag this comment afterwards was extremely unusual: https://t.co/rlF8LVUMJy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chriskkenny your own news organisation has repeatedly reported the same story: https://t.co/QbX1foaGU3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alisoncroggon the idea that people voted for Trump because MO was insufficiently feminist is deeply cooked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump supporters enraged Michelle Obama didn't use First Ladyship as bully pulpit for feminist policies, are good, to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NeilMcMahon it's so confused it can't be guessed, only experienced.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Early contender for worst op-ed of the year: https://t.co/JywUNELtW8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheDingoes @EnDeplorable @RitaPanahi @JosephA63663695 @knockoffshow opposition to Jews, you mean.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EnDeplorable @RitaPanahi @JosephA63663695 @TheDingoes @knockoffshow And these (((are just parentheses))) https://t.co/7vNd1vYc6c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EnDeplorable @RitaPanahi @JosephA63663695 @TheDingoes @knockoffshow https://t.co/eFa72GcFGy Right. And this is about Skype.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EnDeplorable @RitaPanahi "1488" here references Heil Hitler and the Fourteen Words used by white supremacists https://t.co/0yT1iJaWnU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EnDeplorable @RitaPanahi Happy to help. Here they are RTing an endorsement of the idea that they bash black "cunts" and deport Muslims.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EnDeplorable @RitaPanahi they fact they call Jews subhumans who control the media does.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RitaPanahi Claimed by Dingo Twitter. Sure you'll be RTing them in no time, along with the other anti-semitic filth https://t.co/l29foD7RHc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@illywhacker_ he seems to have a crush on her]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamie_hall @tomwestland also what happened to all that talk about 'certainty' now US trade policy is set via random tweets?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClintonDucas she's working on a unified theory of socialism where it's responsible for everything bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomwalkerisgood @IllyBocean Genki Sudo is clearly not a real person.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomwalkerisgood @IllyBocean and button-bashing https://t.co/H4ou6EQIhQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IllyBocean @tomwalkerisgood when there were no weight divisions, and YMCA karate instructors (wearing gi) fighting 200kg brawlers. ☺️]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshButler when did he do this last?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomas_violence or this: https://t.co/QG6j9UiJXI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomas_violence @IllyBocean have you ever seen 'Vibrations'?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonkudelka a seemingly normal Tasmanian person, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pollytics so right from the start? I hadn't encountered even US massacre trutherism then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How long after the event did Port Arthur trutherism begin? Must be almost twenty years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cubisia and 'war atrocities' means the P's mailbag...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cubisia are you talking about yourself?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“From the moment you see the first image, you will change for good.” The human toll of beheadings and dickpics. https://t.co/yVYBrWjgeb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It would explain the golden toilet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshButler $3k per day is a top-of-the-line luxury holiday. $10k a day is Brewster's Millions territory.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomas_violence @MJB_SF 'become more like people who despise you so they move into your neighbourhood']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marrowing is that thing still going?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@megsansmog @OmarjSakr @gisellenguyen potato scallop is the correct term.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OmarjSakr @gisellenguyen based on the concept that commuting into the sun both ways gives you a permanent squint.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OmarjSakr @gisellenguyen agreed. unmentioned there is the best (and rarest) word for bogans/westies etc - 'squinters'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OmarjSakr @gisellenguyen i don't want to reignite the potato cake controversy, but this is good: https://t.co/rrMwiWsvvt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@liamvhogan [extremely Ray Hadley voice] her thesis is called "The Tribunal of Zaragoza and Crypto-Judaism, 1484-1515", what's that about?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OmarjSakr apart from the saving grace note of the McGriddle, it is unbelievably bad and nasty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OmarjSakr perhaps American KFC has undergone the same kind of precipitous decline as the republic itself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OmarjSakr the best international KFC remains Bethnal Green, with a possibly bootlegged collection of herbs and spices.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OmarjSakr you must have got lucky. Twitter was ripping on it the other day, with good reason.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OmarjSakr US KFC is not dope.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jrhennessy IS is an Israeli false flag operation #youknowitmakessense]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jrhennessy and has an Australian commentator fan club]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>