<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@VinLew don't leave out nuclear war.  #allthefunthoughts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jethrocarr it's not like I needed another reason to visit, but I'll take it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pebblesy depends how you hold your toungue whether its 20 mins or 30 mins, just ask.  Too many factors @stevebiddle @mwgnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mwgnz @Pebblesy most people don't have enough hands and feet to drive a truck and motorbike at the same time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pebblesy are they driving an 18 wheeler or a 1200cc motorbike and have no brains/fear?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richms was a phone, which is why they made me courier it rather than parcel post,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlueMaestroNews pretty new app.  But not sure battery is right.  This is reporting 99% I read as 82.3% https://t.co/2YFq4bEa6y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So what's the deal on a tracked domestic package that gets lost in the system?  Are they insured by the courier company?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrancesCook Don't forget mind altering drugs...we have those as well. @themorgan @SiobhanKeoghNZ @ChrisKeall  #notadvocatinguse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richms all depends if he mistakes the coffee button for the nuke button... https://t.co/ixWfsTcUBz  @DylanReeve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richms ours or theirs?  Both are equally likely. @DylanReeve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VinLew he's so hip with the lingo of his peeps. @DylanReeve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Decided to play with fanpass.  Picture quality pretty good.... but ads?!?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonpnz "passive magnetic levitation pod" I win nerd intersectionality today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Must say, the hyperloop pod competition live stream is a little dry.  Lot of down time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hadyngreen I guess that image only makes sense when you see the weekly and monthly passes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbrislen all the cool people have tiny hands...no wait, hang on there's something wrong with that statement @DylanReeve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbrislen you only have to take off from the top joint of the finger, that should leave enough to do that.  @DylanReeve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbrislen if you just chop your fingers off you can't use fingerprint reader. #easysolution @DylanReeve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DylanReeve knowing that lunatic, he'll claim he's god, then all the insurance companies can just beg off that they don't cover acts of god.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hamfritta tho I saw a notification about reduced seating this morning, not sure why @ColdDaemon @stevebiddle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hamfritta nope, (and didn't notice) did they bring the out for expected 7s passengers?  @ColdDaemon @stevebiddle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jethrocarr they stop the tray from warping and get toasty warm tho. https://t.co/fHhCRJtKcH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not a real BBQ until you singe some of the hair off your arm. https://t.co/nJQnRZmvLs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevebiddle I saw nothing in their outage pages.  Broadband was funny from about 9:30]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any @SparkNZ ufb issues in Lower Hutt? Seems like service is down/intermittent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jethrocarr even better when it gb2312]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonpnz breaking all the rules, what's next a Wednesday #coffeeselfie with no selfie and a picture of just a dog?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[influxdb all the things]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevebiddle what model? @jethrocarr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@freitasm more likely to be a plant by the Martians. https://t.co/SYbWm9iHvM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HarryBStard I've switched back to C63 https://t.co/VWPT0ZcIDF  @paulbrislen @Brycepearce @DemiseNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbrislen gees your eyes better than me, or is a AMG badge? @Brycepearce @HarryBStard @DemiseNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbrislen yeah my other gues was a c63 amg...but the wheels look bmw. @Brycepearce @HarryBStard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbrislen 5 series bmw I think]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbrislen checked on a brick courtyard @hadyngreen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevebiddle were they carrying a vhs tape from the video store as well, and letting their partner know what they chose?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hadyngreen "I will be using this photo when taking this driver through our discipline procedures"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hadyngreen got an apology at least.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrancesCook the first ep has a crossover with vanderpump rules.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrancesCook #realityreviewsin140chars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrancesCook yes, like a classier (just) version of geordie shore, but they're from Manhattan at the hamptons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hadyngreen yeah just fired an email off (with the picture) to the operations manager of the local courier branch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hadyngreen I think it was a clothing item...but still. lazy as bro.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder if this is normal for PB Transport?  #rpt https://t.co/kjaAC9yOFR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TFW you've got video of your courier chucking your package from the gate....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrancesCook oh actually, completely different topic, Summer House, seen it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amscraig you should ask for recommendations and we could create a new "Everyone's chair dance tracks" playlist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a mix of country and EDM: https://t.co/jvsoc6z5mg  They need to get a dbanjo in there somewhere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richms they might just siphon off all the netflix...that'd annoy everyone if they couldn't stream @stevebiddle @StuFlemingNZ @marvin_nz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrsNickiPea ha ha ha, what dodgy pages on FB have you been liking to be suggested that shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonpnz its actually really hard (on ios) to delete the cached tracks on @Spotify]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonpnz yeah it'd probably do that, but if you were playing the tracks with mobile turned off, the track is prob still cached.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonpnz I don't know that it actually clears it until it needs the space. @Spotify]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juhasaarinen It is a countdown to extinction, or are we just sweating bullets?  Though I think I head a Symphony of Destruction #magadeath]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DylanReeve tie them up and force them to listen to Cotton Eye Joe and Daphne and Celeste!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonpnz but that'll will wreck everyone's childhood if we can't do what Simon Says. #simageddon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Herbertimo just ride faster than the rain...you'll stay dry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuckwits all round https://t.co/fzWOmPu0tm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DemiseNZ couple of garden hoses, you'll be right mate. @scottjpalmer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tim_Stevens seriously spendy.  I think he crammed a Lamborghini v10 in there also.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VinLew easier just to bite their necks like a vampire isn't it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tim_Stevens if you like carbon fibre, check out what this guy did to his RS6.  From Performance VW Feb 2017. https://t.co/vAW0s4IlPa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlueMaestroNews hmm so lets see how what I've done works with two.  Just bought a 2nd.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hadyngreen Graham Masterton used to give me the shits reading him.  Lot more graphic than king or koontz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@venzann I figured 12 months was a safe period. @freitasm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@freitasm at least she didn't comment that it was kylo ren's dad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WardrobeFlair looks like yours will be finished before one round here that was started  before xmas 2015. #notatypo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How's this for a train set: https://t.co/5ARnfDZAXD  @myleftkidney @AstroDamo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VinLew but you'd hear the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VinLew still, that's a total on 9 minutes when you might have to interact with other people. HOW DO YOU EVEN DEAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VinLew plus the walk on both sides?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chris021 yeah the fancy ones look great.   A very good review site is dcrainmaker he made my decision for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like I was in that diversion for the accident near norsewood today. Pretty narrow roads. Gladly reverse traff… https://t.co/Nn1uQ7c8ZV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chris021 yeah. So only pool based, but it seems to get the lap count right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chris021 plus never take it off when I work around the house - lawns gardening washing cars rubbish removal. I'd say it's had a hard life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chris021 this vivoactive is still going strong. I run at least once a week, wear it all day everyday and swam with it for 6 months]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chris021 also it took an ant+ chest strap rather than always on heart Rate. Which was also my preference. Depends On Requirements]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chris021 yeah I've had the v1 vivoactive over a year now. Not as social as Fitbit, but had GPS and swimming at the time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chris021 Fitbit app for a vivioactive yes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@myleftkidney yeah that was the Hastings markets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@myleftkidney chilli shop https://t.co/lDOKY3QO4Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonpnz just make sure she doesn't put you in the corner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty good food https://t.co/L1nhyvjneY https://t.co/hQ7fSou6UW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ajobbins that's why we drink cheap bubbles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ajobbins twice this January.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ajobbins also I blame you and @TheJessjess This is my 3rd visit to Napier since your wedding]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ajobbins if I was a dirty 1%er it would be Cristal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheJessjess Ehatever. You don't need all that.  @not_friends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottjpalmer nah he's moved up hasn't he?  This would be his lindaur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This holidaying is thirsty work. https://t.co/rYjnN0Rp3O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbrislen @freitasm the question will be, and the outage can start, if it doesn't get put back up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbrislen @freitasm that was the impression I got. So it's not (at the moment) just the lgbt and climate stuff gone but everything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redjungle ha yeah.they need to make another nice building for people to take photos of]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was pretty nice out this morning https://t.co/ixL2OUEQBi https://t.co/p6g7l8uwh3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weirdly nice building...but with big save flags on it. https://t.co/aCIZ393WxV https://t.co/ySPfV6RNyE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottjpalmer I'm still waiting for the Microsoft surface or whatever they call it this week when you can pay at your table]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@plambrechtsen nah pulling stats from router via python.  Nothing I've got has snmp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grafana is a pretty cool toy to play with @plambrechtsen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@freitasm @paulbrislen haven't they removed everything that the Obama administration put in?  The question is what comes back.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>