<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[And their jokes get better, too https://t.co/UNxGbSwU25]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snacking options so dire I've resorted to a stale, novelty Monte Carlo. #grim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could so go for a scallop about now. https://t.co/eO74NyoJL9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rebekkap Every place I ever bought them from called them a scallop. As they should.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@workmanalice Had some good ones from the Watson takeaway over the break. Feeling lucky I got in early, now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rebekkap I just snacked on a peach. Do you have a special name for that, too?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rebekkap This is not an argument. Truths like this do not bend to your post-truth will.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rebekkap On the other hand, how many formative Australian hip-hop songs have used this cake of yours in the lyrics? https://t.co/mazssHBt3H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rebekkap PUH-lease - I speak it the way it's s'posed to be spoke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having the calories free turns the aftertaste from greasy regret to fatty happiness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no happiness like 'enough calories up my sleeve to eat a dirty potato scallop' happiness #happiness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amen. Particularly the looseness. https://t.co/qCoD1w1BtM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eating from your own garden does come with the excitement of the odd snail in the salad. For some. #missedout]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reginapritchard Kitchen Venom (I actually had to go and check...)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fresh Ruckus: Pool Deck Disco (If I Was Daniel Gabriel). Turns out it goes pretty well as Xmas baking music, too. https://t.co/LbjcvABTco]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing more British than queuing is writing about queuing https://t.co/shfPyNcG7X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas reading list 2016: that book that's been on my bedside table since I read the first few pages in July.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying Pool Deck Disco (If I Was Daniel Gabriel) by ♫ https://t.co/PCSGKVsVEs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshThomas87 That's just what happiness sounds like.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#hamberra - easily one of the best parts of the festive season.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Tis the season for... roast ham from The Trough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also: don't wreck things I like, please. Ta. https://t.co/cbGM5l5L59]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no right way or wrong way to read - unless you're an adult reading Fight Club as anything but satire.
https://t.co/3Vx62NYbF4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have never agreed with an article more. https://t.co/V5liX8C7Qj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cooneymj @andrew_porter @TheEconomist I'm overly determined to get a good night's sleep as often as possible, if that's what you're asking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrew_porter @TheEconomist Put decent downpayments on a heart attack, too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrew_porter @TheEconomist Not even the enjoyable way to put yourself at risk, either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm listening to Enter Sandman, wearing volleys and a plaid shirt - and drinking rosé. One thing has changed since 1997.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The connected little capital! https://t.co/2ajRKxqrxC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big congrats, @collectorwines. Well and truly deserved. https://t.co/oFerblF1Ng]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FUN FACT: The active substance that causes this is spermidine. https://t.co/Jghn4SMVXD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@collinsadam On the other hand, everyone will ooh and ahh about how young you look.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gary_Rake @4windsvineyard I got all mine. I'll split one with you, if you like.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't even know what scale to use to weigh up this news https://t.co/7cOpbfyeP0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fresh ruckus: I am more than ready for springtime proper to get here. ♫ https://t.co/UsHVFc7fzz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[October is far too late in the year to have to turn on the heater under the desk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lenoretaylor @guardian not taking on the tube is as British as apologising to other people when they bump you. No wonder they're shocked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok, CBR weather - I get it. I should have kept my winter beard another month. Can we move on from the false spring to the real now, please?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's one good lookin' bride, right there https://t.co/3hX5vH9z3r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't care if it's two days old, it's still great. Especially Grant. How Clinton can get that presidential look https://t.co/thdQoirXyl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the better things I've read on transparency in ages https://t.co/GnSTIAmCSw via @voxdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Truth.

Also noteworthy: @TheEconomist illustrating a story with Paris Hilton. https://t.co/eyANoCK1Zm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“People are not going to be able to tunnel because we are going to have tunnel technology.” https://t.co/VC0bdIN6NR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crossing the streams: how bad planning helped lead to the birth of hip-hop https://t.co/nVOyRb4Els via @thefader]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tech advances cut both ways: autonomous cars will cut gov revenue and costs at the same time https://t.co/izhHMxYBAe via @BrookingsInst]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@russellmahoney it's everyone's secret shame, that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those @BarackObama playlists are pretty good in winter, too, for that matter: https://t.co/wAkz3ZpZ2T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What makes a city cool? https://t.co/jYNV6kC0RW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Leroy_Lynch I think you can escape if you're aware of your own biases, especially your typical responses to different marketing styles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Leroy_Lynch It's a function of wider adoption, I think. It's what happens when a design style becomes the mainstream.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or: hipster taste is now seen as generally tasteful (for about a decade, IMO) https://t.co/3MzTtloJ20 via @verge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who will feed Britain after 'Brexit'? https://t.co/ik8loGyuJj Cheap French reds as central to the British experience as butter chicken, IMHO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrew_porter Silent, defeated English is pretty good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this tweet from 2006 or something?  https://t.co/Y02dmD9H0x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hil_clix_pix Surely he helps people smile, tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are certainly not enough rude place names in Australia https://t.co/u18LfuNtpy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A playlist for the other Grand Old Party: the Canberra house party. On spotify https://t.co/D7sCquVnnU and tumblr https://t.co/UlsuXdg0rm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has anyone got a flag count? #RNCinCLE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not good news: office 'cake culture' is a danger to health: https://t.co/sFayxbk3Qb Second-last para is excellent juxtaposition work, though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder what the budget for Making America Great Again is, exactly? #RNCinCLE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guess that means I better savor my remaining Pialligo smoked neck even more, then. https://t.co/luUzjFSheL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never never. 

With slippers, though... https://t.co/Im0LqJpKi5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpotifyCares Cheers for the quick reply. I’d still to register a plea to bring them back. It’s the feature I used most, after playing tunes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpotifyCares Team - I love notifications. I miss them every day. If there's any way you could bring them back, I'd appreciate it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This goes straight to the door of the fridge, next to the studies showing chocolate is good for you.  https://t.co/1ADIQpSxxm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best rickroll in ages #RNCinCLE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's that time: https://t.co/327OcFfwXk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The coolest little capital #CBR  https://t.co/1YTU9CRvFS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FJKeany Proper weather.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Late nights in the office are definitely best with Charles Bradley ♫ https://t.co/uxDb94jhLx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dudes: there's frost on the ground. If you're on your way to work and your heaviest layer is your shirt, you're doing it wrong #frosty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty much the only diet question worth asking. https://t.co/lr2hVuquVL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As always, science comes through for me in the end, @andrew_porter  https://t.co/jQHRfXggZQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Daly_CE I'm eternally vigilant. It's always the ones you least expect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Daly_CE People who don't drink decaf don't have this problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reginapritchard It just hits all the spots, really.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC Radio 4's Soul Music on 'Feed The Birds' is just perfect for a sick day - or any day: https://t.co/Pq6JGqWeM9 https://t.co/nwRGHhFX9p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fresh ruckus: So many hugs. It's Mop Tops all the way down. On Spotify https://t.co/KPJAj7b8zu and tumblr https://t.co/XoSfgg0rS3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two days. Two visits to Bernie's. Two reuben sandwiches. Too good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fresh ruckus: expectant nerves. On Tumblr:  https://t.co/muas6jMoRm
and spotify: https://t.co/0AiRg1Mxru Not about polls or politics at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The horror! https://t.co/LwnC52xxMO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lenoretaylor It's certainly a persistent one. A Lowy Poll in 2011 showed on average people thought it was 16%, and should be 12%.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tony_stower How is it that I have never heard this excellent and disturbing description before?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IMHO, riding in lycra is like wearing football boots: practical and appropriate in only the narrowest of circumstances.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How could I have never come across @PreferredMode before? Thanks, @CityLab.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hil_clix_pix @pialligoestate the only problem, that is, is that it pretty much spoils you for any other bacon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hil_clix_pix @pialligoestate The only or]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hil_clix_pix @pialligoestate Once you've tried it, you'll never look back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesmassola Holding hands is the best #teamhandhold]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@russellmahoney it's certainly my kind of place]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nah, we never get big crocs here", they all said.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It really was https://t.co/OxPzXNclSn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrseankelly Thanks, Sean. Now I have an iced vovo craving to go with my 'Suspicious Minds' earworm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@montymunford I'm holiday ATM, and saw a whole bunch of things sacred to a group of people today, so authentic tourism is close to heart RN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@montymunford I'm sure medieval pilgrims had a very different idea about how to authentically experience a cathedral than you or me, too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Londonist I would be there with bells on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#standingawkwardly at Cape Leveque. With a fish, and the spear I speared it with. And some very short shorts. https://t.co/rwXWCkTHKM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulBongiorno Some people do naughty things on the internet, too. We should probably just ban it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We should head back to the hovercraft" is definitely the coolest sentence I've said today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#standingawkardly in the Indian Ocean. For the first time ever. https://t.co/an9acNoCvk https://t.co/NYulCMlD8p]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>