<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Thousands of Londoners set to protest at Downing Street against refugee crackdown  https://t.co/MwY7leIz5M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful poem about my late and beloved agent David Miller @maxjohnporter in yesterday's @guardian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Saturday poem: Kneeling Shepherd i.m. David Millerl https://t.co/CIZRjr6vAR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Skeleton offers clues to medieval spread of leprosy https://t.co/d0fu4Q3HMF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greek court to decide on fate of eight Turkish soldiers | World news | The Guardian https://t.co/nlMZEBSYnk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kind of @aegeanairlines to give its passengers New Year cake BUT they have lost my luggage. I am VERY cold and furious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brookfieldgirl I agree. Wonderful person and very sad he has gone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Christmas. Just settling down to read The Optician of Lampedusa.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Victoria Hislop’s “Cartes Postales” from Greece - Greece Is https://t.co/JQu1gqkXI6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Incredible evening at Dingwalls with LP @iamlp - unique talent and voice. Just felt SO lucky to be there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BloomsburyBooks @WHSmith oops don't tell the children - this is all they are getting. Who needs more than Dickens with fur?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Policeman’s tribute to young victim of Moria migrant camp fire | Community | https://t.co/VYbhX3OuFc https://t.co/goMJ0sYA3N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mark Rylance is mesmerising in his own @NiceFishThePlay -huge charm and depth. Truly joyful evening. https://t.co/Oj3iyREhzl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Helenus_ @simpsontravel congratulations!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@athina_kamila thanks - it can get a lot better though. Θα συνεχίσω]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Final carte postale from my November travels around Greece. Sun shining in Syntagma Square. https://t.co/RByUClWZEy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Final carte postale for the day, the Rio-Antirrio bridge near Patra. Maybe the most beautiful in the world. https://t.co/4dMTFGDVmh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And another carte postale - from Messolonghi https://t.co/DmufDDwDmo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's carte postale from Messolonghi - the lagoon https://t.co/3ivUpQEYvA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And serene beauty also in the perfect, small museum of Agrinio https://t.co/C5TZ7fK1Fi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carte postale from Agrinio - very sexy pose from Hellenistic period https://t.co/UQJlsH3AD0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sunset carte postale from Kalamata, a place that's very hard to leave. https://t.co/JBo61m1xlv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@appistol but with such fridge magnets?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carte postale of Kalamata. Warm sea today, a perfect swim. https://t.co/GyvbBFiJ97]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Philosophy in a Peloponnese service station. Only in Greece... https://t.co/IAsqPb7txH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's carte postale - Kavala in North Greece. How can the sky be so blue in November? https://t.co/183DpNaXAt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is my "giorti" in Greece and what better place to celebrate than in Serres https://t.co/m49s7Zf6UY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's carte postale from Greece: a dancer thousands of years old in Amphipoli Museum https://t.co/Qi24VEvGxf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@friderikimar this is so lovely to hear! Very glad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perfect morning in Thessaloniki - top carte postale https://t.co/SsTnuImUOy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's carte postale from Greece... Beautiful Thessaloniki https://t.co/DeRQxlX5Df]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An American Tragedy - The New Yorker https://t.co/Zbj5tQ1b0k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carte Postale of Palamidi Fortress, Nafplio. Beautiful and historic city. https://t.co/956Ma59lQc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carte Postale of the day - beautiful Nafplion https://t.co/6Nh2gbaVkU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carte Postale from Greece - an ancient jockey in the National Archaeological Museum in Athens https://t.co/3aMJAymTqW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AngelaKettlety thank you! Cartes Postales from Greece is out now! Hope you like it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GreekNotesRU hoping too! Will keep Twitter informed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Antinous in the Archaeological Museum Athens. Today's postcard from Greece. https://t.co/OzvES8ymMs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's carte postale from Greece. "Ochi Day" in Syntagma. https://t.co/BlMFEzht2m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhichPennySmith of course! Going on book tour odyssey in Greece and after that - theatre with ps..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhichPennySmith you are so cheeky :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Οι Καρτ Ποστάλ (cartes postales)publication day in Greece!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's carte postale from Greece. Lemons fighting for space on my tree https://t.co/diSud5s1VS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's carte postale from Greece. So many shades of blue... https://t.co/263JT34ZNU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's "Carte Postale" from Greece. The sky really is this colour at the end of October. https://t.co/Dr27Ec6m6m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to it all! https://t.co/s6tBz3iXDT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very exciting - Bon voyage https://t.co/7fQstzVDAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HailoLondon charged today for a non-existent journey!! And can't contact you! This is fraud!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 1980s: Anatomy of a watershed era | Life | https://t.co/VYbhX3OuFc excited about seeing this https://t.co/aXo06W6mI6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very happy!! Thanks so much x https://t.co/OicGkUwM7p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[V happy to be in window of @TheLondonLib! And close to Nutshell - work of genius https://t.co/3xBu3LOYj5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Postcard of the day: pomegranates in Greece. A warm 30c there on Sunday. https://t.co/3LDQ9fMKYe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very thrilled by today's Times chart https://t.co/vRL2h11zKS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrowsersBks @WHManor @CatherineLarner thanks for great afternoon! Much enjoyed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hollymillward have a great holiday!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JerseyWordFest @JsyArtsCentre lovely evening. Thanks so much for having me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@prioritypasscom Ruth's manner was staggeringly rude and aggressive - you should know this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@prioritypasscom I am a travel journalist for mail and times but nobody should face such rudeness - I was shocked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@prioritypasscom premium lounge - rudely refused entry by Ruth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joyless afternoon @prioritypasscom lounges at Gatwick north. Miserable and rude staff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@prioritypasscom unspeakable rudeness and lack of hospitality from your staff at GatwickN today! Speechless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited to see this at Gatwick @WHSmith https://t.co/J0RGLl5CTa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SuTims amazing!! I really want this story to be told]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insider’s Athens — where the locals hang out | Travel | The Times &amp; The Sunday Times https://t.co/hNmFyzVLTm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the Gaffer's office in beautiful @blackwelloxford signing #Cartes Postales https://t.co/iUUHKBPo15]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About to speak @ToppingsEly for #CartesPostales https://t.co/W6ok8ZlQVf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wendy_Holden @headlinepg @HodderFiction @JOJEHARVEY @panmacmillan thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovely evening @CWBookshop meeting readers - thank you so much https://t.co/g3qpmJrxDi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrindleMary he returned today!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@standardnews colin the cat came back - thanks for support]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colin has returned! Thanks for kind words and support!! https://t.co/ohtUl0UR6O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrindleMary thank you. V v attached to him...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Morning spent scouring the streets of Sw3 for Colin the long-haired tabby cat. Still no sign.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[En route to Headline warehouse to sign copies of #Cartes Postales]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annesebba @BBCWomansHour thanks Anne - hope you are well xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vasouli_85 wow. Thanks so much!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colin is awol somewhere in SW3 but normally commutes between his bowl and sofa. House seems empty. Come back Colin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colin the cat has gone missing. If anyone sees him, please contact... https://t.co/TsWHMMXy4G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterc45 missing you too! Back in london two days ago.. :-(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Final "carte postale" of the summer. Agios Nikolaos reminding me a little of Venice. https://t.co/qRVMziaHv9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicola_chandler they are rare! Wish more people could see the tv series of the island!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greek volunteers share UN refugee award | Community | https://t.co/VYbhX3OuFc https://t.co/SETqDewRQC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's "carte postale" from Greece https://t.co/sTkwo9wwiz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aris Messinis: Lesbos migrant crisis photos win French award https://t.co/mx49hugBZR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterc45 so glad! Next stop Thessaloniki!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EleanorFitz so glad to hear this!! Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@olops all fictional except leprosy therapy and dateline.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TracyShephard @Bookywookydooda I am glad and hope happiness drops by again soon. Meanwhile books books books...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AngelaAddington gorgeous picture!!! Next stop Thessaloniki!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's "Carte Postale" from Greece https://t.co/WEmyfZWHj7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pig_witch thank you!! I am glad. The Sunrise is set in Cyprus so you might enjoy that too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nickywallace21  thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very happy to be next to @JRhodesPianist - superstar and dear friend. And will do my best James!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CharlieCox_11 thank you!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dinamedland thank you so much!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daizycrazy thank you so much]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlpinoBookClub start with the island and then the thread. Hope you enjoy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK and Australian citizen Scott Richardson held in Dubai https://t.co/G76WcnVhvT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bobo62 yes! Well guessed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClairePepper thank you!!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>