<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@laurabaker1D what type of job are you looking for?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nxtivetxngue we could either stay at my uncles or tom's (you know the one from ages ago?)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nxtivetxngue lets go, i'll be at home then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmilyyMayy1996 is that juniors or women's? and i think they go up in price with their increase in popularity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmilyyMayy1996 foot asylum, down here.. how much are they?ðŸ˜¬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmilyyMayy1996 i know someone that could probably get you 20% off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[everything has to happen all at once]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jiaregreg they'll probably make you pay for the full price ticket there and then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jiaregreg when you're asked to show your ticket on the train, they'll also ask to see your railcardðŸ‘ŠðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[that is not ok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out what I'm selling on my @depop shop ðŸ’¸ https://t.co/HEln2RH0Vl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mxrganmc teach me your ways!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[follow my insta ~ taramarieallen https://t.co/snagX0Q4di]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nxtivetxngue isn't that closer to wolverhampton?ðŸ˜¬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i'm still struggling to sleep in my single bed after being home almost a week]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmilyyMayy1996 we were horrible people...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[happy birthday to me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nxtivetxngue others offer different deals but try Santander?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nxtivetxngue Santander; they offer free railcards. there's no rush for a student account unless you think you'll need extra money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@voodoodollsz boots in Northampton now have a nyx counter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nxtivetxngue if only my relationships were as 10/10 as this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nxtivetxngue #relationshipgoals #iwannabeyou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[getting drunk on my own lol go me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@racheljohn25 don't mind my singingðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shannonalexlata hopefully you get an answer soon, it's horrible not knowing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shannonalexlata have you been to a specialist? it might be a benign cyst x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[don't wanna work tomorrow, don't know why i agreed to this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the wifi here is terrible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hate long train journeys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarcyme there's toilets on the train you know...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it makes me mad when guys think it's ok to continuously touch girls in clubs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[don't understand how people can live in filth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nxtivetxngue but still a little bit funny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmilyyMayy1996 couldn't agree more, that's all I ever do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nxtivetxngue I read horoscopes, just don't watch YouTube videos on it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nxtivetxngue where did you get this from?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmyLStockwell as much as an ear lobe piercing apart your eyes might water]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[not looking forward to this 12 hour shift on no sleep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cheryl_fyfield if he's anything like mine, he'll ask "is it ok if I weigh you?" ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[northampton tinder game is weak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a free woman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[on a caffeine and sleep deprivation high, all i wanna do is dance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[after I go through all the meat in my freezer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm really considering going vegetarian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[can't find the motivation for this essay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@D33_GURL let me know when you're free and we can arrange something]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[taxi drivers are a piss take]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[third wheeling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so happy to have a working phone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarcyme it's horrible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[great, i now have no phone for the next two weeks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my sleeping pattern is well and truly non existent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nxtivetxngue preach it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[on the verge of giving up with this assignment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hopefully santa can bring me a new phone this year, in desperate need]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it's so difficult being a girl sometimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so excited/nervous for this weekend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[halloween is my favourite holiday ðŸŽƒðŸ‘»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[watching hocus pocus to get into the halloween spirit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@courtneyellene that's not fair ðŸ˜ª]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@courtneyellene I didn't think uni had half term?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmilyyMayy1996 aren't you gonna try it on? ðŸ˜’]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmilyyMayy1996 wheres my pic?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[im such a jealous person]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[can't believe i dressed up as an oompa loompa tonight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[need to go to london soon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nxtivetxngue it's a month wednesday and it still doesn't feel real]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i can do a lot better than you, and im slowly coming to terms with that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[is commitment too much to ask for?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[don't know how im gonna get up tomorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmilyyMayy1996 what's up?ðŸ˜ª]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarcyme thank you ðŸ’˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it's move in day, bring on cardiff !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[im sober after a weird night out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[that was a complete waste of time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hsbc have screwed everyone over]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it's pay day but i haven't been paid??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[all i've done this summer is put on weight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i would rather be back in bed in this weather]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@D33_GURL but u wear tiny heels?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[not looking forward to a six hour coach journey after last night]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if only you could move on and get on with your own life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[not been gone more than two days and i wanna go home]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i need to stop buying shoes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[not in the mood for going away]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[going to ireland alone in the morning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[had enough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i never leave the house anymore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[driving lesson soon but no money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i need to stop having evening naps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[onwards and upwards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[most people are finished with college, im still struggling to complete everything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarcyme and that of course, when do you go?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarcyme think of the money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[despise two faced people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[cant wait until college is over and done with]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[being productive instead of sleeping]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grandmadeath_ happy birthday lovely x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[a bit of retail therapy should cheer me up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[easily distracted]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>