<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrick478 that chest hair though!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrick478 thought it looked familiar https://t.co/lFjwqbrYzn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheAMShowNZ @DuncanGarnerNZ @TV3nz @RadioLIVENZ except for the bits where Mark Richardson speaks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grantrobertson1 sorry for the unpleasantly addressed letter you got. It reminded me of this tweet, so I guess it c… https://t.co/PXafakvwEP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls he's not the boss on the apprentice anymore. Do you realise him talking about it makes the story 10… https://t.co/YAKbipxBLQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GovPenceIN perhaps tell that to your boss. Or did you sell your spine to become Vice @POTUS ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good Piers, I wondered if your moral compass had wandered off, it's still there on a long leish. https://t.co/3Fj30Y16Wb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shaun47 @GaryLineker perhaps you could start with explaining why, Shaun. Can't Gary have an opinion outside football? You seem to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haha, can you imagine the tantrum he'd have? https://t.co/RV3XxxbS0o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@POTUS have you practiced being a terrible human, or does it come naturally?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Yakcall also @PeterDunneMP has won that electorate for 30 odd years, even when he's declared support to National pre-election.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrick478 FIFA think it's OK to play a world cup in the desert.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tea brewed, tennis on, let's roll back the clock #federervsnadal https://t.co/k1ZEed0s2j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SargeantxMelone @AJemaineClement @slightlypunky @LadyHellsBells @PressSec like what?  Building walls?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@POTUS @realDonaldTrump how did it work for the Berliners?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump how many abortions have you paid women to have?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DuncanGarnerNZ so you only have a good time if you drink alcohol? People who believe that "killed the event".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jamming at the gardens again. @ Sound Shell Botanical Gardens https://t.co/WA9BUJXLF0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CanURefuze Why is it a dirty word? Genuinely curious, not trolling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CanURefuze curious to get to the bottom of this hate of socialism. Public roads, police &amp;fire dept, even military, based on socialst policy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls @EW @people people stop to look at car accidents too...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls @PressSec @TheRightScoop hit back with "alternative facts" AKA "shit we made up".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrick478 great! Ive lost count of number of people who think me &amp; CKW are the same person. Even ppl at my wedding thought we were related]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrick478 also, just wanted to check that you're continuing a standing joke and you know that it's not me in the pic? :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ksorbs come to NZ, check out our free healthcare, public schools and average taxes of less than 30% not as scary as you might think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ksorbs @JohnCleese make sure you don't drive on any public roads, that socialism might infect you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrick478 if that makes him think twice about bringing his kids, then that impacts crowd numbers. His point is worth listening to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrick478 when you've got a bunch of largely adults, chanting like that,  kids will think it's OK and copy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrick478 2/2 as acceptable and the abuse that referees have to put up with.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrick478 1/2 I think you're scapegoating on the label he's chosen. There's a direct correlation between chanting like that being seen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrick478 I got along to 70% of matches first 4-5 seasons, stood in YF, that chant &amp; with "fuck 'em up..." made being part uncomfortable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrick478 ah come on, you don't think being called our for unreasonable chants is fair enough?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZNationalParty @RtHon_JohnKey get on with it, the Aussies beat us to this years ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottbstyris @Sdoull crowd definitely helped by price today. Was never going to pay $35 for a single day vs low ranked team.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WgtnCC any news yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gingereejit @koruandthistle and they did same day turn around.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gingereejit @koruandthistle I went to a place on vivian st and it cost be 1/3 of the quote I got from the grand arcade people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WgtnCC the weather looks a big 50-50 out my way. What time will you make a call on tonight's soundshell concert?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Yakcall always fun to watch someone else get yelled at ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Yakcall definitely. I'd been keen for that though. Couple of matches after work a week, higher disbursement and a free weekend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Yakcall and I understand they have a lot more higher quality football on week nights or so I've heard...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Yakcall also, in Auz, refs are paid significantly more than what we get here in Wellington and the Central League.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Yakcall I was on the junior committee at NW around 10 years ago when subs went to 100 per kid. Mine as a cap6 player were around 200]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrick478 yeah, don't think for a minute he meant to cause harm, but tackler has to be responsible for the speed/force when it goes wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrick478 also, Twitter wouldn't be a thing without emotion, so go nuts!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrick478 I just saw it and it looks exactly like the FIFA red card tackle coaching videos.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrick478 I saw the gif of that, doesn't look great. Still happy with the red. If I gave red and saw the replay, I'd be happy I caught it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrick478 when a player is running that fast, there can't not be high force, if that kind of tackle catches a standing leg it breaks it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrick478 studs showing, high speed, plenty of force, foot up off the ground, almost over ball height. I'm seeing lots of red boxes ticked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrick478 phwoah! I've not watched anything but the highlights of the goals and the red card. It looks pretty straightforward red to me...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a kiwi I loved to hate @ShaneWarne the player. But as a commentator I love how he doesn't hold back. Tells it how it is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/NW1BPb80cS always time for a first - I actually agree with @TrevorMallard on something!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzherald Lance Armstrong "won" his first Tour de France in 1999 not 1998. https://t.co/ZT9yltPato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gjaywilkinson @punkrockredshoe I assumed you'd done a joint run for the team at some point and you'd have knocked it on the head.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gjaywilkinson @punkrockredshoe I can't belive it's taken seven years living together, to notice what was happening right in front of me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gjaywilkinson just realised @punkrockredshoe puts milk in tea while teabag is still in cup Need an englishman to tell her I'm right on this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vodafoneNZ my Mum waited all afternoon for someone to show and they didn't. Call centre were without any information or explanation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vodafoneNZ my grandmother has spent weekend without Internet &amp;TV. Ur tech missed deadline without explanation. No answers from call cntre.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gjaywilkinson is that Don King sitting in front of you to the left? ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gjaywilkinson get us a photo of #Zlatan  banging the goals in? 
@Ibra_official]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan you should stick to picking your sore nose.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan it's karma for all your whining. The irony is, your biggest fear is, they might actually win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get this off me Hooman!
#xmascat #catsofinstagram https://t.co/cbIq7qiXlv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@punkrockredshoe you'll appreciate this https://t.co/qDmmgkQpJO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcjnicholas should be extradited and charged with treason for the amount of love he shows for @CricketAus players!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@metlinkwgtn nice to have your staff hollering at passengers to get on the train as if there's some fear that you might be on time this week]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DevlinLive I don't think I've seen such poor fielding and bowling from @BLACKCAPS in repeat performances for a long time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrick478 how'd he get out? I had an ill timed @SKYNZ crap out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DuncanGarnerNZ English as leader makes the next general election a contest, with Key they were a shoe in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is as satisfying as watching a mouthy boxer get smacked, except he's a fat attention seeking chump called… https://t.co/gWGUIAzUAW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BLACKCAPS just going through the motions is like rolling back to NZ mid 90s At least it's nostalgic. I've less hope than @DevlinLive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@honbillenglish you need to demonstrate  what's different about you from the disaster the last time you lead. Stick to the numbers IMHO.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrick478 they are, just for the newspaper though, not the sport.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@metlinkwgtn when will the Kapiti trains be back to running at normal speed through the tunnels?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone else worried that @JimmyNeesh is batting at 4? He's good, but I think the order is short if he's at 4 #ausvnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timomouse @gingereejit the logic seems to ignore Mourhino won the champions league with Porto...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gjaywilkinson where TF have you gone? We gonna head home soon...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/JGxaclpzw1 is there a point where the road crosses the train tracks there? @NZStuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EQ has meant work at north end of lambton quay.  Was on MP watch, saw @DavidShearerMP @DavidParkerMP @DavidCunliffeMP @PeterDunneMP  +others]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's give these @Allbirds shoes a go... https://t.co/QYjvSoYFP6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/W7lkOagWRr? @simonjbridges what a joke. MPs wasted Q&amp;A on readily available info, rather than get insight from industry leader]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didn't realise that was his name. Kind like a joke, what do you call Gareth Barry if he's playing cricket? https://t.co/njZLvKfww3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan @DailyMail you're a well practiced sore loser,  so very qualified to comment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm no fan of @LewisHamilton but talk of punishment is madness. Had one way to win the championship &amp; should be credited for doing that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan ah the good ol' "let's do something stupid, just to teach 'em a lesson".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrick478 I've been buying loads of avacados now that they're vaguely affordable. This one needed to be eaten!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekends are about tasty breakfast and good coffee! https://t.co/Xv3AYDiRkS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonathanYoungMP u had chance to learn from innovative industry leader, instead wasted time on pointless Q&amp;A on readily available info.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonathanYoungMP @AScottWairarapa @suemoroney once again, you seem to miss the point...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SGMNZ @springloadnz *their]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SGMNZ unlikely to be back next week. Luckily @springloadnz have been letting us hangout in there hood.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They need a tew-hundred-and-tewenty-tew cent coin! https://t.co/zF9DzOaqB1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SGMNZ I'm going out of my mind! And I think the cat is sick of listening to me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Yakcall its alright I've seen a certain RDO pack away a fair bit of K-Fry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Yakcall @kfcnz fitness tests getting too easy these days? Need to sandbag? ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MPs getting hung up on pointless detail after they haven't taken time to Google "what is uber" @AScottWairarapa @suemoroney @JonathanYoungMP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/P2qxzdPVd2 we need to start electing more digital native MPs this lot are proving they're out of touch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan top 16 is success when your manager is "not a winner" isn't it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Yakcall nothing quite like the job of copping someone else's abuse for them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KP24 you should remind your buddy @piersmorgan]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>