<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Come work with me at @EHFNewZealand! Bringing visionary entrepreneurs to NZ with the new #GlobalImpactVisa https://t.co/jn0oCnWU0j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be waxing lyrical with poetic storytelling at Speaking With Purpose in March, in #Wellington. #SWP17 Get tix!… https://t.co/W6StmdNIwt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Morena @Allbirds! What are your current shipping times? Arrive by end of week on Waiheke if ordered today?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not true at all. Africans Americans and Hispanics voted for him in much higher numbers than Romney or other re… https://t.co/KK64YjEPaz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time for some pleasant distraction from the world. Yeaaaahh!! #AllTalkWithAnikaMoa #AnikaMoa https://t.co/KOfDVRjAbx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@four_seven Would have saved getting up at 6am right...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JadRahme And no finger prints on your screen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[very cool! I still get a little bit excited when I see Billie or any of the @HipOpCrew on the Waiheke ferry. Lookin… https://t.co/VsBA76wAfJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A belated congratulations to you @justin_lester - Stoked that you're leading the helm for #Wellington for the next three years!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rest easy Helen Kelly, you deserve it after serving NZ above and beyond the call of duty. Love to friends/family https://t.co/yuOGR1ajxy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @EmilyFatu! If only I was as good at Twittering as poeting...  @JennyKayNZ @OSOSNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @WLGAirport - are you seriously not allowing @Uber_NZ drivers to pickup from airport? So my Uber driver tells me #walkingOutTheGates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This makes me very happy. https://t.co/Dv4ruVpTuF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uganda does worse than just imprison gays @RobertGlennieNZ - Question becomes where is balance between fighting the fight, and surviving?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wrote an article on @Medium - Gay or Nay in Vietnam? What happens when Pride and Pragmatism collide? #travel #LGBT https://t.co/yrEcY6DeOe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just published “Gay or Nay in Vietnam? When Pride and Pragmatism Collide” https://t.co/rgxA0Z95rU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In related news, PM John Key refusing to say that the ocean is wet. "I'm not sure, I haven't been swimming recently" https://t.co/0KxmHosOPg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proud of our team! Finalists in the Green Gold category of Wellington @GoldAwards https://t.co/SRoArEFmVn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is pure gold! Can't wait to see the video!  https://t.co/5A8ssCgETT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On of her many talents... this is a great talk Melissa!  https://t.co/ZygSiLKJBv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The part of you that is unresolved is the most powerful part of your story - Michael Margolis @getstoried #storytelling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@where_is_anna filling up quickly but there's still a bit of room in back, sure you could sneak in quietly. #LLXX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Our slightly tipsy idea has turned into a meaningful movement for kindness" @GoodBitchesBake, changing world one cake at a time #TEDxWelly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this how sitcoms build canned laughter?? Michael Armstongs social experiment at #TEDxWelly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best quote of #TEDxWelly so far: "Work doesn't work, without play". @shondarhimes beaming in on video, on life's hum, on playing with kids.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving @charlesbabb's #TEDxWelly talk on diversity in video games. We need this so badly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you look up for three weeks, it is very hard to remain closed" - such true words from @JavaDanceCo #TEDxWelly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Random picture, at the request of @sarb #TEDxWelly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This bus ride is either like a really exciting school field trip.... Or the start of a horror movie. #TEDxWelly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where are these red double decker buses taking me?? I don't know... #TEDxWelly https://t.co/oASIrRdWWA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DSelitskiy @kiwiconnectnz thank you for coming along! Great to have your voice today :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glbt4trump If you think Hilary has taken the community for granted, surely #FeelTheBern would be the logical alternative to support?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glbt4trump I'm trying to understand how one minority group can support a person who so openly hates upon other minorities?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glbt4trump Well absolutely she has taken us for granted. But why would you support someone who is so driven by hate and bigotry?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't decide if @glbt4trump is a joke Twitter account or not... Acceptance needs to be universal: race &amp; religion as well as sexuality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$4.5mil from NZ govt to Syria... meanwhile $450mil spent on outfitting EACH of our navy ships. @maidaborn - we can do so much more for Syria]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessicaManins @msbananapeel Aaaw thanks you two :) #Wellington's not short of inspiring women!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @msbananapeel :) I had a great time performing it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks Jonny - Tickets still available for tonight, and just a handful left for tomorrow! https://t.co/LsZAuobir7 https://t.co/LzG7e0CLYP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thx @where_is_anna I'll perform my wee heart out just for you! (And everyone else who participates in best Mon ever) https://t.co/4634Oowp6d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One down, three to go... Get in quick for tickets to #JaggedLittlePilgrimage tonight/tomorrow. Weds almost sold out! https://t.co/LsZAuobir7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do you call an ironic situation that's not actually all that #ironic? Find out at my @NZFringe show! #Alanis
https://t.co/LsZAuobir7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tickets are SOLD OUT for opening night of #JaggedLittlePilgrimage, get in quick! #Alanis @BATS_Theatre @NZFringe https://t.co/LsZAuobir7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be chatting with @RadioActivefm in 20 minutes about my upcoming 
@NZFringe show #JaggedLittlePilgrimage . Tune in on 88.6fm or online]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks Rogue &amp; Vagabond team standing against gender-based violence. #ReturnOfKings not welcome in #Wellington https://t.co/tVCvid4UHl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tedxwellington thanks, keep us posted please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justadandak WTF man. I watched the clock tick down 3,2,1... Click buy tickets.... Nope. Disappointing :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tedxwellington Ahhh... no. I think you'll find they're sold out. At least that's what Eventfinda is telling me. Sold out before on sale...?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @justadandak Is Eventfinda telling me what I think Eventfinda is telling me??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @where_is_anna! Come see some #IronicShituations at my @NZFringe show @BATS_Theatre https://t.co/LsZAuobir7 https://t.co/9VkiQZQH8c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Related: Famed Australian white whale @Migaloo1 has a Twitter account.  https://t.co/ha79UCyENY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’ll be on Access Radio in twenty minutes talking about my upcoming @NZFringe show. Tune in online! @BATS_Theatre https://t.co/FFTpQvphb6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Win a double-pass to my Alanis Morissette-themed @NZFringe show, Jagged Little Pilgrimage! Details on this post...
https://t.co/rMnM0eT8TE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BATS_Theatre Come to the show, for a good ole dose of nostalgia! And questionable co-opting...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My @NZFringe show is getting close! Tix for #JaggedLittlePilgrimage avail at @BATS_Theatre. 14-17 Feb, 6.30pm. https://t.co/BW3M9OrvBn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't believe the hype #ThankGodForThis https://t.co/IfV1u6cLRu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@where_is_anna *Goes immediately there to find out if my name was one of those deleted...*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're glad to have you on our shores @katetempest, can't wait to see you tonight. We should swap poems in back alley after ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zenpeacekeeper A good antidote to it, which I read to balance the universe, is Ishmael by Daniel Quin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zenpeacekeeper I read this one too over the hols. It is indeed terrifying. I think of it every time I post on social media.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fastercamels Good to know thanks. Comedy gigs have been hard work in past with spoken word. But open to it in future, I love Moon!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fastercamels Hey Jonny, just saw this now. Not sure the show poems would fit comedy crowd, there is humour in there, but mixed with serious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So cool @Alanis taking over @guardian's advice column. I'm doing a show in @NZFringe on the advice I've taken from JLP over past 20 years :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Alanis Yes! - more feminine, valuing balance. @ceisenstein would be a great podcast guest to dive deep on this. #ConversationWithAlanis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gerardoperry @Alanis How can you possibly separate the two? Music without authenticity is killing music industry. #ConversationWithAlanis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Alanis How can we encourage vulnerability and real-ness into business lives? Some workplaces more open than others #ConversationWithAlanis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Alanis How can we encourage vulnerability and real-ness into business lives? Some workplaces more open than others #ConversationsWithAlanis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great night out with @where_is_anna @SianSimpson @SavIsSavvy and @ashalhashim last night! @Silicon_Val even made a star appearance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am so freakin' stoked for #Canada today. Finally the topple of the ice-blue-baby-eyed-killer-of-all-things-good. #Trudeau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WhyWellington? Because pretty flowers grow out of the footpath by @embassytheatre #Wellington #GreenCity http://t.co/gFacI6FsyB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BountingNathan @Alanis @iTunesPodcasts I think we can safely award a giant #Fail on trying not to sound rude there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @JessicaManins! There's always room for more insights. Love to hear your highlights from the day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessicaManins @nataliaalbert @where_is_anna @KristenLunman Yes! I'll be there with bells on. Or feathers. Or something. #IdiomProblems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nataliaalbert @JessicaManins @where_is_anna @KristenLunman I could do Monday or Weds next week, but other days no good. Love this idea!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That moment when @B_Faumuina retweets your @Idealog article. Yep, that just happened. Kia ora Queen B!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[woohoo! I made my publishing debut on @idealogmag on failure, assumptions &amp; ethics in #lean #startup-land. http://t.co/KTCuzncs1h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who's been thinking about joining @Uber in NZ? Hit me up for free ride codes! Value reduces after 30 Oct from $25 to $10, now is the time!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And also "Flight to the Next World" by Yakush Project @NorthwardsDS. Incredible tune, next-world design material. #DesignersPlaylist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If story designers count too @NorthwardsDS, I'm suggesting any uplifting progressive house #DesignersPlaylist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anything by @rhiansheehan is amazing for deep concentration esp #StoriesFromElsewhere @PalairetNathan @NorthwardsDS #DesignersPlaylist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Justin_Wilcox @lightyouonfire Thx for taking on board my concerns today. As I said, difference btwn sharing w 1 person vs 150 is key.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cwodtke @Justin_Wilcox Thx I plan to. But not within next hour or 2. cool down period necessary. Generally love the live startup build idea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cwodtke @Justin_Wilcox As far as we know he wrote the (very unclear) Customer Discovery Ninja request in front of us. #supercharge #lean15]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdNZ Yeah, I'm not too sure eh? Where's the line?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone interested in an #ethics discussion about that phone call @justin_wilcox just conducted? #Supercharge #Lean15 #UnsureAboutThat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So we did @nataliaalbert! Huge thankyous to @kcolbin and @TEDxChCh for providing the space to connect. Was also start of new career for me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am so sad to be missing #TEDxChCh today!  @nataliaalbert @TEDChCh  :( Hope ya'll are having an incredible day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@obmmusic Was awesome. Quite the lesson in Aussie hip hop as well!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished #HereComeTheDogs today @obmmusic - Brilliant story! so great to read real, raw stuff from this end of the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@where_is_anna Don't we all...? Except @_jjw_ - He wants a goat. The world wants ponies and Jackson wants a goat. Go figure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@where_is_anna "You said there would be a pony. Where the #*&amp;$ is my pony??"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rowsell (FYI - Al's Diner on Upper Queen Street is the only place I know in NZ that serves caesars, if you've caught the bug)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rowsell Tomato and clam make a pretty good combo, don't you think? Bacon is the added bonus!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@builtinwgtn @kiwiconnectnz @extraord_tales @tashmahal Thanks! Tash pulled off something pretty extraordinary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nataliaalbert Sure... why not :) Two tweets for the price of one...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sustaincoasts Ban them like California. Or make them prohibitively expensive. It won't take long for people to start bringing their own]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nataliaalbert @kiwiconnectnz Thanks lady! My name is without a "k" though ;) Loving the new photoshoot pics!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nevarware If you're an engineer then you know better than anyone that characters matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WaterPuppetry Yep life is great. Have jumped from water to social enterprise / tech startup space. Loving it ! nice to be back in NZ :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WaterPuppetry Hey! Long time no see, hope you're still repping Canadian water leaders, doing the good stuff :)]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>