<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The most incredible snow crash of all time  https://t.co/uCXkeTzYcf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UBC FYI: I couldn't make it in from North Van. Capilaino Rd is at a stand sill all the way up to Montroyal. Many students with same issue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why I'm at UBC becoming a #cleanenergy engineer https://t.co/9oS1EPn6e2 I cant watch this shit happen and do nothing... #NoKeystoneXL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future of #renewables is not decided in the White House, it is decided by #energy markets https://t.co/bDGcfHk7LX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scream I am finally in BC for a summer and booked July weekend @PacificRimNPR with @msmithdesignuk!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ohhhhh we will just slot right into that wild card spot! Go @Canucks Go!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Early morning #engineering @ubcengineering https://t.co/VbJG3AGaWT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best. https://t.co/du8k1TGe2Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just pledged to The Happy Hero by @GreenSolitaire! https://t.co/gSuima6O62 via @unbounders - real excited for you!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pan-Canadian Framework on #CleanEnergy Growth and #ClimateChange following the First Ministers’ Meeting https://t.co/fzFEqUfbTb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Super Salmon is the BEST film I have seen @BanffMtnFest - @SalmonNoBorders what an inspiration to stand up for what is right for nature!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BanffMtnFest this year's films were so great! #3yearsgoing with @msmithdesignuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/RhhlYmLwYA Canada Top Searches 2016
Canadian Dollar
NHL
Blue Jays
Trump
Trudeau
Rio 2016
Game of Thrones
Euro 2016
Clinton
Dion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Impressive #sustainable city in states: https://t.co/y3eJv0DesE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've joined DAWEG to help promote #WomenInEngineering! Come join me at a networking event in Van on the 6th December https://t.co/75NTkAUkJv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#thefourthphase @TravRice is amazing #itssnowtime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh man! The Jamaican bobsled team's van breaks down and Calgarians take them to the qualifier! https://t.co/42IiBB0Paz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alpha female by @WildBeasts is what I need.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fact: The latest #JungleBook is an epic movie. @TheJungleBook]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016 has been such a bonkers year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HSBC_UK_Help Hi there, can you call me please? This is in regards to being sent someone else's card. My number is in the email I sent you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HSBC_UK_Help I'm glad you got the email. As I said in the email I am available 5pm UK time in Tuesday. I am away until Monday evening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HSBC_UK_Help I sent it right after you gave me the email ukhelp@hsbc.com. I've resent it now, as well as sent it from another account.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HSBC_UK_Help OK thanks. I have sent you the information. Please let me know if you have gotten the email asap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HSBC_UK_Help Can you call me? I have called you twice already and it costs a lot of money. This is not my fault what has happened.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HSBC_UK_Help Yes, I called last week. The Islington branch manager was suppose to mail it to me in Canada. He sent me the wrong card.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@HSBC_UK I have been waiting a month for a bank card. One came in the mail today. You shipped me a card with SOMEONE ELSE'S NAME ON IT!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All Canadian federal government buildings will source their electricity from #renewableenergy sources within 8 yrs https://t.co/mwUswi7xAq…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A step in the right direction https://t.co/lLeCjBQsCW #renewables]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Students asked for this! #solar #forwardthinking #comesfromthekids https://t.co/OhzhoyoqQC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#solarenergy fundamentals for success: bring down cost of installed systems, manage cost of capital &amp; improve ops https://t.co/naMWk4rr9E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THIS IS AWESOME. On Monday women in Iceland left work 14% early, equivalent to the gender pay gap. https://t.co/QLJhL306Pk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have never made a plan longer than a year and never will because of exactly this... https://t.co/TaFggt9ruc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoa #fusionenergy temp and pressure record broken @MIT https://t.co/9eziCj4OcH #35milliondegrees #2atms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lessons of the day - #3. Humans should leave big dangerous animals the f*ck alone. #whatarewedoing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lessons of the day - #2. Dont look at Great White Sharks in a cage. They will get you. #greatwhiteshark #cageattack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lessons of the day - #1. Gorillas should not be kept in tiny enclosures #LondonZoo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clinton pledges that US will generate enough #renewableenergy to power every home in America within 10 yrs https://t.co/RkZDJ5LB3y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada’s #cleantech industry is growing at four times the rate of the overall economy. Colleges need to keep up https://t.co/H8qBbrbVkf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thespiritofjazz thanks!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Living under an @Airbnb sucks! People in and out with no respect for the people WHO LIVE IN THE BLOODY BUILDING.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah great idea Boris, rush leaving the EU https://t.co/YBGwV1mkOz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A 14 year old kid dies trying to get to the UK and you say this gov't is doing enough, @theresa_may I dislike you https://t.co/2pdp56IEfJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our reality with constant turnover @Airbnb above us: Loud visitors banging wheelie bags &amp; breaching building rules https://t.co/0EUehsq9tQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ha refer to earlier tweet! #gochelsea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh nooooo not so wonderful now #gochelsea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Britain to miss its 2020 renewable energy targets https://t.co/tk342xD2zB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile in Kent kids get turned away for wearing uniforms which weren't exactly as 'they should be'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Beethoven the best movie ever?! #ithinkso]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waaaaa you mega deserve that @NicolaAdams2012!! @TeamGB #Olympics2016 #boxingchamp https://t.co/LcayeiANJy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah @NicolaAdams2012 with the win! You go champ!!! #Olympicsboxing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving this #debolt bromance https://t.co/DSyr9sp2as]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatieTaylor way to be an amazing role model for girls wanting to box. They look at your skills and go do it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can stay Conte you can stay #GoChelsea #backinit #earlywarning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@awstuckert thanks for the retweet ... You may also have noticed that Donovan also retweeted this - boom!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love remembering @donovanbailey v @MJGold rivalry! Then watch their 150m race 4 fastest man on Earth https://t.co/nnp3SvvBkI #CanadaWon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did da podium ting, then had to try and pee into a cup. Love these brutally honest hilarious Irish silver medalists https://t.co/qIkEbJJdCH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being in England and not being able to watch the Canadian ladies vball team kick ass is painful! #GoCANADAGo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canadian women are killing it! https://t.co/s4JQ2bd9W3 #Olympics2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@realDonaldTrump's comment about gun owners going after Hilary put secret service on alert. He is out of his mind. https://t.co/ADB26w2Fdh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How I feel about @CitImmCanada receiving our family class application https://t.co/HdH03E4vHh Like Frodo dropping the ring into the volcano]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WayneBennett165 haha I can't even remember. It might have been golf.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America, listen to Michelle PLEASE!!! https://t.co/tiriGk2Tvu @FLOTUS @HillaryClinton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Instead of wasting our time on wind turbines we need to start planning how to survive' says James Lovelock https://t.co/CjEvWo8IgW -]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best hoaky quote out there! #sciencegeek https://t.co/9kkpfUKv0W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perspective https://t.co/p5egUJpfuJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cringe... https://t.co/F8iy653bUC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow! That is so much money, how is anyone going to afford going to a good University in this country? https://t.co/w5uFoXPZt3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada's largest bank @RBC gets behind carbon price https://t.co/GBccTvGbyS But of course they would, it's money at the end of the day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Map of  #CleanEnergy Resources and Projects (CERP) in #Canada https://t.co/w8vnC2PPX6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sid and the #StanleyCup hanging out in @TimHortons and about in home town - love this guy https://t.co/rJB2b75Kkj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something I will not miss is British sports commentating, can you please stay focussed on what is ACTUALLY HAPPENING IN THE GAME?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reinforcing grid transmission connection between Canada and US to help 3.8m homes get #renewable energy https://t.co/TBiHpFLrsv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Community owned #renewable projects get a push from @SaskWind https://t.co/Nfr6UHlWoi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laurie_winkless I know! It was a cool article and I'm not just saying that because I'm biased. You know that I tell no lies :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems like Canada's money wins with its diffraction gratings. Clever reading high in the sky by @laurie_winkless https://t.co/ymmNG6ZLvs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ontario's grid operator is awarding contracts to 907 #solar projects 10-500 kW in capacity under its FIT 4 program https://t.co/8q6Hzn5d4d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thespiritofjazz @msmithdesignuk I just ask Matt who and where everything is. He told me to look at the map and some family list but I dont.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thespiritofjazz @msmithdesignuk I don't watch the show, too violent and too many boobies, not interested.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thespiritofjazz @msmithdesignuk What?! Does it turn into a porno with 10,000 characters. I may read something else]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@msmithdesignuk so many characters just yimmy yammering at eachother atm - wheres the action?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just registered as a student with Association of Professional Engineers &amp; Geoscientists of BC @APEGBC #thisisawesome #womeninengineering]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is cool -&gt; 88% of new investment in Canada's grid was #renewable, and 83% of capacity added last year was renewable #CEQuarterly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Current utility mandates are a barrier - need an overhaul to allow the #cleanenergy shift. #CEQuarterly webinar by @cleanenergycan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expect a Canadian climate plan with exciting outcomes for #cleanenergy in early 2017 #CEQuarterly webinar by @cleanenergycan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tuning into "Crafting Canada's Clean Economy" webinar by @cleanenergycan from Londontown!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Companies with women in leadership roles crush the competition https://t.co/ra4h99L4P4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also love how the @penguins #StanleyCupChampions are owned by the epic former Canadian #hockey player @MarioLemieuxFdn #wayitshouldbe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the @NHL #StanleyCupFinal especially when Sidney lifts that sucker up!!! Hardest trophy in sports to win #hockeyisthebest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A whole lot of yikes for the US of A https://t.co/kVlK0SuQNV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlobalBC ahhhh noooo that is shitty news!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's love, that's for sure! #smithweddingbali https://t.co/p3uct216pQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@msmithdesignuk the weather brought to the rest of London by weather matt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been here a day, love Bali already! https://t.co/VEPKoXju0r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting and promising #solar math by @DKeithClimate https://t.co/2lFM5Nsefj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@saraneame I see them!!! What is this show?! #bestshowever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@saraneame you mean channel 5! I missed the Bulldogs nooooo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@saraneame oh I saw that! Was cool!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoSkiNordic @GreenpeaceCA never mind, Ive just looked at your feed and how you call loads of people idiots. You are just a hater.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoSkiNordic @GreenpeaceCA whoa calm down that's a bit offensive. Why don't you express WHY this tweet upsets you instead of being a JERK.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>