<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@krissssm Yes, but do you have WANDS for them?!?!?!? (They love you, they really do, but the important part is when you unpack the goodies.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@STFUParents @nealpollack Pre-schoolers of today have to suffer the consequences of climate change inaction, in 40-… https://t.co/cirE8AYtal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Clisare I read Executive Order.  Cites only one act of terrorism,  9/11, then doesn't put Saudi on list. Because,  $$$$, you know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CatherineQ I'm imagining that Zygolski once had an immigrant ancestor who was looked down upon in the same way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Um . . . when law officials ignore the courts, that's Rule over Law, &amp; Facism. Unbelievable that this is happening. https://t.co/fbgDaY78C4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When exactly did USA LOSE control over borders &amp; nat'l security? I'm curious. Genuine citations would be appreciate… https://t.co/5cFwPkgN92]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sole example of a terrorist attack on USA soil cited in this document is 9/11. Committed by Saudis. Why is Saud… https://t.co/c6uYgX2M1q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MMFlint Next step: do something for dual citizenship people. Many normal businessmen or women whose job it is to visit USA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cooper_m @lstwrd A pity that Hitler didn't get more objective coverage. Just too darn much emotion in the coverage of his genocide.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cooper_m Will we someday see a remake of "The Great Escape", but set in America?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tarynoneill Please do. Be careful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrissyteigen What? You're on planet Mongo? Say 'hi' to Ming for us!😃 #flashgordon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lbeldreams Can I say it? I'm glad that you're tweeting about this, Laura.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Isi_Cathy @BBC_Joe_Lynam @standupdouble @Mo_Farah Mea culpa. Misunderstood &amp; fully chastised. Am AGHAST at the ful… https://t.co/02r6ZagRYV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBC_Joe_Lynam @standupdouble @Mo_Farah Surely that doesn't apply if he has a UK passport. He doesn't have refugee status.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Incisive article w many solid points. https://t.co/5CjqgNYbNM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@silentmoviesera Has to be the inspiration for the Joker. Tho original Joker appearance in comics was in 1940, 12 years after.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CValdizan Actually,  I never saw Ukraine! Con says v bad, too. I was in Nepal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CValdizan AHHHH!!! The winner is a girl singing a VERY boring ballad, we all agree. We're very frustrated, 2 bette… https://t.co/HUvNbbditH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CValdizan Watching Britain Eurovision competition on BBC2. Very entertaining. Sadly, no one will vote for them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TVsAndyDaly @nealpollack All by himself, too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aleashuhh @nealpollack "Nazi gems" "(Trump) truly is a warrior." Going by this terminology, there's a Grand Canyon… https://t.co/OHuFm8z4Dm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can confirm that it's brilliant, information, &amp; very funny at times. #NovshowinDubln https://t.co/8EAFvcFd17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Clisare @Forbes I'd love a Dublin science March too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@altNOAA "Hey, God. Screwed up Earth. Didn't pay enough attention. Can you give us another one, and let us do-over?" #peoplearehardofhearing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bessbell @realDonaldTrump But Bess! It. Still. Hurts! 😭]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @seanhannity @FoxNews That's a no-brainer interview. Literally.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @MiamiHerald Weak! (We could go back &amp; forth about this, but you're hyper-sensitive, so take a pil… https://t.co/1qlWm1rIUg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColleenDoran And you have a lovely home out &amp; away from everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cooper_m @realDonaldTrump Will some reporter please confront Trump with this, just to make him aware of his hypocr… https://t.co/p0lqdBLEBU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CatherineQ Still comes down to Americans pay for the wall. Any fool can see that. #lottalottafoolsoutthere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump As President, you have no higher duty than to serve the American people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Clisare Ah. I have a chocolate cookie recipe for you. Chocolate Crinkles. Follow faithfully, they're insanely good. https://t.co/vSanRZYexv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Blackmail. Works every time. The Emperor has taught you well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daraobriain You're been watching too many seasons of Homeland.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AltNatParkSer You mistake him for someone who cares about future generations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I never heard this. If so terrible, why tweet &amp; quote &amp; give her publicity?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carolynporco No date set yet, according to this website. https://t.co/i01a4MkqNw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenSanders @documentcloud ah, they surely don't know as much as The Donald. Donald knows best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yup. Perfectly safe. &amp; I'm perfectly sarcastic. Really, this should be fought tooth &amp; nail. Politicians are all lin… https://t.co/2XxjFzrkqL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Washington is a bit far, but if they held a #ScienceMarch in London or Dublin, I'd be there. Will you lead @daraobriain ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump There was a time, when the Berlin Wall was an affront to all the Western world, that any wall was a symbol of oppression]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephenAtHome You're discounting the possibility of "Science Fiction", which has a sub-category of Alternative History &amp; Reality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@euronews @WilksJeremy He could create some more jobs in the manufacturing industry, such as automotive. . . . . th… https://t.co/xO8vWlYr8B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Zombie turn-out was phenomenal in California, especially at polling booths in Death Valley.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnRMoffitt in fact,  they have the right to provide info, as long as it is not designated Confidential. In theory,  can ignore directive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump while u hold stock in them. Greed, greed, greed, greed, greed, greed, greed, greed, and so incredibly NOT Green.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProfBrianCox @neiltyson @AstroKatie I would be delighted if you guys were leading the march. https://t.co/i01a4MkqNw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neiltyson @JeriLRyan It's time that you &amp; other prominent scientists produce programs that are now EQUAL parts sci… https://t.co/vP3j2klgXf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamWangPhD @tanyaofmars Unless Trump fires them--&amp; many may not afford losing their jobs, nor seeking redress thru… https://t.co/Gn2Cze4IEx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pourmecoffee @Alex_Parker Enlisting the help of Genghis Khan, Colonel Green, Zora, Khaliss &amp; Abraham Lincoln, along the way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bessbell I remember buying the Rolling Stone magazine w that cover. Um, the one with Yoko &amp; John, not the cats. God. I'm so old.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In other words, did we elect a terribly intelligent genius of manipulative powers, or did we elect an immature schoolboy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's a debate in itself: is Trump being super-clever &amp; sly? Or is he truly so thin-skinned &amp; narcissistic to insist on his own "facts"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some say that Trump is only being very clever with this Alternative Facts stuff. It's just a distraction from more serious decisions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perfectly understandable when folks of different religions debate nature of reality. But when a President insists on a fictional reality?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Usually when there's an argument over reality, it involves the intangible &amp; unquantifiable. Such as God and the afterlife. Religion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spock &amp; Kirk land on Earth, 2017. "Fascinating. Two sets of realities within one universe," observes Spock.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/2 What is happening w White House &amp; gagging of all their departments is just plain not right. Also shows lack of trust &amp; paranoia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I *detest* any sort of censorship or gagging. I've seen it happen in my place of work. (I'm a bookseller.) 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JPMajor @AstroKatie @BadlandsNPS Shock! Horror! NPS tweeted FACTS! &amp; not Trumpian Alternative Facts! Muzzle! Censo… https://t.co/mEJmXKDbLF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CatherineQ I need a button to click that says, "I agree with what you said, but it depresses the shit out of me."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bessbell @realDonaldTrump Size matters, @realDonaldTrump . It really, really matters. It's all about SIZE. The big… https://t.co/OeazELPu2Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrissyteigen They can rely on the faithful to tune in &amp; believe. They also rely on rest of us getting so jaded, w… https://t.co/udbAbCCHmB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're all puzzled which Alternative Universe this chart was pulled from, cuz it's not the Alt-Universe Trump believ… https://t.co/oIstF1zxBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TOWN. https://t.co/7AovnQ5y6H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Episode IX: a whole bunch of crazy Jedis will be found in an Empire asylum, otherwise known as Return of the JedWard. #Jedward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nah. True age of cat is 50. https://t.co/xzPARaNZ8P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Best thing you've tweeted, almost ever. Well said.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Geez, Donald, you're the absolute BEST at everything! Now, if I could only believe you, because yo… https://t.co/RZRgFtOpWf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time Machine. https://t.co/Mo4bHCc6uQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AstroKatie @guardian Wait until they introduce "Alternative Science 101" into classrooms.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bessbell @realDonaldTrump It was Richard Nixon. 55 times. Google it. Trump has some catching up to do to surpass N… https://t.co/LHrlA7oh31]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They all got sucked into an Alternative Universe that only exists in Trump's head. &amp; Spicer's. &amp; Conway's. https://t.co/sSW5pvXOBy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CatherineQ Of course not. Trump's are actually far higher than Obama's. Because--he says so. #AlternativeFacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bessbell Someone who has been stuck watching "Father Knows Best" &amp; "Donna Reed Show". Didn't even know Netflix showed those old ones.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone else see the irony of the Pussyhats being hand-knitted &amp; produced in USA, while the Trumps #MAGA caps were all made in China.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One woman in a sea of men discussing #WomensMarch Full of clever insights, I'm sure. (sigh) https://t.co/GBSsnTyArX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @realDonaldTrump you weren't on the cover of Time magazine the most times. Richard Nixon was, 55 times. Keep going, u might match him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's speech to CIA meandering into a defense of the numbers at his inauguration speech. Insecure, methinks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tarynoneill Total respect for you all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@krissssm Do you do colouring w the new colouring book craze? That might help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redheadlefthand There's coverage of the Women's March in Washington on Periscope. https://t.co/TaOcyK5oIv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@luisaftoledo They recommend ice baths after a run. I still have not followed this advice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@krissssm There are millions of women who have families to look or jobs to do, &amp; cannot march today. But we know yo… https://t.co/v8wBx7XJrk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@krissssm @MelissaBenoist Watching the March on Periscope--not on any TV channel I can find--delighted to see Melis… https://t.co/ooLry55pRp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarionFiedlerTN Big tea drinkers in our house! Barry's Gold Blend Irish tea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I agree that "bubbles" of ideology is causing rift in USA society, &amp; elsewhere. Putin must shaking his head. No such bubbles in Russia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can Executive Branch impose censorship on their own administrators, or does that go against the First Amendment? Ru… https://t.co/UlyPN1Q8U4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I spent 2 years in Tanzania &amp; learned patience. I get impatient with impatient people. If that makes sense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're an impatient society. I blame McDonalds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missed my park run this morning due to other errands to run. (grumble, grumble, grumble) Must run in late afternoon. Not the same.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or--especially when it comes to social media--don't sing or dance at all, just keep totally quiet. Too many feathers to ruffle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With certain friends, I have a dance a certain way; with others, I have to dance a different way. Keep them all happy. Metaphor, btw.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thisbemesara @tconnellyRTE No, it's a fake. Bee Movie doesn't have that line.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bessbell @realDonaldTrump Are you applying for the job, Bess? 😊]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bessbell @realDonaldTrump What's most annoying about this is that Obama did a decent job reducing unemployment. Bu… https://t.co/EYeSBaddFU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarionFiedlerTN Love to, but think I just missed. Timing wrong again. Have a lovely weekend! Stay warm!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redheadlefthand I have a cousin &amp; a friend's wife both in the women's march tomorrow. I hope it's peaceful, but powerful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redheadlefthand The conversations you must be having.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>