<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[New Zealand Is 'the Future,' Peter Thiel Said in His Push for Citizenship: The New… https://t.co/hqrClQvDKG #Credit_Repair_in_New_York]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In “sanctuary” fight, Abbott cuts off funding to Travis County: Gov. Greg Abbott has… https://t.co/aAvHOUZPod #Credit_Repair_in_Texas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minnesota Law Would Set Precedent For Unregulated Monolopies: In January, the Minnesota Public… https://t.co/WjXdGtKy8n #Credit_Repair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michigan's Signing of the Stars 2017: calls out Coach Jim Harbaugh after the final recruits Donovan… https://t.co/Fj0nRs8swg #Credit_Repair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Credit Repair in Colorado: Free Credit Repair Consultation in Colorado call (888) 502-1260 fix bad…… https://t.co/PiHfke8qe5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maine Solar Customers to Receive Lower Bill Credits Starting in 2018: The Maine Public Utilities… https://t.co/dpe6Z6dkEL #Credit_Repair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Louisiana DR team's assistance prove blessing to stroke victim: WOODWARD, Okla. – A small team of… https://t.co/iIuN1YLRsq #Credit_Repair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kentucky Wildcats Football National Signing Day: How to Watch and Follow: National Signing Day is… https://t.co/b447mjxT4Z #Credit_Repair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report: Kansas player Vick likely hit female student: LAWRENCE, Kan. (AP) — The University of… https://t.co/wLev3Az7cV #Credit_Repair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Indiana mayor replaces pick to head state highway agency: FRANKLIN, Ind. (AP) – A central… https://t.co/F8nx8K9EfL #Credit_Repair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Credit Repair in Arkansas: Free Credit Repair Consultation in Arkansas call (888) 502-1260 fix bad…… https://t.co/v96hojuH2m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Washington, DC, Wi-Fi bill gets new life: Washington, D.C., Wi-Fi bill gets new life. A citywide network is… https://t.co/GIra3mhdHz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iowa pickup driver charged in Florida bicyclist's death: GLENWOOD, Iowa (AP) – A pickup driver has… https://t.co/fVzhFBVOiZ #Credit_Repair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oklahoma State basketball: Five takeaways from OSU's wild Bedlam win: Oklahoma State… https://t.co/xOKxkMOoNM #Credit_Repair_in_Oklahoma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Georgia lands commitment from 2018 linebacker Donovan Georges: While the class of 2017 is Georgia’s… https://t.co/dWbnhcEvTt #Credit_Repair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Statewide alert for 2-year-old boy missing from West Florida: PORT RICHEY, Fla. – Police across the… https://t.co/yBS5KwSGVZ #Credit_Repair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delaware middle school students invited to build and race solar-powered cars in annual Junior …:… https://t.co/np1Nus5yyH #Credit_Repair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Study: Connecticut ranked most profane state, third in integrity: NORWALK – Connecticut ranks as the… https://t.co/AZDKoYWZV4 #Connecticut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pot pioneer Colorado just now taking look at PTSD treatment: DENVER — The first state to legalize… https://t.co/i0psgOdKEo #Credit_Repair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wisconsin tops national list for racial inequality: Data from a new study revealed… https://t.co/aDn34VVrzP #Credit_Repair_in_Wisconsin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arkansas House votes to revive state's voter ID law: LITTLE ROCK — The Arkansas House has approved… https://t.co/IcX5YTM7zP #Credit_Repair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alabama NAACP head says prosecution possible after second arrest outside Jeff Sessions' office: Benard… https://t.co/hcBBQaeHxm #Alabama]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fear returns to Wall Street after Trump border flap: Fear, which has been… https://t.co/n3aaL5y412… https://t.co/UGgq0bWnd6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump immigration order triggers strong emotions on both sides: Questions about the… https://t.co/L6aW5Joga3… https://t.co/sTFPAMTXbR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[San Diego's bishop slams Trump travel ban as 'shameful,' 'rooted in xenophobia and religious… https://t.co/czJVzO7Xx6 #Credit_Repair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where's the buzz? Tom Herman faced challenges in his first Texas class: Mack Brown left… https://t.co/jw9SRDSLkj #Credit_Repair_in_Texas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Virginia Congressman Says Women Are All Up 'In My Grill' About Healthcare: Virginia… https://t.co/zrHMYZNbGe #Credit_Repair_in_Virginia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did Donald Trump just set his relationship with Hill Republicans on fire?: Politico… https://t.co/g7IqY1DNt2 #Credit_Repair_in_Washington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Virgin Islands At Crossroads, Mapp Says At State Of Territory Address: “In… https://t.co/GbkbKs211p #Credit_Repair_in_U_S_Virgin_Islands]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congressman: Prioritize southern West Virginia roads: U.S. Representative Evan… https://t.co/IO2LmNM6I4 #Credit_Repair_in_West_Virginia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's the biggest question surrounding Tennessee for National Signing Day?:… https://t.co/ccSw694zt8 #Credit_Repair_in_Tennessee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ALERT: Anti-Transgender Legislation Returns in South Dakota: The 2017 legislative… https://t.co/NfjPiTqaLs #Credit_Repair_in_South_Dakota]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SC Lottery Commission announces 2 Midlands winners: The South Carolina Lottery… https://t.co/H6qSR7bqmZ #Credit_Repair_in_South_Carolina]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RI religious leaders condemn Trump on refugees, but not Tobin: PROVIDENCE, R.I. –… https://t.co/jv1DSX5jlz #Credit_Repair_in_Rhode_Island]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Credit Repair in New York: Free Credit Repair Consultation in New York call (888) 502-1260 fix bad…… https://t.co/t2pz5Ec5Gu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women's march organizers return to DC to protest Sessions: Organizers from the Women's March on Washington are back… https://t.co/2JPq411sqD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oregon Attorney General Threatens Legal Action In Response To Presidential Executive Order https://t.co/70KpZod9g8 #Credit_Repair_in_Oregon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oklahoma men's tennis: Sooner senior leads the way as OU qualifies for ITA National… https://t.co/v8NioJeye3 #Credit_Repair_in_Oklahoma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recruiting expert: Ohio State DE commit Chase Young could be a future No. 1 pick in the NFL… https://t.co/D5m0DSAIJP #Credit_Repair_in_Ohio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five ways Indian Country can challenge Trump's policies: And possibly the very… https://t.co/pTNN5q16BK #Credit_Repair_in_North_Dakota]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Refugee Families In North Carolina Feeling Impact Of Trump Order: Advocates for… https://t.co/gyUvEuJZS4 #Credit_Repair_in_North_Carolina]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brooke Salas Earns Multiple Player of the Week Honors: LAS CRUCES, N.M. – New Mexico… https://t.co/lDSkNrIrQV #Credit_Repair_in_New_Mexico]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Southern New Jersey mostly spared by latest winter storm: Forecasters say the heavier… https://t.co/wV5Kg3jp9b #Credit_Repair_in_New_Jersey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marblehead woman faces aggravated DWI charge in New Hampshire: MANCHESTER, N.H. —… https://t.co/A6unaBDgZA #Credit_Repair_in_New_Hampshire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Credit Repair in Washington, District of Columbia: Free Credit Repair Consultation in Washington,…… https://t.co/Lnj0ZMpF4Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[University of Montana president addresses Trump travel ban: University of Montana President Sheila… https://t.co/KAqgpJ1Ggh #Montana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Confederate emblem has staying power on Mississippi flag: The Confederate battle emblem still waves… https://t.co/fuiwWyxHCU #Mississippi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['I’m not going to do it.' Police aren't eager to help Trump enforce immigration laws: A day after…… https://t.co/K8hfkjZyDX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Texas is Broken: How the State Government Has Utterly Failed Its People: Texas mothers are… https://t.co/j3ju62R4U9 #Credit_Repair_in_Texas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[College hockey: Minnesota Duluth back on top of https://t.co/521y7FedYV rankings: After a four-week… https://t.co/JfVsQiOadz #Credit_Repair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michigan State hits home runs with top four recruits in 2017 class: Michigan State head coach Mark… https://t.co/qSNnxolQUa #Credit_Repair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Credit Repair in Wisconsin: Free Credit Repair Consultation in Wisconsin call (888) 502-1260 fix…… https://t.co/leqfpNIlUL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Authorities disrupt Maine heroin ring that was supplied from Mass.: An alleged heroin distribution… https://t.co/1NHnrmcMj6 #Credit_Repair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Louisiana teen desperately looking for bone marrow donor: Dana Griffin Nugent of Rayne Catholic… https://t.co/xKoq2sTmGX #Credit_Repair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eastern Kentucky rolls past Tennessee Tech 79-66 (Jan 28, 2017): COOKEVILLE, Tenn. (AP) Nick Mayo… https://t.co/cGwFojyd1Z #Credit_Repair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The troubled 'Kansas experiment' goes to Washington: Would Gov. Sam Brownback, once House Speaker… https://t.co/XF70WcoijN #Credit_Repair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two arrested in Indiana drug bust: Two Indiana residents were arrested Thursday morning after… https://t.co/bGAi2sddZV #Credit_Repair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Idaho woman saved by NY police while broadcasting suicide attempt on Facebook: ROCKVILLE CENTRE,… https://t.co/w8EjlxPLpm #Credit_Repair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Library of Congress Card Catalog: “But to some people, it's an icon,” LC Director of Planning Bob Zich told the… https://t.co/5OBTfECVF5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eastern Iowa gets in on ground floor of Virtual Reality: Marcin Kasica, left, director of Global… https://t.co/v3iz073L9a #Credit_Repair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oklahoma governor considers 3 for her first high court nod: OKLAHOMA CITY (AP) — Two… https://t.co/gBsquZ643j #Credit_Repair_in_Oklahoma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Georgia Tech gains 21st commit: Three-star defensive tackle from Harbor City, Calif. Boe Tufele… https://t.co/87DorIZuOc #Credit_Repair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Historic home to well-known Florida governor finally opening: (AP) – After spending nearly $6… https://t.co/gVl3F4ahn5 #Credit_Repair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Update Georgetown: Pilot Jumps From Moving Plane As Fire And Smoke Fill The Cockpit: Georgetown –… https://t.co/Kb5xWTU62v #Credit_Repair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actress Mary Tyler Moore to be laid to rest in Connecticut: Legendary actress Mary Tyler Moore will… https://t.co/JwxvYXCF4C #Connecticut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lawmakers try a new strategy to help bring condos back to Colorado: A precision-strike approach at… https://t.co/Ocr0cPIIQW #Credit_Repair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Credit Repair in U.S. Virgin Islands: Free Credit Repair Consultation in  U.S. Virgin Islands call…… https://t.co/LOJN68ssvB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pups &amp; Suds event for Basset Hound Rescue of Alabama set for February 11th: The Basset Hound Rescue of… https://t.co/NGccwXT7EJ #Alabama]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Entrepreneurs, embrace the power of video: Have you watched a video on your… https://t.co/veW3fUyY1k… https://t.co/IJ4AgiNAxc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Credit Repair in Tennessee: Free Credit Repair Consultation in Tennessee call (888) 502-1260 fix…… https://t.co/nNZC1w2dh9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump defends refugee policy, attacks New York Times: President Trump, the subject of… https://t.co/kVEKpRVPt9 #Credit_Repair_in_New_York]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Texas man fatally shoots wife, teenager before killing self: McALLEN, Texas (AP) – A South… https://t.co/v4P1gnXIFJ #Credit_Repair_in_Texas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Push to allow backyard hens in Virginia Beach heats up: The idea has come up several… https://t.co/i72kkreBSL #Credit_Repair_in_Virginia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live scoring, stats: Michigan State hosts Michigan in big game for both teams: Radio: Michigan IMG… https://t.co/ylzBI1yYcT #Credit_Repair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jackson's 28 points lead No. 22 Maryland past Minnesota: MINNEAPOLIS (AP) — Justin Jackson had a… https://t.co/DOlEo9PFbY #Credit_Repair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 hurt in shooting at Tennessee National Guard Armory: 29 (UPI) — Ten people were… https://t.co/VIgSkE0tVs #Credit_Repair_in_Tennessee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Credit Repair in West Virginia: Free Credit Repair Consultation in West Virginia call (888)…… https://t.co/Vhn5KT6Q6l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Credit Repair in Maryland: Free Credit Repair Consultation in Maryland call (888) 502-1260 fix bad…… https://t.co/rurmDWHeSz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man gets life term in women's death after home invasion: (AP) — A man accused of… https://t.co/pBrKNWVTM9 #Credit_Repair_in_Pennsylvania]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attorney: Man charged in DC actress' death is innocent: WASHINGTON (AP) - Attorneys for a man charged in the death… https://t.co/qGwFxyspS6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finance site ranks Oklahoma No. 41 of most educated states https://t.co/i8xuWDn6qK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ohio offers redesigned northern cardinal license plate https://t.co/YXkgJPKEfH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hayes powers No. 25 Florida past Oklahoma 84-52 https://t.co/Lcoi3c8q5R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attorney: Man charged in DC actress' death is innocent https://t.co/JyaAepx2So]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Credit Repair in Virginia https://t.co/cvHocM924r https://t.co/5tsAn8Z8pt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump era opens in New Jersey with blocked pay equity bill https://t.co/NNN3GmoF5J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Badgers women's hockey: Wisconsin freshman defensemen step up in rout of Minnesota State … https://t.co/9FBnDSRJd5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Green helps lift Northern Arizona to win against UND men https://t.co/6MAIMXsTCb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alabama in good position to have nation's No. 1 class come signing day https://t.co/m55bgmEyjq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mountain Lion confirmed in Missouri https://t.co/LwDO8eGobL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oil pipeline protest in Plattsburgh https://t.co/YGz5lxWbf2 https://t.co/qVMQqfvlgC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Refugees Detained at US Airports, Prompting Legal Challenges to Trump's Immigration Order https://t.co/Ghjv9GVaGd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Texas mosque destroyed in early-morning blaze; cause unknown https://t.co/Z8UrsyQx5F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former refugees are finding peace, rebuilding lives in Southwest Virginia https://t.co/CuABnjrdjv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump, Putin set for phone call; GOP concerns on sanctions https://t.co/eCLIMklLtX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Credit Repair in Puerto Rico https://t.co/quVeRTh9yH https://t.co/b8S5wN9IK2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Texas A&amp;M falls to on the road to West Virginia 81-77 https://t.co/AZH4KrLf2K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rodeo Rapid City welcomes South Dakota rodeo queens https://t.co/bUnsOxRxSj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Carolina's Brandon McIlwain happy with baseball, football opportunities https://t.co/B9oHjVLslD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Comparing costs of RI, Mass. state governments https://t.co/1LRy57yUXh]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>