<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Adopted Young Woman Confronts Pelosi: Shouldn’t We All Have the Right to ‘Thrive and Succeed’? https://t.co/QJGeCaL4S1 via @LifeZette]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Trump tells McConnell to GO NUCLEAR for Supreme Court nominee! https://t.co/sWbwumHtzr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pelosi Crumbles in Bizarre Town Hall https://t.co/4h5PM6CsbN via @LifeZette]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Politico: Senate Dems Will Filibuster Trumpâs Supreme Court Nominee: https://t.co/3ngPjjBlWb .@DineshDSouza]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maxkellerman u are misinformed on your facts when it comes to Trump. Obama was authoritarian.  Not Trump.  U are angry because Hillary lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump fires acting AG for refusing to defend travel ban https://t.co/ZmGc4TJhVw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YOU'RE FIRED: Trump Sacks Acting Attorney General For Refusing To Defend Immigration Executive Order In Court https://t.co/MN6sga8Ygi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trey Gowdy Has Quite Possibly the BEST Response to Trump’s New “Muslim Ban” https://t.co/kafMhjqZ7n via @youngcons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SallyQYates You r a disgrace &amp; an embarrassment to our Country. YOu have to follow the Executive Order. You cant pick &amp; choose! #TrumpBan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intolerance: Starbucks To Hire 10,000 Refugees While Black Unemployment Is Nearly Double The National Average https://t.co/H7fx7otVD8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama and Jimmy Carter had IMMIGRATION BANS on jihad nations https://t.co/sv7S9Of6v4 via @pamelageller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Tamps Down ‘Muslim Ban’ Hysteria https://t.co/OQGxHBKVwG via @LifeZette]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conway: If MSM Were 'A Real Business,' Heads Would Roll https://t.co/P2cCx973RJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Hardly First President to Pause Refugee Programs https://t.co/A6A9zWvNFs via @LifeZette]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoopi Falsely Claims Obama Waited 'Months' to Issue Executive Orders https://t.co/zOtQeXnrYI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shameful — Another Comic Condones the Bullying of Barron Trump https://t.co/XgBa698pR3 via @LifeZette]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘You don’t speak for Britain’ Anger at BBC’s Confrontation with President Trump’s  https://t.co/GHMnsCbnwH via @pamelageller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MMFlint @realDonaldTrump Mr. Moore, you are a fat Buffoon who needs to go to 24 hour fitness center. YOu are a Disgrace &amp; an Embarrassment!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women’s March Featured Speaker Who Kidnapped And Tortured A Man https://t.co/fGAc9GmwIt via @pamelageller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LeBron James Takes a Shot at Trump Voters https://t.co/ipkr6eQ2Is via @LifeZette]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pink_lady56 Liberals are murderers &amp; they have no conscience ! They will answer to God Almighty 1 day !! #ProLife #WomensMarchOnWashington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will The Trump DOJ Finally Launch a Criminal Investigation Into Planned Parenthood? https://t.co/C453h9k8dZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Sets Insane Pace in Just Five Days https://t.co/feNnieeorU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Congressional Bill Protects Babies Who Are Born Alive After Botched Abortions https://t.co/gdyhzcqOyk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BIG JOE (Trump Supporter) SUMS UP "Women's March" at L.A. March https://t.co/dg6rJWJgje via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brent Musburger: Keith Olbermann 'Should Get Off That Soapbox' and Talk Sports Instead of Politics https://t.co/1InUnQZXbx via @mediaite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump to Sign Executive Order Ending Obama's Unconstitutional Executive Amnesty https://t.co/INRgwGtUYV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious: Deadspin Tells Ted Cruz To ‘Eat S**t,’ Cruz’s Response Is Absolutely Perfect https://t.co/W9kkBED2KO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black Waitress Who Joined Women's March Stunned By White Trump Supporters' Incredibly Generous Tip https://t.co/KeVxDdQZAW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ted Cruz slaps down scumbag libs at Deadspin with class https://t.co/12rJeZff47]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sen. Ted Cruz on The Today Show - Jan. 20, 2017 https://t.co/15STeSUQPH via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Islamic State Took 31 Major Hits Saturday https://t.co/YfE6c0CPlI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Mad Dog’ Mattis Celebrating On Day One, Blows Up ISIS 31 Times https://t.co/DQ0QC8fZul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shia LaBeouf Bullies and Accosts Trump Supporter https://t.co/fcCLIhyqZO via @LifeZette]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SNL Writer Suspended Indefinitely For Viciously Targeting 10-Year-Old Barron Trump https://t.co/yazxcfcplF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Faith Is Central at President Trump’s Inauguration https://t.co/OHVAgqiDlw via @LifeZette]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sudanese Man Falls to His Knees in Middle of Texas Airport to Praise God After Emotional Reunion https://t.co/qkMF3msEep via @faithwirenews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ali @ananavarro @ShocknAwe25   Ana has disgraced the Republican party and our Country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShocknAwe25  These women have no patriotism They are the reason why America is not Great. Trump will make America great again!#WomensMarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These women have no patriotism They are the reason why America is not Great. @realDonaldTrump will make America great again!#WomensMarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TEN_GOP These are liberal criminals and sore losers who are on welfare. They were waiting 8 years for this moment. #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShocknAwe25 @KatiePavlich LOL Justin!! These are Obama's prisoners causing havoc and riots. This is why Trump won ! #Inaugural2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DLoesch @whyimsmrtthnyou @ShocknAwe25  The more guns the more safe our public becomes. Thank goodness for the 2nd amendment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShocknAwe25 @ananavarro @thehill Oh wait, I forgot. You voted for Hillary. You are part of the left now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShocknAwe25 @ananavarro @thehill Ana, you are yesterdays news. Please go into Anger Management. Throwing racial attacks are the lefts job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LMM1952 @bbusa617 Thats exactly right Linda!! They should be exposed and fired immediately !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch: Sen. Susan Collins HUMILIATES Elizabeth Warren In 15 Seconds https://t.co/N0TfwTq3mD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WEdwarda CNN Sucks ! Communist News Network! Or is it Corrupt News Network ? I hope Trump pisses them off everyday for 4 yrs #Inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren Refuses to Shake DeVos’s Hand https://t.co/Dkbhb1vv3V via @LifeZette]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Shameful War on Betsy DeVos https://t.co/aInU7Nrhbd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Brooks Shames John Lewis: So Much for 'They Go Low, We Go High' https://t.co/itqjZfyJoz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marclamonthill Frederick Douglas was a Republican !! Thats a historical fact.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The numbers are in! Tucker is already KILLING Megyn Kelly's ratings - and that's not all . . . https://t.co/Dbc7YWVAeT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leftists Keep Saying The Richest People r Wealthier Than Billions Of Other People Combined. Here’s y That’s Stupid. https://t.co/toQyxCqgM5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jam1p @JFABtm @RealSkipBayless Skip is a Bufffoon !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Levin: Obama and 'jerk' Jeh Johnson just ignited a TAKEOVER of local elections in the dead of the night https://t.co/BNus71MaPL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rubio’s Revenge: Puts Tillerson in Hot Seat https://t.co/wca5GOV2sU via @LifeZette]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Carolde @mike_pence @fayingegneri @ericbolling @ShocknAwe25 Awesome !! Clarence drives the liberals mad because he's a black Conservative !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JFABtm no evil. They just want to live in their liberal fantasy land of gay rights &amp; race riots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JFABtm Exactly right Jae. I"m sick of their dumb foolish attacks on anyone who disagrees. They live in LaLa Land where there is no ISIS or]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BocaRatonRC @JoyAnnReid @ShocknAwe25 U and Obama are a disgrace &amp; an embarrassment to our Country. Mocking Cubans makes u RACISTS! #cubans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congress Takes Aim at Sanctuary City Funding https://t.co/uwNmc0thmH via @LifeZette]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama's Final Revenge: Screws Cuban Refugees https://t.co/8qiy73kIP6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ted Cruz asks General Mattis to discuss why a 'WARRIOR ETHOS' is essential for the military https://t.co/4ZsPuVduaO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinJacksonTBS @realDonaldTrump @KellyannePolls @EricTrump @CNNPolitics @ShocknAwe25 CNN &amp; the News Media r a Disgrace &amp; an embarrassment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ByronYork @ShocknAwe25 Climate change is a hoax. That hysteria was made up in the 70s so the govt can TAX US !! ONly the naive believe it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ted Cruz: Putin a 'thug' and we must stand up to him https://t.co/dRVJqw9M2t via @msnbc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dem Congresswoman Tries to Guilt Black Sessions Supporter https://t.co/IsRNZu9uJT via @LifeZette]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sen. Cruz's Remarks at Sen. Sessions Nomination Hearing - Pt. 4 https://t.co/2Hq5zEto9n via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ted Cruz just put the ACLU on BLAST for attempting to hide the FACTS about Jeff Sessions https://t.co/dZzi3Q7fEn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stevenwhirsch99 @debraraes And take Hollywood with you !! #ObamaFarewell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DLoesch @ChrisLoesch Just block the haters Dana.  Dont waste your time on them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @tedcruz for an awesome job you did today in exposing the hypocrisy of the Democrats and Obama !! #JeffSessions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama has disgraced himself. He is an embarrassment &amp; a Buffoon! He made our country the laughingstock of the world #ObamaFarewell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealJamesWoods @MTV MTV and Hollywood are a Disgrace and an Embarrassment to our Country !! They should be ashamed of themselves !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DLoesch I"m sad that Democrats dont realize that they're the party of the Ku Klux Klan &amp; theyre the ones causing division in our country !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@You_DeplorableG Send him to jail and let him out after 8 years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Levin: Dems fear Sessions 'not because he's a racist, but because he's a conservative!' https://t.co/mMVvEcl32P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShocknAwe25 @ananavarro @thehill Ana is a disgrace and an embarrassment to our party and to our country. She is a secret Democrat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matt Walsh:Don’t flatter yourself, Meryl Streep. u people r the biggest bullies of all. https://t.co/z2STEVCb0R via @MattWalshBlog @theblaze]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tony Romo Reveals Why His Faith In Jesus Christ Will Always Be More Important Than Football https://t.co/uNbFPyAyyi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WEdwarda Hollywood hates America unlike real hardworking Americans who voted Trump.Hollywood is a disgrace &amp; an embarrassment. #GoldenGlobe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhillyCustoms His is the reaction of real Americans who love their Country. GoldenGlobes is a disgrace &amp; an embarrassment. #GoldenGlobe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheClemReport His is the reaction of real Americans who love their Country. GoldenGlobes is a disgrace &amp; an embarrassment. #GoldenGlobe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jesseberney His is the reaction of real Americans who love their Country. GoldenGlobes is a disgrace &amp; an embarrassment. #GoldenGlobe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JillianSed THis is the reaction of real Americans who love their Country. GoldenGlobes is a disgrace &amp; an embarrassment. #GoldenGlobe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Wheel of Fortune' Guest Started Behaving Oddly with Strange Letter Choices—Then Pat Figured Out Why https://t.co/UniRimdEmd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShocknAwe25 @lizsalandar @CatLady06121335 @JebSanford Shes a liberal buffoon who believes tht the earth is still flat becos tht was science]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lizsalandar @ShocknAwe25 @CatLady06121335 @JebSanford The Pope is a socialist buffoon ! Climate Change is a Hoax. They want to tax you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lizsalandar @ShocknAwe25 @CatLady06121335 @JebSanford Yea, scientists all thought that the earth was flat also. They are usually wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lizsalandar @ShocknAwe25 @CatLady06121335 @JebSanford Look at the satellite data. Use your brain and investigate. This is a HOAX !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Miss World: ‘I’m pro-life’ and ‘Sex is for marriage’ | News | LifeSite https://t.co/OY5xlGVw66]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lizsalandar @ShocknAwe25 @CatLady06121335 @JebSanford These agencies work for governments so they can fool the naive and TAX them HUGELY !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lizsalandar @ShocknAwe25 @CatLady06121335 @JebSanford 95 percent of scientists also stated that the earth was flat. They were wrong !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lizsalandar Change? Give me a break. They are using you and this issue so they can tax the hell out of us. Wake up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lizsalandar Says who? in the 70s they said it was Global Cooling. FALSE. Then they changed it to Global Warming. AGAIN FALSE. Now Climate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JFABtm @POTUS Exactly. Hes a Jew Hating Hypocrite !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stevenwhirsch99 @JFABtm Hahaha. Hilarious but sadly true. Obama is a Disgrace!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShocknAwe25 @lizsalandar @CatLady06121335 @JebSanford Exactly. Build the wall &amp; deport Illegals &amp; stop funding the FAKE Climate Change HOAX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@skylar617 @ANA4PEACE2016 @TEN_GOP @DebraBostock @sganim @ShocknAwe25 @CNN She did enjoy it. Hillary supporters love terrorizing the weak.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>