<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Go on!! Selby boy 👊 #AndNew #Wales]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Boxing #UFC &amp; #MOTD tonight.   I highly recommend @FightfulOnline for All combat sports, best of the best @FightfulMMA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FightfulOnlineTaker passes torch to Reigns #AsAFace??

Only works if Reigns leaves Taker in a bloody mess cementing his #topheel status]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chavs up the school do my f***** nut in.  Control your kids and actually teach them how to be decent human beings. #ChavvyFucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Said back be4 Xmas wen MU drew w/Burnley that  see them challengin this yr.  They win tomoz their 2 pts behind 2nd.  Chelski will win it tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cant believe that manager of Klopp's quality hasnt gone into transf/market. Scousers desperate for @ least 3 to challenge &amp; Deffo need a gk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xJusTCLarKYx @KennyOmegamanX Who could blame you but still gotta get the facts right when attempting to be dick to people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KennyOmegamanX @xJusTCLarKYx John Cena literally did that last week. I'm wwe fan but take off the blinkers dude. #embarrassing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why not give Wyatt the Rumble win and Orton the EC win then give Wyatt his first title win at WM.   Surely makes more sense.  #puzzling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strebby1 Enjoy mate.  I'm just on CW title match.  Hoping Neville wins.  I hope they have Wyatt win the Rumble as shock.  #kiddingMyself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strebby1 ye, I didn't like Hogan either nor Cena once he abandoned the rap gimmick. Reckon ppl hate cos they know he's Vince chosen one tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strebby1 Cheers for not spoiling it.  He's ok he just bores me same shit all the time.   Gets beat up overcomes odds.  #TurntheFuckerHeel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never been happier to see Braun Strowman.  Sadly think that means Cena is beating AJ later.  Happy though cos Reigns bores the shit outta me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fingers crossed for @ShinsukeN attacking @AJStylesOrg to set up WM match along w/ @SamoaJoe &amp; Tye Dillinger debuting in the #RoyalRumble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NXTSanAntonio was awesome.  As usual NXT delivers.   Everything that VKM's booking is not.  Over delivered.  Over to the main roster]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why oh why didn't #CCFC keep Tom Lawrence.   He's Welsh and the lad is 🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥🔥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AustinAries Pretty sure his inauguration was the signal for the end of days.  Hope you have built a bunker full of non perishables. 😎]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm confused so is Jurgen Klopp the 2nd coming or no? #AsYouWere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PPL y how #mufc fans are plastic but their away fans are some of the best in the premier league easily.  Miss real atmospheres &amp; fan banter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheFansPodcast I don't know who I'd be more gutted by if they don't turn up Joe or Tye.Probably Joe because I want see him wreck Cena at WM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheFansPodcast @isaacganguiano @WWEDillinger If he's not 10 then it has to be The Miz doing Bryan's Yes entrance but with 10s #HeelGold]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another 'top' flight game &amp; another dreadful refereeing decision changes a game. They get paid big £s these refs &amp; every week they're poor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I watched 3 Hull games since Silva took over and they have looked decent.  Playing the right way #impressive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KennyMc1985  it's imperative he loses the match then decimates Taker into a CzW style bloody mess retiring Taker &amp; finally turning heel 🖒]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanRossSapp Seems a huge waste. Of the BITW tho.  Looks like my dream of @AJStylesOrg vs @KennyOmegamanX or @ShinsukeN at WM is just that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanRossSapp I'd be on board w/ that as long as Reigns turns heel &amp; leaves Taker a bloody mess &amp; Bray Wyatt finally gets main event push]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KarlAndersonWWE @SashaBanksWWE #NewClubMember 🤘

👌]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wud 💙 2 see Orton bout to screw @WWEBrayWyatt at RR, suddenly lights out &amp; he's surrounded by Bray &amp; SaNity #SawItComing #NewCerebralAssasin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRobDyke on the money again 🖒 Anyone who has half a brain should watch &amp; share this video.  #triggered
https://t.co/NuaUMDeS3D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another @wwe #Raw Another case of Reigns overcomin heavily stacked odds #boring #embarrassing #SameOldShit @FightfulOnline @pawlowskithe4th]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So pleased for @evitthealey he has been long overdue a go.  First goal, always nice in injury time. 👌]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanRossSapp Wyatt eliminatin Bryan frm behind last wud have solidified him as a top heel &amp; got mega heat.They fucked 14 &amp; 15 up so badly 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who Should Main Event Wrestlemania 33?  Vote here! https://t.co/G5yHClqfGn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanRossSapp @pawlowskithe4th really hoping it ends up on WWE network.  Joe Hendrys custom entrances are thing of pure fun &amp; entertainment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanRossSapp @pawlowskithe4th I've just started watching @InsaneChampWres It's everything WWE Raw isn't #NotPG #Entertaining]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad news about Superfly. Was my favorite when my friends liked Hogan. Gr8 wrestler but once I was adult &amp; learned what he did.  Lost respect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dmf180593 OMG! Football fan talkin sense on social media.Hang your head in shame Daniel. Social media for over reactions &amp; needless abuse 🙃]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It would be refreshing for @WWEBrayWyatt to see Ortons plan coming &amp; just as Orton about strike he is surrounded by new family. #WyattForRR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only thing that #WWEUKCT missing is one and only @KadeCallous , it's travesty he's not there he's a unique wrestler &amp; top fella #TheirLoss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK wrestling fans showing US what crowd at wrestling should be like.  Other than smarky towns &amp; big 4 PPV that is.  #WWEUKCT Great so far]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As usual @wwe tease cool @WWEBrayWyatt push/story only to rush it &amp; ultimately ruin something great.  Bray &amp; Wyatts deserve better #wwechamp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My new favorite thing to do when givin my son &amp; mates a lift is to breakout the @MATTHARDYBRAND gimmick. They don't get my #brokenbrilliance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigAntStudios  Love that on @DonBradmanUk career mode is really hard. Scored 1st few tons &amp; felt like achievement #GreatestCricketGameEver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lewb89 yep,it's a shame @wwe screwed up Club booking so badly as they could have kept refreshing bringing in new guys #WastedChance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AJV1Beta  They will never learn apparently. Shame as a shock win for a Wyatt or a Rusev would be awesome even Corbin be better than obvious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lewb89 ye kinda agree Omega has been incredible last 12 months. WK match was thing of beauty. Dont think he comes to WWE til nxt yr myself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lewb89 @KarlAndersonWWE Get them in as well.  Love to see 2 versions of BC on Raw/SD. BC vs Coperate wwe=💸 BC vs Wyatts=💸 BC vs Shield etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WWE wastin @KarlAndersonWWE @LukeGallowsWWE big time.Give them the belts then bring back Finn &amp; get in Omega.  Have #BC run wild #Easy 👌]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KennyMc1985 @liosi They can't click because they are constantly puttin over 45+ yr olds.Wyatt,Owens,Rollins etc all been well over at pts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AJV1Beta @liosi @KennyMc1985 Thats been the issue with Rumble for past 3 or 4 yrs it's been predictably boring. No Wyatt shock win for me 👎]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KennyMc1985 Wud have rathered Taker vs AJ #NeverThoughtPossible They should be using legs &amp; Veterans to get over young guys not main focus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JDfromNY206 Raw focused on 45+ yr olds #SameOldShit SD usin Veterans eg Cena &amp; Orton to get Wyatt etc over #UsePartTimersToPutOverNewGuys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wwe Reason Smackdown better than Raw is because they are at least tryin to get young guys over using veterans like Orton &amp; Cena #Raw=Boring]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Taker but entrance longer than his promo.  Buildin RR around Brock,Goldberg &amp; Taker instead of around building new stars #SameOldShit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bored of @wwe focusing on past legends. Cant get new guys over cos they keep pushin 45+ yr olds over them unless they are named Cena/Reigns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Cena has to go over @AJStylesOrg at RR I really hope it's because @ShinsukeN costs him to build to an incredible #wm33 feud between them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some1 tried tellin me other week Aresnal could win league as defence was sorted now😂 If Preston took chances AFC been 3 down at HT again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dmf180593 DDG,Shaw,Young,Smalling,Jones,Bastian,Herrera,Pogba,Mykitarian,Martial,Rashford, WR
Bring on TFM(BS) Mata(HM) Valencia (Rashford)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I'm @TripleH or @wwe I'm giving Omega whatever he wants to get him in.  Build the main roster round AJ,Nakamura,Bray,Omega, KO etc #Stars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Crapgame13 @ShakeThemRopes Do you think @wwe should bite the bullet &amp; tape #205Live at Full Sail. Get some hot crowds &amp; write some stories]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TripleH @WWENXT It's great to see him back but how will signing him make Roman look strong????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShakeThemRopes Yes until Chris Hero, Adam Cole and Kyle O Reilly turn up at Full Sail in 2017 👌]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KennyOmegamanX v Okada @ #wrestlekingdom11 was easily in top 3 matches I have ever seen.  45 mins + &amp; I couldnt take my eyes off it 👌#BC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FightfulOnline #askfightful Will any more Bullet Club members jump to WWE in 2017.  Love to see Adam Cole on Smackdown myself 🖒]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CodyRhodes American Nightmare tights and #BulletClub boots are bad ass.   WWE dropped the ball so badly not just with Cody but BC members]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only up to the entrances of Cody on #wrestlekingdom11 &amp; it's #great More I watch #NJPW &amp; #roh the more I realise how wasted talent at wwe is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy shit!! 25 years ago.  I am officially old 🖑 https://t.co/EHGtZzEjxh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jeez!! It's hard to believe that @wwe produces Raw &amp; SD.  SD is must watch whilst Raw is boring same shit.  Rollins, Owens, Y2J deserve more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For my friends who are Gooners I really hope #AFC dont make top 4 this season as nothing will change til they miss out on CL #UnderAchieving]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear @wwe Please put Roman Reigns on last so I can switch off early. #SameOldShit #WWEwastingTalent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't believe I didn't know that @TheRobDyke had brought back #wwyptoti I feel like all is right on the Internet again.  #footpussy 😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidTutonda Good luck boss, always hoped you'd break through with City.  All the best \o/&lt;o&gt;\o/&lt;o&gt;\o/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The standard of refereeing in the premier league has been piss poor in 2016.  No wonder so many top managers look so stressed. #PubReferees]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cody_Nolove absolutely destroyed Cruz, outclassed him in 5 rounds.  Congrats champ! #AndNew #UFC207 #deserved]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShowdownJoe called Nunes win on @FightfulOnline podcast.  If Joe speaks on #ufc then you listen.  #BITW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ufc #WWE #tna #roh #titan #bellator #titan No matter company, No matter ifs #mma #boxing or #wrestling @FightfulOnline essential for ppvs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait for #UFC207 it's gonna be gr8.  Follow w/ @FightfulOnline
 Sean &amp; @ShowdownJoe even have me excited for 1st time viewing if Rizin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanRossSapp @riddletuf7 #askfightful What does he think WWE should do with Connor Mcgregor?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WWE wasting a @WWEBrayWyatt push, again!!! WWE rushing a Wyatts storyline - Shock Horror!! American Alpha winning first wwe gold - #wmMoment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I said after Utd played Burnley that if they keep Pogba, Zlatan &amp; Mykiterian fit they will be pushin Chelsea by May.  Be interesting january]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wishing a merry Xmas to the hardworking @SeanRossSapp @pawlowskithe4th &amp; co at @FightfulOnline #TopGuys #TopSite #UFC #MMA #WWE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SKILLITWORLD @ashroseuk @wwegp I called it!! #justsaying 👌 https://t.co/gZW8SDZ63U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PapaJohnsUK yes he promised a refund and didn't turn up. #classy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PapaJohnsUK After your canton shop ruined .my sons birthday yesterday think I'll go to @Dominos_UK in future #Disgusting #Shameful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PCraigmma Good good, keep up the good work.  The Welsh and Scottish have arrived in #ufc #Celts #submssionKing 🖒]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#UFCSacramento prelims were awesome.  Ladies went toe to toe for 3 rounds but @PCraigmma tore it up &amp; was emphatic in victory, get in 👊]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watchin the Leicester game frm earlier, Christ I thought that ref was bad on Weds even worse 2day as great Ian Brown said "fuckin amateurs'']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WWE @WWEUK No @KadeCallous in this tournament is hugely disappointing.   ✌]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That referee in Utd v Palace should be refereeing non league this weekend.  Absolutely piss poor, got everything big call badly wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First penalty awarded via video evidence
BBC Sport - Atletico Nacional 0-3 Kashima Antlers https://t.co/lEqSWB6XVb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LMFAO! Reigns gets booed even when saving a face Seth frm 2 v1 beat down When will they realise that 90% fans r bored w/Superman bookin #Raw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great show again @wwegp @AshroseUK @SKILLITWORLd Is it just me thinking Samoa Joe will be DB's proxy as a mystery opponent vs Miz at RR?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanRossSapp What do you think of Jack Marshmans chances of going far in #ufc? #wales]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could listen to @SeanRossSapp &amp; @ShowdownJoe talk #ufc and #mma forever on @FightfulOnline podcast.  They called it last week as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LCMee24 @TheNotoriousMMA Don't see how it's lucky when Diaz has been only one capable of taking his left hand. Everyone else has gone down]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hell of chin on @KoreanSuperBoy7 though.  That fight was brutal and you should absolutely go out of your way to watch it. #ufc206]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LCMee24 @TheNotoriousMMA a bit of a sham tho giving it to Aldo who got ko'd in seconds.  Get that he didn't defend but still.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ufc206 was brutal. I wasn't that psyched for it but delivered.  Refuse to acknowledge any1 but @TheNotoriousMMA as #FeatherweightChamp tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watchin Y'day UfC before switching to AJ fight then back to UFC. For top coverage in combat sports then follow @FightfulOnline @ShowdownJoe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jennings with a reverse sweep to make 100 on debut vs the best team in the world in their conditions. Scintillating! #Thefuture #BBCCricket]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>