<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Reason 2 why I love hiking: when you're caught in a storm and the hut is freezing you can build a mattress igloo. I… https://t.co/BPW1n5JCLi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the many reasons I love hiking: siting on a stairway above the clouds at sunrise. -- Mt Holdsworth, Tararua https://t.co/gfBVQNGcaU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FinnDinneen Baring Head is also worth the shortish walk. Oh, and for nature, Kāpiti Island.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FinnDinneen for hiking, the Tararua. For ocean, Castle Point and Cape Palliser, For cutesy village, Paekak.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FinnDinneen thanks. I find Wellington never runs out of offerings for photographers :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TKRobb thanks. It's my favourite Tararua hut so far. Though I'm keen to get to Tarn Ridge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cupoteacoast thanks, will do. This is a panorama from Maungahuka Hut's deck during a cloud storm. https://t.co/Jvv5kHVeZb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can see the red-roof hut in middle on left. The spur going down below it leads to a plane wreck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of Welly's best getaways: Maungahuka Hut, sitting next to a tarn high up in the Tararua. Just takes a couple of… https://t.co/uUWOg7V5dd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anarkaytie I took that shot about 10 hours into day two of a five-day hike.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever looked up Hutt Valley to Tararua Ranges and wondered what they look like from other side? https://t.co/LbIquznGac]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spotted Bradley Cooper and his wolf pack down Oriental Bay https://t.co/zsQBz58VT6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lagatabeth @DomPost that's cool. So glad I stopped to ask if I could take a photo :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_hehir_ @GraemeEdgeler I'd argue that 'compulsory', in this context, is a dysphemism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GraemeEdgeler 'compulsory' evokes a negative reaction from many voters. It makes more sense to use synonyms.I'm not arguing for 'universal']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wellingtonians: If you need a cute fix there's baby alpacas up Takapu Valley https://t.co/aE6SOW3irf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irihapeta you mean Trump stuff?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irihapeta I find it's good to have a decent break from social media at least once a year:)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found out hard way alpacas don't like pats. This fella up Takapu Valley spat at me. Apparently he came over just to… https://t.co/ozNbKanUSN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Zagzigger2 @Pno_nwa I might've questioned it if I hadn't have seen how happy the cat seemed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Zagzigger2 @Pno_nwa ah. I watched the cat for a while and it seemed to love the opportunity to adventure places it couldn't otherwise go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Zagzigger2 @Pno_nwa what's "pfoff"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lagatabeth here's another shot I got of you when we met earlier. https://t.co/mC8fMo8Om5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cat's name is Beth. If anyone knows her lovely owner could you please pass on the pic above to her]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't see that everyday: cat on leash confidently walking through central city https://t.co/CjGhMY7H7r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dovil aw thanks :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@corrinacellist thanks :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am reviewing my 'top tweets' from this year. Thought some of you might enjoy a few of them too. Self-RTs to follow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShaneHarmon @Wellington_NZ @WestpacStadium that's a very cool photo. Thanks for posting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NOISEBOXER yeah, I liked it enough to keep watching.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NOISEBOXER yup. The end didn't work so well for me. Thought Stranger Things was better overall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NOISEBOXER took me a moment to get that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last light on the longest day. Mt Victoria https://t.co/Kfa8Be0PJ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@avancenz they're under obligation to compensate https://t.co/ah4rGFelXN. @Icelandair were brilliant when they misplaced my luggage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With #1 and #3 on @publicaddress's Word of the Year list in mind, here's a link to Slate's fake news debunking tool… https://t.co/3tsF4G2CUj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't usually like to Godwin, but these jellyfish at Oriental Bay are real... https://t.co/mb76706iUP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@merxplat ah shit, didn't realise there was sound. heh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wellington waterfront today https://t.co/dcohgnWI1r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stoked to have photo in new Best of Wellington book! And big thanks to mystery surfer https://t.co/qDSWgiPmHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of a family of stingray scanning @OrientalBayNZ shoreline just now. Have so far spotted a few surprised swimmers https://t.co/Fq0ej4TCkx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching what appears to be mum &amp; dad stingray teaching their youngun to prowl @OrientalBayNZ shoreline for food]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lyallbaynz @OrientalBayNZ I kept an eye out but didn't see them :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@teJoshuaJames in one move]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzpxm I'd argue a feminist theme]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quake monster is messing with me. Only thing big one knocked over in my house was the toilet seat. Now it's the white king on my chess board]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help convince Twitter @translator to include Māori. Take 30s to fill this form out https://t.co/9XqaqOf1p8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police rescuing a capsized yachtie on Evans Bay moments ago. Saw at least two overturned boats https://t.co/NeMz75vZ56]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @translator could you please include Māori? Twitter's translate algorithm often reads tweets with te reo words as Romanian or Indonesian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonder if kava's Kiwi cousin kawakawa shares that benefit? https://t.co/BurGu4v3Tj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tlscadden1 @mojocoffeenz @WellingtonZoo they're still there :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColeyTangerina that is awesome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_sofistry quite enjoyed that, thanks :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tim_McCready @mojocoffeenz @WellingtonZoo my sanity might've been preserved had the iguana eaten some of the children ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best @mojocoffeenz cafe in Welly must be @WellingtonZoo. Watched this through window next to my table. https://t.co/RIszBQbcSS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dovil good point, Displeased Dovil.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@craigireson I'll have to try those. Cheers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am putting together an xmas song playlist. Any recs? My faves so far are by LCD Soundsystem and The Cosmonauts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fire is apparently at Hutt Valley High School]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big fire happening in Petone right now https://t.co/8gB0ebeB3y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimbakerwilson @suzikyla23 reminds me of this street in Wellington. Never been sure how to say it correctly. https://t.co/OcHbaHxIks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeterDunneMP @philiplyth sheesh, four terms!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philiplyth thanks. I did mean 'ever' rather than 'next'. First is understandable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tmurphyNZ paywall, gah. Who made the offer?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@meganjwhelan you just took me to a very dark place]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juhasaarinen @keith_ng the durian was surprisingly tasty. Can't say same for the feet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juhasaarinen @keith_ng true that. He's caused me to eat durian balls and what I suspect was chicken feet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juhasaarinen @keith_ng I'm surprised twitter hasn't as yet coined #KeithiNg in the same way we've used #Edgelered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wimon_song at least the Bill boards will work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emmawehipeihana @GuyonEspiner have on many occasions found them to be an excellent resource.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emmawehipeihana he does great profiles of politicians. So glad he can still write for the Listener while doing MR.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mykuhl @bryce_edwards sure, but it warrants noting and not being glossed over.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bryce_edwards and I'm glad you didn't say "first Māori PM". There has been an acting-PM who was Māori.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bryce_edwards at very least it'd raise public discussion about being of Māori heritage and being culturally Māori.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bullhale I would have guessed that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlackCapsNo1Fan nope. But I'm hoping to get a good close up of one of those this summer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brenakiwi I wish. Still to see one of those in the wild.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Angel_of_FilmPR thanks :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nature quiz: what bird is this? https://t.co/xWNGtQ85IQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantails usually flutter about too fast to photograph. This guy just sat there staring at me https://t.co/TxcOyVCsb3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am reminded of photo I took a few years ago. Mood seems fitting https://t.co/8vfEXh7cf2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DuncanGarnerNZ @RadioLIVENZ curious to hear their thoughts on what challenges they'd face regarding US and China relationships?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toby_etc all these divides... someone needs to build some Bridges]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CAM_AnnaMac I see agreeing to disagree as an important tool in politics. It leads to better decision making when agreement is possible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CAM_AnnaMac some of us aren't here for the echo chamber.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matthewjpb it was very trendy all around the world. But after WWII everyone pretended it was only a German problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dovil I'd love to see Curia's data/research. Especially regarding which potential replacements could and couldn't win an election.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aurynn yay for cool people, right!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friend left purse on boot, drove off, driver behind picked up, followed for 10 mins, told cyclist, cyclist told us, wallet returned.Thanks!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@powderkeig airport control tower :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The leaning tower of Lyall Bay is starting to take shape https://t.co/1LGqDQAvlE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friend with PHD and years of post-doc research has barista certificate framed on kitchen wall. Says it's been more helpful with employment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xCaron you're welcome :) I got idea from @DrSeaRotmann]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of summer's many awesome attributes: bubbly &amp; pomegranate https://t.co/Hnpd1Dmlzy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creek crossing at Belmont Regional Park is a little deeper than we expected https://t.co/qgtW3hjcRi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@msbananapeel so cool.... It's Oamaru. Here's a video of penguins using it https://t.co/2kD3zdvmvR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ingarihi that's very cool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reckon @tmurphyNZ's avatar tells us a lot about what we can expect from his coming-news venture with Mark Jennings https://t.co/olNqUguzwX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I told someone 700 earthquakes had hit New Zealand in last 19 days they'd probably think it was a lot. But there's been 7000.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WalkingAccess Northern Tararua?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@madinnz the end of the world mightn't be that far away...]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>