<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@philosodork @rjblaskiewicz Being a lawyer I disagree with her interpretation of how nonprofits must act now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philosodork @rjblaskiewicz @resisterhood They would lose. This is not compulsion or stifling of speech.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SwiftRead @LetThereBeKatie @DCPoliceDept oh shut up you fat old fuck, you aren't as funny as you think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be surprised by Trump's immigration crackdown. Be shocked. https://t.co/gt8Cty03Q1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oscar Nominated Director Allegedly Unable To Attend Award Ceremony Due To Muslim Ban https://t.co/IzHNu5X1GE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Green card holders included in Trump ban: Homeland Security https://t.co/lWhw6W7Dig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattW1188 Jews were denied entry as refugees and then died in the Holocaust you historically illiterate vile shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gabriella_akat @KellyannePolls @Lrihendry You all are vile humans who will burn in hell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tapperdon It will never happen and even if it did, it would never look like that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepLouBarletta shut up ugly cunt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[British Reporters Were Temporarily Barred From The White House Because America Does Dates Wrong https://t.co/hOqcNNYxLe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jealoushe It's definitely real you vile shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump has hourlong conversation with Mexico’s president amid standoff over wall https://t.co/xaDIIUuV34]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kdrum Threats to our democracy and lies pushed by the president must be very "entertaining" to you, huh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump faces criticism over prospect of enhanced interrogation techniques https://t.co/9IparCn2C9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s Impulses Now Carry the Force of the Presidency https://t.co/20oenC4d4D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arbordayde @babycommie666 violence is the answer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Body language experts explain Donald and Melania Trump's strange inauguration behavior https://t.co/KhhtUQf0Fn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That Old Phone Trump Uses for Twitter Could Be an Opening to Security Threats https://t.co/uMSIzelc2R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mattis, Pompeo stunned by CIA 'black sites' report https://t.co/QaHNwOQISK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump 101: What he reads and watches https://t.co/4NFYdZzMTw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: Read draft text of Trump's executive order limiting Muslim entry to the U.S. https://t.co/W2au5YsArK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Biggest Moments in xoJane History https://t.co/U5jblWDO26]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theresa May to seek special deal with Trump in White House visit https://t.co/FatJsYDoNw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is the Doomsday Clock and why does it matter? https://t.co/4TlwdyGzO2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EPA Employees During Media Blackout: 'There's A Real Sense Of Dread' https://t.co/jT9AIyvXHl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mar-a-Lago membership fees double to $200k https://t.co/pIzxdn3tik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump to nominate Philip Bilden as Navy secretary https://t.co/1pf7AfLKLb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ISIS fight stays the course for now under Trump, Army general says https://t.co/5LEcPYvJA8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House sources: No plan to revive CIA 'black site' prisons https://t.co/7OtnurIW9m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minnesota Governor Collapses During Speech | NBC 10 Philadelphia https://t.co/4oUjib2Lls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pentagon: Mattis has 'hit the ground running' https://t.co/i0Kvy9HICx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fox News signs ex-Kerry adviser Marie Harf as contributor https://t.co/8fMnYXepkh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Trump's America, 'Felony Riot' Charges Against Inauguration Protesters Signal Dangerous Wave of Repression https://t.co/GUh14brNO0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump to Order Defense Chiefs to Draft ISIS Plan, Despite Promised Secret Plan https://t.co/47XQMJg1T0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrisonPlanet that's not Islam, that's called authoritarianism, dipshit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conservatives still trying to blame everything on Obama. Can't work for much longer. https://t.co/dVPrFBxPGu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Legend Addresses Paparazzo Who Allegedly Made Racist Comment: 'It's a Shame' https://t.co/CI12jsFydt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Gambia Is Back Again,’ but Its New Leader Is Still in Senegal https://t.co/22cisGnLMR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DeltaTheBravo @SandiLib @seanmdav Some of us objected to that and this, dipshit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump takes on Women's March, inauguration TV ratings on Twitter https://t.co/xhvGOklJ3n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Forensics4Real @michellemalkin @justice4danielh @realDonaldTrump fuck you he's a convicted rapist and deserves to rot in jail and hell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dem Pledges To Begin Impeachment Process Against Trump https://t.co/magZZ3nGAF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Is How Gay Republicans Partied After Donald Trump's Inauguration https://t.co/RVuaywwlib]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OhMyGOFF @nbcwashington How hasn't this been deleted yet? And you still have your job?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McCain, Graham say they will support Tillerson https://t.co/gYlOTsSxDn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York Times investigating apparent Twitter hack https://t.co/A564jdMQNt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone changed the BBC's inaugration subtitles, and it was incredible https://t.co/5hCd5Fyv7X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@divocsa what the fuck is this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 dead, 20 injured after car ploughs into pedestrians in Melbourne; 1 man arrested https://t.co/3CBgczuOez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@protanope It's sad to watch some dude who can't take a joke blunder around. Shut up already.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@protanope give it up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report: Melania Trump Will Return To New York Two Days After The Inauguration https://t.co/sPfQ4eMHy6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet the Trumps: From Immigrant to President review – a warning from history https://t.co/IDc8DrotuH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Davos: The common ground of Trump and Xi https://t.co/GPjtTx7xjR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inside Rachel Maddow’s Plans to Reinvent Her MSNBC Show in Trump Era https://t.co/YyhAKfwkNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘No New Taxes, No Cuts To Services’; Hogan Outlines Budget https://t.co/OZhaaRcP5w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A history of inaugural fashion – in pictures https://t.co/LhLY0qD9Uc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[BREAKING] Former President George H.W. Bush hospitalized (@HoustonChron)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChristiChat @LindaSuhler Who made you racist pieces of garbage?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarketWatch more millennial bashing sans context]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump advisers tell French officials: We strenuously object to Paris peace conference https://t.co/ItfFbGEDvL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every Trump tweet activates thousands of computer algorithms https://t.co/7nLOxNuw8q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Major powers meet in Paris to revive Israeli-Palestinian peace talks https://t.co/vESiBBMsoc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In parts of Mosul, a semblance of normality despite war https://t.co/t4aA0srCE7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SohrabAhmari who cares? Who takes the time out of their day to make dumb snippy comments about someone leaving the job of a lifetime?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Possible Murder Site Revealed Ahead Of Anniversary Of Cold Case Teen's Death https://t.co/yoHC7OdJSi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GovCorrupted fine, if it's real, you'll have no problem sending me the link to the final draft of the law! Can't wait!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GovCorrupted It was not reported by anyone credible because neither of those lies are true in the least]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Black-ish' presents message of unity in first post-election episode @CNN https://t.co/yPKShbRrgK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Trump’s bogus plan to avoid conflicts of interest, explained” by @JuddLegum https://t.co/b69b1eAMs3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GovCorrupted prove that bill was passed. Or that 4.5 million illegal votes were cast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GovCorrupted that's a lie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FeraPasq hahaha I'm not crying but I would if I had such an ugly wife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cdgh5h1 the electoral college was created to protect slave states. You educate yourself you dolt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SSestanovich @MaxBoot @lrozen They orchestrated this so why would they be surprised?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GovCorrupted hahahahaha spreading lies to prop up your Russian puppet, you hair brained fool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter Thiel considering bid for California governor https://t.co/sIsZPavtfd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GovCorrupted The people that voted for Hillary Clinton by almost 3 million votes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being trans, and an immigrant, under the Trump administration  https://t.co/TzYkClkhMn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AP Interview: Lynch says US must hold police accountable https://t.co/klFcYQQ7CZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here are the Democrats boycotting Donald Trump’s inauguration https://t.co/mokNAZU0HD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnieLinskey @reidepstein candidates who want to lead an organization shouldn't be interested in what makes an organization run properly??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On sensitive U.S. stopover, Taiwan leader connects to Twitter https://t.co/UU7gf8uq6c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Singer Jennifer Holliday pulls out of inauguration performance https://t.co/HmPdgT8FfI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scores dead after migrant ship capsizes in Mediterranean https://t.co/RYyyTnZxCO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hyperpartisan Sites And Facebook Pages Are Publishing False Stories And Conspiracy Theories About Angela Merkel https://t.co/Id71m8RDoL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealAlexJones fake news]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CIA nominee says he would disregard Trump on torture https://t.co/X86lQq1aVb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump National Security Adviser Called Russian Envoy Day Before Sanctions Were Imposed https://t.co/UyYVow0pYl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@liamstack Technically Yediot Ahronot report republished by Haaretz.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sugarcubedog They rejected amendments that would have protected those parts of the law specifically, that's not the same as repealing them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sugarcubedog What are you talking about? I live in DC. They did not repeal those parts; they are unable to do so without 60 votes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sugarcubedog No they didn't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Britain, Turkey, Greece meet to discuss Cyprus settlement https://t.co/SFZ4wL2llE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Samsung chief questioned as suspect in national corruption scandal https://t.co/M66xDvdIle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Financial Mystery Emerges. Its Name? Steven T. Mnuchin Inc. https://t.co/F1z78GavOi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@usweekly fuck that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chamber of Commerce to Trump: Don't mess with trade https://t.co/Db1VMvlRVi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caroline Kennedy, an Ambassador Whose Role Transcended the Embassy https://t.co/dLtsD1tCB5]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>