<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmodoh @jo_moir Ah grasshopper. Life's successes are not determined by how you travel but where you get off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmodoh Save your sledging for when you're winning. How did an ocker get so snobbish?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah Wellington as the hottest month of the year kicks off. Shall I compare it to a summer's day? Yeah, nah. https://t.co/BMFxhxMdN1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe I'm being unfair but on the face of it Thiel's citizenship documents remind me of nothing so much as an honorary university degree.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thiel resided as a permanent resident in NZ over 5 years for (redacted) days. Looks like the black ink covers two digits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thiel did not meet "presence in NZ" or "intention to continue to reside". Exceptional circumstances = enterpreneurship and philanthropy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Officials reveal businessman Peter Thiel attended a private citizenship ceremony at the New Zealand Consulate in Santa Monica in August 2011]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[English nominates the 'Goldilocks' election date: https://t.co/wk6XzXNPuq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robhosking @philiplyth kind. Did pick Sept 23 last yr and more recently but deservedly punished for wavering when English first took over.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[June 23 is start of regulated period for election advertising spending says Electoral Commission.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[English talking a balance of infrastructure, spending, debt reduction and income improvements across the board. So family tax package on!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[English refuses to rule anything in or out when it comes to Winston Peters as deputy PM.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[English says NZ First an unlikely partner but he would be prepared to talk to them depending on the outcome of the election]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[English says National will have an ambitious and positive programme for the Sept 23 election.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Election date is September 23]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does the date really matter. Only if it's really early or late ... and because it is a nerd-off between pundits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Speculating whether a spring winter or summer campaign is best. Then we realised all dates are winter campaigns in Wellington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Cullen" Super Fund earned 13.2% in 2016. Worth $32.7 billion, &gt; twice the $14.88b Govt has put in. Annual return of 9.9% since inception.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Morgan Foundation's CoS Geoff Simmons to stand in the Mt Albert by-election for Gareth Morgan's Opportunites Party to :"Make NZ fair again".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unemployment rate rose to 5.2% in December 2016 quarter (up from 4.9% in the previous 1/4) while employment and labour force grew - Stats NZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ministry staffer alleged to have helped foreign firm prepare licence application https://t.co/icL0jlNCG8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnJCampbell indeed. May have missed the plane but that might have been the wiser option- though tracked the win on cricinfo in the taxi!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I left the ground to head to the airport when Aust were nine down. This may have been a strategic error.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmodoh @CTrevettNZH He is ducking well. Wish you were here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@metcalph Outwards and flipped upwards ... since you ask! Sort of comb-forward flap maybe?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Revelation1 from State of Nation speeches: Sign language for Donald Trump is a hand flipped up on the forehead like (an orange) lock of hair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmodoh @DeborahMTNZ We can't all wear a suit every waking hour, mate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There seems to be general enthusiasm for Turei's idea of Andrew Little as the next PM at the joint Labour-Green state of the nation speeches]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Metiria Turei delivering opening speech at joint state of the nation with Andrew little - as the Spark comms issues seem to get resolved!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jo Goodhew drops out of Rangitata election contest https://t.co/TobP4vG89X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmodoh Why, thank you. May I help in return with the day of the week. It's Tuesday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The minimum wage will rise by 50c to $15.75 an hour on April 1. The starting-out and training rate will go from $12.20 to $12.60 an hour.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump signals one-on-one trade deals with NZ, TPP countries https://t.co/4s0fUQuXpu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rumpole3 @philquin But is there one fool?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's the right thing to do. https://t.co/OpucRFDdCT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisEichbaum Have you looked at Moolah which was advertising on tv the other day. AIR 51 to 547%]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Standard and Poor’s has reaffirmed NZ's AA foreign currency and AA+ local currency sovereign credit ratings with a stable outlook.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["[As a] busy politician + family man you don't have time for skeletons, you're just in the closet trying to find the other shoe." PM English]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kiwi businessman Chris Liddell named as assistant to Donald Trump https://t.co/x6H5slcnuM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoy the breeze that's on the way. Son has bailed out for the capital! https://t.co/msvy7rkB7b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Green lawyer hopes to be first refugee to win a seat in Parliament  https://t.co/NmOzqIRGNa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The NZ Govt plans to ban the sale or manufacture of personal care products containing plastic microbeads, Environment Min Nick Smith says]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hilary_Barry Very jealous - was there last week but they were a no show for us. I guess the weather was too bad even for them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What ever happened to the recheck lane at vehicle testing @vtnz? Another long wait for quick OK puts you off using them again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarristerNZ it looks like it only a couple are concentrating.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrfreemannz @damienmgrant  The hours of pain ... it feels only like yesterday. Maybe veterans' lightning chess?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah yes now I remember. The NZ Chess Championships Wellington 2017 is winding up today. https://t.co/nJlNLbSVDl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's very sad news. A thoroughly kind and erudite man. https://t.co/z2D5vStRIB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Selwyn_Manning Cold. cold ...  so cold ... losing consciousness ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah a roaring fire in the Speights ale house a hint of sleet and 9deg outside. A great Summer's day in Invercargill.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heading to far south and Stewart Island this week for "summer" holiday as forecast warns of frosts. Is there a word, or an emoji for that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israel's reaction to the UN resolution plus threats reminiscent of "fog in the channel, Europe cut off" joke from the UK in the 50s.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nelson's Saxton Oval. Where bowling averages go to die eh? Looking forward to that. https://t.co/c2t7tZyK5l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just paid $7 more for an Air NZ ticket to invercargill than it would have cost to get to Tahiti. Will be good to see younger son though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why am I looking for political symbolism in this? Why? It's summer holiday for @&amp;"0 sake. https://t.co/swQoClphVP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems China knew about the steel dumping probe on Monday. https://t.co/NutlInwdFq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephenJacobi I see the report in the Chinese media and your approval of them as following WTO rules. Hardly = MBIE opening informing NZ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephenJacobi I don't think gazetting something without a press release shows huge commitment to openness do you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephenJacobi where?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So MBIE quietly slips out just before Xmas its decision to hold an inquiry into Chinese steel dumping.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labour (Ardern) versus Greens (probably Genter) in Mt Albert - seems to offer tactical National voters intriguing options for mischief.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelcolhoun I am bereft of an answer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Room for confusion over ministers Paula Bennett and David Bennett.when we use surnames only.  Might I respectfully suggest B1 and B2?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LynnGrieveson @BrookSabin I reckon. Just seemed incredibly tame alongside Brook's catalogue of wildlife ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found myself watching demolition of 61 Molesworth St while I wait for my lift home. You gotta make your own festive fun Mum always said.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrookSabin excellent. We nearly ran over a tortoise in the south of Greece - sigh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidClarkNZ Yea I know. When I get a few more years under my belt ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying to decide if Todd Barclay that popular in caucus, given the Twitter love on his re-selection...or if MPs just don't like challenges.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[National list MP Nuk Korako has been re-selected in the Port Hills electorate for 2017, where Labour's Ruth Dyson is the sitting MP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steven Joyce aka Pool Shark. is lining up tax thresholds but warns of overseas threats to rosy economic outlook  https://t.co/rDcsd3uhU6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@felixmarwick yep - that's the return match]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Finance Minister Steven Joyce casually suggests a game of bar room pool, be very cautious ....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For thems who cares; Roy Morgan poll puts Nats down 4.5% to 45, Lab up 5.5 to 28.5, Greens 14.5, NZ First at 7.5%. Maori 1, Act 0.5, UF 0%.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toby_etc @robhosking Don't try yr pro-intellectual snobbery here mate. Check out how many Nat lost to Lab on party vote (non-Maori seats).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toby_etc @robhosking @jgmccl More to the point why quote a party vote when electorate vote went another way and this is an electorate vote?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suggest headline should be 45% of Americans not bothered ... https://t.co/3uq3PMjOma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[National will not run a candidate in Mt Albert byelection on Feb 25 says PM English]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Definitely way to go. And they cite small claims tribunal wrongly when there's no precedent value even if there are… https://t.co/K4wM7LrYDa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[61 Molesworth St as of Sunday. Dec 18, 2016 https://t.co/RcG5bI9xfC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rumpole3 Or "why not me?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And every colleague/academic/pundit has probably gone: Meh. https://t.co/Rl5wnupGaQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Confess to feeling a bit antsy. More than 24 hours and no ministerial career-ending announcements.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former GG Sir Jerry Mateparae confirmed as our High Commissioner in London]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Foreign Minister Murray McCully confirms he will not be back after the 2017 election.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The House has risen for Xmas. It passed 107 bills; 98 Govt, 4 members 3 prvte and 2 local .There were 1055 oral and 15,445 written questions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minister Craig Foss joins the conga line of exiting MPs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Shearer follows Phil Goff's lead and has one last nostalgic meal on Copperfields https://t.co/iiEEXDvf7I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does Stuart Nash know he is in shot on Parliament TV? A study in wanting to be somewhere else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Cabinet reshuffle two-step begins. Sam Lotu-Iiga will not seek re-election in 2017. Does that mean Alfred Ngaro gets ethnic affairs?.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Govt bosses pay: Av increase base pay Public Service CEs: 1.3%. Crown entity CEs: 3.4%. PSCE salaries 5.5 X employees. Cost of  PSCEs $14.3m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Key: I'm the kind of person who likes to be liked."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So it's farewell from John Key. His last stand up on the tiles as PM. https://t.co/DUBeM4fUC9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[English signals he is unlikely to take a portfolio a la Key and tourism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill English does a bit of Lit Crit crossed with social commentary on his "digging up diamonds" quote from a poem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[English says he will deal in the new year with the election date but will not be driven by Labour's internal problems.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[English says he is not making the same pledge (to quit if superannuation changes) as John Key.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[English says "I don't think gay marriage is a threat to anyone else's marriage ...in some ways it's an affirmation of the concept."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[English says on the word stage NZ will maintain the role of "honest broker".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cabinet reshuffle will be later this week and certainly before Christmas says Bill English. "There will be change."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PM-elect English quotes poem "lead and dig up the diamonds around you".]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>