<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@wildobaggins kinda agree but .com just wanted to change govt, I feel like PT has far more sinister motives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@badtom @ShakingStick wow a whole million, many generous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@doctorsynth @washingtonpost believe me, we're just thrilled to have him here ðŸ˜•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Them geezers wot did that research into SAD in the UK should get down here, I reckon Wellington would be a pretty interesting case study rn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MICFlyger olive skin, beard, robes, talkin' some funny for'n language...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Trump saw Jesus in the street he'd be even more scared of him than he is of stairs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forget the election and immigration, I want to know what @pmbillenglish is proposing to deal with the state of @Wellington_NZ summer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BanksyBeeBoo @shaxhuxmo every freaking day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@loukoelzer Donald Trump puts too much milk in his tea and uses cutlery to eat pizza. He also can't pronounce the word "pillow".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crywank @TheACCnz can't beat a good pressed ham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grantrobertson1 @Garage_Project @NZStuffBusiness "you don't need to be bought to grow" awesome guys ðŸ‘ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShakingStick @ShaunKing sounds like ye olde "dead cat strategy"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Half my football team a few years back. Lovely lads, funny as hell and great players too https://t.co/k6Y4WonMze]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeerhiveBlog @TuataraBrew they're 1 of bigger players making decent (not huge) $ &amp; balancing w/innovation/agility/"craft". Goldilocks zone?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeerhiveBlog @TuataraBrew constant drive to produce more, get bigger, more $. Obv ignorant of personal circs. here bt would hav thought 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeerhiveBlog @TuataraBrew how much is "enough"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkDiStef @BuzzFeedNews maybe it's a hair thing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great, that saffer commentator is going to punish our ears during the #DreamFinal Mute button #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yet another example of NIMBYs shouting down solutions to the housing crisis  https://t.co/bQlIEAl711]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matthaig1 @Dovil it's totally like the end of Superbad with all the dick drawings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShakingStick Love the presumption from the leader of a party which literally polled 0.0% in Nov 2016 giving a "state of the nation" speech.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessEtheridge @ShakingStick never mind the nut, I can't get past the "mylk"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@baylandsbrewery hit up Hot Water Brewing, pretty sure they use them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What about this from @ish_sodhi ! https://t.co/uvi84LEVVP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[cycling home will be an adventure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnneWheaton yeah well according to the cheesecake box I am a family of four]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How am I just discovering @Houndmouth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaxhuxmo I get parameters to work within/every aspect nitpicked, for next time the parameters change (I'm not told, natch) rinse &amp; repeat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaxhuxmo my job is lit. your 1st point then same process 2w later but with shifted goalposts bc "we didn't like how you did it last time"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LadPolitics @toby_etc you got odds for "arrested after police chase broadcast live"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labour had nine long years to stop Trump repealing Obamacare.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SweatyJester tbf your head looks fuckin' delicious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Curtisgwalker "shit, nobody wants to be stuck there!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gerald Ford, you halfwits @NZStuff @SimpsonsQOTD https://t.co/0BjrDp69Og]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just noticed my shaving cream is "for external use only". Um, sure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@weirdwellington ooh ooh Mitchell &amp; Todman?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Better be a good wedding, @velosteo https://t.co/H5qUWzGqFt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StaceyKirkNZ you can't miss with any of them, pork belly is awesome, venison also ðŸ‘Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StaceyKirkNZ flag the burger, the beef cheek pie from fergbaker will change your life!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DylanReeve don't worry, I'm still on Breaking Bad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaxhuxmo @hownottodraw my 2017 will be great for the next couple of weeks but it's not too late for the new update and it will be the best]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2017 setting the bar high early for disgusting Wellington weather https://t.co/sArWPpOn16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One day* we'll all look back, smile wryly &amp; go "oh man, remember 2016, that shit was pretty bad." 
*unless Trump starts a nuclear war.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lqpharriet @Handsprings1 my biggest fear would be getting lots of weird responses, or more likely, none whatsoever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarfend @NZTAWgtn that's kiwirail replacing tracks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThatEricAlper Carmen Sandiego on 5 1/4" floppy disk. "Don't touch the write-protect tab". "Please insert disk 4"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aldersonnotes boy's got wheels...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnaGConnell I'll always wonder if that baboon ever made it to the moon!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnaGConnell my childhood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aldersonnotes @lancearmstrong @Lion_NZ @nzherald Is there a more bitter man in NZ than SS? It was 22 years ago, move on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Andrew_Mulligan @DuncanGarnerNZ at what point do we start referring to Duncan as Yoko?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HaydenDonnell @TheSpinoffTV ...burglar-proof your home; pic of the PM on Xmas Day...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HaydenDonnell @TheSpinoffTV also: avoid food poisoning at BBQ; swim between flags; sunscreen; NYD hangover cures; arrests at the Mt...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it's not even 0900 and almond crunching motherfucker is steaming into those bad boys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZMorningReport @dbseymour seems like every time you're interviewed you have to explain yourself on twitter. Maybe work on your message.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The thing that always gets me about watching Home Alone as an adult is the horrible pain &amp; lasting damage those traps would inflict]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tina_nguyen 's hilarious takedown of Tump's horrible Grille(e) will be one of the best things you read all week https://t.co/GMakTnY9mn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hipsterroadie cool! https://t.co/cYNVNqrNwv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anirvan Steve Bannon always looks like he needs a bloody good wash]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteveBraunias Are all bags not "tote bags"? What is a bag for, if not toting things? Asking for a friend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cucumbers are fucking shit, as is cucumber gin and anything with celery in it https://t.co/jIVNXdtKs1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A real estate twat has left a flyer boasting about a local sale he made which was double the RV. Congratulations Mike Robbers. Apt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaxhuxmo I'm in a "team strategy workshop", beat that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@david8hughes "s-m-r-t, I mean s-m-a-r-t"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I agree with @Andrew_Mulligan cricket is cancelled for the summer #ausvnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are Australia so much better at reviewing than NZ? Always right v always wrong #ausvnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, nice one Munro. (Remember those ads?)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Young teenage girls with faux-American accents, what is that about]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shit this is money https://t.co/s4YuVQjuAE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaxhuxmo people are downright confused that I've refused to go to ours tomorrow. "But it's a party!" My time, my choice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Send down some more half volleys you fucking morons @BLACKCAPS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaxhuxmo there is a woman who sits near me who has crystals on her desk to absorb the excess electricity from her computer monitor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dovil Coleman already is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anitathetweeter @ShakingStick I'm surprised she was ok with having her picture taken with a horse that isn't white]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheACCnz I'd like to draw your attention to Adam Zampa's Alice band #AUSvNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SweatyJester looks like he should be robbing car stereos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[all the guy next to me does all day is crunch almonds and crack his fingers, fuck I hate other people's noises]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lqpharriet you must have seen this https://t.co/HB6ulTLz24]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was my birthday yesterday and each year I'm grateful to my Mum for not letting me get a haircut like MacGuyver when I was a kid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the best photo of the year https://t.co/NIpLwjOeh2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/2 OIC thundered "Police investigate homicide. Juries determine murder!" I felt about a foot tall! https://t.co/leKg69444S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/2 This reminds me of my first police press conference as a young journo. I asked about "the murder inquiry".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@janikaterellen @GraemeEdgeler the way this year's gone, would anyone really be surprised?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markmywordsCGW please give us an entertaining diatribe on India's constant overappealing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do people say "tuna fish", I mean what other kids of tuna are there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this is perfect https://t.co/0gqH0i1yx2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edmuzik @ShakingStick I hate "erys". Drinkery. Beanery. Chippery. So twee.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSpinoffTV sure, but when is "safe"? Risk always there. If every single building fully checked, city would be closed for a year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not allowing myself lunch until I've finished editing a document and I'm procrastinating because I'm hungry. This is how I starve to death.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drivethrupod @katieabradford nah, twas Crampton. High prices prevent a few buying it all was the argument, I think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katieabradford @drivethrupod a certain high-profile RW economist wrote a # of columns post Chch defending price-gouging etc. All hail $]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShakingStick @nzherald whatever Key's discomfort over Trump, there's a bit of him going "well, he does own heaps of sweet golf courses..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went to the dairy with @niksiedelrado and @hipsterroadie for milk. 5 hours, many pints and a pub quiz later, no milk. #winning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least someone's happy that I'm mostly stuck at home today https://t.co/FRTiWA2rVq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Antonio Conte looks like the guy Liam Neeson spends a whole movie coming after https://t.co/PO0ccoeQgg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WinstonAldworth @SimonNRicketts you didn't ask me, but @NicoleAtkins doing bird on a wire is gorgeous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["England lead 2-0, and through English eyes, the world is now a safer, better place". No hyperbole there. #EnglandvScotland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That iguana v snakes vid is very 2016. Every time you think you're out of the shit, there's MORE FUCKING SNAKES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the rules of buses is whenever they go past you they have to make that loud as fuck compressed air noise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After 7 years, 100,000km and countless awesome road trips, my little red Skode tootles away. See ya mate, we had fun https://t.co/8MWw0zDpAC]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>