<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[A hero and a reporter. Today reporters should also be brave, achieve the impossible and fight for justice. Behave a… https://t.co/Y8cKuclmfb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I gained 20 followers in the last week. You? Know your stats and grow with https://t.co/vSYKgiZ2ZH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please read. Really Love this story. Thanks @AndreaVieira100 for telling me about it. Abigail Gray Swartz https://t.co/DfS9bJuvkQ @newyorker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another friendly makeover. Worth looking at! https://t.co/ySB0UmHIoL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just a friendly commentary on fashion from CQ. This is funny stuff. https://t.co/48CDKeYcWg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do they use them? Is common sense still around? https://t.co/Mh4cAJYY1c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 people followed me and 2 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/CGI62As15T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @saharcastic @MonnaKashfi @isilmengi @ElaineReyesTV @AndreaVieira100 and all my @cgtnamerica friends for suc… https://t.co/z9yySAgSfn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for a wonderful day. Began my morning with the best coffee ever and wrapped up with a basketball night game. Ain't a lonely planet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Achachay" https://t.co/Ee7UHyqpDc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such a Bilingual country. Wait a sec! Wasn't quichua what they were promoting? Correa's English is such fantástico… https://t.co/rVv3HfKU1n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Refugee ban could be used as ISIL recruiting tool, some say  https://t.co/JhXzIya2QN via @USATODAY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We will hunt monsters," he said. https://t.co/4sKONeJVEU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dory may run away for good. We will never see her again. Bye bye sequel. https://t.co/j3sF5A3GyY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very eloquent and clear explanation by @franifio #thewall https://t.co/w2UzI4IMBo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the North Pole to the South Pole.DelPolo norte al Polo Sur / Corona Let’s make America great again https://t.co/OJDTcJcfbo via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is super funny. And this is also what we are: a very diverse team of talented and charming people! Hahaha Kiki… https://t.co/aM21GZISZN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder how would it be with Putin. #HoldingHands https://t.co/V3g7EDzoRP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such a wake up call. Great story by @leloveluck https://t.co/QvYnlmZhXR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8 people followed me and 3 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/CGI62As15T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Record man https://t.co/9XeMTjG6ev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The night. https://t.co/BS8vFbM2In]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know what that means people: get your tequila today! And Margaritas tonight! https://t.co/3sTQBi3HAZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I kind of agree. https://t.co/xLR4sSMhNQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know who are awesome? My 13 new followers in the last week! Growing with https://t.co/vSYKgiZ2ZH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You look like a movie. You sound like a song ..." / Turkish musician claims he is Adele's REAL father https://t.co/VaFCQNCuPe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are the best Spanish student I have ever had @moubrava I am sure @julio_aliaga is very proud too! https://t.co/gQQKfHA15O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please note the date at the bottom of that picture. The inauguration was on the 20th or the 21st? Just offering alt… https://t.co/JRw9jhalOV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unas Alitas para cerrar el día. Hungry? Get $10 off your first order on #UberEATS with my code: eats-josev7344ue. https://t.co/PLOsBBGWxT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great pic @gerryhadden
Looking forward to see this! (You probably meant to tag @joselevelasquez with S and Z, haha). https://t.co/strn2MW5u8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 people followed me and 4 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/CGI62As15T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#trump asking some 50 top members of the #Obama administration to stay including undersecretary Tom Shannon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning Donald! Thinking about you and how thinks will be scrambled very soon. Trump #Inauguration https://t.co/RMt1bakO2c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_the_islander Hahaha i didn't post that! It is automatic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump is millions of miles away from Lincoln.
Remember that in the South, African Americans (former slave descenda… https://t.co/6jRaLM8eiL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[January 19th. The last day of Barack and Michelle #Obama at the White House. Many of those who celebrate today will soon miss them. No doubt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will be missed. Nobody can never take your place. https://t.co/xHQLWD0MAW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know who are awesome? My 21 new followers in the last week! Growing with https://t.co/vSYKgiZ2ZH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomcolicchio @davebernstein That hair under the rain would look like melting butter. 
Can I have your recipe for Eggs Benedict?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crack! https://t.co/TbzMUMnlLP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Easy now. Take it easy. https://t.co/IPMxhyBy4W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So what happened here @wikileaks ? You didn't know @Potus was going to do it? You couldn't hack the info? Will your… https://t.co/D8BvE1qdT0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His brother from another mother // Putin says Russian prostitutes are 'best in the world' as he slams Trump dossier https://t.co/18qvIBY0pj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can’t wait to hear more about #InvestingSustainably at #WEF17 from @BofA_News! You can too, what interests you? https://t.co/eJUx5jucnu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A snack made in Ukraine with a very Latino (and maybe inappropriate) name. Peanuts can be Macho too. https://t.co/pxVCCApJv4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love when civil society spontaneously gets it together and speaks out. #trump https://t.co/PRU8Cc3NRp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This song is about to make me cry. I had forgotten about it. Thanks for bringing it up. It is a great song. Made my… https://t.co/ALPOpvNhGi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About time, I would say. Seven years in jail sounds enough for what he did. #ObamaLegacy https://t.co/W0VGKfQi7v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great investigative piece by @joel_richards on the "triple border"
Really enjoyed it @cgtnamerica 
https://t.co/zDkqZlFNx3…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dying for these pork sandwiches from @perubrothers  Now, who is with me? @cgtnamerica @chriss_pena @ElaineReyesTV 
https://t.co/J9zbFahykO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two icons of hope: #martinlutherking and #BarackObama.
A place in history for the beloved president who changed thi… https://t.co/HY8mRo1d9S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump will take office as the least popular president since the 70s
Obama had 81% approval on inauguration day, Bush 60%, Trump 40% CNNpoll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Papá lagarto! A lo bestia!! / This giant alligator looks like a dinosaur https://t.co/aFe6Xwfajf via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alecbaldwin made my day! / Trump Press Conference Cold Open from Saturday Night Live on https://t.co/GCvlz6m9XS —  https://t.co/MuNw60HO6Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 people followed me and 2 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/CGI62As15T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tranquilos: "Avanzamos" pero no sabemos a dónde
Ecuador has begun drilling for oil in the world’s richest rainforest https://t.co/1fhopD8acv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amelia_draper This is my first year in DC and my children Ana and Joaquin are dying to see more snow. Please tell them snow will come soon!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the circus industry dying or has it just mutated and moved to the political arena? https://t.co/ikzFAm3toe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amelia_draper @nbcwashington No numbers or spelling. It does not matter. There is no excuse for bringing down a student. (I prefer words!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is an understandable reaction but why Cubans should have preference over other immigrants? It has been an advant… https://t.co/69KO9Ljkz1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's inauguration planning meeting. @cgtnamerica https://t.co/YCGf3i2bFN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT? What are the chances? https://t.co/cWAG7WJQg7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need the address please! https://t.co/LzoE6ylw6S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seanspicer @GlennKesslerWP Because the only person allowed to be out of line is the Donald.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forget unfollowers, I believe in growing. 22 new followers in the last week! Stats via https://t.co/vSYKgiZ2ZH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[17 people followed me and 11 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/CGI62As15T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do we really need to? We already know is bad. https://t.co/vEQcNKeoFe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need a four year-long nap https://t.co/Mh61kHFDld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you very much Mr. Roboto. https://t.co/9TIGo9IKbC https://t.co/FOslFG7tZg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I agree. Seven years is enough. https://t.co/C0tcQ6nNt4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I share your sentiments about punks and bullies. Enough is enough." Robert De Niro to Meryl Streep.
Next stop? De… https://t.co/lquvEx0W8s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He never gave a straight answer. Twice the same question. Twice the same dance move. https://t.co/qoGL2jbsLZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mega super tweet! A lo Bestia. Jajaja https://t.co/qF6eQ562t1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["That, after all, is why we serve. Not to score points or take credit, but to make people’s lives better." @POTUS Maestro! #ObamaFarewell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a rock star! It is painful watch him leave. https://t.co/8tpOJQXg4Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Making America Great Again." Here we go!
Such a sad story. https://t.co/cC26sNCvnE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NitzaSoledad @cgtnamerica Let's! Thanks Nitza!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NitzaSoledad @cgtnamerica I lived in Miami for two years and never knew. Next time I stop by I will love to go!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zero emotional intelligence. Such a vulnerable person, so exposed to manipulation. https://t.co/JRqPOpoZUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pants on fire. https://t.co/FbN1CoR6vB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She is only the most awarded person in the history of filmmaking. It is like climate change: deny it even tough is… https://t.co/XXMVWkKCp0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marin Le Pen. Like Donald and Johnson. Spooky! Let's just build a big wall!!! https://t.co/odEeP2hqLh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @_the_islander 
This one is for you! LOL https://t.co/nLElKOcdnk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In case you didn't notice @realDonaldTrump she is talking about you. And as she said, we will be watching.  We won'… https://t.co/tXA7zi3AsW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sfcallebs @NBCNews @cgtnamerica Too brief of a package to talk about something so important. Dont know if it is a series. Maybe more on web]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Distracted by Facebook? By Twitter? By an empty social live? This might be the reason you're procrastinating https://t.co/R2f2XVGOwn @wef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morellamorenoz "Who are you wearing?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go gators! A Game Changer in Colombia saving endangered crocodiles. https://t.co/B5AifGd9OA @cgtnamerica #AmericasNow
Thanks @mbegue !!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A glance to a Miami neighborhood with an artistic soul
Great piece by @NitzaSoledad for Americas Now @cgtnamerica    https://t.co/QMPN6jRKIv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NBCNews just aired a slim pkg on the opioid epidemic. Very proud Americas Now aired last month a @sfcallebs mini d… https://t.co/KP1O3fQ79F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crack!!! https://t.co/uML2GjXefH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is beautiful Yeyyyy!!! https://t.co/NImmHNGuBq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michelle Obama. I miss you already. You are the biggest rock star in the planet. Smart, charming and human. https://t.co/O4r8dTvIgs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Head clown"? Is this the way a US president should behave? Calling names and insulting? https://t.co/J4Kzshvser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should it be a show? Am I missing something? Is he missing something? https://t.co/e4IGRHRhnk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ecuador stands for Biodiversity. Ilike it! / This map shows what every country in the world is best at doing https://t.co/4UysjYlONC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not a very "creative list". You clearly haven't been in Buenos Aires or Havana. Necessity is the mother of inventio… https://t.co/3NqTKVA06n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bergenmatters sounds like a plan!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bergenmatters  Hey John. Yes there is. Did you know I am living in DC? We should meet one of these days. Say hi to Dennis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[15 people followed me and 7 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/CGI62As15T]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>