<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Doing exercise &amp; mindfulness when you have a severe migraine is too late. These services need to be offered before #medicationnation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The problem is a lack of real solutions.GP services are hugely under-resourced &amp; have nothing else to offer #medicationnation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes. People do not get that addiction can be to prescription &amp; legal over the counter drugs. There's huge denial #medicationnation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MittieHelyAmy I don't get how it's even affecting @NicolaMcLean 's life @planetjedward being in #Speidi 's bed #CBB Any excuse with her]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SlayAllDayBey @planetjedward @bbuk deleted from Facebook? I think #CBB are showing their true colours. Such a stitch up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RedJed7 Totally agree. That was shameful on the part of @bbuk #CBB They're easy targets, but the show is allowing it. Such double standards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EamonnHolmes You'd defend a nasty bully like her? I don't think she need you to she has enough claws for everyone #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bbuk @TheLuluLife @NicolaMcLean @planetjedward I think the judging process was so easy on Nicole.She's so much worse &amp; totally deluded #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spencerpratt If it was @planetjedward throwing around the water, there would be war. Hypocrites lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MissKatiePrice OMG! Good for you. Disgusting man picking on a child]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calum on the drink after one argument. How would he take Nicola sticking the knife into him for weeks like @planetjedward have @bbuk #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nicole loves angry Calum cos she's a massive sh*t stirrer. That's literally her only purpose in life #ReginaGeorge @bbuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stacyfrancis @bbuk What tips would you give?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calum can give it but can't take it.I actually liked him,but he's not taking being nominated well.Why is he the authority on Jedward? @bbuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Funniest thing is Nicola thinks she's the victim @bbuk typical bully. Zero insight in her own behaviour.Anyone else woulda blown ages ago]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I HATE bullies so much. @bbuk  this is honestly disgraceful the way @planetjedward are being treated. Tolerating Nicola's abuse for weeks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why has @NicolaMcLean not got called up on her BULLYING @bbuk You're not a good man @CalumBest You're Nicola's puppet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NicolaMcLean is a TYPICAL bully girl... She'll only face @planetjedward when it's on HER terms &amp; she needs her pack behind always @bbuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woah... Why did @CalumBest  tell Jamie to "respect the vote'? @bbuk Totally lost respect for him,pack mentality.Nicola's puppet #TeamJedward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bbuk @planetjedward @CalumBest @channel5_tv I think Calum is the one who needs to take notes. He can't see the light "gentleman" my arse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bbuk @planetjedward @CalumBest @channel5_tv You can't keep coming and coming for someone, Nicola and expect them never to come back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bbuk @planetjedward @CalumBest @channel5_tv Nicola has picked on them from day 1 and is constantly going at them &amp; now playing the victim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bbuk @planetjedward @CalumBest @channel5_tv OMG Finally Jedward stand up to Regina George aka Nicola McMean]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StigAbell  Oh.My.God..Poor baby. Truly, truly heartbreaking &amp; sickening. There are no words]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Corrie yasmeen's acting is the worst I've seen in a long time #cringeworthytv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can @adamthomas21 do every trial? I'm still in convulsions #imacelebrity keep him in #entertainmentvalue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#imacelebrity Adam This is THE funniest trial I've seen in the jungle. Ever. The reactions. Proper convulsing with laughter 😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JMalaulau I think that was getting off lightly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whatisgoingon0 Omg Lol. You are too much. Take your fake joke account somewhere else 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whatisgoingon0 you don't realise how much of a hypocrite your opinion makes you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whatisgoingon0 are you saying I'd need to ref a different match to actually use my eyes &amp; see the calls were WRONG in this one?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#IREvNZL frustrating.From NZL dangerous tackles, all the Ire injuries, to 2 tries NZL shouldn't have got due to lying/blind match officials]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cooper_m it's scary. I think it's one of their dirty tactics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok that was a forward pass #IREvNZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can Ireland not have a try, they're doing everything? #coybig my nerves]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spectacular catch by Andrew Trimble #IREvNZL match highlight #COYBIG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That TMO is either blind or a liar #irelandrugby #IREvNZL @rte]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheXFactor is too long. An hour to find out who stays. It's too much to ask of a person. I'm getting old here  #XFactor #XFactorResults]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mf3101 @GameOfThrones Yes.. PLEEeeeeASE  #epicness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When someone who is the biggest #GameofThrones fan &amp; THE biggest #AngelaLansbury fan hears their two most favourite things could join #epic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Terry_Calab @_AngelaLansbury that is class.. Yaaaasss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_AngelaLansbury @EW what? That would be EPiC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrankieJGrande loved the sparkles &amp; glitter tonight #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope Bear wins. He's been the most entertaining for good or bad #cbbfinal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The two bffs Ricky &amp; Bear in the final #cbb @bbuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaudyTear @bbuk lol he really is a nice person, but his personality just never came out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#cbb I think from this series people will remember Bear &amp; even Renee, but I don't think anyone will remember Ricky #cbb @bbuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a feeling Ricky might win.But I think he was too boring, he didn't bring enough of anything to the series to b the winner #cbb @bbuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealJamesArgent @stephen_bear I think people are trying to sabotage Bear with fix claims #cbb but he's the winner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bbuk @FrankieJGrande I was shocked Aubrey &amp; Renee didn't go before Frankie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh for God's sake Renee. You gave as good as you got &amp; more. You're no victim #cbb @bbuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Bear is insignificant sh** why r Renee &amp; Aubrey investin such energy in him,Renee cryin &amp; screamin.&amp;Aubrey w/face like slapped arse #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aubrey is so controlling of Frankie. Poor Frankie. She's trying to dull his sparkle.Squashing others doesn't make you bigger #cbb @bbuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frankie is in absolute hell lol #cbb @bbuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The more I see of Renee the more sickened I am at the kind of person she is. Nasty, threatening, bullying hypocrite crazy person #cbb @bbuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woooaaah did Renee just actually make a real threat there towards Bear with "kinda pple she knows" That is beyond nasty #CBB @bbuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiteraryPop @docslabsf @losertakesall omg! I'm obsessed with this show. Jessica Fletcher is my hero]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some sunshine 🌞🌞 #lateIrishSummer #please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GraceESaunders @stephen_bear yes. He apologised to her &amp; the whole time she was at fault #justiceforbear #cbb @bbuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarnieGShore standing up to the mean girls tonight on @bbuk just shows what a genuine girl she is standing by her friends #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loved how @MarnieGShore stood up for Chloe Khan tonight.Renee thought she could dog her cus she wasn't there to defend herself #cbb @bbuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bbuk Bear, Ricky or Marnie for the win. I feel sorry for Frankie, the mean girls has him scared to step out of line #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RICKY, MARNIE or BEAR for the win #CBB @bbuk #celebritybigbrother]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aubrey has Frankie marching to her tune &amp; she's still dragging the poor guy through the mud #cbb @bbuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aubrey says "we're all equals in here" after she's trashed everyone in the house for being lower than her #cbb @bbuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aubrey thinks the public needs their head examined? Lol #cbb @bbuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aubrey played at Madison square garden as part of PDiddy's band. She did nothing on her own #cbb @bbuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've lost all respect for Aubrey &amp; Renee after tonight's show. I hope Bear wins #cbb @bbuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Renee already broke her own rule to not talk to Bear.Frankie looks terrified to speak. That's abusive. He can't talk to someone? #cbb @bbuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So now Frankie is being told he can't talk to Bear? What bullies are the mean girls #cbb @bbuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did @bbuk not warn Renee for causing sh** to go off by winding Bear up &amp; starting a fight with him in bedroom? But Bear is warned? #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Daily_Star everything with Aubrey is full psycho #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aubrey spits in Bear's food. Throws food all over his bed &amp; Bear is the one who's always warned? Come on @bbuk #cbb #doublestandards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Aubrey nominates/bitches bout someone it's not personal, but as soon as someone nominates her or says a bad word she goes psycho #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aubrey is trying to manipulate Frankie now telling him not to talk to Bear. When she is so two faced &amp; manipulative herself #CBB @bbuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Renee knows well Bear wasn't threatening her. She's the one always issuing threats saying she's gonna finish everyone #cbb @bbuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CBBBear is always saying sorry, but #CBBAubrey &amp; #CBBRenee are just bitter. A custard pie in the face? For God's sake lighten up @bbuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are Aubrey &amp; Renee never reprimanded when they are constantly starting on Bear? #CBB @bbuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel sorry for #CBBBear now. Why do @bbuk keep calling Bear to the diary room for doing the same things that Renee &amp; Aubrey do?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrPhil "it takes two to tango &amp; he doesn't want to dance" thank you Dr.Phil for telling it like it is #coryknowsbest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TessARooo62 @DrPhil Elizabeth needs to leave this abusive fossil for the sake of her baby &amp; herself. He doesn't deserve anyone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#coryknowsbest people only act like this cus people let them get away with it #drphil if this behav wasn't tolerated it would change]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel sorry for this guy's kids. Guys like this should not be allowed infect  the future generation with their abuse #coryknowsbest #drphil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was absolutely amazing McLeod from Jamaica for gold #Olympics2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidGillick @TomBarr247 delighted I was up to see that. Thanks insomnia #Olympics2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DervalORourke @TomBarr247 loving your work Derval. Well done Thomas Barr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insomnia has its advantages sometimes @RTEsport #Olympics2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RTEsport delighted I stayed up to see Thomas Barr for #teamireland #Olympics2016 qualify as a finalist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How cute is Sonia O Sullivan bringing her lucky horseshoe into studio for luck for #teamIreland A legend &amp; a genuine lady #Olympics2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JakeQuickenden Aubrey is the biggest player in there #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Xtrapromo @sleazeball once again, we're going to disagree 😄]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aisleyne1 but he doesn't care so she's only upsetting herself &amp; wasting her time #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@muminuh he's refused to lie down &amp; let her bully him &amp; he's unaffected by her threads &amp; insults #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sleazeball Renee's no angel. There's a pair of them in it. I actually think she's the worst out of the two #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sleazeball Renee's goin round runnin her mouth, talking tough, making threats &amp; if she could get better of him she wouldn't hold back #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilippaGrace13 Renee is a typical bully. She's threatening bully boy tactics &amp; when she can't get the upper hand she cries victim #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan poor Biggins. Are people that easily offended? @bbuk #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bbuk @onebiggins clearly meant no harm by what he said.He was having a discussion.U can't eject everyone who has an opinion you don't like]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bbuk how can you have reality programme when people can't voice real opinions? Let the public decide  #christopherbiggins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimmyosmond I'm watching this now. Love your positive attitude]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>