<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@martinmccluskey @RossMcCaff @Cat_Headley Martin you know we ALL need one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RossMcCaff @Cat_Headley @martinmccluskey haha! Was going to say same. Will get some printed off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cat_Headley @martinmccluskey why does Martin look Photoshopped?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dani Garavelli: May caught in Trump’s post-truth trap https://t.co/Y67XKYIXQq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kezia Dugdale: Labour will never support second referendum https://t.co/U5xHEoOxma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emiliemcmeekan totally. Feel it's not as far fetched as it might otherwise be. You're welcome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iainmartin1 feel light-hearted after watching that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why support for indyref2 has barely increased since Brexit vote https://t.co/TxK0upcgQf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrantStottOnAir OMG. What have I missed??? Is this Brexit related?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redhotraggle Obv need to hightail it out of there!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sturgeon: "we will consider reasonable proposals on our budget".
Scottish Labour doesn't believe £327m cuts to local services is reasonable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brianjaffa not a lot of laughs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CT_Microbiol you're welcome. How's the head today?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EwanAitken @lyceumtheatre such drama, for want of a better word. So well staged, excellent actors, and brilliant music and sound.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EwanAitken @lyceumtheatre isn't it fantastic ? So eerie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drew_matheson couldn't be happier for them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drew_matheson I know, but the body language in that video is loud and clear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrsCupcake79 the difference is amazing. Another thing to miss about the Obamas - their obvious, open love and respect for each other.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Melania looks like she cannot bear her husband.
BBC News - Presidential inaugural ball: Trumps enjoy first dance https://t.co/gCnKUCdnei]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCJamesCook @MalcolmChishol1 more people than yesterday James?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@libertonhockey @CT_Microbiol your sympathy is overwhelming :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sandradick @CT_Microbiol @libertonhockey ricochet off a stick. Hard to avoid!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProfArno @CT_Microbiol @libertonhockey ball had co.e down the opposition's right wing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doing my good Samaritan bit as ambulance for poor @CT_Microbiol
@libertonhockey better have won! https://t.co/Y43BPCLMVO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaniGaravelli1 good for you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaniGaravelli1 too much gin? :) you writing about the march or marching? I've a friend in US taking part in march in DC...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HumzaYousaf improvement plan Sept, PPM all over place since. 86%, 83%, 89%... target is 91.3% no? Looking forward to that by March end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HumzaYousaf @kezdugdale Scotrail apologising to passengers once every 51 minutes. PPM last met in July.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HumzaYousaf @kezdugdale one in ten trains late. Rolling PPM figure lower than this time last year. PPM MMA has never hit target. What lie?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@randallwrites @indiaknight as much as I love Phil, dignified isn't the word that springs to mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@randallwrites @indiaknight see Modern Family.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That speech has just ruined #Dryjanuary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This faux religious schtick is just the worst.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Patriotism and prejudice. Jane Austen decided against that title.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the people to his left are managing to keep quiet through this diatribe god only knows. Where is the "healing"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sniff has begun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's raining on his hair.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nicola was one of my inspirations when I started at @edinburghpaper a wonderful writer and journalist with a wicked wit This is just so sad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is just terrible news. https://t.co/P110eTpsCj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redhotraggle @hugorifkind @BuzzFeed I was the creme de la creme obvs!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KirstyStricklan aarrgggh! Just watched a clip. Absolutely appalling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KirstyStricklan what? It's gone...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redhotraggle whit? The man's a staunch 'burgher @hugorifkind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Labour government would hand back wealth and control to people and communities&amp;#8217; - Jeremy Corbyn https://t.co/gwKNGAKl7o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labour will be the voice of radical change - Kezia Dugdale https://t.co/XDYqA3ZLuI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Investigation: INEOS failed despite $129 million in taxpayer subsidies https://t.co/bHOWZyiAL7 via @tcpalm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@randallwrites ooh, I've got those satsumas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kenny__Stewart sorry, forgot experts no longer wanted :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thistlejohn @KayeNicolson @alistairkgrant @TheScotsman ah yes. I remember. Electric Circus. In @AndrewMarr9 days it was Buster Browns.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thistlejohn @KayeNicolson @alistairkgrant @TheScotsman @AndrewMarr9 where was this? You're right about my old lady memory....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thistlejohn @KayeNicolson @alistairkgrant @TheScotsman @AndrewMarr9 @edinburghpaper @ianswansonen you were Northern Soul dancing??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deputypics @PeterAlanRoss love that hsshtag #forevernorthbridge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrancisStuart1 Hi Francis, can you possibly follow me so I can DM you? Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brianjaffa @TheScotsman better be worth it Brian!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brianjaffa @TheScotsman you in it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A really important piece.
America, America https://t.co/kCHwr5bbrR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LucyHunterB @athole @MrMcEnaney remember all extra curricular activities being cancelled, particularly sport and lots of "at home" days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeoffShadbold hat! https://t.co/CYjZJP6vbP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomChivers @chrisdeerin @jamesdoleman no! though actually relieved. After which I washed my hands.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LucyHunterB and bookings to his casinos suddenly cancelled.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Oldmanmackie @MrMcEnaney thanks for that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardKerley @jamesdoleman boys are gross.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LucyHunterB haha! Or hand sanitizer and whip it out in front of him, dousing hands liberally, after the handshake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh. Dear. God. https://t.co/K3hFkmMMW7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@empowermint it's too late. they cant agree on something so basic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@empowermint they should give up now. Coffees to go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gadgeagoogoo misread that as emergency shoes...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrMcEnaney of course. I'd suggest we're trying to move things on, but the constitution keeps dragging everything into its vortex.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrMcEnaney agree.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In his head my dad's still riding the tiger - even though he's 77 today. https://t.co/t2fMRVM8Dy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelPDeacon haha! But that way lies Trump. You've a duty to your country Michael to have another.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelPDeacon wait til you have a daughter with v long hair. Soaks up sick like a sponge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IanDunt I like a couple of potato scones on a roll.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KennyFarq @HelenMilburn ah, the Jingler.... such.. er... vague memories...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LucyHunterB @severincarrell but the budget is not set. Changes can be made in Holyrood to give councils these tax freedoms.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really moving thread. https://t.co/0Y6tUe1YLF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@6038479 @KevinJPringle which is why a great many stories are derived from "data journalism" and FOIs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@6038479 @KevinJPringle sadly dwindling numbers of journalists employed by papers mean they don't have time to scrutinise properly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gordonguthrie @iainmartin1 @MarinaHyde *looks at Scarlett's leather jumpsuit, looks at own post-Christmas belly* ... not waiting for a call]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What hope for journalism when an editor resigns after just two weeks? https://t.co/Rb1CobJx0E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeoffShadbold she was great. Episode was miles better than last week's awful effort.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Liam_Beattie @muteswann @coffeebucks @Victoriaparkrun Liam there are parjruns at Porty and Cramond every Saturday morning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gary_Bainbridge the lights stay on our tree...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeoffShadbold will search out. Got a "new" Poirot the other month. So disappointing. Cheering up with Insp Montalbano.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeoffShadbold ooh. Don't know him at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scotsman editor in shock exit as anniversary looms  https://t.co/YmoxRBCohU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Labour's Kezia Dugdale says UK is Scotland's more important union https://t.co/0DFshANsP2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@euanmccolm sounds a cad and a bounder to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time for this.
https://t.co/xILIOtec2H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone built a dam in the trickle down effect... https://t.co/rMhnByfXFl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emiliemcmeekan have you read The Three by Sarah Lotz? Fantastic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheMainstand @MaureenChild1 @EdinburghLabour @JamTarts @EdiHelpingHands  have no idea what you're referring to. Always been a Hearts fan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheMainstand @MaureenChild1 @bighearts @JamTarts @EdiHelpingHands @holyroodboxing @JimSlaven I have no idea what this is about?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joepike saw this and thought of you! :) https://t.co/UhLPfvUAbG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gillian_Philip God knows.... the abominable bride was awful; last night's a mess. Tho I was glad Mary went. All downhill since she arrived.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy New Year people. It's starting pretty much as it ended in our house... MoTD on loop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GordonAikman such a good year already with you in it x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brendanjmcginty terrible news.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gary_Bainbridge who whipped out something surgical looking which opened door immediately. Once he left, first locksmith just said "SAS".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gary_Bainbridge then drill out the lock of front door from inside. But not before he called another locksmith with "special, own-made" tool]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>