<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@WooduLove Brilliant Ian... Wishing you all the best with your new career X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has anyone else ever talked to their #goldfish ?? Anyone?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WooduLove @VirginMediaIE @tescomobile is the best for value ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WooduLove hahaha little used it says... They look like they've been used since the 50's Now what a shame they missed Octobers bonfire ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you've had a really bad day #worsebeforeitgetsbetter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WooduLove @DoneDeal there are just no words. ðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@planetjedward just watched #LivingwithLucy John and Edward are two really lovely guys. Their mother must be so proud and so she should be x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FML I suppose in life every time you're feeling happy something comes along and kicks you in the nuts #sotospeak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@caroldecker i wouldn't say so ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WooduLove I'd put a match to that,, perfect for a bomb fire ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜·ðŸ˜·]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WooduLove I know.. And god forbid if you ask them to leave any money off something it's like Blasphemy .ðŸ˜ðŸ˜¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WooduLove sure look at the prices in oxfam Francis St. It's a bloody disgrace for a charity shop ðŸ˜¡ https://t.co/ZsCKn0f11C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WooduLove yep it's like going back in time but in a bad way. I like vintage but that stuffs shocking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WooduLove oh god I nearly threw up... Are these people for real ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#phoenixpark #Dublin #peaceful https://t.co/bHfJ5Y7NC0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WooduLove That's great news.. So did I four weeks ago. Love it ðŸ‘ŒðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NarcissisticDub D is for dope ðŸ˜œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#BadMoms what a shite movie ðŸ‘ŽðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HauntedHour I've lots of photos that have a rope like item in them. They freak me out don't know what it could be ðŸ˜¦]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And also out of anybody on the planet, why am I dreaming about Brian Dowling?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dreamt last night that Brian Dowling was my son. What the hell was that about?  he's nearly my age.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WooduLove by the way, I hope they are throwing in those cushions ðŸ‘ŒðŸ»ðŸ‘ŒðŸ»ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WooduLove only â‚¬650... ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ I can't cope ðŸ™ˆ. Unbelievable ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onebiggins @rickygervais you should of won Biggins ðŸ˜ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WooduLove Hahahahah ah sure what's â‚¬15?just round it off and give them â‚¬200 .. What a bargain ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ™ˆ they're getting better ðŸ™ŠðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WooduLove ahhhhhaaaaa ffs.. StunningðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ that's it, I want it. Urine  stains included.. ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leannemurphy223 what are you talking about he was never fat!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am honestly in a food coma #FatFriday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WooduLove Hahahahah â‚¬650 ah Ian who are these people? And what planet do they live on.... ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big black spider ran as fast as his legs could carry him down behind my bed How many spiders do we eat in a lifetime while asleep #nothungry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How did @hughie_maughan not win ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­@bbuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IL0VEthe80s ahhhh memories]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watched a program on Jean Harlow... Didn't know she died so young ðŸ˜•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WooduLove Fantastic..Fair play.. â˜ºï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WooduLove lovely job ðŸ‘ŒðŸ»Are you going to rent it out?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is #Everest worth a watch?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulReadST good good ðŸ‘ðŸ» happy to hear it ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If anybody wakes me up tomorrow you better run fast #Wrecked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@foofightersnews ah old news. ðŸ˜œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let me get through another week ðŸ™ˆ https://t.co/uP2wRl8uuI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not a bit of butter, cheese triangles to the rescue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WooduLove are they for real ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think I need a steak.. #RightNow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishBeast78 haven't stopped ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ what is it about Friday evenings that make you pig out ðŸ˜ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah here Andy.. Talking to yourself now. #getagrip #BBUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talking on phone not realising you've  just eaten large bar of Cadbury #oops]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TweeterPeter20 @WooduLove I wish Peter â˜ºï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TweeterPeter20 @WooduLove well it's not me ðŸ˜ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#truestory https://t.co/dpuKcbynYi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friends invited us out for dinner I'm only home and as pissed as a fart I knew the taxi man so that was free also brilliant night #goodtimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Yfielding is so down to earth and so lovely, she'd make a lovely friend excluding the ghosts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bbuk ahhhh i thought it was in at ten tonight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Alltheway80s Cagney and Lacey were my fav #80s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hmmmm  #music #foofighters #decisions #Sunday @ Dublin, Ireland https://t.co/rKhPBe9z7f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#needisaymore #saturday #ðŸ˜‚ @ Dublin, Ireland https://t.co/mTJGzH9Aij]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving one or two gin and tonics tonight #surewhynot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd love to be as free as a bird camping at #Glastonbury well not camping and definitely not in the rain ðŸ˜œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bbuk he's such a loveable chicken, delighted @hughie_maughan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leannemurphy223 yes to all,, just not short!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NarcissisticDub Jaysus.... Doesn't mean they listened]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Alltheway80s in the 80's I was such a  Madonna wannabe â˜ºï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Alltheway80s used to have nightmares bout him ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bbuk he does my head in!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dickndom we miss you ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/xu2TenhEzR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saturday night in waiting for #BigBrother what the hell happened my life ðŸ™ˆ #sadface]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WooduLove are you still there? Hope you're ok Ian.. See once you hit 40, downhill ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NarcissisticDub they were handed to me I had to drink them it was a thirsty nightðŸ˜†. (Especially after 4 bags of crisps) ðŸ’ðŸ¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NarcissisticDub I admit I didn't know it #hangsheadinshame ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NarcissisticDub I'll shake my head and think about it ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishBeast78 I'll watch the sequel but it can't be as good as the first, can it? #weshallsee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishBeast78 Deadpool  has to be one of the funniest this year. What a brilliant movie ðŸ‘ŒðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishBeast78 I loved the first one, but I did get a few good laughs out of the 2nd one, I do agree it could have been so much better ðŸ‘ŒðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#BBUK would want to throw in some undatables  ðŸ˜’]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just tasted the new soft drink 7up mojito actually tastes like mojito #unbelievable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wallabywoods very cute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WooduLove @rickygervais I think it's Cake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stuck in all day with a swollen face over yesterday's dentist visit #elephantman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's that time ðŸ‘ŒðŸ» https://t.co/IDR1tWkntI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It gets better year after year #Fakemarraigefacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's been a bad couple of years #icouldrunmiles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need a new hair do #dangerofbeingbored]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never want see Nesbitts face ever again  #TheSecret]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also wine, wine makes me hungrier #blamethealcohol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For some strange reason the hotter the weather the hungrier I get #weird #gluttony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TheSecret he likes his blondes sicko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TheSecret not much of a secret now ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TheSecret if I was married to Nesbitt I'd sleep with one I open #hegivesmethewillies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TheSecret wtf??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#thesecret on what is she doing in that chair!! Here we go again.. Vomit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rylan really ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TweeterPeter20 hopefully fingers crossed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TweeterPeter20 oh no, ah she might get it back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes all you can do is laugh. https://t.co/xE5Q4TRqui]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching #pulpfiction where's my life gone ðŸ˜’]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NarcissisticDub you won't last all of May ðŸ˜œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching #theoffice @rickygervais the best comedy ever!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like  @DavidHasselhoff but never will I watch that shite again #raydarcyshow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NarcissisticDub why?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just can't watch James Nesbitt #really]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VirginMediaIE @roisinbtw ours is the same. I'm sick and tired ringing customer services. Waste of timeðŸ˜¡]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>