<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[She's now imprisoned in a detention centre. Hey you people who work at @ukhomeoffice. It's not someone else doing t… https://t.co/0vj0RhzrSj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the biggest geo-strategic question facing the UK since 1939, our parliament just voted through a side of A4. I'm speechless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @TheScotsman, want some proper journalism? Read this: https://t.co/mOGDV3xmDa No wonder you're dying on your feet. #DontBuyAPaper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Currently running at 10 new signings a second.
https://t.co/pMRhrT4iBn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alanthegasman @thoughtland If an authoritative take-down of that £15bn so-called deficit was pushed thro every letter box in Sco, we'd win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not an unintended consequence: executive order best understood as a deliberate provocation. Security states need en… https://t.co/3bZp7qWYbK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@c_jas @simon_brooke @jk_rowling @GuyVerhofstadt You're hand-waving now! Anyway, we're going round in circles here. Nice talking to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@c_jas @simon_brooke @jk_rowling @GuyVerhofstadt The rest is just arguments about process.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@c_jas @simon_brooke @jk_rowling @GuyVerhofstadt I'm assuming EU/EFTA have compelling economic reasons to protect the SM, including Sco.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@c_jas @simon_brooke @jk_rowling @GuyVerhofstadt If you can retain Sco in SM and you choose not to, you're expelling it. Why would they?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WingsScotland Say EU loses 20% of trade w rUK post-Brexit. For rest of EU it's 20% of 5%. For Sco it's 20% of 64%.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WingsScotland OK, but if EU/rUK deal is worse for both than SM, might it not be *really* bad for Sco cos so much of our trade is with rUK?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@c_jas @simon_brooke @jk_rowling @GuyVerhofstadt Unmotivated speculation. Why would EU/EFTA expel an existing, functioning part of the SM?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@c_jas @simon_brooke @jk_rowling @GuyVerhofstadt Yes but that's all about process not outcome. If Sco goes indy, Sco will be in SM.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@c_jas @simon_brooke @jk_rowling @GuyVerhofstadt Fair enough. But if SM is critical issue, EFTA means Scots membership is pretty definite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@c_jas @simon_brooke @jk_rowling @GuyVerhofstadt Worst case surely is Scotland joins EFTA. Spain has no say on that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would be interesting to know tho how much of Sco / rUK trade is services, which might be (partially) excluded from… https://t.co/M0zuhJprDX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quite. If Brexit works, indy works too. If Brexit doesn't work, indy is an economic imperative. https://t.co/ATO6gN9ylg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So a lot of fine words spoken just before the indyref, and written into the Scot Act after it, have buttered not a parsnip. Hence the anger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supreme Court judgement confirms Sco is not 1 of 4 equal nations in a political union, but is just 8.3% of the population of a unitary state]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2014 promise that Sco would be "equal partner" in Union &amp; to entrench Sewel in law *seemed* to give Sco a standing analogous to a US state.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those puzzled as to why Scotland would expect to have a voice equal to England's on Brexit should reflect that this is how the USA works.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After EU ref, visitor from federal USA expressed puzzlement to me: "Eng + Wales for Leave, Sco + NI for Remain. For us that's 2 all, a draw"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fig for those by law protected
Liberty's a glorious feast
Courts for cowards were erected
Churches built to please the priests
- Burns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smith declared the parliament should be ‘made permanent' in UK legislation and Sewel put ‘on a statutory footing.'
https://t.co/IGZfx7TgLV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottreid1980 @WingsScotland Kill that £15 billion nonsense &amp; push the reasoning through every letterbox in Sco: that will be enough imho.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2014 brought the UK to the brink of dissolution. Yet still the British state will not give Scotland a constitutional say on its own future.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every Trump accusation of institutional failure - media, political class, CIA - prepares the ground for the state of emergency.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Risk with Trump is not exactly fascism. Fascism is populist. Trump is not popular. Risk is tyranny: a state-of-emergency then a police state]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pity Malaperte's "Technica del Colpo di Stato" hasn't been translated. Shows how Mussolini overthrew Italy's democracy in a few simple moves]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Re that White House press conference. What Spicer said was not intended primarily to be believed. It sets the context for subsequent action.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DerekBateman2 @Mae_Carson2 Also England has significantly higher level of private health &amp; education. Never seen effect of this quantified.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The gift that keeps giving. Do Lab strategists really think telling Scots they can't survive wo England will bring… https://t.co/Hd8q4ZqWSB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The Single Market has been a huge force for peace in Europe."
-Yes it has. https://t.co/PLKc4d2ezY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["AI machines are thinking like us."
 - No. You're thinking like them. https://t.co/4b5m3pPfLp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seantduffy Of course. It was UK Labour I was referring to. If the SNP can *lead* opinion on immigration, and win power, why not UK Labour?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The SNP leads public opinion. Labour follows it. https://t.co/1YT4x7OVH5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A case of good invention twisted to bad purpose, or the reverse? Military research surely dominates the automation… https://t.co/W4gE3EzZDH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NorrieStew @WingsScotland True, care homes may be no safer from infection than hospitals. Your own home probably is though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WingsScotland Sure. We'd need to know how these patients died and where. So Sarwar's "dangerous" comment is stupid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WingsScotland Not if you're at home in bed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WingsScotland Yes but in hospital you're bang up against a lot of sick people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WingsScotland That said, presumably most of these patients would have died anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WingsScotland Delayed discharge *can* be dangerous: people die often from disease caught in hospital. Faster you're out the better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WingsScotland Yes. It's the standard hospital systems term for "we're done here", but it doesn't fit well if you're going home to die.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WingsScotland I think that just means there is no medical reason to keep them in  an acute hospital. They can still be terminally ill.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidJFHalliday @WingsScotland Yes. Patients who should have died at home, or in nursing or respite care. It is a real issue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wings showing once again why ever fewer people read even so-called quality papers like the Herald, Scotsman and Gua… https://t.co/A14CtlrDHU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unless the problem is solved *on that ground*, the AI algorithm that solves it is just a complicated washing machine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intelligence isn't problem-solving. It precedes &amp; follows the problem. It is the ground on which problems are proposed, resolved &amp; discarded]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The AI that plays chess can't drive a car &amp; the AI that drives a car can't play chess. Human intelligence does both &amp; grasps the difference.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Humans don't just solve problems: they create them first. We can build an AI to play chess, but can we build one to *invent* chess?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@thoughtland Do you know Paul Virilio? Tech=speed, speed=power, history=acceleration to final cataclysmic accident. See e.g. his Pure War.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our AI machines are always engineered to solve a problem. Can we build one that meditates, that soothes away the problem it exists to solve?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just read an academic book about Greek religion. Put me to sleep. Now reading one by a practising witch. Much better!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They've spent years thinking about this. Years I tell you. https://t.co/gmTKngIamf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cri de coeur from a Highlands priced out of its own land ... https://t.co/S8E6gaG9Iw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@thoughtland I wld contend tech can't be evaluated cept side-by-side w structure which isn't tech. No such structure being debated *afaik*.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@thoughtland Prevalence of technocracy &amp; authority of scientific model is giving tech a *metaphysical* position it perhaps does not deserve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@thoughtland Buddhism plays to idea of nature as tech: articulation w no centre &amp; no limits. But not clear nature can be modelled this way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@thoughtland Something Buddhist tho about Banks' holographic worlds: if we were content w a cloak, a bowl &amp; a spoon we could be there now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@thoughtland A divide is coming: Iain Banks' AI Culture, or a smashing of the tech idols &amp; return to the land, to earth, air fire &amp; water.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@thoughtland But what political power will the population have, if nobody works? Cf Marx, passim.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we lose work to AI we lose finally, permanently any relationship to the land more serious than hiking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Folk write about the AI takeover as if erasing work were inevitable like the weather, and not a policy choice conjo… https://t.co/UNz71RzK5X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey well ... a stopped clock and all that ... https://t.co/KpX9O5rxkK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not much post-Brexit goodwill out there for UK state. https://t.co/3tX4pX132N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@moh_kohn Yes. And can we find a simple way to convey "fiscal multiplier"? Public spending comes back as tax.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smacfadyen11 Aha! Great stuff! Too bad it's not on TV tho ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boards mean boards. https://t.co/2ZihTEyrOt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually this is really interesting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@AlasdairStephen @1GKh @thecommongreen @snp @AndrewWilson But that's growth. No effective SNP response to £15b GERS deficit figure so far.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I am," he says, with relish, "Thomas Cromwell in the court of the Tudors."
Brilliant article.
https://t.co/QQBQo7gjRD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to know why that £15 billion Scot deficit figure is nonsense? Read this:
https://t.co/LU6bX6QBpS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very good start on indy Scot finances from @thecommongreen:
https://t.co/LU6bX6QBpS
Good to see, but why are @SNP not doing this stuff too?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I honestly do not understand how an organisation like the BBC can write this article and not mention the SNP. https://t.co/75xEYTCscy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephenkb Not just SNP. Anti-immigration is not a political issue here. No newspaper makes an issue of it. No party in Holyrood raises it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I cannot emphasise enough how the SNP and positive Scottish experience of nationalism have transformed my understanding of Brexit / Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thread ... https://t.co/Qk973vqlnQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't see a basic problem with global capitalism? Then blame the voters, as racist, sexist. *They* may be, but *you* have the wrong target.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Communities want back power over their lives. You can do it nicely (SNP) or nastily (UKIP), but the demand is just and it won't go away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WingsScotland See the *swings* from 2012 in this: https://t.co/hYij2MPLl1
16% swing to GOP among those earning &lt; $30k.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@smacfadyen11 Just fell over it! Shows the swing from 2012. Biggest swings around income, education and race. https://t.co/hYij2My9Wr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smacfadyen11 Wd be interesting to  compare these 2016 splits with the same stats for Obama's election.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smacfadyen11 V interesting, thanks. But enough poor folk voted for Trump's working class champion line to swing it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poor people voting absolute power to one wealthy fixer, their friend among the elite, is one of the world's oldest political tropes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People think democracy can control capitalism. But capitalism is a runaway truck. Nobody controls it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smacfadyen11 Ah yes I suppose it's bound to be sold out. Not normally an issue in the Borders. More sheep than people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks great! I'd go if I could but I can't. What about you tho @smacfadyen11?
https://t.co/hilpsSE1h4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WingsScotland Would we rather the Prime Minister alone overturned it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alistairjegray Scots and rUK parliaments would have legitimate view on terms of separation between Scotland &amp; rUK. Parliaments, not execs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would we prefer it to be vetoed by the Prime Minister alone? https://t.co/I5pNYxObh2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WingsScotland If Leavers thought parl't more pro-Brexit than gov't they'd back parl't over exec. So not standing for any const'l principle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WingsScotland ... which shows you it's public opinion which is unprincipled, not the constitutional judgement which is surely sound.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WingsScotland Cos the perception is the gov't is firmer for Brexit than parliament. Could easily have been the other way round.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WingsScotland But parliament can fairly withhold consent to Article 50, *until* the government publishes a sensible plan. I would.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@WingsScotland But parliament can review govt's plan re how to Brexit, &amp; demand a better plan, without disrespecting result of referendum.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thread ... The land people live on should not be in the hands of private landlords. Absurd that you can't build a h… https://t.co/OJfml9F2UB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Article and thread. Both v illuminating. https://t.co/0uABSVGX9Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thoughtland @murrayf00te @MhairiHunter UK state spend is centralised in London. I don't get why SNP not saying that loudly and repeatedly.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>