<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@bendreyfuss How many glasses of Mogen David have you consumed tonight? Yeah... that's what I thought.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephaniemain2 @cridge17 I know THAT LOOK and it didn't come from the cat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT He only reads page six to see if he is mentioned and knowing that, he somehow became President of the U.S. lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such an appropriate posting for right now. If everyone thinks about Sept 12th, 2001 - we are more alike than diff a… https://t.co/WocjBB8HVf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bendreyfuss It doesn't really help the cause of 'safe gun control' when you're holding a gun and a glass of wine ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bendreyfuss You're one of the most sane and stable human beings I've encountered on the net. You should have ALL the guns and no one else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You Have to See This Weekend's Best Amazon Deals

https://t.co/4EWDj6CSEW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for a recipe for "deflated cheater balls" but haven't found them yet. 
https://t.co/n3Px78P5VS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrbiffo @tkdmike someone needs to fwd that to his twitter acct... over and over and over again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ever notice how the highest paid guys smile the most? https://t.co/G8fZZ9NL3B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SporkenWord Not a problem for me! I'm a minimalist - just ask any girl who has had sex with me!  @superherofbmx 
C'mon... it's Saturday!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How long do we have to wait to read "Killing Trump" by Bill O'Reilly
*oh BOO yourself!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ditzkoff Plz stop giving oxygen to Palin, Newt, Santorium, Huckabee et al]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not the public interference that crushes you; it's the news media reporting it to your constituents that kills… https://t.co/1mUi13Vwc6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonRiley7 He says it better than me lol.  Your defense in 140 characters. https://t.co/tpSz3wB0oE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theawold @goonerheD @JonRiley7 Alex, you're not wrong but nor are you right. It casts to wide of a net. The EO must be more defined/focused]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AP Who are they appealing to?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonRiley7 I don't mean to sound like a broken record but... They have to kill O-care so the voters experience what the true GOP congress is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT How long ago did Trump get the questions that O'Reilly would be asking him and who wrote the answers for Trump?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thewritertype Sorry for the nightmare but Piers Morgan will be on Real Time with Bill Maher Friday Feb 10th]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jbarro I want a oompa loompa and I want it RIGHT NOW ...and a pony!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adamhopps I had the same review of the 2017 inauguration.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonRiley7 Anyone else singing AC/DC's ''Big Balls"?
"The social pages say 'I've got the biggest' balls of them all"
https://t.co/C3aiLxKJbG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if you're not following... you might want to look into this?
@RoguePOTUSStaff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shit_reviews I love the first pic. Looks like the 'rapture' lmao!

https://t.co/r6Wds6fEQj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Breaking911 cheaters may win the Superbowl but they don't go to the Hall of Fame.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder if Trump celebrates African-American History Month by watching Major Payne &amp; Boys in the Hood?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@loneoak78130 @bendreyfuss Not a fan of Bud/Coors. I have had Killian's Red in Chicago :)  Turbo Dog in Nawlins. And Sam Adams is the worst!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SharpRabbit1 @Milbank get rid of that pesky Congress along with those nosy Judges then King Donald could really Make America Grope Again!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey Republicans... here's a great example of how to know whether to use 'your' or 'you're' when tweeting.
Thx… https://t.co/CUfAdrXRvG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ditzkoff Mr Trump forgets that HE works for the PEOPLE, not the other way around; then again most of Washington has forgotten this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonRiley7 Obstructing won't change Gorsuch on SCOTUS.  Is it worth pissing off Trump. Cud they negot a Trill$ infrastructr pkg in exchange]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@d1Vinman @famdocparker1 Does anyone know what the lower/middle class Trump supporters think of what he has done?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While it's still up and available you might want to watch it?
https://t.co/xKNsnlhMnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Trump is like Isis. One destroyed and purged the ruins of Palmyra and the other is doing the same of protection… https://t.co/zZJM8P0Lrg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bendreyfuss Ooo Ooo Ooo I know the answer to this one! Pay adweek to write a story about how great your ads are promoting your shitty beer!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidCornDC According to the Russians... there's a whole family history of 'leaking'
#nosurprisehere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@inflightexpert  Such a cool retro-pic and the food looks good as well. https://t.co/EOIxV51v33]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonRiley7 Now you're just saying nice things about him Jon! lol  (@cridge17)  
"So two Corinthians walk into a bar...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HunkyGayJesus @tkdmike THAT'S FUNNY!  Thx Jesus &amp; Mike! (I still think it's the Conway family reunion)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember Kids:  It's not how talented you are or how hard you worked - it's how well you cheat! All that matters in… https://t.co/pEMStFYVkj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're a Rus. who became a $bil by stealing from the State. U.S. blocks ur bnk accts. Won't you just steal more so sanctions don't effect u?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone should read the stats on White Nationalist hate crimes since 9/11 - very short read
https://t.co/eBrAXJran4
Read &amp; Retweet plz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How could this not go smooth? lmfao https://t.co/EKfmAch6yw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you shove your face into every post pic on Twitter... this what you look like.

https://t.co/GmCbqyzQrW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starting Monday, get FREE Krispy Kreme doughnuts when you purchase a coffee — seriously

https://t.co/73Ge3zWBqy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IKEA Börder Wåll provides Trump with affordable construction option

https://t.co/zK3Ui503pq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Florida heroin bust reveals something bizarre: Drugs covered in Donald Trump’s face

https://t.co/OE7d7lUES8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still laughing at the arrogance &amp; stupidity of the U.S. administration 
https://t.co/9ctKygRMJv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I always thought it was Saudi Arabia 
https://t.co/GhLwFCVx05]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@feministabulous @SporkenWord CNN might finally be regaining some respectability.  Interviewing Conway means you are spreading fake news]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrnickharvey @cridge17 If you remove the humour and sarcasm from twitter... you'd be left with the GOP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So where does Trump go now?  SCOTUS?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good News: and I seem to recall an episode of the West Wing that was very similar.  If you do that praying thingy..… https://t.co/XKEdIj5GXk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one more reminder of the reality that we are more similar than we are different.
#GOODTHINGS https://t.co/LmkzAmxNzQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bendreyfuss Election-reform was just dropped this wk in Cda over fear of an extreme fringe party taking control of the country. #NoTeaBags]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonRiley7 When crafting Alt-Legislation, one can't cast a wide net hoping to catch someone; rather it must be in pursuit of a specific goal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senor Fox has become a hero for his fearless defense of right over wrong.
Another great post from @tkdmike - our th… https://t.co/Wndp8oITZg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @tkdmike for the unsettling reminder of how Washington really works.  See the political comic strip! https://t.co/i5i1KXbuUe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuddLegum @famdocparker1 Not sure why it shows a pic of a 50'ish Prince William talking to a human can opener?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These little Hilteresque moments of terror; Que Cty, San Bernadino, Charleston have failed spectacularly and brought mankind together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Trump's voting base growing or declining at the moment?  Can anyone provide any proof of it going either way?  I'm guessing it is growing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything I love about America is in this picture... see that cheap gas!
Thx @tkdmike for a great pic of the Conwa… https://t.co/kKmwVan0GH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bendreyfuss 
A great office is a home-away-from-home... but put your pants back on when taking pics that reflect in the glass.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EVERYONE needs to look at these two pictures and RETWEET.
It's horrific! https://t.co/dvKr4sk3uB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jaketapper @famdocparker1 @MarkWarner Why go to all the trouble? Block Trump from NSC and future problems are solved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei @famdocparker1 
DAMMIT!  I gave away all of my Axis of Evil trading cards! :(  Who knew we would playing this game again?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thx to @JonRiley7 for this important share. We all are a little sadder tonight after the horrific terror attack in… https://t.co/Xk4igF9sR1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hirschorn @jonathanalter So members of Trump's team and WH staff could own a gun?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[KIDS! This is your FACE on ALCOHOL &amp; DRUGS! https://t.co/vO1ia33q15]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonRiley7 Would really like someone to ask him to solve Cancer?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonRiley7 Plants a seed of doubt in voter's minds then appearing to fix a radical problem that never existed; takes credit for prob solved]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilipWatson8 ...didn't want to post that I don't really need a partner either (lol)
Got this one covered! https://t.co/Dji3VvAWDT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Betting Bannon gets this framed and hung up in his office, bathroom, over this bed... https://t.co/KT4MeAAc6h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bendreyfuss You have the wittiest &amp; nicest followers!  The love, humour &amp; sarcasm is awesome. Must consider following you one day...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every day I learn how little I know thanks to Paul. 
If I could only follow one person on Twitter... this is the ma… https://t.co/9BO6DEuJdG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've said this for years! Best orgasms happen within 20 mins of a puff :) Note: you might forego long-term stamina 

https://t.co/MtqDXhE5WG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vancouver artist's anti-Trump cartoon takes off on social media

https://t.co/exG6widEY6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Daddy’ Trump’s Empty Threat to Defund Berkeley Over Milo

https://t.co/1m4nG4NbRt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@puppymnkey @cridge17 
I kind of thought he was doing a PISS poor job 
:-Þ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very cool... never heard of such a thing before.
#LifeBeforeTheCloud https://t.co/B93fnaK3i9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CrazyinRussia The covered in money totally had me, until I saw his unibrow...  that, and being a guy thingy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@famdocparker1 I wondering if it's cheaper to have the wall built in Mexico and shipped up and assembled in the U.S.? 
;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kurteichenwald @famdocparker1 But what is the penalty for a GOP to not fight for his country?  nothing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mindymerv @liberalincincy @samsteinhp I respectfully disagree. His ego is more important than his job. Bannon's expendable, like his wives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@club_reid @famdocparker1 @maddow 
Blockbuster is all out of Dr. Strangelove ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*BURN* lol
...and if you're going to burn someone, do it with class! &lt;read below&gt; https://t.co/R5MZQeqWQI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SporkenWord 
I was going to make a joke and thank Ben @superherofbmx for icing them... but only the three of us would get it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's hard to make the phrase,"people just knifing each other" sound like a bad thing when it is in the Trump WH lol https://t.co/7fTRNg1IeY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NicholsUprising @famdocparker1 It's also not a surprise. When Trump realizes that the world say that he is Bannon's puppet - He'll be gone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AP_Top25 So... this means they win the Superbowl right? Cause that's kind of how it works...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LOL  thx to @famdocparker1 for a brighter repost! https://t.co/IP757w0i4S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@famdocparker1 Thank You! completely made from scratch by me. 
 Who's the most popular guy at work tomorrow??  Yeah, I know, not me...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Homemade Cinnamon Buns:
1) Proofing
2) Proofing - close up
3) Baked - half iced/half plain
4) Baked - close up iced… https://t.co/CufApXFDD3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is my cooking guru. I wood take a bullet for her, though I would prefer an 'outrageous brownie'. #NoneBetter

https://t.co/F929AfYauI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck Krispy Kreme, I'm making cinnamon buns. And they'll be better than that crap. (Pics coming)

https://t.co/QlouZbGt20]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For all of my right wing followers who might think I don't show enuff love?
#becauseIloveYou

https://t.co/in4LkZauqh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What we know so far about Trump’s phone calls with foreign leaders

https://t.co/1EtcwdENZq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take a bite out of melt-in-your-mouth bacon cheeseburger bombs

https://t.co/zzLUZ0fNCB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GregCurtin Removal of any mention of Jews in a Holocaust statement certainly gives street cred to Pelosi's 'white supremacist' charge.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>