<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@7NewsMelbourne maybe Foxtel can make your main events channel cheaper?!?!?!???!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@roshart @PodSaveAmerica is this the episode that came out this morning?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thunderluver23 weak! Flex when you slam over somebody!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thunderluver23 that's what happens when you flex your muscles Steph Curry!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OKCThunderHeads I hope this experiment for the Warriors ends this season]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GMegalogenis of the day, Turnbull can't abandon the refugees stuck on Manus &amp; Nauru]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GMegalogenis that's what I said to my parents last night. The refugees are Turnbull responsibility. Trump is a loose cannon but at the end]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rodgerrodgersu @YouTube I'm surprised Paul Murray is not a fan of Bruce Springsteen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rohan_connolly should've sucked up to Trump since January 2016! What rot!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rohan_connolly Chris Kenny is an idiot. Too busy trying to please LNP. I was right. Paul Murray is blaming Turnbull. Said Turnbull]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhillipAdams_1 why no story about Turnbull phone call with Trump tonight on FNL?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rohan_connolly I figured i need to know what the RWNJ's are thinking so I can see for myself what's wrong with the world. I just laugh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rohan_connolly you mean Sky News? Would be interesting to hear Paul Murray tonight. He hates Turnbull so he'll be on Trump side]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hamishNews lol Ben Fordham. I listen to that interview &amp; I thought that was an odd question to start off interviewing Turnbull]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GregBe_ON1 with teammates who can't shoot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GregBe_ON1 I've been on the tanking camp 76's style since ðŸ left coz I wanted OKC to start again. I rather see RW win a ring than get stuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@susanamet oh god that was years ago!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@susanamet how is this ALP fault? ALP didn't speak to Obama or Trump about his deal. Turnbull did! He needs to accept responsibility!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can someone tell me what The Bolt had to say about Turnbull vs Trump? I missed the start of the panel hence the question #pmagenda #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gorill_Jas I've always been a RW fan coz I liked his 6 pack. Ill follow him where ever he goes too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gorill_Jas that's rights. &amp; then I went NO! Hahahaha!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gorill_Jas im on the record in saying that Presti should've traded RW back in July so OKC can start the tanking process 76's style]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KOCOKeating Presti needs to make some changes to the bench]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vanOnselenP this is worse than a soap opera!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@btckr Laura Jayes &amp; Sky News are covering up for Turnbull incompetence. Typical]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ljayes @TurnbullMalcolm haha! Yeah right. Turnbull was caught lying. Why are you guys covering up for Turnbull?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shesforOKC @Smoove_Vic i disagree. Presti hands were tied coz ðŸ left OKC with no free agents left! I don't know what else Presti can do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mickdundee48 @MisdaMagoo @TurnbullMalcolm TONES!!!! Urgh!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ross Cameron is PISSED!!!! For once I agree with him! Turnbull is FINISHED!!!! #auspol #tothepoint]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamJosephSport that's the why it should be. The young needs to learn how to win games or at least hold leads &amp; not depend on RW so much]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blah blah blah LNP Senator complaining about Labor &amp; the unions #ffs #neverendingstory #auspol #pvonewsday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@woolkebb @TurnbullMalcolm @MarkDiStef &amp; trust Sky News trying to cover up the phone call by saying that Trump "accepted" the deal. Liars!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@woolkebb @TurnbullMalcolm Shorten is right. Turnbull is gutless &amp; doesn't stand up to Australian values.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markhumphries @washingtonpost just proves that Turnbull is a coward &amp; didn't call out Trump a few days ago!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@workmanalice @MSMWatchdog2013 I'm just wondering coz I'm not sure of these candidates are for real or they're making stuff up for attention]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MSMWatchdog2013 @workmanalice @BuzzFeedNews where does Pauline Hanson finds these ppl?!?!?!?!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RNLifeMatters access to the Life Matters facebook page which is why I'm asking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RNLifeMatters hey Life Matters I just wanted to know where I can post a comment about today's discussion on food &amp; depression? I don't have]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gorill_Jas lol Harden always has an off game in OKC. Presti needs to fix this bench]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A daily reminder that Presti needs to fix the bench.... #OKCvsSAS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gorill_Jas JAMES HARDEN IN THE FIRST MEETING AT OKC!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gorill_Jas I don't care anymore. He needs to be traded. Hasn't developed a shot since 2013-2014.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gorill_Jas Roberson is hopeless...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vanOnselenP I had to turn off Turnbull speech. Had no passion whatsoever in his speech. Turnbull is going through the motions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GregBe_ON1 @Jhickness9 I have to coz I've got league pass. Need to make my money spent on a useless NBA season worthwhile for 2 weeks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leftocentre has he finished his speech?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leftocentre don't forget about THE DOLT!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leftocentre wait until Paul Murray lays into him tonight....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leftocentre no passion whatsoever in his speech. Even TONES made his speech interesting by talking about wonderful nonsense!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@plbrocks all I heard was blah blah blah, jobs, education, make everything equal for everybody (lol)... BORING!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkDiStef mark Latham. I read he wants to back a comeback. Will not be surprised with he joins the One Nation crew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leftocentre @TurnbullMalcolm I turned his speech off. Boring as bat shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter let me know when the journalists start asking questions to Turnbull. His speech was putting me to sleep #npc #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@killmebilly @SkyNewsAust hey Sky News pleasing for the RWNJ hate bashing won't last long! It gets boring FAST!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@killmebilly @SkyNewsAust I only got Foxtel recently so I can watch HBO shows. Sky News brings me the horrors on what's wrong with society]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@killmebilly @SkyNewsAust they will now!!!!! Lol poor Nationals! That's what happens when you have BARNABY JOYCE as your leader!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@killmebilly @SkyNewsAust now Paul Murray &amp; Peta Credlin is promoting Pauline Hanson as the "3rd force" in Oz politics. FFS!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@killmebilly @SkyNewsAust I turned it off as soon as I saw George C was going to be on. I Didn't want to hear Muslim this, Muslim that again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Forthleft2 @730report @billshortenmp huh? I didn't hear the "drain the swamp" reference? That Andrew guy must've been drunk during NPC!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TraceySpicer I turned off that show once I saw George C was going to be on. Have no time to hear his rant on "making Oz great again"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Cormann talking about in #PMAgenda?!?!? I didn't want to go back to sleep so I avoided listening to Cormann #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samdastyari listen back to that interview instead of making up stuff!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samdastyari Sam I listen to your RN Drive interview that you gave last night saying the exact same thing. The conspiracy theorist needs to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jhickness9 im turning off that presentation as soon as GSW as won the NBA Finals. Don't wanna see ðŸ fake tears &amp; Draymond screaming for joy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickFeik @nytimes NYT has nothing to lose anymore. Can do whatever they want despite Trump fighting with them on Twitter. Good to see]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyNewsAust @samanthamaiden @billshortenmp @TurnbullMalcolm ummmm Turnbull is WEAK! Everyone knows this as a fact!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@James_Jeffrey @THR what about Rupert Murdoch? I'll like to hear what he has to say]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@triplejHack hey I just wanted to know when is the podcast for yesterday show coming out on the PodCast app?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SHIT! I agree with Pauline Hanson about her reasons why coal stem gas should be removed from rural areas! #wtf #beattieandreith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@killmebilly @SkyNewsAust @GChristensenMP hahahaha! He really needs to join One Nation....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@killmebilly @SkyNewsAust @GChristensenMP all I heard was blah blah blah.... Muslims this Muslims that... Ban everyone... ect ect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@killmebilly @SkyNewsAust @GChristensenMP I fell asleep during that interview.........]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jhickness9 agree. Donovan doing the best he can with this roster. Could be worse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrpford I thought Delta was dating someone else. That's what I read a few weeks ago]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WELL DONE MR FED!!!!! NADAL STILL AWESOME!!!! #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@okcthundergal I'm convinced this experiment will end if GSW don't win the title this season. Curry will leave in FA &amp; ðŸ who cares]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KOCOCarson &amp; because of that the NBA has become unwatchable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@okcthundergal @thunderluver23 no. La la will have a fit if she mixes with "middle America". Stupid really]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My all time fav tennis match up is BACK!!!! The Fed vs Rafa! WHOO!!!!! #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RAFA YOU LEGEND!!!!! WELCOME BACK TO THE #AusOpen FINALS!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuliaGillard Congratulations Julia! Well deserved award!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey wasn't that Commonwealth guy on the #4Corners program about Commonwealth Bank insurance policy DUDDING their customers?!? #ausoftheyear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helen_privett @suthernx Jealous of your bookcase! I've recently brought 2 new bookshelves so I can rekindle my love for reading again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@roshart what's the designer background compared to the rest of the candidates? Seems like that sway the vote more than what that award mean]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RNDrive @PatsKarvelas I don't see a problem working for free. If you want the job then you should work for it. Experience is the key]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RNDrive @PatsKarvelas I worked for free for 10 days because I knew nothing about the job &amp; after 10 days I was offered the job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@okcthundergal @theScore I still remember Perk bulldozing Beverley in the middle of the court after Beverley injured RW knee in Game 3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnw6804 @gorill_Jas &amp; make Harden a starter into of Thabo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnw6804 @gorill_Jas of course. I never agreed with trading Harden. That was stupid. Perk should've e traded instead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnw6804 @gorill_Jas You can blame the salary cap as well. &amp; not keeping Harden.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnw6804 @gorill_Jas Presti &amp; he doesn't get involved. What ðŸ did was pulled the coward way out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnw6804 @gorill_Jas ðŸshould've pulled a LeBron &amp; demand to make roster changes in the public domain &amp; not go to the media &amp; say he "trust]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RNLifeMatters call up the show &amp; talk about their opinions on a topic currently on air like previous years?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RNLifeMatters hey Life Matters team I'm enjoying the show so far into 2017, but I was wondering if you are still going to have listeners]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnw6804 @gorill_Jas I disagree it was built around RW. Presti was still catering towards the ðŸ. But it doesn't matter this season]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnw6804 @gorill_Jas that roster was built around ðŸ, not RW. That's why I'm giving Presti some slack. But he needs to fix the bench]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gorill_Jas but I rather Harden come back to OKC. Lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gorill_Jas with his FA decision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gorill_Jas I think KD will come back to OKC. He keeps talking about OKC like they traded him to GSW. That's a sign that he's uncomfortable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gorill_Jas did you know that ðŸ hasn't put his OKC home on the market?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>