<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@BraddJaffy Thank you for always telling it and backing it up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA @realDonaldTrump Maybe if we can find a picture version of The Constitution it might be easier.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markknoller At least the country was safe for 5 hours! Yay us!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump We are in agreement then! That means you, Bannon, and Kellyanne are leaving. Thanks for the best day since Jan 19!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattdpearce My colleagues in Germany, UK, Spain, Portugal are horrified and embarrassed for us. Not a real sampling, just anecdotal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ezlusztig I offered to send a Cliffs Notes version of The Constitution to @POTUS but he didn't take me up. Is there a picture version?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Evan_McMullin @realDonaldTrump Thank you! This Liberal just donated to @StandUpRepublic Keep up the great work @Evan_McMullin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlecMacGillis The hardest I've laughed all week. Thank you! Donated to @ProPublica too. Keep it up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tribelaw I think applause?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DAPLFacts @Forbes And destroys sacred land 4 which u have 0 respect. U only care about $. #DespicableDAPL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanAdamini Calling bullshit on u! Oh sorry folks, didn't mean 2 make light of KSU or imply killing protesters. U said what u meant #asswipe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid How is it that everyone in USA is not screaming at the top of their lungs? Never so baffled in my life. #worldgonemad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep, I'm a lifer with @nytimes and @washingtonpost and @guardian https://t.co/2hdXtCKUnI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BionicBEB @dozerrand @POTUS @realDonaldTrump As I've said all along we went from Class to ASS on January 20.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leahmcelrath Uh oh. "You're fired."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best tweet so far today! https://t.co/bQh1YPpgoO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BraddJaffy You win for best tweet of the day!  Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MSNBC @elynn_prehn Oops! Maybe the unsubstantiated peepee files could be true? Or worse?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YCortlund @elynn_prehn Thanks. Called and spoke to DC staffer. Line in NC busy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nytimes Consider me a #NYTimesLifer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LawyerRogelio @thedailybeast Do we want them banned? How else do we monitor activity? I struggle w/that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VanJones68 @CNN @YouTube Yes, what everyone with a brain did! Thanks for sharing. Keep up the great work @VanJones68]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice job @Evan_McMullin  Thank you (from a flaming liberal)! https://t.co/J9RWPF1Qip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealD0n0ldTrump I'm not going anywhere. In for the long haul! Me thinks the dumbass underestimated #RESISTANCE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealD0n0ldTrump Praise Geezus for Fox &amp; DJT! Where would we be without them? Oh. Not in deep $#!+]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealD0n0ldTrump Exactly! Divert from Yemen f-up, NSC with Bannon ... losing track of it all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nytimes Please take @POTUS phone/iPad away! How about a conversation w Iran. Wait. Bad idea (per Aussies).  @POTUS just stop agitating! xo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JillDLawrence @LOLGOP Thanks. Do we really need a poll to tell us how off DJT is?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JustinTrudeau THIS is true leadership. I wish I could say the same for my country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@el_gray @TheRealDratch Thank you! Calling right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Punxsutawney Phil says "You need to give a shit about the next 4 years &amp; not whether it's going to b cold x6 weeks!" https://t.co/KQdp8wzcAm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidCornDC @BlueVoterut Only of it's brown!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bixtian @C_Stroop Rare but sometimes happens. I was raised as fundamentalist but then started thinking &gt;30 yrs ago! #proudagnostic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProPublica Thank you! Just donated online to @ProPublica last night!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello @POTUS Just a thought for a new idea for you. @richardbranson has some fabulous ideas too. Available in pictu… https://t.co/sWG5B9CBhG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRealDratch Refugee child octopus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#RESISTANCE doesn't quite cut it. #WeWillFuckingResist is a better fit! https://t.co/DU0JIs1wxf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carlquintanilla @BraddJaffy Absolutely! I had no idea who he was. I sure do now! Of course he has no idea who I am! LOL!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SalmanWorld @TeaPainUSA  I think that means we can throw DJT out because we don't like his questions, comments, hmm... everything about him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh good! Now we know who @POTUS will alienate next! Yay us! https://t.co/dqwOl5M1er]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA Thank you, Tea Pain! #Trumpghazi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost And I even reminded him and provided PM Trudeau's Twitter handle to make it easy for him. Go figure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please RT! https://t.co/enPtASFHzn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ezlusztig He diverting attention from NSC &amp; Yemen F-up. Conquer/divide so we're putting out fires everywhere. He knows free speech gets us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@antine608 @LawyerRogelio Spin the wheel of "Trump Fucks the World". Makes it a fun little game for Trumpbannon!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Stop diverting attention from Yemen f-up, insane call with Australia &amp; Mexico, &amp; what you've done to the NSC!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LawyerRogelio He's diverting attention from NSC; relations with Australia, Mexico, world; Yemen F-up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I'm referencing &amp; agreeing with an ultra conservative, things have gotten REALLY scary. https://t.co/51M8oP7gXU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProPublica Made my donation tonight. Thank you for your work. https://t.co/kvLf446AQR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bdice37 @trenni @DeannaHoak When you call someone a dummy and say Obama approved it, it sounds like it. Not sure how else to read it. Thx.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@trenni @bdice37 @DeannaHoak Yes, let's continue to blame Pres. Obama for whatever. That means DJT didn't have balls to change decision. 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Evan_McMullin @realDonaldTrump Oh please don't get my hopes up for a trade!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh hell yes! https://t.co/swB32X8hPr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Evan_McMullin @realDonaldTrump Thank you Mr. McMullen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BraddJaffy @washingtonpost Would be great if people didn't respond to DJT and no longer feed his narcissism. DJT thrives on it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This person is seriously insane. https://t.co/tDLVoT924t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @POTUS You are insane. Seriously insane.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jaketapper You have no idea how this country appreciates and counts on you. Ok, well, I do and I am speaking for fellow Americans. 😀]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AynRandPaulRyan @ImTheGrimes @SpeakerRyan Thank you! They are such hypocrites. #PlannedParenthood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aravosis I prefer Immigrants! I love the perspective.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, JFC! Seriously? https://t.co/fZWqEonLj0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best tweet of the day! https://t.co/vA01Od0I6m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcuban And thank you, Mr. Cuban! Well done, sir! Glad we have such a wonderful motherfucker!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA Yay for peepee!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Oh well now that you've explained it that way, you'll be leaving, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Thank you for having the cajones that most didn't have.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcorubio Like when Pres Obama tried for 10 months for SCOTUS nom? Go figure! I actually thought you had cajones re:DJT. Wrong. Sad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeithOlbermann @realDonaldTrump But that's no surprise, is it? Everything is about him in his little alternate brain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best news so far! Must mean DJT, Bannon, Reince, &amp; Kellyanne are leaving! #YayUs https://t.co/BjRwH7kFSE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nytimes Oh good! Does that mean he, Bannon, Reince, and Kellyanne are leaving the country? #YayUs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ImTheGrimes Or maybe he does have an idea? #Resist  #RESISTANCE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey, Repubs, where is the uproar now? https://t.co/ayda70aIXq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HuffingtonPost A day brightened especially for dachshund lovers. Thank you #dachshundbuttsarecutest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MMFlint Thank you! Steady, stalwart, #Resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read 1984 again. https://t.co/vTale2c7Cp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LawyerRogelio Thanks for the laugh to start the day! #Resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michikokakutani @MMFlint @nytimes Thank you! Was horrified when read in 1984 and even more so now. #Resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the best tweets. Ever. LMAO! https://t.co/Q941dEi35c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crypticsea @seanhannity @newtgingrich Thx for the very loud deep belly laugh! Much needed since Jan20.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@altUSEPA @snopes When did you decide it is no longer offensive to ban Muslims, @VP ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ActualEPAFacts Not only does he grab pussies, he IS one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA @realDonaldTrump Absofuckinglutely!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheGoodGodAbove Please, could you do now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seanhannity @newtgingrich Bankrolling my own. bought poster board and Sharpies. Yep, outside $rolling in. Asswipe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh dear god! 😂 Where's Rudy? Sitting right across from you, dumbfuck! 😂😂 https://t.co/VxJ72ZcgMf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BraddJaffy Oh dear god! 😂 Look up! Like Where's Waldo but no need to search.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN Well, aren't we proud? Asked no one with a working brain cell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LawyerRogelio Not wasting my time to watch. Can't bear to look at him. Already know will be anti-choice pick so doesn't matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump We're all feeding his narcissism. All @POTUS Wants is to stir up shit &amp; divide/conquer. Would be great 2 ignore him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr. @POTUS @realDonaldTrump  Want to let u know there was a massacre in Quebec in case u want to send condolences to @JustinTrudeau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker Thank you from the bottom of my North Carolina heart!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump sacks defiant attorney general https://t.co/3DmtTWq5sg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnFugelsang @realDonaldTrump You are assuming there are teachable moments.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Wow, must be a little different from calling the shots in  Trumpdom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA @globeandmail Yep, time to ban them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BetteMidler @WesSmith123 America should be proud of this fine upstanding and professional citizen...said no one who matters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @DaleJr . Hope you can convince others. Thanks again. You have a new fan. https://t.co/3Z1XHAKqEJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @POTUS44 @BarackObama! You are admired &amp; missed. To say thank 1k times not nearly enough. https://t.co/niKgVaJ3dI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marvymuse @LawyerRogelio Indeed! And let's not forget the Crusades. What continues to be done to Native Americans is reprehensible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LawyerRogelio True but looks like white male Christians are major contenders!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>