<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@has_hasabala it's all crazy. So sorry our government is so bad to you folks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickKristof @gordolake this? https://t.co/TXdL9cq22m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelRadioScanner @newscomauHQ *cough* single point of failure *cough* ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elakdawalla it was like that in Australia for me when Tony Abbott was elected, plus I joined a political party.. Never thought I'd do that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poor GitLab :-(
"So in other words, out of 5 backup/replication techniques deployed none are working reliably or se… https://t.co/rLZkAf7TqR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not what I was expecting to see on Swanston St tonight walking back from @unimelb.. #kitten https://t.co/ewgTEuvNzD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to move SC17 to Canada, @ACM_President @Supercomputing ? #HPC https://t.co/oIFZyFeZmz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hmm, "@Cirque du Soleil: physics with attitude" does have a certain ring to it... :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last night attended extensive 2+ hour demonstration of physics. Newtons laws of motion, angular momentum, levers &amp;… https://t.co/2Rm0kiCbqV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@metrotrains 9:04 from Camberwell to city forgot to stop at Glenferrie today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bulletford it's a feature, not a bug (for them)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isn't this just the logical final state of Facebook? https://t.co/VEGA396bSY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mahtabm81 so sorry for you and Yousef over this. Utterly crazy world. :-(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pjf actually he said that back in November, he's just saying now he's sticking by that (which is still great) https://t.co/ET7Vlnlufz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@hpcprogrammer @SCInclusivity IMHO given state of play in US the most inclusive option for @Supercomputing now is move to Canda ASAP.. #HPC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LapTop006 perhaps SkyMesh, depends on your CSA. They're not here yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally got around to uninstalling @vicemergency app after 3 separate notifications of tomorrow's TFB. Bring back @CFA_Updates FireReady app]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That thing where you finally are able to get NBN but then find neither your existing ISP nor 2 good alternatives do HFC NBN.. :-(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Refugees come in all shapes &amp; sizes. This is an incredible story. https://t.co/Svh6KwNs9n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dyllyp thank you so much for sharing that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@R_Chirgwin never actually heard that yet, and we've got a few around here. Something to keep an ear out for...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheNikhita @mozilla none that I know of yet sadly. :-(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh no, TabGroups for @mozilla Firefox is dead, an add-on I rely on to organise my billions of tabs.. :-( https://t.co/a0gXU5AD26]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time for the @IEEEorg @Supercomputing conference to relocate to a location outside the USA, so the worldwide #HPC community can freely meet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@folded correct (for now at least) https://t.co/4snt4zEfam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd never heard of the Leica Freedom Train before. A "must read" thread. https://t.co/9ZH1TFOCPK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spufidoo @jimfinnis @YouTube hehehe, wonderful! Thanks for that... ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taster from @paperowlfilmsNI for proposed doco on my fab wife @donna_williams &amp; her philosophy on cancer &amp; death https://t.co/ebN9S2SAIG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bendigobank thanks - might lose Android Pay but found I don't use it any more anyway. Vendor Android is already insecure, no more updates.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AstroKatie point them at s4.3 of @unimelb Academic Freedom of Expression Policy https://t.co/tThdusRvj2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["4.3. The liberty to speak freely extends to making statements on political matters" https://t.co/tThdusRvj2 https://t.co/wNS3YLmYEb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Atlantean7001 @firstdogonmoon @lenoretaylor yup, plus best news app I've used so far (though only got ABC &amp; BBC to compare to) :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @firstdogonmoon @lenoretaylor, looking forward to the spinach &amp; trousers.. https://t.co/glyxhQFZgq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GSGCounsel @DwayneMallard thanks, I understand that part now. Link is the same one I sent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Doomsday Clock was moved 30 seconds closer to midnight, now stands at 2.5 minutes to midnight. https://t.co/x9zp2YIuVh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice to see at least 4 other @MBObservatory members at the Belgrave #SurvivalDay today, plus @YRRMuseum!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mass traditional dancing at Belgrave #SurvivalDay. https://t.co/7EayShj8JT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Traditional Wurundjeri dancers at Belgrave #SurvivalDay https://t.co/EMbiXXWBcJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@YRRMuseum here at Belgrave #SurvivalDay with lots of photos. https://t.co/mFj4LSPgp6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice to see @BOM_Vic @BOM_au here at the Belgrave #SurvivalDay! https://t.co/7C5CWJM7tK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Belgrave #SurvivalDay welcome to country &amp; smoking ceremony. https://t.co/0lUDO5Tu2T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ernie Dingo - Listen To The News #SurvivalDay https://t.co/v1AYYhoNHN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yothu Yindi - Treaty #SurvivalDay https://t.co/CqUlSsB5qj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Comrade Trump mandates best political science for glorious American republic. What could go wrong? https://t.co/ylEokdAdJD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DwayneMallard ah gotcha, I was more thinking about provenance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DwayneMallard sorry, I don't understand what you mean?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My #AustraliaDay recommended reading for you, all about First Peoples agriculture, villages &amp; more: https://t.co/3rJN0DRNaA #SurvivalDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NovaPeris do be aware that was actually created as promo material for the SBS series "First Australians" in 2008. https://t.co/9krKdPyysr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorLudlam welcome back sir, hope things are good for you now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stilgherrian @purserj @R_Chirgwin @SnarkyPlatypus fingers crossed. I worry he just won't be able to help himself &amp; stumble into escalation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stilgherrian @purserj @R_Chirgwin @SnarkyPlatypus for someone who doesn't want it he's doing a good job getting China to threaten conflict]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@purserj @R_Chirgwin @stilgherrian @SnarkyPlatypus your enemies enemy may be your friend, but getting your 2 enemies to scrap is priceless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@purserj @R_Chirgwin @stilgherrian @SnarkyPlatypus if I was Putin &amp; had influence over Trump I'd try &amp; make him trigger a US-China conflict]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This makes no sense; who turns up at a check-in desk at an airport to find out whether you've got a visa or not?  https://t.co/ua1xYSNsYt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bendigobank or do I need to stay on "official" (but now insecure &amp; not updated) Android that came with my @oneplus One for them to work?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bendigobank my Android phone is no longer supported by vendor, but works. If I flash LineageOS to get security updates will your apps work?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is where we plan to spend #AustraliaDay https://t.co/d4rdDJPpvZ #SurvivalDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is my #AustraliaDay jam.. https://t.co/BL7G0gyBb1 #SurvivalDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thedeadline good point, I was involved in that long before Beowulf &amp; HPC so took it as a given but FOSS is really important to its success!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thedeadline I guess Beowulf was a grass roots initiative that led to the democratisation of #HPC by demonstrating how easy it could be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ajdecon @jamesdotcuff perhaps they could split into the upper and lower mesolithic, er, mesoscale? :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...I know that technically there are 3 systems listed on the last @top500supercomp list for Australia, but only those 2 are still in service]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By this measure Australia's 2 Top500 #HPC systems, @PawseyCentre Magnus &amp; @NCInews Raijin are "mesoscale", well sho… https://t.co/m17lhoYHqK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@germ_nation1 @Kon__K you can read his original deposition on page 14 of this original document: https://t.co/6o6JC8YKPp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@germ_nation1 @Kon__K goes on to say the only eyewitness who was there for the whole action (Sergeant John Lee) testified 40-50 were killed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlecMuffett @X2_AI *cough* M-x psychoanalyze-pinhead ? ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Counting down to break up of the UK in 5 4 3 2 1... #indyref2 

https://t.co/09yHb7Q99W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@purserj unfortunately @TurnbullMalcolm seem to be about 20 years behind current tech, so he's only just got to the mid 1990s.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnthoPantho coming to the dinner tonight?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In reality it was much cuter, the photo makes it look like it's scheming to leap on me &amp; rip my head off. I don't think it was...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rescued baby ring-tailed possum from ground in our garden, taken to vet for check-up (no visible injuries) &amp; rehous… https://t.co/fo7AOtNyRw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dr_dbw perhaps one for @mikekuiper ? :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@howthafugareya @Qantas @metrotrains it was a pretty quiet train, thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to the Open-MPI project, now under the "Software in the Public Interest" (SPI) umbrella! https://t.co/arnuZJUQqZ #HPC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mej0 @lwnnet eh? sorry - don't know the context or reference]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mej0 how about https://t.co/3vRW3Zms52 ? @lwnnet has reviewed it a few times: https://t.co/maOC38aPgE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@manaz_d @Qantas @metrotrains to paraphrase Douglas Adams: they hang in the sky in much the same way that bricks don't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Qantas thanks! Looked a lot larger in reality, could clearly see the kangaroo on the tail. ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just flown over by @Qantas QF94 at Auburn. Always impressive how large those A380's are! https://t.co/vMvGFw8HsO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fab day today on French Island with my glorious wife @donna_williams &amp; our great friend Scott. Only fell off the bi… https://t.co/zFRnD23MaZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Includes photos by myself, @neilcreek, @IbnulHussaini, @JacquieMilner, @cafuego and many other awesome MBO folks! https://t.co/47yA42hllC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["modern art simplified" :-) https://t.co/nTxwFnLKgx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First time to see Venus during daytime for me... https://t.co/9iLcbrCKSF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not surprised by these conversations, but it is still chilling reading.. https://t.co/zFfusDVO2k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another Australian #HPC job, this time on the other side of the continent in Perth!  https://t.co/kPd7fhI391 via @doctorcbpower]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Original image here: https://t.co/YZ0hxtJQhO :-) https://t.co/iIrwInJZ78]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...and another #HPC job here in Melbourne, Australia, this time at @cray_inc! https://t.co/9LCrYdxEoG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I for one welcome our new waterfowl overlords... https://t.co/XiX74qpnrp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aenveigh @penguin_brian @metrotrains @ptv_official signal problems for the lines on platform 1 between Melb Central and Flagstaff I believe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@metrotrains clear now, was from signal problems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty busy at Melbourne Central platform 4 @metrotrains, problems? https://t.co/bXUixEPBao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@voltagex you mean C *and* FORTRAN?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...another #HPC position at @DEDJTR, this time as a "Senior Advanced Computing Specialist - Computational Biology" https://t.co/pRoNoydy43]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posting for a friend of mine - #HPC manager position available at @DEDJTR here in Melbourne - https://t.co/gsNCiKrpSp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrDonnaYates @buffer thanks, always useful to have an outsiders perspective!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrDonnaYates @buffer very interesting, to a Welsh person whilst sounds more antique, but no cringe. Perhaps due to familiarity?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrDonnaYates @buffer not sure I follow, why did whilst suddenly become a bad word? "Eventuate" I could understand, but whilst is Middle Eng]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@metrotrains no worries, hope it's helpful! Driver just explained situation before we got to Box Hill which is good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@metrotrains OK thanks. Might want to update your PIDs then (if not done already). Was quite confusing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@metrotrains meeting a friend at Blackburn but PIDs say alternative transport arranged between Box Hill &amp; Blackburn.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>