<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@susanthesquark I have one of these https://t.co/AZmYmbMYxu and it does the same for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elonmusk the original is deplorable. Using 9/11 when none of these countries had anything to do with it. Not unlike the invasion of Iraq.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kait_oc also tired from the Dimitrov match, perhaps not recovering as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a word for those who support the #MuslimBan, um what was it....oh yeah, #deplorable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenRothenberg Dimitrov, need to deprive Rafa of getting closer to 17. Also nicer match up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I were #Mexico I'd just start building the wall to hide the creepy neighbour. Well played #Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timClicks just disappointed we got Peter and not Elon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@longislandyanky @MichaelSocolow @mmasnick *would have]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jackmcgraf @FoxNews @outline probably hands to small for handle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenRothenberg wow, perhaps a newly created account shouldn't be able to @ anyone for some period.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tennisabstract Awesome work Jeff, thanks for what you're doing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tennisabstract @sPETEcore curious why such a small sample size?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kait_oc Wouldn't surprise me, apparently quite a few of the US players are quite politically conservative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidLawTennis and it has a roof for potentially 37C.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RaybonKan @AJemaineClement is this a wall for ants!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keith_ng @fogonwater he says 'best practice', that doesn't mean just picking the largest number. Seems to allow for domain expertise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Declaring 2017 Word of the Year competition over early #kompromat is the winner. Looking forward to 2018 comp.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenRothenberg Wonder why https://t.co/aPbrq2faMl has his name as Duckhee Lee, that's how I've always seen it, but looks like you're right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@octonion One of the first with the Snapdragon 835 too, makes me doubt whether I should get the Pixel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When someone calls your language sexist and blocks you, but uses the language the exact same way themselves.… https://t.co/0QTbcXSR5k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bouncingbrick @WillHearYou @Spacekatgal @functiontelechy I wasn't rude. Brianna uses 'guys' in a gender neutral way herself. But blocked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WillHearYou @bouncingbrick @Spacekatgal @functiontelechy Wow she blocked me, and she uses 'guys' that way herself. https://t.co/tQtRW64ubi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevebiddle yes you're infringing the rights holder, it is an illegal download.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevebiddle vpn? that's not really worth the pain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevebiddle that's still piracy, and Netflix has shut that method down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Spacekatgal @functiontelechy that's your choice. Language evolves, I think you're in the minority.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Spacekatgal @functiontelechy context matters, 'guys' isn't gender neutral, but I say 'hey guys' to my daughters and its intent is neutral.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulg @pkedrosky Steven Pinker doesn't have children, so I'm choosing to be confused about what he really thinks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cgpgrey Dictator's Handbook on sale today on Audible. https://t.co/2BK5At6Qd1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenRothenberg are there limits for when it's too windy to play?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonathonmorgan @johnb30 I'm tempted by this too, Ubuntu looks possible https://t.co/u2TN8sP8O8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kncukier he seems easily annoyed. Probably said something innocuous on podcast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@octonion @soccermatics wow it's $1.99 on Kindle today. No brainer. https://t.co/CCVAdpLuJk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@squirrellyninja @UbisoftStudioSF .. But it's summer for me. :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sacca @tferriss the answer is actually crème fraiche. Check out Gordon Ramsay scrambled eggs on YouTube. Has 19 million views for a reason]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@octonion @mathbabedotorg what about when he gets the @potus account?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fchollet there's some decent python interfaces to the Neurosky Mindwave.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@susanthesquark @sivers He has a great interview with @tferriss I still regularly think about. https://t.co/xjIwA7qfM7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@susanthesquark Reminds me of this: https://t.co/VXwbQIXPYP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@siracusa Thought the Copenhagen model does imply true randomness. Einstein claimed 'God does not play dice' because he didn't believe it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuRendy good luck for the season.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timClicks @garethmorgannz @ThomasMeadia @TheSpinoffTV tax the increase in house value as an unrealised income like we do foreign shares.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kennethreitz maybe there's needs to be a from past import print]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TennisPodcast @DavidLawTennis seeds based on Elo rather than world ranking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlyAirNZ why not offer some refund on non-flexi tickets so you can then resell? No incentive to cancel otherwise. #wasteful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tiafoeasd you travels,  lots of places you're not underage :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Voltaire on #pizzagate Those who can make you believe absurdities, can make you commit atrocities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@veen @imyke presumably a lot of those in SV weren't raised there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evankuchar @LibyaLiberty tries not to be too literal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Smerity @fchollet @mat_kelcey get citizenship and move to Florida.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Smerity @FiveThirtyEight @rabois he's tweeting you his dreams now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnsontrading @pkedrosky @audible_com they used to have it too :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pocketcasts @akm hrm not sure what I'm doing wrong. https://t.co/hfRGd4EGmZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pocketcasts Still not seeing Adversarial Learning in search. Says it's added but has been &gt; 1 week. https://t.co/XBapV5qpv8 @joelgrus @akm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tennisabstract Murray could be number one with Elo if you had a higher K-factor, no?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidLawTennis Djokovic has a ton of points in the first half of the season, he'll have to be back to top form to hold on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tennisabstract as a match progresses does fatigue make it harder to hold serve?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ForecasterEnten seems pretty common to a lot of democracies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pkedrosky @ParticipACTION or New Zealand's. Although I might welcome the switch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ForecasterEnten at what point do the numerous subversions of the value of an individual's vote amount to theft?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickTimiraos wow that's buried fairly far down in that article. Toxic stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cetaceanism @marcoarment @adam_0293 says full boil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sivers yep I'm still shaking :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@octonion still waiting for Google to roll it out to New Zealand :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ihavearashmadan @octonion questioning a judge's impartiality because of his heritage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dhh @mvanier42 then you're lucky they sleep well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@skepticalsports @CarlBialik undecided about legalising marijuana?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WestWorld must generate some crazy datasets from users.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@octonion was thinking the same thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenRothenberg What's wrong with being the slowest hc Masters? I would've thought it would benefit some of the French players.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NateSilver538 what chance Trump out performs polls because people ashamed to say they'd vote for him, but will do it when no one's watching]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tennisratings Benoit Paire with the last-minute break-back from set and break down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoubleJake @csoghoian not likely with 2-factor authentication.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewpprice This is a great exploration of both points of view. https://t.co/TJt7JEWUHh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pkedrosky my wife started a website  to provide some small counterbalance  https://t.co/g164scftnd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pkedrosky @brent_alvord now you're living it, me too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickKyrgios just pretend to give a shit and you'll save yourself a bunch of drama,  unless the drama is what you like.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stucchio Bernie's list was about universal coverage. Those countries mange cost-effectiveness and coverage. India only cost-effective.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stucchio it's great and no doubt much more cost-effective than the US, but only for those who can afford it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KrisKoivisto @audible_com I've been read that book :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stucchio doesn't make the situation look better for the US.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is urgent to know whether Hillary prefers tabs or spaces. https://t.co/rEwgQs2f02]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidLawTennis @BenRothenberg Perhaps they're waiting to be asked their opinion on it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CameronMehlhopt @SimplicityNz  Looks cool, need something similar for non-Kiwisaver funds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jowyang I'll vote for the robotic overlord.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kminx because Home and Away became popular in all the other countries. #halfjoking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MKBHD shame too because it seems like a solid phone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aliafshar @mitsuhiko yeah, I'd like a reference too, is it an old stat? they have improved it seems.. https://t.co/SAjCm74tUZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@octonion it's going to be funny when he's the only one left supporting Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnaK_4ever @BenRothenberg might try this later to see which group I fit into.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeremyjkun @kjam @mathbabedotorg Find a story reporting a Trump rally those topics are now all mapped together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TennysSandgren @JRBlake @ryanharrison92 @SportsCenter Well it got you thinking and talking about it, so I guessed it worked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenRothenberg 5 sets distinguishes it from other tournaments. Can be a test of endurance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@octonion for the US OPEN yes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vika7 The Meaning of Life, 42.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@codinghorror @paulg If they're licking food off the floor, I accept the compliment to the cook that it is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@octonion do you ever use machine learning?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marzoTennis @usopen yes! and bonus of fewer players (and spectators)  cramping or passing out from heat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@elonmusk Someone needs to talk to this bird. https://t.co/q4b0d2iNoN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteveTignor wants to avoid the awkwardness with Del Potro in round 2.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>