<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂 like last season... how did that go https://t.co/alvWUwDTfW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@liberal_leftie @mclaffertyevan @5liveSport @bbc5live @chris_sutton73 if it is wasnt fir Scottish football your club wud b fuck all numpty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WestPilton @iain4546 ah canny vote🙈]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billydoyle07 @HeadCase666 thats the crazy masonic world of Scotland 🙈]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCTomEnglish can imagine whats coming your way now🙈🙈😂😂😂😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billydoyle07 yep, the irony from this is off the scale, at least the sane in scotland mostly voted for a free n open country]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan You not dead yet 🙈]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Scotland_future @mikedisbury a despicable blatant lying waste of space]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Film4 @IrvineWelsh watched these at mates on Friday night, absolutely class and funny as fuck,  just wonder where Irvine gets it all from😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scotsunsport @Kenny_Millar @Arsenal @RangersFC @ChelseaFC waiting for Barca to offer a reported £20m...🚶🚶🚶]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SoupCruncher @billydoyle07 @RuthDavidsonMSP this is the poll, complete lies from the shouty bint, I mean even she… https://t.co/TuGeQEh9Cr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@splbanter nahnit for long, 2 busy having a love in with the old rangers... fud of the highest order]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ray fuckin Wilkins😡😡😡 to this day i still hate the fact that that despicable prick played for, sorry, stole a wage… https://t.co/IfZpuz0x3n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck off ya clown😂😂😂😂 https://t.co/E3onJZzVov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndoHugh @iain4546 @TerraceImages which is why you felt the need to involve urself in a chat between 2 mates eh😘😘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndoHugh @iain4546 @TerraceImages its the gunts in pain..far worse pain than they think they inflicted on us. why butt in. u still hurting😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WestPilton Air force 1 is in the air🙈]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should  @WestPilton be allowed to carry on putting polls up whenever he likes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnnyBriton haha dont think so, ur just a racist clown.. best ignored, probably the reason u have no friends😘👋]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How embarrassing can the tories get🙈🙈🙈🙈🙈 https://t.co/UR7n6CLeqx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnnyBriton maybe u should leave ur house/shed and find some friends mr no mates👋👋👋]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This says everything about you... hapoy to share😘😘 https://t.co/SQT1tYWEq5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You wee man are just an ignorant uneducated racist clown..👋👋 racists😂🙈 is that why our country is OPEN TO EVERYONE.… https://t.co/31y73Yvtgc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hiya @murdo_fraser 😂😂😂😂😂 is this the biggest mouthpiece loser in political history🙈🙈🙈🙈 https://t.co/Vw4aLBfcQG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll ask again smart arse as u cant have it both ways, oh no🙈 not the % card again🙈🙈 https://t.co/ZvzSLeFPtM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@murdoch_charles @afneil shows how gullible unionists are to tory lies and spin...deary me🙈]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@murdoch_charles @afneil only the village idiots believe its 23%😂😂look for urself, if u can read..... just more spi… https://t.co/VNiQnZdYA4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also i take it u ignore the fact racism in ingerlund has increased in hugely since brexit vote won..... not and exa… https://t.co/cvmLCsEJue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ur logic, but dodged the Q...we voted to stay in EU with a far bigger % so the smart scots as you say want in the E… https://t.co/5pOnq5EIwg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnnyBriton wow.....what s democratic about GB🙈🙈 A Union where the rest get dictated to by the English.....not ve… https://t.co/ND5bpBtwYG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnnyBriton is there🙈🙈🙈 uk is dying.. greed racism and xenophobic ersewipes making it so easy for respectabke scots to get out!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laidlawjock 😂😹😂😂😂😂 what is wrong with these mutants🙈🙈]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laidlawjock "the famous" 😂😂😂😂😂what? 😂😂Hibs have the famous five, but "the famous" is the cringiest pile of 💩💩💩 ive ever read😂😂😂😂😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[😂😂😂😂😹 sting the fans for another £25😂😂😂 and a new shirt due out in about 4 months 🙈 talk about greed after making £… https://t.co/TM3ZSTOkD6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does that mean we also know we are safer and better off in the EU?? Far bigger % voted to stay in EU..so which is i… https://t.co/qo5W6pPI0Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[😂😂😂😂we shall see... that poll has been shredded for credibility all over the place, just u keep believing 🙈🙈 better… https://t.co/4tu1ZQsLJu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rangers to release a statement 🙈 https://t.co/7CQJCj4zyG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading this thinking, wtf is handling, maybe boring for 5 years but its a wage eh.....then realised who u were tal… https://t.co/CN0rpf9b7u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh ffs, now ur using my statements to you🙈🙈🙈😹 https://t.co/KtPw7BiEb2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And here is said clown....Neil Doncaster still telling UEFA what to do? Fuck knows how u got that from what i said🙈… https://t.co/Mcyg1Qwp9q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GemsFoxHFC @Robertmcc13 @neil_stewart_ @Craigm0808 i said UEFA get their info re scots clubs from SFA, he said, "so SPL running uefa" 🙈🙈🙈🙈]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GemsFoxHFC @Robertmcc13 @neil_stewart_ @Craigm0808 a pair right out the asylum i think]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GemsFoxHFC @Robertmcc13 @neil_stewart_ @Craigm0808 yet ignore the facts re Derry city cos it doesnt suit their argument....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GemsFoxHFC @Robertmcc13 @neil_stewart_ @Craigm0808 yeah, company not club, company not club...   company not club fenian cunt😂😂😂😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GemsFoxHFC @Robertmcc13 @neil_stewart_ @Craigm0808 yep his own arguement was coming back to prove him wrong like a right retard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GemsFoxHFC @Robertmcc13 @neil_stewart_ @Craigm0808 id like him to tellme exactly who the legal entity is.......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GemsFoxHFC @Robertmcc13 @neil_stewart_ @Craigm0808 dont think he even knows who the legal entity is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GemsFoxHFC @Robertmcc13 @neil_stewart_ @Craigm0808 yeah, more like a rat who belongs in the gutter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robertmcc13 @GemsFoxHFC @neil_stewart_ @Craigm0808 soif newco rangers fc isnt a new legal entity,  is it the old one🙈🙈🙈🙈🙈😂😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robertmcc13 @GemsFoxHFC @neil_stewart_ @Craigm0808 his plot is thinner than a rizzla paper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GemsFoxHFC @Robertmcc13 @neil_stewart_ @Craigm0808 hes a bit confused over entity's...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robertmcc13 @GemsFoxHFC @neil_stewart_ @Craigm0808 ur intelligence there in a tweet...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Craigm0808 @GemsFoxHFC @Robertmcc13 @neil_stewart_ 😂😂😂😂 well see what happened when Derry city done that😂😂😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robertmcc13 @GemsFoxHFC @neil_stewart_ @Craigm0808 your arguement is sll over the place]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robertmcc13 @GemsFoxHFC @neil_stewart_ @Craigm0808 seriously?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robertmcc13 @GemsFoxHFC @neil_stewart_ @Craigm0808 ignore it all u want, but newco rangers fc is a new legal entity is it not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robertmcc13 @GemsFoxHFC @neil_stewart_ @Craigm0808 but newco rangers fc are a new legal entity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robertmcc13 @GemsFoxHFC @neil_stewart_ @Craigm0808 so its not a new entity?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robertmcc13 @GemsFoxHFC @neil_stewart_ @Craigm0808 no, the club?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robertmcc13 @GemsFoxHFC @neil_stewart_ @Craigm0808 u agree u are a new legal entity?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robertmcc13 @FenianSlayer67 @GemsFoxHFC @Craigm0808 @neil_stewart_ ah the truth that doesnt suit ur agenda, check it up, its factual]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GemsFoxHFC @Robertmcc13 @neil_stewart_ @Craigm0808 theyre ignoring everything that doesnt suit their agenda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robertmcc13 @neil_stewart_ @GemsFoxHFC @Craigm0808 u tead Derry yet, bet you havent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robertmcc13 @FenianSlayer67 @GemsFoxHFC @Craigm0808 @neil_stewart_ so Did Derry city, Ive mentioned this loads but it doesnt suit ur agenda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lisa____xx @Robertmcc13 @GemsFoxHFC @Craigm0808 @neil_stewart_ says a wee bint showing her ass on social media🙈🙈]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robertmcc13 @neil_stewart_ @GemsFoxHFC @Craigm0808 can u read? GLASGOW IS THE JUNKIE CAPITAL. Officially.... get with the times junkie boy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robertmcc13 @GemsFoxHFC @Craigm0808 @neil_stewart_ search Derry city...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neil_stewart_ @Robertmcc13 @GemsFoxHFC @Craigm0808 weegies??? U forgot already that the weegie is the 💉💉💉💉💉 capital]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GemsFoxHFC @Robertmcc13 @Craigm0808 @neil_stewart_ its like pulling teeth..they mutter shite wbout companies non stop...the club is the co]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robertmcc13 @GemsFoxHFC @Craigm0808 @neil_stewart_ point is "formerly known as rangers football club" CLUB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robertmcc13 @GemsFoxHFC @Craigm0808 @neil_stewart_ ive asked you sbout my post 4 times snd all u do is ask another question 😴😴😴😴😴]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[😂😂😂😂😂😂 yeah yeah yeah tell urself it over n over it still wont come true https://t.co/0qWpWMKOwV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GemsFoxHFC @Robertmcc13 @Craigm0808 @neil_stewart_ legal facts dont matter wi huns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neil_stewart_ @GemsFoxHFC @Craigm0808 @Robertmcc13 Derry citys coefficient same after liquidation. then taken away wen try  2 play in euro🙈]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robertmcc13 @GemsFoxHFC @Craigm0808 @neil_stewart_ formerly rangers football club 🙈🙈🙈]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robertmcc13 @GemsFoxHFC @Craigm0808 @neil_stewart_  READ THAT https://t.co/RoWkapETwn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robertmcc13 @GemsFoxHFC @neil_stewart_ @Craigm0808 no less than yous, u still not won SPL yet🙈🙈telling aw the dafties ud win it easy..ooops]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GemsFoxHFC @neil_stewart_ @Craigm0808 @Robertmcc13 they never got put into liquidation..their club didn't die, although it become new club🙈]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neil_stewart_ @Robertmcc13 😂😂😂 naw u never, yous slavered pish aw night n bored the tits off me #zombies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Craigm0808 @Robertmcc13 @neil_stewart_  hmmmm i think thst mightve been indy1 ya retard😂😂😂😂🙈]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Craigm0808 @GemsFoxHFC @neil_stewart_ @Robertmcc13 perspective...well we'll have champ trophy AND still have won the cup last yr, unlike u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂😂 seriously😂😂😂😂 well have that this year..but still no major for u😹💩 https://t.co/5vJlTaZwZT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robertmcc13 @neil_stewart_ @Craigm0808 ur precious uk is dying its death.... Huns will be raging, ur beloved queen on her way oot an aw😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Craigm0808 @Robertmcc13 @neil_stewart_ gotta say, my forehead is about the same size as your wee Emilys 🙈😹🙈😹😹]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neil_stewart_ @Craigm0808 @Robertmcc13 makes me so happy to know huns have looked through it👻👻👻👻👻💚💚💚💚💚💚💚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neil_stewart_ @Craigm0808 @Robertmcc13 you mustve seen loads cracking pics of huns pissed off 😂😂😂😂😂 indy2 hasnt started yet retard😂😂😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Craigm0808 @Robertmcc13 @neil_stewart_ top banter... u that sad, hope u enjoyed my profile...💚💚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[🙈🙈🙈 thats brilliant 🙈🙈🙈🙈🚶🚶🚶 https://t.co/ZqC67XnbMP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@allez_allez_au @neil_stewart_ @Ryan4watson @KeiranRFC @chxrliebxnks75 @jetpack they tried 2 play in EURO, refused nd points taken off 🙈 2/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@allez_allez_au @neil_stewart_ @Ryan4watson @KeiranRFC @chxrliebxnks75 @jetpack derrys co-efficient points were still there 4 new club..🙈1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Craigm0808 @Robertmcc13 @neil_stewart_ 😂😂😂 look at the nick of you 😂😂 i know pics of the cup, doing you on and off the pitch is sore for u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@allez_allez_au @neil_stewart_ @Ryan4watson @KeiranRFC @chxrliebxnks75 @jetpack @BBCSport im sure they will say "its different" 💩💩]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@allez_allez_au @neil_stewart_ @Ryan4watson @KeiranRFC @chxrliebxnks75 @jetpack only hun based propoganda and weak SFA spin they listen to..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neil_stewart_ @Robertmcc13 yeah the company died, which was the club.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neil_stewart_ @Robertmcc13 ur fuckin kidding, the company and club is  the fuckin same, cant have company without club can you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neil_stewart_ @Robertmcc13 u dont half slaver shite, the club was sold in parts to charlie boy...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neil_stewart_ @Robertmcc13 aye aye, you have answered nowt, co which is club put into liquidation, club no more, new club new contracts💚💚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neil_stewart_ @Robertmcc13 the company is the club, check that one, UEFA states u cant have company withoutthe club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robertmcc13 @neil_stewart_ so ar u saying as its still in process that the oldco and newco are both still alive😂😂😂😂😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robertmcc13 @neil_stewart_ u get fed in the asylum?? Im certainly not here to educate the school dunces💚💚]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>