<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@razorleaves they tend to be rewarding to listen to all the way through so I'll keep on trying the ones I haven't heard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bingaEX since yesterday I watched 9 episodes of terrace house. This is horribly addictive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razorleaves I was enjoying The Seer quite a bit tonight. That is my favourite of their new albums, at least from first impression.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razorleaves that sounds alright. I'll get onto that sometime soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razorleaves never watched the original. This is some good ass television is it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razorleaves huh, maybe I should watch the David Lynch film to get a better idea then. Sounds deeper than I originally thought.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grandpunkalex and as it turns out you read a book by the guy so I'm a bit out of my depth in the issue now. Probably worth discuss sometime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grandpunkalex it was an instinctual "hey I remember that this guy is a dick to athiests" kind of response.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grandpunkalex probably important to say that I don't pay very close attention to atheist issues right now because they get tiresome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razorleaves I really don't know much about Dune at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grandpunkalex the feud, I don't read that much so I don't have counter arguments to his book.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grandpunkalex honestly didn't pay that much attention to it. But I'd be surprised if I felt that way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razorleaves that would be good. We haven't had that in a while.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razorleaves yeah it'll be interesting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grandpunkalex yeah, lmao
He and atheists have a history.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razorleaves I do have some very expensive options for that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razorleaves the stringer bell western film will be interesting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razorleaves yeah it's dumb that way. Can't really thumb type an essay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razorleaves I just ought to read more (not uni stuff) in general. It is my weak point ATM.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razorleaves I picked a tablet instead of a laptop because cheap tablets are good these days. But obviously no keyboard is a problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razorleaves clearly not my thing either lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razorleaves $50 would be fine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razorleaves I might keep it up since I have an Android phone and tablet. So it's convenient for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razorleaves instead I could buy an album every two months and use adblock on YouTube.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razorleaves yeah it's a good value proposition really. Mostly I try to avoid unnecessary subscriptions though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even in these shitty times, I'm not going to listen to Reza Aslan because of his religious superiority complex.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razorleaves I've addicted my family to Netflix so that's not a problem. Rest of my fam uses spotify since it is free with ads.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razorleaves too much unless you are on a family account. Like $9 a month maybe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razorleaves I've got 4 months free so may as well use it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razorleaves swans albums like to fuck my brain up and then have a very melodic track to follow up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razorleaves this fucking track. https://t.co/NSOXtC1ZyU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razorleaves I feel like I must have done it at some point. Will try again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a weird way trump validated twitter as a platform when it was fading away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razorleaves fuck yes, I want this album already.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razorleaves I've listened to that one in the past for that reason. Maybe I'll come back to it after the others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This MV and track are fucking dope.
https://t.co/C4aQyynBHa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razorleaves will check them out too. I've got plenty of time for listening to music.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razorleaves also I never mentioned that I like Soundtracks for the Blind. That's some good shit. Love the fucked up intro.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razorleaves But yeah I agree it is still great. Q tip really pulled it all together, much respect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razorleaves he is on at least 5 tracks I think. Apparently there are more Phife tracks that are going to get released.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razorleaves fuck yeah. The latest/last tribe album was what got me looking at more 90s.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm listening to 90s Hip Hop lately. Didn't realise I'd seen The Pharcyde before, Spike Jonze directed their video.
https://t.co/thgvokxGgR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well I've watched a lot of trash in Japanese so it's just an extension probably.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alright yeah, I think I'm enjoying Terrace House.
Me enjoying reality television, what are the odds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_BADCATBAD well there is being right and there is being a dick about something. Anyway thanks for your perspective.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_BADCATBAD yep getting psychotic on someone is very concerning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_BADCATBAD this is all a very clear and logical policy to me. Retrospectively I was wrong in my first post, probably just feeling moody.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_BADCATBAD presuming X person isn't shaming anyone into a relationship it seems somewhat reasonable to me for them to ask Y out. No?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_BADCATBAD well yeah, I would hope things would be cut and dry to avoid confusion. Maybe it is only young people who aren't this confident.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_BADCATBAD I mean to suggest more that lots of relationships with other intentions but they wouldn't say because it comes off scummy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anecdotally over the years I would say I agree that is a good rule of thumb. https://t.co/hVd3ZCK3Kv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bingaEX from the first episode I'm very intrigued. Also it's cool that I know one of the hosts from another japanese variety show.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bingaEX alright then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bingaEX which one am I suppose to start with? I see it on Netflix.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razorleaves exactly, the intention is all the same but there are weird connotations. Makes it hard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Years of "good afternoon Mr./Mrs./Miss X" in primary school has ruined the nicety of the phrase for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trashy idol anime is becoming self-aware. https://t.co/f567p85Hie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch “Yassin Falafel” on #Vimeo
Good short doco about a refugee family.
https://t.co/yJcXTzJipS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only recently have I started to realize that they aren't translated because it is so dull that it's not worth the effort.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As long as I've been into Seiyuu culture I've wondered why interviews and live broadcast get so few translations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grandpunkalex ooh, solid choice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grandpunkalex what're you gonna get for lunch?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shinichick_39 even those who deny it secretly love JJ.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nyoomiz FLUME!!!
*shakes fist at cloud*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[XD Definitely nothing better than Kid Cudi. https://t.co/DnmgOl4FEH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey look, The Red Turtle is nominated for the Zootopia award. https://t.co/x0UJgLZZaH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine being this sensitive to a "?" https://t.co/HyMGqW8bQV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Madi_karp https://t.co/YfuUQ2p95x
I have Android but it uploaded in my phone browser.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Madi_karp does your phone do it better? (btw I'm totally fine if you can't be bothered haha)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Madi_karp maybe the quality doesn't matter so much if it is the only option?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_BADCATBAD you just need a few small loans to get started.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_BADCATBAD idk we both shitpost on twitter a fair bit too, so we are pretty much trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_BADCATBAD Obama having digs at fox news is what I'm thinking about.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_BADCATBAD well at least not in real time. I'm sure they all respond at some point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grandpunkalex @Retawes @yamiflea always remember to bring a towel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razorleaves I couldn't do it again. That shit is rough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this Skull Girls? https://t.co/2uTSbivRLV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BasuP she was the best and only rtv reporter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeneralVonLily good to hear, and good luck with the moving stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeneralVonLily you paint a grim picture but still it seems kind of awesome to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeneralVonLily my condolences for your day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redactedtext it doesn't make me feel very good about the left the way violence is being praised online.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lemonator I get why they are asking but Jeez it's midnight on the weekend and I'm paying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somehow the police checked my opal and student card at almost midnight.
Then asked if I'm still a student despite card not being expired.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lemonator it went alright. I'm drunk but can still make it home.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grandpunkalex I'll remember never to trust marquees.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dannyodwyer I think he is an ass-hole who doesn't deserve any attention as much as the next person but this meme seems really shitty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grandpunkalex how didn't you know? :0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've got some coconut water as a chaser for whisky tonight because Open Mike Eagle said it in a rap song. So I'm hoping it goes well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ano-chan was asked to say the Trump catch phrase "lock her up". https://t.co/Qpto5LyCnH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone should avoid this trashy action film. https://t.co/nVyKrTWGZN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@salbears95 oh no, I was joking about how it was related. Some internal business stuff is why they fired the people. Probably outsourcing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@salbears95 the statement was that they layed off 17 engineers for the company. Sounds like an odd place to work at.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@salbears95 yeah I think that's what they had said. Reminds me to follow up on the firing stuff, I only heard word of mouth stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razorleaves alright I'll start SFTB because even To Be Kind I find very dense and difficult to listen to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razorleaves will do. I'll probably listen to them all today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razorleaves I haven't listened to them in a while. To Be Kind was the album I listened to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razorleaves lately it's been great to listen to while driving for work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nyoomiz since it was the whiplash director I wasn't too surprised. If anything not enough jazz in la la land and I love the film.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thought of the day is that I like RTJ3 a whole lot. Get on that people.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>