<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Garnerk13 actually women tend to gain alcohol tolerance with age.  If you're still getting hungover on few drinks you're still young ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope having the @NWSL on @lifetimetv will make it easier for highlights to be featured on recap shows on dedicated sports networks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think i'll be playing Majora's Mask to celebrate #GroundhogDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HockeyIsForEveryone I will be showing my support for women in hockey by attending the @TheCWHL All Star Game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ShaunKing @NYDailyNews For anyone that wants to use it: Quebec City flag, half mast. GFDL https://t.co/RC2zdbGUwC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe we are the alternate universe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today, for every tweet using #BellLetsTalk, Bell donates 5¢ to #MentalHealth initiatives. Join the conversation:  https://t.co/t1rQgaQZ85]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Asha_Suzanne Ice Cream Floats are drinks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@twitemerald @CMW_Week My future aspirations will now be to arrange local talent to perform at half-time during @NWSL games in Toronto!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @CMW_Week followed me!  Guess that means i'm one of the top 18,100 people in the music industry now ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Asha_Suzanne It's a pun. On the Bus sounds like "Omnibus" ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scATX ie. I agree that it's profoundly sad—But I'm not surprised that there's people in GG management that are likely anti-woman.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@scATX inviting girls to adult events, is done either to hide the absence of grown women, or to overshadow their participation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@scATX I think sexism is often disguised as support for (young) girls; in a circuitous way of oppressing grown women.  1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#nwsldraft Happy with the picks so far.  Would love it if @BostonBreakers could grab @Kailen_Sheridan later! https://t.co/Ugu9mH75k3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's the @NWSL draft day.  Guess it's time for me to be active on twitter again! #DoYouEvenWoso]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Garnerk13 no more music tweets on NWSL draft day! =p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welp.. guess i'm not hopping on a megabus to Rochester afterall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Asha_Suzanne  Let's go with #4ı20 and pretend the dotless 'i' is a blunt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@LGaltonn Badly wrapped presents are easier to open! #TrueFacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Garnerk13 I'd think they're still not planning on coming to Canada.

Your reaction: https://t.co/aQYc8DBnBW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BostonBreakers Would love to see Toronto's own @TheQuinny5  on my favourite team.  Toronto's colour is blue too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wore orange socks today.  I had a feeling it was going to lead to a @HoustonDash announcement! https://t.co/MOqQMb3KXt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahLerner I vowed in the summer that i'd get a passport and go to a midweek @WNYFlash game next year. Now I'm not so sure I want to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Asha_Suzanne I think there's less sugar in cake than most breakfast cereals!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In our society physically large men are entitled to get their way.  Physically small men are babies when they compl… https://t.co/BcteWCKzYO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@torontostar: CFL players blast ‘baby’ Giovinco for field criticism https://t.co/yzfDo6WXiK via @torontostar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had a doctor's appointment today, so i decided not to eat an apple.  She might have cancelled if I did.  #FridgeLogic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffKassouf @PaulTenorio link is sending me back to TFCvNYCFC game recap.  This one is working for me: https://t.co/lYaM63UVsX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anybody know of a stream from brasil for tonight's games? #BRACRC #ITARUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Garnerk13 I'm chalked that you had a religion class in a public school!  #SWIDT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, I forgot to wear my jersey to bed, so France women are still undefeated when i wear it. #PRKFRA #U20WWC I guess the loss is my fault.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@janinebeckie4 And the best WDL in the olympics! https://t.co/mVH1lrT7ke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[France women are still undefeated when i wear my jersey.  It's starting to get a little yellow, afraid to wash out the luck. #FRA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Garnerk13 I know her!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toronto is cheering the team in Red.  Montreal is cheering the team in Blue.  Oh the irony.  #MTLVTOR #MLSCupPlayoffs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Garnerk13 1999 and 2003 too ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chicagoredstars I think you could make a poem about Johnson and Johnston together ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philpurple Pugh skipped going to college for soccer. Jessie Fleming didn't, nothing wrong with fleming's decision. https://t.co/4HLPdF2gxN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philpurple i think it's more like Pugh shouldn't have been there either. But the USSF rules forced her not to play for her college.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not just soccer. But nearly everything in the media. The only acceptable feminism to them is for young girls, not g… https://t.co/sbEX3ixj9R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@kpiperphotos @backlinesoccer I agree: It seems grown women's issues are not important, it only matters if painted as a young girls' issue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much would you pay for one @Garnerk13? =p https://t.co/lIW21eDlYe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@TwitEmerald  Was really hoping that it would be Labbé to Boston!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I did expect @WashSpirit to trade with @BostonBreakers for the #1 distributions spot.  But still surprised at the p… https://t.co/SLaWwDmHcN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@BostonBreakers Also thank you for only charging me 10$ shipping, when it really cost more than that. That's why you're my favourite team!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My @BostonBreakers Mystery Box came today. But since i don't know what's in it, my mom figured she should wrap it for me for the holidays.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would love to own a t-shirt that has a big QR code that links to the @NWSL youtube page.  #NudgeNudge #WinkWink #FreeAdvertising]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#signsimagrownup  My social life goal is to get out once a month!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess I have to wear my France jersey to bed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@TwitEmerald But it's hard to bet against home field advantage for Brazil, so i'm predicting CRC in 2nd place!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They're ranked the lowest of the 4, but I have high hopes for #CRC; they have the talent and teamwork to do well! @TwitEmerald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like Brazil's invitational tournament this year is Costa Rica, Italy, and Russia #CRC #ITA #RUS #BRA https://t.co/oWasvLk8wu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think #Califarewell or #Califoregone have a better ring than #Calexit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somethings Finally on it's way :)  Can't wait to see what's in it. https://t.co/UJlbuMf2UH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited to watch Leon vs Lyon!  @LeonAdriana9 #UWCL #OLFCZ  If i can find a stream that works...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@BostonBreakers Maybe Gemma Bonner? Played for Beard in chelsea &amp; liverpool. Just hearing that Smith is healthy and signed would be great 2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm 6.84 feet tall if I use my own foot instead of the imperial standard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wait until @Garnerk13 randomly sends me a link to listen to something! https://t.co/AO57Y6pu3u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[no edit button, so i'll just delete my tweet and hope nobody noticed.. and hope they don't have email notifications..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things like this are why i wish @NWSL had voting for a midfield play of the week. Sometimes it's better than goals… https://t.co/LTqYEyRXF2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Garnerk13 Does that mean if you get married and get a new last name, your middle name will be dangerous?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@backlinesoccer Obviously the Hat looked up some facts!  #GoForGlory https://t.co/QaNJ3G96mI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#SpiritCooking Mildly disappointed that it has nothing to do with Washington WoSo.
Majorly disappointed that Satanic-Panic is still a thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always seems so obvious in hind sight.  "Matt Beard signs yet another player who played for him before" https://t.co/VJJCUhK3D1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder if @WashSpirit know something we don't. Will some CANWNT players skip the college draft? Is Australia goin… https://t.co/Q7Iso89CQx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe the @WashSpirit are expelling the #USWNT players so they can relocate to Canada!   #iwish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After shipping and exchange rate ~40$ Canadian.  Bought one!  Merry Christmas to me! https://t.co/qXhsge0Qrz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SandHerrera_ Chicago is the 4th most populous US metro.
Perth is Australia's 4th.  #GoForGlory]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All dressed up for halloween! But no where to go yet... #BlackMage #finalfantasy https://t.co/uIngaQva2L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now that @CocaColaLife is available in Canada, my decor is complete.  Just didn't look the same with the red box an… https://t.co/j13Siw958H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@backlinesoccer @SandHerrera_  thanks for the replies-Already letdown with CAN for missing previous windows, don't want missing players too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Question for @CanadaSoccerEN  
also would like to hear @backlinesoccer and @SandHerrera_  thoughts on this particul… https://t.co/FRjGq0Jgr1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 17/02/04 CANvMEX match is outside of the FIFA window.  Does this mean players in Europe leagues will be missing?
https://t.co/DBbF8539F8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@backlinesoccer I think in olympic/WC years we also need an award for replacement keeper of the year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TwitEmerald @Garnerk13   Sorry for the #GuiltTrip. :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[apparently TFC home closer isn't that popular. Having trouble finding people to go with! Wish it was a CANWNT game! that was a little easier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@backlinesoccer Only @chicagoredstars, @SkyBlueFC  and @WNYFlash have ever liked my tweets. With CRS liking nearly every vote for G/S otW.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The colour of disappointment this year.
#Breakers #FRA #MapleLeafs #BlueJays #TORvsCLE.
Guess i'll cheer on #TFC in… https://t.co/es3jDJmHfj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SimoneGiertz @TwitEmerald  Even native English speakers usually don't know that rule.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SimoneGiertz @TwitEmerald Even when making new words, the suffix and root word have to come to english through the same language.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SimoneGiertz OUAT Facebook had "defriend" which was more popular than "unfriend." But they had to change it because "unfriend" is correct.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I clicked the #CaptainCanada hashtag, expecting it to be something about @sincy12.  But it's just baseball.. and Jays aren't even winning!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PresChoice i.e. I would like to be able to plan my shopping thursday night so i can do it first thing friday morning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PresChoice The new offers email keeps coming later every week. I can load by signing in on friday, it would be bet… https://t.co/A3UCOa8xSx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will start buying whichever Toronto Newspaper reports on this story! @TorontoStar @TheTorontoSun @globeandmail… https://t.co/uhpF5aXjAx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lets Bring FCKC to Ontario @torontofc  @MLSEPR @MLSEFoundation  @MLSELIVE  ... and someone call Jim Balsilie! https://t.co/aBq0JeiMbI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SandHerrera_ @sammymewy @BacklineSoccer Please excuse my tardiness, and really bad kerning, and trademark infring… https://t.co/rVRdYc8TTt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop trying to make the six happen.  It's not going to happen! https://t.co/paH3JR1fka]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After the playoffs, @HoustonDash is the only team not to lose to @WNYFlash this season.  (If you cont losing on penalties as a loss.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@TwitEmerald  at least after being spoil I can use twitter again, hopefully won't have the score spoiled too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[still waiting for the @NWSL final to be posted to youtube.. I lasted til yesterday early afternoon before being spoiled who won.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#GEOBLOCKED #WASvWNY #NWSLChampionship]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I sure hope someone at @TSN_Sports will be watching the @NWSL Championship for potential plays of the week!  #NWSLChampionship  #WASvWNY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am thankful that the NWSL final will be put on youtube later, cuz i'm gonna miss it live #CanadianThanksgiving. #NWSLChampionship #WASvWNY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Garnerk13  I want a Sam Mewis vs Everybody shirt. https://t.co/AfxztdVc85]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Asha_Suzanne better drink it all now, before the alcohol starts dissolving the plastic!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even 30C tropical water puts people at risk for hypothermia. If you imagine mermaids as having slim waists: why don't we see skinny whales?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@TwitEmerald Is it too late to move the #NWSLFinal to Toronto?  #PORvWNY #WASvWNY @WashSpirit @WNYFlash]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#PORvWNY #WASvWNY The team with the most Canadians playing against the team closest to Canada, but in the stadium furthest away! #NWSLFinal]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>