<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@SelassieTaylor @MisssBeccaWhite @nickildn @NishaaNicole @TeeyanaAromi omg these thieving taxi drivers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NishaaNicole @chanteparis @linkuptv he gotta release the whole track]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NishaaNicole @chanteparis @linkuptv omg there's more, extreme measure ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mayycakes it's quite disgusting how people of your own race are racist towards each other]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The security at #joyeuxbordel are RACIST towards black women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenericTwoShoes @thenudequeen looool I guess you never know, he might get a promotion ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenericTwoShoes @SoCasperr Loool tell me about it, I'm in bed aswell ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm tired of being tired ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drunk people are actually funny ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looool how can this guy say cheating doesn't count if your drunk ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenericTwoShoes I'm off sick at the moment but sally will be replying to my emails]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenericTwoShoes Lool I was actually gonna type it again ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TamiMustafa1 @suitelifeondick loool it's actually so truee ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This year just keeps on getting shit, but I pray that December turns it around]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people love to lie on social media, it's actually not that deep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whatttt Gifty is so talented, this is why I don't watch X factor, absolute joke #XFactor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually can't breathe, this guy stinkkssss.... Like why would you come out smelling like this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't understand why people love to stink and have the audacity to come out of their house smelling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Missguided_help Where is my parcel? I payed for next day delivery and it's still not here....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OfficialPLT_CS where is my delivery??? I ordered using next day delivery but it's still not here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NishaaNicole I don't think we ate the same thing, it's delicious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yo! Sushi for brunch ðŸ‘…ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still can't believe this guy tried to rub off my eyebrows to see if I had eyebrows #cheeky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those 5 minutes felt like 30 minutes, this is why I HATE rush hour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worst journey to Stratford ever, stuck on the jubliee line for 5 minutes during rush hour and it was hot and smelly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenericTwoShoes @DevonteMJay loooool it actually is ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ I'm trying to work on being on time ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only I would go ham at the gym and then want to go to Bagel King after ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #fatty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm really trying to stick to this healthy diet/exercise plan but I love eating carbs and working out is soo long ðŸ˜”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the birds (part 2) is one of the best songs by the weeknd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenericTwoShoes loool it's getting really bad ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually spend too much time on social media]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Oloni wow, I just don't understand why some girls allow this to go on for sooo long??? 5 years, what a waste of timeðŸ˜’]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xoGiaxo_ @NishaaNicole lool, he's not rated at all ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lisha_paradise @GenericTwoShoes looool this is so us, we are #rebels]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NishaaNicole @Uncle_De loooooooool his face at the end ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In desperate need of a detox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going to try a #rawvegan diet lol lets see how long I last ðŸ˜‚ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't deal with people who have constant mood swings ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#french is a beautiful language]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol I always stumble across random things ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenericTwoShoes yeah it's so clapped and my voice sounds weird ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This dirty tonsillitis actually needs to go...ðŸ˜©ðŸ˜’]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dominos_UK I have called the store about 10 times and they keep on putting me on hold]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dominos_UK my pizza was delivered cold what's going on dominos?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dominos_UK but it's not here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dominos_UK I have been waiting for over an hour for my order, I ordered via the app and it said that the pizza has been delievered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@burger_lobster Their behaviour was very unprofessional and I will not be returning or recommend the #burgerandlobster in #holborn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@burger_lobster Unfortunately, i didn't get this love when i went there. The customer service was poor and some of the waiters were rude.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When everything is going according to plan ðŸ™Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loool this uncle just said Happy New Year, it's July mate.... I can't deal with freshies ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenericTwoShoes @RelatableQuote looool omg it's actually so true ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NishaaNicole this is the year of realising things]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't deal with iPhones anymore it's not everyday the screen must crack ðŸ˜¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I finally listened to the life of Pablo properly and its amazing. I'm actually soo late ðŸ˜‚ðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally the 1st of May]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NishaaNicole RESPECK IT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm suppose to be revising...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenericTwoShoes @urmce it's nowhere near funny at all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NishaaNicole loooll happy fucking halloween]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NishaaNicole Where's the blow at]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my mood literally just went from 0 to 100 real quick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenericTwoShoes lool oh my for real girl you gotta get some z'ss ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NishaaNicole @dapperlaughs loool what you fucking swearing at me for ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im actually addicted to #HTGAWM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#RandomActsOfKindnessDay get inspired and make someone day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My shoulder and back are actually aching]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TamiMustafa1 @kimmy_sk5 loool for real ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NishaaNicole I know girlðŸ˜‚ now we some grandmas ðŸ˜”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@karishamap aww I'm glad you love them, enjoy!! â˜ºï¸â˜ºï¸ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too young to be feeling like this ðŸ˜¶]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to eat fufu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate being in awkward situations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#BestMemoriesOf2015 WirelessðŸŽ‰ with @TamiMustafa1 @NishaaNicole]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LoveestlikeXO for real]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LoveestlikeXO omg yeess I was actually saying this today ðŸ™Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ohmxks I'm good thanks hunn what about youu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenericTwoShoes @TamiMustafa1 @chanteparis Looooool omg that was funny ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenericTwoShoes @TamiMustafa1 @chanteparis looool that dirty neighbour ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been sleeping on Avocado Co-washðŸ˜± it left my hair feeling soo soft and it smells amazing #lushcosmetics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My natural hair has grown but it's time to get it trimmed ðŸ˜•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenericTwoShoes lool why the ðŸ˜‚ face ðŸ˜‚what makes you sad ??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NishaaNicole I can't breathe ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ it actually crackedd me up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AbiTheGreatest I actually love this â¤ï¸â¤ï¸"we need to persevere and never give up on what we want"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AbiTheGreatest Oohh I think I left it near your bed but I'm not too sure ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AbiTheGreatest @chanteparis aww abi thanks for having us â¤ï¸ xx lool I just realised that I left my charger ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had a beautiful morning walk ðŸ’–]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Temporary Happiness ðŸ˜ªðŸ˜”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The good ones go if you wait too long ðŸ•‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait til after Thursday ðŸ™ŒðŸ˜«ðŸŽ‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you let a good thing go...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want a selfie stick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually love mick â˜ºï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eat hot shit ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Khleopatra_VII oh okay thankss x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenericTwoShoes ikr tell me about it ðŸ˜ª]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenericTwoShoes ikr and I'm at home in bed ðŸ˜ªðŸ˜ª]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AbiTheGreatest Ive been trying to call you as well and it kept on going to voicemail no wonder why :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[iphone chargers are so shitty they always break]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fucking rip off mate]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>