<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoupeReVille there's so much more I should say but I'm not adequately equipped to do so. So I will share what I can from others who are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoupeReVille thank you all for the amazing work you do, twitter friends and twitter strangers! I appreciate you all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not to get sentimental (although, what's the harm?) but the amazing people on my feed have helped me keep perspective these last few days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CianTormey fierce hair game. A+]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jp_jordan Christ above...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoupeReVille oh yeah! and Yoshi's Wooley world for 3DS. But I'll save that one till I'm on my holidays...which will be when??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoupeReVille Aaaannnnnnd I'm picking up Resident Evil 7 today. For the love of God help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoupeReVille I bought Rise of the Tomb Raider and turned it off as soon Lara got the stuffing beat out of her by nature. Again. Will resume]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoupeReVille I'm about 50% through Hitman (2016). I'm about 20% through The Last Guardian. I'm still trying to platinum Dishonored 2...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I keep buying all these games I have to time to plaaaaayyyyy🎶🎶]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neevok you're on!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pauljholden I couldn't say PJ! I haven't seen that film either -_-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jp_jordan by all accounts I hear he's quite good?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoupeReVille I had no plans to see it before...but it might be worth a watch now out of sheer curiosity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having not watched Split myself but having learned of the ending just this second (from a podcast) all I can think is...what?!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taoiseach Enda Kenny: Cancel the Taoiseach's St Patrick's Day visit to Washington under Trump. - Sign... https://t.co/Opz1DRL2SM via @Change]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jp_jordan @rebnalty @ruairicoleman @DontStopRewop @eoinmarron this is the red squad. they already know how to co-ordinate! damn good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jp_jordan @Bennessy @SeanOhOgain @CianTormey what a gang to be included in! Thanks JP!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheers guys! Some mad talent in display, as always. https://t.co/AZcA8qYeH5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stephen_C_Ward thanks Stephen!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had a lovely evening bombarding @neevok with info about all my male celebrity crushes. She is far too patient and good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wanna feel unfit? Try keeping juuuust ahead of a stranger who walks exactly as fast as you do. Phew!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@declanshalvey @whoajordie An amazing set of answers Dec, thank you! What a history!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@declanshalvey @whoajordie either/or! 😀]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@declanshalvey @whoajordie this is a terribly uninformed question to ask but what was the first project you two worked on together? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@falldogs this is one of the coolest versions of this I've seen! 💖]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To rephrase my tweet...I'm really freaking excited for this! https://t.co/w0mtSX1pfn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jp_jordan how dare they? It's "Jappers"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday was terrifying and I felt genuine despair, but today has renewed my sense of hope. Thank you to all who march #WomensMarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@falldogs I'm having a lot of fun with it at the moment 😀]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@falldogs you might know this already but I discovered Hitman (2016) features mirrors with actual reflections. A rare sighting indeed!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Priello he just can't contain all those feelings!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These are amazing 💖 https://t.co/DZao4OpkUe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't get over the pouty face on Kylo's Nendoroid...just kill me dead! https://t.co/5QuHptU0sY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jp_jordan ...looking at this again this might read like sarcasm but I swear it's not!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jp_jordan oooh! that'll be a heck of a script. Full of that classic JP wit!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fffits it's too cute for words!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mardcon hmm I see, I see. I guess I won't know how I feel for sure till were done 🤔]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Treestumped it's the original series we're on, and we're watching it in Japanese. That might be a contributing factor 🤔]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoupeReVille also no spoilers please! We've a third of the series left to watch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoupeReVille I guess I can see how he'd be a devisive character but on the other hand...I'll fight you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Shinji an unpopular character? Some friends are showing me Evangelion for the first time and I gotta say I empathise with Shinji a lot...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. I'm honored to have been a part of this team! Holy moly. https://t.co/wDpjMU9JL3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Treestumped @finchmeredith1 this is so beautiful! You guys make a great team!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CartoonRobinson these are great!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rhino_ryanotto thank you!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neevok aw youuuu 💖I knew if I didn't do him justice, there'd be hell to pay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jp_jordan ah yes I've seen this before. it's a good watch!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jp_jordan thanks Jeepers!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HugoBoylan aw thanks Hugo, that means a lot! 💖]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stephen_C_Ward thanks so much Stephen 😀]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lazyafternooner this is so powerful!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@falldogs also, I had a terrible joke prepared about already having two arms...but I respect you too much to follow through with that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jp_jordan it might end up like the PS3 and get stronger over time. Hopefully.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Drop_Wallet yeah that's the one thing that has me tempted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@falldogs admittedly, I hadn't seen that trailer. https://t.co/aMk37zkYpd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Currently the Switch is a no-go for me. I'll give it a year maybe and see? Also, it'll need amazing virtual console options to win me over.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stephen_C_Ward thanks Stephen!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoupeReVille I'm getting real Sonic '06 vibes from Odessey though. The "humans" look real bad 0_0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoupeReVille Breath of the Wild and Mario Odessey look fun. There's nothing else that jumps out at me though. Will wait for a bit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much Switch news.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RedCube_Studio you're probably booked up with cats so I'll use this as an excuse to show off. Rascal https://t.co/O4K0YMRbAF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Katiecanartgood excellent design choice Katie !!! If I were to get a tattoo I would get something like this. My childhood summed up!💖💖]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DontStopRewop @declanshalvey ooh! This is awesome!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sketching what was probably my first ot3, way back before I knew what an ot3 was. 💖💖💖

I want to… https://t.co/jovpQEoqiD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdlaiM I'm particularly fond of that last one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@declanshalvey Happy Birthday Dec!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deevseverything Aw, thanks so much Dee!! This made my morning 😀😀]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bless this cast. https://t.co/5GhAJtRF5Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheBigBang_ this looks like a candid on-set photo. DC are so weird with their promo images for this film...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My kingdom for an AU road trip movie. https://t.co/IkSBH07bTZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got around to Arrival at long last and it is just such a beautiful film. I was close to tears at several points.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fffits Ahhhhh!!! Louise that's amazing news!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rebnalty woah Rebecca! 😀😀]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just booked a table for Dublin Comic Con in August.

Commence panic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stephen_C_Ward thanks Stephen!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bru_bat that's where you shave the middle and keep the sides long, yeah?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoupeReVille other than that it's an exercise in embarrassment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only good aspect of making a new profile pic is that I get to give myself nicer hair than I actually have.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fffits I LOVE this!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know so little about it to date, and I'm delighted. I wanna go in blind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woah?? I only have to avoid media for two more months? Hot dang! https://t.co/CzUHJC3VRa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaraaFerguson oh goodness Tara!! Congratulations!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdlaiM is a treasure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really wish I didn't have places to be today. https://t.co/uBt1sq7MAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdlaiM aw, I missed this but what a nice idea!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lazyafternooner those two are perfect!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cat_Mangan thanks Cat! Looking forward to seeing what you do too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@declanshalvey @whoajordie amazing work guys! Holy cow...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deevseverything ohmygod Dee. I don't think there's a more fabulous person on Twitter than you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@declanshalvey thank you so, so much Dec! Happy New Year to you and the crew at @RedCube_Studio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lets_hopscotch aw thanks Rebecca! Your work is a constant inspiration for me 💖💖]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KirbishArt incredible work Martin!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ruairicoleman we absolutely do! I can't wait to see what you do this year, Ru. I've no doubt it'll be a great year for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@saintworksart thanks very much Matthew! You have some incredible work yourself!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoupeReVille thank you all so much for following along and for the words of encouragement. I'd be lost without ye all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I produced more art more than I ever have in a single year this year. I want to keep that going in 2017. Some plans in the works already.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ruairicoleman @CianTormey yeah but will Buzzfeed write a list based around it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StockmanNate aw thanks for saying so Nate. I went back and forth on the layout a lot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lazyafternooner aw, thank you very much Jen!!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>