<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Developing movement: a march of scientists on Washington. https://t.co/0d9Bu6bDiU Thanks... https://t.co/ihhiv1ojXD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop Harassment in Science https://t.co/a5jOCf5IAK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Firing a professor who used private email for work and encouraged postdoc to be critical is not right. Petition at https://t.co/Nym1CUmkhe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The grounds for dismissal are 1) using a private gmail address for work purposes and 2) encouraging an outgoing... https://t.co/lD4UEsdmzz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jtuttlekeane Nah, you're just pioneering InSAR on Mars!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Students at AGU need your help! https://t.co/zGRXJR93h7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Valgren6 @asrivkin Don't let any luxemburgish read that. You will be followed by a seriously dark look all the way to the border!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday's canyon du jour was Bruce. Most surreal!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday's highlight was Arches. Then drive west closer to Bryce.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quick detour through Monument Valley and afternoon at Canyonland NP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today we visited Canyon de Chelly. Pictures don't do it justice What a magnificent place! Geology + ruins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moving on, this was Petrified Forest NP yesterday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day 3 and 4 = Grand Canyon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally good enough Internet to post an update. That's day 2: Joshua Tree NP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The crew on the way back https://t.co/KPJm7UsHKg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting close to the punchbowl https://t.co/tmyxPh29Le]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/HNqcLrPGMi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great first day on the road with stop at Devil's punchbowl. Even saw some geology crossing Cocktail fault!
Green... https://t.co/i2g1UHxaZb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Canada Day to all our friends North of the Border!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just Father/Son movie night at @saintanselms Rocky, 1976 version]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hurford: #Phobos orbital decay create stress that can fracture crust but interior needs to be weaker than surface #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hurford: Grooves on #Phobos as 1st hint of disruption of satellites as its orbit decays #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nathan Williams notes 1972 moonquake focus OK with chain of recent lobate scarps E of Mare Frigoris: Are these still active?
#LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nathan Williams: Mare Frigoris is essentially the Man-on-the-Moon's  unibrow. #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Byrne: if monoclines are analogue to lobate scarps, we have a lot of that on Earth! #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Byrne advances East Kaibab monocline as #Earth analogue for wrinkle ridge #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryan_N_Watkins @HOAshcroft Wouldn't be LPSC without hearing that a couple time :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cole: Reject 30° dip for wrinkle  ridge plane so horizontal strain &amp; decrease in planetary radius greater than previously thought. #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cole: Ridge in Melas Chasma may resist erosion because of magmatic intrusion in wrinkle ridge fault plane #LPSC2016 #Mars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cole: Dip of wrinkle ridge on #mars that continues in Valles Marineris wall is only 12°. #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Geo_JackJack that was actually Sinan Özeren speaking, not Celâl Şengör]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nahm: Small scale graben are small scale. Highland terrain is in the highlands. I'm feeling in a rhyming mood. #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorApatite So, not worth running out between talks to grab a cup, right? #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sinan Özeren: long Coprates-like troughs formed when no drainage, closed Hebes Chasma like troughs without drainage. #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sinan Özeren: collapse driven by melting some ice underneath flour. Cohesion produces terraces #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Özeren: analogue experiments of #Mars dike intrusion using wheat flour because of relatively large cohesion. #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Özeren: As a mathematician, I have problems with the way elastic thickness is calculated. But talk is about tectonics, so... #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brustel maps dikes on walls of Coprates Chasma, #Mars. See different orientation E vs. W of Coprates Rise #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matt Weller uses estimates of #Mars mantle temperature to argue for episodic mobile lid in Northern hemisphere in Noachian #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thiriet: If S. hemisphere crust of #Mars is more enriched than N. (due to Borealis impact), elastic thickness can differ by 60 km #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andrews-Hanna argues No major impact on #Mars between Borealis/dichotomy and Hellas etc. impacts 400 Myr later. #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[O'Neill: impacts can induce short-lived subduction, increase core heat flux in Hadean. #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bethell: circumferential dike systems like around Lake Victoria analog to coronae (same scale, morphology, etc.) #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@planetpatman @amytoast Noticed that. "Venus found the fountain of Youth".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Treiman: Chlorapatite as the only ferroelectric rock-forming mineral to maybe 695±4K: good match for #Venus emissivity systematics #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When title doubles as conclusion slide: Venus radar-bright highlands: chloroapatite near the equator but not on Maxwell Montes #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lynn_carter8 higher resolution orbital radar images of #Venus (with polarization) would be great. Hear! Hear! #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lynn_carter8 describes detections of pyroclastic flows on #Venus using Radar polarimetry #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smrekar: Did Venus find the fountain of youth ? #LPSC2016 (age revised to 200-150 Ma from earlier 300-1000 Ma estimates)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gazel: Felsic rocks from Gale very different from Archean TTG. More likely fractional crystallization products —similar to Iceland #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kruijer: Isotopes of martian meteorites imply magma ocean 20-40 Ma after CAI formation and second differentiation event at 60 Ma #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Deschscoveries thermal evolution of #Charon would have 2 episodes of global ocean. Second ocean freezes 0.5 billion years ago. #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Deschdiscoveries thermal evolution of #Charon would have 2 episodes of global ocean. Second freezes 0.5 billion years ago. #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @jtuttlekeane for the wonderful sketch. #LPSC2016  https://t.co/6Qw35LI3gf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Umurhan: ice flow can reflect basal topography, May explain what's seen on #Pluto but should disappear long-term. #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jawin: irregular cones at Aristarchus would be largest pyroclastic cones on #Moon. Eruption later forms Schröter rille. #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glacier on #Pluto looks lots like Earth, but no freeze-thaw cycle ( =&gt; no cirques), possible floating water ice blocks #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Schenk asks to silence phones and screaming infants. #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#3Dglasses are coming out on the #Ceres #Pluto session at #LPSC2016 Get excited!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ruesch: Ahuna Mons morphology is very consistent with volcanic domes, although not silicic, of course. Also &lt;1Ga old. #LPSC2016 #Ceres]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Common aspects of cryovolcanic(?) flows on Ceres: blueish color, preferential direction, and small H/L #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Le Corvec take home message: presenting at a conference one week before moving out of the country is a bad idea #LPSC2016 #WisdomWednesday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goot love planetary volcanology at #LPSC2016 We went to Mars, Io, and Venus in less than an hour!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shootout to @planetpatman Live tweeting paper link from #LPSC2016 podium! https://t.co/FPkDZmVpC8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@planetpatman compares shape of magma ascent criteria with University of Miami logo. Only at #LPSC2016 . Big volcano helps ascent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@planetpatman at #LPSC2016 magma on Io have trouble getting to surface because of compression. vertical stress gradients to the rescue!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McKinnon + Spencer: Forward scattering shows smoother ice in center of proposed convection cells #Pluto  #LPSC2016 https://t.co/Rb8Dj8EWHq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Game changer #Venus would be younger Earth's oceans! #LPSC2016  https://t.co/HfYXyEMoe2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jtuttlekeane actually 3 talks for 1: now atmospheric sciences with Sputnik as cold trap, N2 deposition drives polar wander #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jtuttlekeane adds tectonics to constraints on #Pluto polar wander. 2 talks for price of 1! Good match if polar wander + loading #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jtuttlekeane takes on #Pluto polar wander. No sketching live, it seems. Great title "Pluto followed its heart" #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wright Mons looks amazing in 3D (better on projection screen). Green line is Kelsey's laser pointer #LPSC2016 https://t.co/aLFToYJiBW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nimmo: if no ocean, Sputnik mascon needs thin elastic crust, N2 thickness &gt; 35km. If ocean, Te=60-80 km and N2 &lt;5km thick. Better! #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nimmo: Sputnik is along tidal axis of #Pluto likely because positive mass anomaly. Analog to mascon with ocean instead of mantle #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More 3D glass in Kelsey Singer's talk. Cthulhu Burney. high-res non-3D image has nice nested craters (subsurface layers) #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Paul Schenk keeping the best pictures for the end? Like a concert encore? #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schenk: West Tombaugh regio consistent with large oblique impact. Based on scaling, ice would be no more than 6 km thick. #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Total relief on Pluto is 5km, Charon 18km. "not a surprise" dixit Paul Schenk. #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Craters in #Charon 's plains have pancake ejecta, same as Mars. #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Schenk: I'm just going to show pretty pictures, that's all. #Pluto #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Schenk speaking; time to put on 3D glasses #Pluto #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tanyaofmars @Geo_JackJack That comes from a German town, so I'd follow the germans' way. Can we exhume ancient greeks for Io/Charon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Geo_JackJack reminds of the old Eye-oh vs. hee-oh controversy (for Io). You could identify peoples academic affiliation with that one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Random thought:heads-on impact simulations with strength look awfully like a snitch (from Harry Potter) #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am really confused with the correct pronunciation of #Charon. heard from speakers at #LPSC2016 tcharon, karon, sharon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Davies transitions to impacts on #Pluto at #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone at #LPSC2016 is messing up with the light during talk on spectroscopy. Maybe they try to reproduce the blue slope of #Pluto tholins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dalle Ore: explains clustering of spectra with a classification of noses in the audience. Only at #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cook: #Pluto non-volatile composition is water with some small grain size and methanol. methanol anticorrelated with H2O and CH4. #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just realized that @NASANewHorizons logo is an nonagon. I guess, #pluto is still 9th planet, dwarf or not (forgetting Ceres). #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cruikshank: #Charon grey color made of carbonize tholin + H2O ice. Mordor macula still red because recently processed. #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cruikshank: #Pluto ice tholin (short organic molecules) made from electron radiolysis of ice mixture N2+CH4+CO at 15K. #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cruikshank: none of the ices on #Pluto and #Charon are colored, so red must be something else. #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bowling: Occator models imply target has rock rheology. If ice, rim would not be steep enough. #LPSC2016 #Ceres]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Toy_Meister @NASA_Dawn that's right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scully #Ceres 2 fracture sets, spacing correlates with crustal thickness. Also older than most craters #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buczkowski: #Ceres tectonics: grooves, pit crater chains, fractures and troughs: intrusion at craters; ejecta blanket compaction #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Otto: polygonal craters on #Ceres density may correlate with topography, more near regional linear features (and aligned) #LPSC2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fejokoo: hexagonal crater on # ceres #LPSC2016 https://t.co/KCdijuJILc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Otto: polygonal craters. Start by reminding us that Barringer (Meteor) crater is not so simple! #LPSC2016]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>