<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenFranken Thank you from NC, where my senators are determined to ignore constituent voice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Andy_Karl Bought my tickets today! See you in May!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ilanalevine I can't DM you. Sent message through your website. Will be happy to send magic peanut brittle in exchange for cookies. 😊]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorBurr Gorsuch loves fascism so much he founded a club for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorBurr You did not honor results of 2012 election. You taught us this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatMcCroryNC And you exemplified to seem rather than to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Karnythia @staceyNYCDC And that's a big maybe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FascismForeverClub 😡😬😳😟😒💩 https://t.co/PFoABqYe5I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshRadnor @WhitfordBradley As do I. Subscribed to both.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenGillibrand @AudraEqualityMc @womensmarch Marching w/ @RevDrBarber next week. Writing and calling reps daily. Recruiting friends. #RESIST]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rose_n_Disguise @pattonoswalt I think they do this to appease home voters knowing GOP had votes w/o them. Could have said no in committee.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GorsuchFacts He looks a lot like dt! Clones?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ilanalevine @TatesBakeShop Darn, I thought I beat the buzzer on this!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lawrence I watched Spotlight on Netflix. Different story, but same reminder that journalism needs to shine light on these monsters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I can get some more yarn. Should be doable. I think I promised you one before, but that was before I got sidetracked by my burglary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaganChild I'm going high. Rewatching Spotlight to appreciate journalists. Oh, and knitting another pussyhat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netflix and Knit. Another hat for Feb 11 march with @RevDrBarber. https://t.co/oAlnyPEsPk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jaketapper Does dt walk through the dressing room to ogle when they change clothes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeffzeleny @maggieNYT @JusticeGorsuch @JusticeHardiman Identical horrors. Good grief, this isn't Miss Universe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rosie Women's March w/5 friends in DC. Next week w @RevDrBarber in Raleigh. Science and tax day coming up. Retired… https://t.co/u8pox1eJPD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ilanalevine @TatesBakeShop @BroadwayCon A Program from Good Man Charlie Brown! She got her 'period'!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@activist360 Jared's no angel. No sympathy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThePatriot143 @TTHOOM Poor dt. Outside, looking in. Will never be loved nor respected by the people whose affection he craves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@womensmarch @JudiciaryDems Will he be able to 'say no' to the president?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lin_Manuel It plays in order on iPad. Loving it, btw. Thank You!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PAUL RYAN
700 ST. LAWRENCE AVE.
JANESVILLE, WI 53545

Looking for place to send concerns about ACA and Planned Parenthood? #alternateaddress]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls Get some sleep, bless your heart. You and your guys are looking kinda rough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@saletan @AngryNatlPark Her lack of sleep shows. Not sure how she could sleep anyway with that horror show of a boss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Is that Bannon's puppet hand up your back? https://t.co/ECdtTm2LEy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@educationgadfly Needs editing to specify "white Christian kids" &amp; add "freedom from accountability over equal oppo… https://t.co/4LqyCkJlQT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamstevenhale @WhitfordBradley You are a very frightened person.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Why do you not condemn your supporter in Canada who murdered six people?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Right, cause you can start that war all by your little self. Well, you and #PresidentBannon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobertT28783561 @RollingStone Scaredy cat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Solidar @RollingStone Scaredy cat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RenieriArts @RollingStone Scaredy cat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StevePasquale Thank you. Sharing here and on FB. Good to talk to actual person. #NoBanNoBannon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CatholicPrblm A fetus is not a baby 👶]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aubrey_huff I retired from 40 years teaching public school. Substitute now, leaving plenty time to 'march,protest,&amp;riot' 4 American values]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteveHofstetter @benjancewicz I retired from 40 years of teaching in public schools. Substitute now, leaving plent… https://t.co/8VtPKUCN7b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[18 Leadership Lessons And Quotes From Hidden Figures https://t.co/cp3dophuYa via @JosephLalonde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MMFlint @StephanieJBlock Comments line is closed. Told they only do directory assistance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I'm counting the days until a president is impeached for gross incompetence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Allen_Clifton All Lives Matter whitewashers strike again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And cussing. I can't stop using - and thinking - the f-word. Guess all that anger was just lurking, ready to break… https://t.co/CS6XkLhZHx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill Well, they will have to look even harder once environmental protections are rolled back. #StopPresidentBannon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Two Americans killed per year by outside extremists. More killed by toddlers with gun. Time to go after toddlers next.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Muslims have been killed in large numbers, with help from your puppet master Putin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC As one of the few standing against this nonsense, what can you do to help? And isn't it time to ta… https://t.co/PCH4GxE9Bd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffFlake @Medium What about the NSC coup?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adriennelwarren She says, "Let them eat cake."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mnla57 @graphikjunkie @IvankaTrump Nope. They don't have dt businesses. Indonesia much more dangerous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IvankaTrump Let them eat cake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JordanPeele Yes! I keep saying that. Nazi-in-chief.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardBSpencer @ACLU And when another white Nazi murders Americans again, the blood will be on you, the NRA and a… https://t.co/oMEZpfnUgw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LivingBlueinRed @Ms_DH No. It's Bannon. Bannon is pulling the strings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrumpHotels My favorite travel memory will be when they take a wrecking ball to your crappy hotel. Do any of you even get paid?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls @POTUS Traitor. History will note your disgrace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kayleighmcenany Facts indeed matter. Why were the only countries on the list ones without Trump businesses?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid How many horrified Americans can they take?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeithOlbermann Bannon is puppeteer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenateMajLdr @MarthaRaddatz @ThisWeekABC @POTUS Address the National Security Council overthrow and the ban. Both… https://t.co/Ok1rKcdVvE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenateMajLdr Address the ban and Natl Security Council debacle instead. All appts should wait. History has its eyes on you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepJeffDuncan Have you no sense of decency, sir, at long last? Have you left no sense of decency?Stop this madman.… https://t.co/AYwvw5BBPS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you no sense of decency, sir, at long last? Have you left no sense of decency?Stop this madman. History has its eyes on you.#NoBan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenateDems Vote NO on every nominee of this dictator. #Resist!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sia @ACLU Thank you for this. #RiseUp #NoBanNoWall #NoHateNoFear https://t.co/I0RXshqmrt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pronounced_ing @ACLU I'm already a member but donated again. Thanks for matching. https://t.co/Bp8qp9vHKA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't stop crying either. Who are we? https://t.co/xoi3lNMWqW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC Can you help Nazanin Zinouri, data scientist from Clemson not allowed back into US? This ban is tragic. Please help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls @POTUS Conveniently ignoring that no places on this list attacked the US, but countries where dt do… https://t.co/I8GRxwGnkk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AltHooverNPS Betting dt has not read 600 pages in his lifetime. Sad!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @nytimes Their failure was in overestimating thinking skills of American voters. I subscribe to… https://t.co/RDitD4Hm0A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TPM @andrea_kisiner Omg. When I agree with Joe Walsh, Dick Cheney, Lindsey Graham, &amp; John McCain in the same month… https://t.co/16m3uus6Fy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelenKennedy @JustSchmeltzer Not sure he's able to read anything beyond chyrons and bullet points.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @nytimes You keep using those words FAKE NEWS. I do not think it means what you think it means. FA… https://t.co/umJJjQ7EUT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaganChild Time to 👀 Caine Mutiny. dt is Captain Queeg. Next will call for 1a.m. mtg to find who ate the strawberr… https://t.co/8wlnDWdG8X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RoguePOTUSStaff Captain Queeg is melting down. Time for a one a.m. meeting to find out who ate the strawberries. T… https://t.co/kOTX3xOFl3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shredderfeeder Agreed. Usually he is just dt. In small letters, like his hands, his brain, his heart, and, I suppose, his dick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bobcesca_go @ElizabethClore We welcome refugees of all races and religions...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpeakerRyan @SenMajLeader @VP On Holocaust Remembrance Day, no less. POTUS&amp;Bannon would send Jesus back. Proud? I'… https://t.co/6X31RCFX4L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@khaleesi___b @BookofMormon @Bitmoji Me too. It's on my #resistance playlist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilipsNA Stop using jargon and explain this better. There are a lot of justifiably frightened people out here loo… https://t.co/jgwJjJsRkx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChristinePedi Thx for playing Pimpernel Into the Fire. You reminded me to add it to my #Resistance  playlist. @sxmOnBroadway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpeakerRyan You lie. No health care for Congress and their families until you actually have a plan in place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxNews @SpeakerRyan When we all die from poison air, water, no workplace protections, climate disaster, no health… https://t.co/2vITclLANo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpeakerRyan @POTUS Billions for useless wall, no help for devastation in Flint caused by horrid GOP policies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpeakerRyan Maybe you should get rid of your staffs first. They certainly aren't taking phone calls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThisWeekABC @SpeakerRyan Meaning you are ALL petty and deranged?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxNews @SpeakerRyan @realDonaldTrump Because establishing a fascist state is okay by you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cspan @SpeakerRyan @politico @PRyan @apalmerdc @JakeSherman Please explain how denying healthcare to millions is pro-life?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpeakerRyan Thousands of refugees died in WWII when we turned them away. Will you support resettling Syrian refuge… https://t.co/qiTYzC52jZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpeakerRyan Just let them die, right? https://t.co/GRCrDpdFKz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thisismylifeUSA Then good. You are rare in my experience. Are you for shutting down women's health providers like Planned Parenthood?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenJohnMcCain @POTUS Thank you for this, Senator. We are looking for reasonable people who understand the dangers… https://t.co/2qUhD3H96X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@March_for_Life @mindyfinn I wish your support for birth translated into support for life, for living, breathing human beings in need.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AltUSFWS @realDonaldTrump @SpeakerRyan @realDonaldTrump @SpeakerRyan @SenMajLeader Drain your swamp, not this one.… https://t.co/Bw5IpF5EHL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VP @POTUS @WhiteHouse Public education, informed citizenry are crucial for democracy. Is it too much to ask our le… https://t.co/stbySWNFwu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VP @March_for_Life Pro birth is not the same as pro life. I do not think you understand your Jesus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I'm sending you the bird to add to your swamp. https://t.co/XOryGCDuaf]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>