<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is it that I always get the Hanzo/Mercy team on 3v3 Elimination against an Ana/Hog/Widow...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know everybody with a social media account is upset about Trump rn but ABC just cancelled #GoodGame and that isn't good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonywonyrony you gotta keep it otherwise the female Krogan will die during the Tuchanka mission.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I JUST WANT TO BUY SKINS BLIZZARD PLEASE https://t.co/AFV8sSi9EL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally got the golden particle cannon awwwwwyeahhh https://t.co/WQiG5obyaL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One minor grievance with #TheLastJedi as a title is that it's going to be more confusing to refer to Return of the Jedi simply as 'Jedi'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TheLastJedi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am so excited for @masseffect Andromeda's multiplayer. Had such a blast playing ME3's one! https://t.co/SrC997Gmxy #MEAndromeda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today I am planning on fighting jet lag purely through countless games of Overwatch. Zarya I have missed you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can argue about Trump as much as you want but who can argue with a gif of an adorable kitten or pupper?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So like how long until the internet dials it down on Trump? Protests are good and all but everybody could use some cat/dog gifs and chill.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder if @billburr will read his child a fairytale the same way he does the ad reads on the @theMMPodcast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Air France really wasn't fucking around today. At this rate I'll be back in Perth in like four hours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lyon to Paris flight was meant to be 75min. Pilot comes on 45mins in "The shortcuts have been v successful, beginning our descent" WHAT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protesting is great, but destroying public/private property totally undoes whatever you're standing for. #ProtestTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least I had a lot of fun with Snapchat during the #Inauguration https://t.co/hP8SukuX14]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a productive holiday. Started playing on the bus to Val D'Isere and now we're leaving tomorrow. @GAMEVIL https://t.co/tcNbjz6wLG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeeksPrevail there is no way to do this by default with Windows. Does it need to be simultaneous?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful day of skiing in Val D'Isere today. Gonna miss it. Also bears. https://t.co/jIzWZaEtLs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good to hear about the commutation of #chelseamanning 's sentence. If only Edward Snowden could get a similar pardon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonywonyrony those same Normandy / Shuttle schematic ones were cool the first few times...100 loading screens later maybe not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had a lot of fun on the snow yesterday! https://t.co/bLItYko7KO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely gorgeous day for skiing in Val D'Isere! https://t.co/MqgggxLt6f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[View from our balcony in Val D'Isere is pretty cool. Looking forward to two weeks of skiing! https://t.co/kYS4YQrund]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me: We're in France, we should try out as much local food as possible. 
Also Me: Find a Nandos https://t.co/8ve6DgnUB9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have made it to Lyon! Man there is a lot of graffiti and abandoned buildings here...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About to see #MOANA ! https://t.co/TiP5BILSrS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I get the feeling #2017 will be a lot like my New Years party. Great fun until midnight, then politely waiting 2hrs for everyone to leave.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just threw out a bunch of old boxes in storage. Anyone going through my recylcing will think I had some great Christmas presents for 2011.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MEANWHILE IN LOVELY, SUNNY WESTERN AUSTRALIA #melbweather https://t.co/mtetR7HL6A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She is at one with the Force, and the Force is with her. #RIPCarrieFisher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Literally woke up at 3am in the morning, checked my phone and saw that #CarrieFisher had passed away. I'm completely speechless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course #2016 would try and kill #CarrieFisher at the end. I hope she pulls through.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It wouldn't be Christmas Eve without a wild panic to buy last minute presents before heading back to the farm...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vakarians @thegrandtour pretty sure Clarkson almost had a tear in his eye it was done so beautifully]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love my iPhone but iOS has become complete garbage. Marketers run Apple now, not Engineers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I turned on Apple Music and it deleted all the songs on my iPhone. Except 'Gold Digger' by Kanye. What the fuck… https://t.co/ho15aZBIj1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta hand it to Blizzard for having the strongest multimedia support for Overwatch this year. The shorts &amp; comics have been A++]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If anyone wants to become a property tycoon at age 20 turns out all you need is a 'seasoned investor' parent and $6… https://t.co/zCLofFFM0h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TyronePeiris absolutely, I'm going to be viewing it in theaters a few times alone just for the last act. Amazing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I haven't played #Overwatch since #Titanfall2 came out but the Winter Wonderland event is making me seriously consider jumping back in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hell, the entire third act of #RogueOne was phenomenal. Not without fault, but still such a strong start to the Star Wars anthology films.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The final scene of #RogueOne is one of the best in the entire Star Wars series. Nailed something we've all wanted to see for a long time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perfect thing to listen to for the end of the week at work. #RogueOne https://t.co/HoeRjWj7LH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Australia has decided to start blocking torrent websites? Well jokes on you I was going to buy #RogueOne on blu-ray anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am here to see at Star War. #RogueOne https://t.co/k9UxSfcYcc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Titanfall2 is the best FPS I've played for years (excluding Overwatch) Really hoping it's sales pick up for Christmas...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I haven't seen the track listing for the #RogueOne score but I'm hoping that @m_giacchino has been able to sneak in a pun somewhere...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd be lying if I said I was here for anything except hearing Star Wars theme. #wasositc https://t.co/86FBjtTUUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could @Showtime please renew @SHO_Shameless for season 8. I'm really getting nervous this season is the end... #shameless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saw 'Your Name' today, it left me absolutely speechless. One of the best anime films I have ever seen, cannot recommend it enough! #YourName]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Mass Effect Andromeda looks like The Witcher 3 in space!' IT'S INQUISITION IN SPACE NOT THE WITCHER GOD DAMMIT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ShamelessUS keeps gearing up like this will be the final season and I really hope that is not the case.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got my #RogueOne midnight screening tickets I am set to have a happy December now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rockatansky_ I used draw.io hooks up to Google Drive and stuff really well too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With the PC release of #watch_dogs_2 delay I'm gonna be a bit disappointed if there are any bad issues on launch. Ubisoft please do good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing beats a Friday night like having to quickly inhale a Nandos meal before rushing to a late screening of #FantasticBeasts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just started Season 4 of The West Wing and President Bartlet winning re-election is the most surreal experience given the past week IRL.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice to see that my plans to play #Dishonored2 this weekend have been derailed because its frame rate consistency is like a flipbook :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does anyone in #Titanfall2 play anything other than Attrition?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving it already. Can't wait until February for @LosCampesinos new album! https://t.co/quhqsMjVyq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peaceful protests and everything is totally fine to make yourself heard, but rioting because Hillary didn't win is not helping anyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can understand the pain and upset that a lot of people are going through right now but gang beating someone for voting for Trump is fucked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rockatansky_ I did comsci for two years with that exact experience, ended up switching because it wasn't fun or giving me much of a career]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rockatansky_ what are you studying?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Applying for the #MassEffectAndromeda multiplayer tech test and I'm just hoping that Bioware sees +400hrs on my ME3 Multiplayer...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to see #HacksawRidge ! https://t.co/NvObKlQRJ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I kinda want to play Skyrim Special Edition but I really struggled to get into Skyrim back in 2011 so I'm not sure if it'll be the same..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am having A LOT of fun with this costume #Trump2016 #halloween https://t.co/P6E3K1Pt20]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My #halloween costume worked out really well this year. #Trump2016 https://t.co/bB0jkQUtHv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GilbyRanger unlocked for me about 15hrs ago in Aus - worth the wait!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Without a doubt the best #Overwatch video I have ever made https://t.co/7cmvdlfJIS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why has the Facebook Messenger app suddenly become another Snapchat clone? I just want to message people!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ShinGodzilla was great. Very much a Hideaki Anno film, even to the point that several moments reused the intense Eva 3.0 into score.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billy_b0nes @Rockatansky_ @SombraIsGay fair it's also still over 5 months away and EA have to market BF1 and Titanfall 2 before ME:A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SombraIsGay @Rockatansky_ they're gonna release so much content on November 7 :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Overwatch https://t.co/nQieBLcGNE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the Dwarf in your party decides to take on 30+ Orcs at once. #dnd https://t.co/gb0VB0eBv5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least I can play competitive Overwatch whilst other people in the house stream HD Netflix and download stuff though!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever since upgrading to 100mbps NBN I can't help but feel my internet is slower. It's like having 10x10mbps streams rather than 1x100mbps.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just remembered Tom Clancy's The Division was a thing and I kinda feel bad that the game was such a non-event after the open beta.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight has been a good night of #DnD https://t.co/kuFIg85DQ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Update: I have cast Haste on the Land-Dolphin. It is fighting the Cerberus and a Chimera. #DnD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Update: I have summoned a Land Dolphin, it is getting eaten by a Cerberus. #DnD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What kind of DM doesn't let you use a 20+ Animal Handling check to summon a land-dolphin during combat in #DnD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just found out that a new season of #Shameless is coming out this month?! Two seasons in a year! Fantastic news has made my day even better!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got home from after making it to the Overwatch quarter-finals at #RFLan and the final episode of Breaking Bad is on ABC2 awww yeahhh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just beat a Team called 'No Hanzo' in a golden point tiebreaker in Overwatch at #RFLan with a perfect Zarya/Hanzo ult combo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the #RFLan games are on hold whilst we watch the Dogs defeat the Swans! #AFLGrandFinal https://t.co/UEjnhEThTl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arrived at #RFLan! Had to make sure our team name was an informative, yet friendly reminder to the other five team… https://t.co/JmPmhW4Xip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonywonyrony BUT THE SCREEN IS THE SAME DISTANCE TO YOUR EYES AT ALL POINTS HOW ARE YOU NOT IMPRESSED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlizzardCS losing tonnes of competitive elo due to group members getting dropped due to server errors is really frustrating :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just had one of the best Crucible games since picking up #RiseofIron again. https://t.co/0W8B70F5dT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the hell does an ENTIRE STATE lose power?! #SouthAustralia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Playing Destiny / Overwatch recently has really made me appreciate how much a little polish and continued dev presence can change a game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Upgraded my NBN plan to 100mbps and purchased an ASUS RT-AC87U Router all in time for the long weekend. Now for 72hrs of straight Overwatch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonywonyrony I mean who breaks up with someone in the middle of the CBD it's right in front of everyone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonywonyrony almost as awks as seeing a fight/breakup then one of them walking off whilst the other cries in the middle of the street]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now time for glorious Overwatch and Rise of Iron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My NBN is back up and running after someone apparently disconnected my optical wire at the node. Why the fuck would someone even do that.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>