<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes. Yes. A thousand times yes. https://t.co/YOITK5Io52]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bmairs @globeandmail Ha!  Thanks... so happy to be here!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On #TBThursday, I stumbled onto this today. Still think I made the right call. :)
https://t.co/Bg5jlOmvtU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Search &amp; rescue aircraft circling English Bay are simply doing training exercises. No need for alarm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is everything. https://t.co/VkXlzsTfpG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On @CKNW now with background on IIO recommending charges against RCMP connected to death of constable Sarah Beckett.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brett_shipp Ha!  Sadly no, however that is the estimated value of the home based on a group sale of neighbouring homes too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've watched row after row on Cambie and King Edward rezoned and condo-fied. No doubt same will happen along Broadw… https://t.co/t7r8Ey1wiR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agreed, part of land assembly but demonstrates shocking value of single family homes along transportation corridors. https://t.co/9do8AcU0Gs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lest you think Vancouver home prices are in the tank: https://t.co/1y5aqFiuBX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Showing excellent judgement. Thank you! https://t.co/5s0FGaqTbF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@sophielui @sbarnesglobal @MMadryga have all the fun and consume the best food/drinks on the @GlobalBC News at Noo… https://t.co/zJ0K2uAbfH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ha! At least @DOUBLEJGLOBALBC ran highlights on weekend! https://t.co/mhRyFjJtGe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've seen stranger things. 😄 https://t.co/Es9yCdfAga]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just when we need him most... Thank you, Jeff, and enjoy this new chapter in your life! https://t.co/3Q0ydxjdF0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This could be us, or America, or wherever. But it feels like what we need right now. Nice job TV2! https://t.co/XNIZVS0Vgf via @youtube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feed was really hitchy on https://t.co/zX1SgxfEJZ, but glad I caught it. Great effort and results in Wellington!! https://t.co/QTTIpdcqBd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevewrk Around,maybe. But perfected and mainstreamed like today, I'm not so sure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JAMESHAUGHTON1 Did that really bug you enough to leave a message? That's semi-ridiculous. #proudCanadian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ianstrachan42 Exactly! However he does have a point that MSM can sometimes do a better job of listening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And yet millions continue to buy into the hysterical fear of foreigners peddled by Donald Trump. America's undoing… https://t.co/fAIyNYYHXz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevewrk Thank you. And you too. But Breitbart (Steve Bannon) wrote the book on those tactics, opposing every Dem. policy for years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevewrk of MSM, no true journalist is interested in lying, only exposing repeated (intentional or not) attempts to mislead. Which we must.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is happening in American politics needs careful scrutiny and thoughtful analysis. Hysterics on both sides are… https://t.co/szaqpEnXOC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going to keep my eye on this kid. A brilliant young producer following his dream to TO. Good luck @JLewisGlobal… https://t.co/FHoeVbvprz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Big crash W-bound highway 1 through Surrey. Major delays at 176th Street and beyond.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevewrk Listening is never a bad thing. We should all remember that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @GlobalBC News at 5 will be commencing forthrightly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, thank goodness they're rare. https://t.co/n0DRQuFSCV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks Bhup! https://t.co/ClORsbOocV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mostly this is good but it's also sad that it's necessary. https://t.co/Sd6jXJBsZI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeordieMoski Rolly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Doomsday Clock is an arbitrary human invention. Just FYI. https://t.co/LN70t2aFhc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GraemeMcRanor So, basically, your status is awesome?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DROP EVERYTHING! @GlobalBC News at 5 starts now. 😃]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WendyWilliams Hey Wendy 'memba that time we hosted Good Day NY together? Give @TVAshleigh a hug from me! @michcoll too just for fun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On deck to join @drex and @steeletalks980 on @CKNW for the Daily Debrief next!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JillSlattery @MattGertz @mmfa Don't even go there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bobbyboucher604  Rob, get some help. Your misguided rage is toxic and totally destructive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To anyone with even a tenuous grip on reality, this is chilling if true. https://t.co/8UudCFSJRN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks Terry! https://t.co/vc7C45J0b2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sit down and read this. It's right on target. https://t.co/hEROYdcp0I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here it is in full: https://t.co/jlk5vZ5cHG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the greatest opening sequences ever. https://t.co/k09zjkB873]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steeletalks980 It's a left-over from when he spent most of his time there and had to check appearance before dashing back out on cam.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But it is a finite resource though, right? https://t.co/xpb057GzSG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cause @MMadryga uses it too. :) https://t.co/nka5qtz37j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoops. Here's the pic. https://t.co/ulU8Nc5bQX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can you spot the mirror? Just about to join @steeletalks980 and @drex on @CKNW for #DailyDebrief]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's better! https://t.co/xVy3FUz9yd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Update on #AmberAlert involving BC girl, mother located at motel in #Bellingham, no contact made so far. https://t.co/xi4eGOFTOM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[URGENT: Clarification, #AmberAlert for missing BC girl was issued in WA State, not BC because she has crossed the border.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[URGENT: #AmberAlert issued for BC girl believed to have crossed US border with her mother, concern for her safety.
https://t.co/T6cpFuBIBM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KimJohnston No media source is perfect, but I'll take NY Times over Daily Wire any day. I don't expect you to agree.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mervunger @GlobalBC Correct, but there is a reason that particular tradition exists and other politicians have respected it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This just makes me so angry. What is happening??? https://t.co/z0qduAYJlZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrating my distant Scottish heritage at a superb Robbie Burns dinner last night at the… https://t.co/zs0smBJsTX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go home #GreenBayPackers. That was embarrassing. #sadshanel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not sure what's worse, Trump's refusal to release tax returns, or WikiLeaks' open request for someone to leak t… https://t.co/jrD61YbAKU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the record, I hugged him today.  But I wasn't always ready to forgive... #SadShanel
https://t.co/mDqheiDW6H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks Matt! https://t.co/38pmPo6bSW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As always, context is essential. The @nytimes provides it here: https://t.co/KMHBJPFtU2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Major fire at auto recycler on Mitchell Island in #Richmond. @GlobalBC https://t.co/qc2aVxyxvZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By far, the best thing about the inauguration so far. https://t.co/t7oNHVKPlA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no comparison. https://t.co/dL1aq0turj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep, it is. https://t.co/bQ1Me4RdJV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KGordonGlobalBC Like one of these? #Retrocool https://t.co/irGY4h6gSb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An olive would be tougher. https://t.co/iMnO5uYruT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ooh, neither one is going to be happy about this. https://t.co/jxyT9jli8L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to sign all of those things. https://t.co/Xs0e6t8A8k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's your definition of crazy? https://t.co/PndICuAmLt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@moorehn That would be terrible. Very bad!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the whole point: https://t.co/rqqUrJQIyu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because they're my neighbors and doing great things for youth baseball, a huge shoutout to @vancanadians baseball c… https://t.co/zpdebO9Zw2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patkiernan Thanks Pat! Pleased we're not up against you... Ha!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AirCanada Any estimate on how long it will take to clear the backlog?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So proud to be nominated alongside pal @sophielui. @mgabrielGlobal @timtomperry deserve credit too! @GlobalBC https://t.co/caxxQW4LrC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gunnarolla yes, don't cross them. Good luck!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@casualcactii @nytimes @GlobeBC Globe BC is Globe and Mail, not Global BC. That's why.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @GlobalDurant I'm with a bunch of sunburned 12s watching the seahawks in #puertovallarta… https://t.co/R1QizZep59]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That should go without saying. https://t.co/Xw6JMmg7IE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not unless it has a removable top and a snowplow option. #earlybroncorules https://t.co/nJ7aBjOovV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Submission accepted. https://t.co/RJ9E5ktmka]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any more of this bs @mashable and I'm going to mute you. https://t.co/B9FGO6u978]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CdnGrl2 I may do that. But my opinion of Orcas in captivity is already fully formed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JH_smallplanet Please send a list of the movies you've seen so I can judge your "enlightenment".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe Twitter with its 140 character limit is not the best place to debate, discuss or defend your plan. Just sayin… https://t.co/S9YkrxKQAM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And fake. https://t.co/T5l6QVWTmC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're goin' to overtime! https://t.co/d0MKohFpQ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes an entire community to care for the most vulnerable! https://t.co/4z8PM0n0Ru]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Funny/Serious. https://t.co/89h3MjHrkd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lining up 50 deep in a nice orderly fashion at @CanadianTire on Grandview to buy ice melter. https://t.co/my5QCjpL66]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty. Impressive.  But there is a lot more to establishing a car company than producing a super-slick promotional… https://t.co/DhfgazY20D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proof hard work pays off. Thanks for the gym motivation and good luck @Bighill44 ! #savage https://t.co/di4gyscosE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, so much for redeeming our view of humanity. https://t.co/89Nqumh6QZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No but they are going for $10 on Craigslist. *
*this is a joke. https://t.co/1oyJqO1Y0O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlairKing_ca I'm of fan of your analyses by the way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlairKing_ca Also, home-based charging occurs mostly overnight, when overall demand is weakest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlairKing_ca If that power is largely hydro-generated, is that not "cleaner" than burning 40x80L tanks of gas/year? Data please!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen to the pros in Prince George. Thanks Wendy! #SaltCrisis https://t.co/dfKuGnM4bJ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>