<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[hot take if u prefer smooth peanut butter over crunchy you're actually fuckt in the dome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[what are all you crows eating out of those rain gutters up there did u find a lil buggy or what]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wonder how much malware ive accumulated by logging into gmail via windows xp computers at print shops]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[me, after one toke:
ðŸŽ¶ i'm one toke over the line, sweet Jesus! ðŸŽ¶]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[listening to the grateful dead for the first time ever with my bff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[holy fuck https://t.co/ag7Vc6fb9O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[me in 2014: i'm just going to write about going to parties with my friends
me in 2017: https://t.co/AExN3bVhad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[just texted my friend "i hope" while stoned and realized that i can imagine/relate to "hope" much more strongly as a verb than as a noun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i really liked my life; it was starting to seem like it was right on the brink of getting really amazing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i hope i live to one day write a good novel about the experiences of me and my friends and family during World War Three]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this thread has destroyed my every hope https://t.co/BazSGtxDPN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[can't remember ever feeling this proud of lawyers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yokoono thats cool, you must have a lot of money ðŸ™‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WordsandGuitar grow it out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[shaving my face is the only thing that keeps me from total hideousness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[finding out last year that my ex had started using #Uber in toronto was a helpful event in the narrative of my getting over her]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@illiterich self-exceptionalism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[major shout out to every muslim person out there, i love you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[aiming to become someone who more frequently gives people books as spontaneous gifts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@unknownmobility @pigo_the_swine i unfollowed every torontonian 'cept Pigo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wish my favourite rappers would stop repping the words "savage" and "Uber" but it's not my place]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[constantly gaslighting and doxxing myself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[most of my favourite memes are about being too stoned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hey @WordsandGuitar, @CarleighBaker just lead me and others in a reading of your sweet essay over here at UBC ðŸ˜›ðŸ¤“ https://t.co/RABlj4m3PL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[me in 2014: racism is subtle and systematic, it lives in our unconscious
me in 2017: literally every second person i click on is a neo-nazi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[me recommending a film to my parents: "dad will like it because the camera barely ever moves"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the electoral college elected Dr. Robotnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[brb gotta do some meaningless homework for my meaningless MFA as society literally descends into chaos all around me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[cant believe all those millennials checked into north dakota on facebook for nothing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NapEyes i know we are all hip nihilist jokers but tbh tv does very little for me and nap eyes is god]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kowal14820 @NathanDamigo that's pretty cool that you're living in the 1700's! was it hard to get Twitter?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump great photoshop on this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when a dj throws one really painful nasal post-punky song into an otherwise smooth/bangin mix is it supposed to be an avant garde gesture?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@isis_whitehead @NathanDamigo i just mean, if he's making land claims based on seniority, the word "first" is in First Nations for a reason]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NathanDamigo you are an alien who invaded the country from Europe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[how do these dudes' tiny little toques stay on their little bald heads?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@unknownmobility cool hat man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ok finally my favourite video has been created https://t.co/JgeD7YubUW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i wish i didn't 100% identify with both my astro sign and my myers-briggs... really fucks with my ruthless mocking nihilism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[how did i finesse all of this shit from ragged point road]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when u text your latest Meitu to the whole squad but no one responds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wow so blessed to be released from quarantine and slurping soup elbow to elbow with the canadian people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@illiterich dudeee take some probiotics it helped me so much]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[unpopular opinion: the world is extremely complicated and no one is perfect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[freaks and geeks has the best character development/revelation of any tv show i've ever watched (which i guess isn't a big claim)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i have a love/hate relationship with my phone but im so glad 'twas there to text my roommates to prepare food and bringeth to mine feverbed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@croonjuice that would be cool i would find that very manly of him!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my british roommate is stomping as hard as he can on my ceiling and screaming full volume as he watches "football"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[beginning to sense that this might be the type of flu that wouldve caused me to expire without modern medicine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i wish i could peel my white skin off and pour gasoline on it and burn it in the street]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i want people to listen to each other]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i want everyone to love each other radically]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my burrito's bad and budgie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i'm not watching; has anyone shot at him yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i recommend twitter as a great website for those who want to feel bad about themselves and the world]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[curtis, your book is so fucking good. it's crazy. https://t.co/froF5pn4EW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ahhh can everyone please stop saying we live in a "post-truth world"???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@generosonido i don't wish people would write more about 19th century english gentry frolicking around their summer cottages]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@generosonido i meant i wish people would write more intricate sentences that let themselves "tell" instead of "show"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@generosonido i'm mostly just comparing their sentence structures]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@generosonido no those are not the options lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marquisdecod that tilework in the background doesnt look like the good old wholesome american tilework i remember from my youth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wish people wrote a lot less like hemingway and a lot more like henry james]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elainecorden never write at home]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elainecorden write on paper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[now i'm no rocket scientist but i believe you mean "no two days are alike" on the space station! https://t.co/FaVw57aUaj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elainecorden physically turn your phone off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[realized that the shorter you are, the larger an area of coverage a given umbrella will provide you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[allow me to be the first to admit that i don't really know how to use "purport"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[never felt nick cave was as talented as he was purported to be]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i'm really glad we at least have one studiomate who's not human]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@veeeebeeebb whatever you makes you feel like the most badass who-gives-a-fuck version of yrself ðŸ¤™ðŸ¼ðŸ¤´ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[its been a long time since ive felt the quality of excitement that i now feel, as i think about renting a party limo for my birthday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[people should stop making films that aren't documentaries]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[realized after saying writing was "the only thing i care about" for the fourth time in &lt;24 hours that i should prob find a few other things]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[at first i loved that they got rid of the real gun emoji; now i hate it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[every time someone asks me to describe what another person "is like" i'm at a loss for effective words; i think that's why i write fiction]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the subtext of every tweet i write is "think of me at this moment"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[entertained, for approx. five seconds, the thought of titling my thesis novel "FML"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nice_laydee so empathetic and yet so cutting simultaneously â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@veeeebeeebb sounds great]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[crazy when you realize that having no single BFF's means having no one to dance with anymore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[american: (talks about horrific hate crimes she's witnessed post-Trump)
me: (laughs)
old friend: "he laughs when he's nervous"
ðŸ˜“ðŸ˜“ðŸ˜“]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i sure hope my novel isn't 100% aesthetics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[proud of the bottom half of my design for this invoice i just sent https://t.co/YvYGGD8dpf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[a thing i ordered on the internet came with a sticker that said "Compliant for Formaldehyde Phase 2"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[just scrolled twitter for ~20 minutes without recognizing what even a single tweet was referencing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[people hating on vancouver haven't spent enough time in any of canada's other cities imho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[omg just woke up from a dream about an instagram story i was trying to post ðŸ˜¨]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my roommate hannah just tried to convince me to exchange my BLOOD for ice cream]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[why am i not drawing cartoons for the new yorker look at this fucking shit https://t.co/D2ka29IIkS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ddoorroo shit tastes like zip-loc of water]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alextrnka literally me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marquisdecod hi what is your favourite of the songs you've written?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WordsandGuitar maybe i will try to do it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[walked by UBC Counselling Services listening to Adam's Song]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[must be weird to be a hip musician and realize that your audience is 21 year olds and that that never changes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nietzsche's ego is forty times the size of Kanye's]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marquisdecod you find out pretty early in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[just killed one of my main characters because i am God]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>