<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Hi0gJ9acRO YES it is #Neoliberalism #Liberalism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#muslimban could be just the tip of the iceberg. Progressives need a proper strategy to ensure that #trump doesn't get 8 years #resisttrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- https://t.co/aXDwOH6i7a via @FT The punitive #Greece Bailout terms are undermining the legitimacy of the European Project #Eu #ECB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lamhfada Sanders seems to be effective at reaching out to the population but his party won't listen to him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lamhfada sad but true, it seems every centre left party from Corbyns Labour to US Dems have it wrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #Trump presidency is turning out the as absurd as we all feared If progressives don't get their act together we will face 8 years of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time for business leaders to wake up - https://t.co/EMVeLjmVjc via @FT #Trump #trumpnomics #voodoo #globaltrade]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/mDrn9HS7he via @FT the fact that it took #Trump to pull the plug on #TPP proves that the Democrats need to seriously reflect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/dZg18laJ9H #MMT #rethinkingeconomics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- https://t.co/mW8WRPoleR an minor nod to state intervention suggests the Tories are shunnng legacy of #thatcher #rethinkingeconomics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is officially making an economic promise that will be nearly impossible to keep - Read at Business Insider: https://t.co/aNedsY0pgH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Henshaw and Ringrose have the potential to be a world beating centre combination #leivcastre #Erchampionscup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is now a duty to rebuild the progressive movement, it must reach out to the disillusioned not preach to the converted. #ResistTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Schauble is wrong to tout a wage restraint model that works uniquely for #Germany  as the cure to #europes' economic problems #Davos #wef17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm no fan of #trump but progressives who are skipping his inauguration better be also thinking of a strategy to win back voters lost to him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mays' speech proves that the third way insurgency in Centre Left parties is now being out-lefted by the mainstream right #wef17 @PES_PSE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be fair to May, her speech is a far cry from Thatcher "there is no such thing as Society" It's time for EU Centre Left to cop on #wef17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@activedan If #TTIP passed this type of thing would become a regular occurance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teresa May laments how people have moved away from "mainstream" Politics, but she's not willing to take responsibility for it. #wef17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/IbZvvGZCpx should be nailed to the door of the #bundesbank and the #ECB #rethinkingeconomics @EvonomicsMag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Squeezed and Angry: How to Fix the Middle-Class Crisis https://t.co/UPo2kcRm3v via @wef #globaleconomy #wef17 #davos2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackAEustace there ain't no capitalism like State Capitalism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm calling for the Fair Deal Scheme to be allowed for #homecare @SimonHarrisTD @HMcEntee https://t.co/dBuT8qKDaE via @UpliftIRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't agree with Saramucci but he shows how mainstream progressives have ceded decline of Working Class to the right #wef17 #davos2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/6xYN7xD3W0 @LabourParty_NI this is how @labour have betrayed you despite motions passed at Conference 2015]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't help but think that Chinese Presidents' opening at Davos is the #wef17  two fingers to @realDonaldTrump #davos2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope National Govs and EU listen to WEF Chair on fixing deficiencies in the system and restoring the Social Contract #wef17 #davos2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does Trump’s rise mark the end of Davos Man’s influence? - https://t.co/tEhoT3WmUG via @FT #davos2017 #wef17 #globalisation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edbrophy @glennthefitz @thejournal_ie you  were on about perception so I posted the breach of paycap you benefited from personally]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glennthefitz @edbrophy perception you say? Posted without comment https://t.co/B9ecIzddnY we're all in this together etc...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/yvhaXaAyE2 Well done to @NERI_research for exposing what we all suspected, market solutions have caused the Housing crisis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This week is #Glastonbury for those of use who love #economics #davos2017 #wef17 #Davos #WEFLIVE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/B6NHfq3XZa its time his entire #NeoLiberal ideology which corrupted #economics was laid to rest. #rethinkingeconomics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeorgiaMaq Hi, is there a possibility of Camp Cope playing in Ireland in the future?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/HBPwPrwnCe  #macroeconomics #samuelson #Keynesianeconomics #rethinkingeconomics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At #apollohouse to support #HomeSweetHome https://t.co/XBysWIrIx0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/jLS94hNeyk #secularstagnation #rethinkingeconomics #globaleconomy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shane_RossTD and by do something about #Dublinbus I mean increase the frequency of service not the slash and burn model you seem to favour.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shane_RossTD The 75 bus which serves your consitiuency is so packed people are standing on the stairs, when will your dept do something?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/PuYwcOR8Xj Sanders is showing true spirit and leadership where the Democrats have failed #StillSanders #ResistTrump #DnC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/WoRk3M1ypz #inequality #fairwages]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/6wx0J9q1ys #inequality #gobaleconomy #rethinkingeconomics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/MbAZ2YIDO4 #Dnc if the #Democrats are serious about returning to power and resisiting #Trump they should pick #Ellison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/4tWNe6WMq4 60% of US Household Wealth is inherited @EvonomicsMag #economics #rethinkingeconomics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Tkd0LoBKYZ great #economics books for #2017.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/WkXZHUiJwX  No trade off for suppressing wages, Employer intransigence must stop #irishecononomy #secularstagnation #fairwages]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/eVSgUfmUFj Food for thought on the current rental crisis #irishpropertymarket #rentersarise #irisheconomy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/QoTeoIkYnk essential points about misusing the word "recovery" in #economic debate. #Macroeconomics #globaleconomy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HomeSweetHome embodies the true spirit of Democracy and Civic Duty, one of the best Grassroots campaigns launched in a long time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your attitude towards @homesweethome says a lot about your empathy with vulnerable people.  Which is why many people are disappointing me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Since when is 12.5% too high of a tax for a company with a $60 billion gross profit Irish Government should be ashamed #AppleTax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing try from Adam Byrne this is a classic European tie #LeinsterRugby #Leinstervnorthampton #ERCC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HomeSweetHome occupation going strong https://t.co/RKKHUxF7e9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delighted to be at the Alicia Brady commemoration to see the Childcare Workers receive a well deserved reward #SIPTU @SIPTU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/C11WmsicM7 #Economics #rethinkingeconomics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who stand with Landlords against rent controls, stand against renters, and vulnerable people with housing needs. #rentersarise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/pE28L9Yh2j #trump (ed up) #trckleldown is voodoo and sadly #USA citizens will learn the hard way #USeconomy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/9y79KYSoZ8 what's true for #Australia is also true for #Ireland and #Europe #Austerity #Globaleconomy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/KlvZaUMWnt can The need for a new kind of #Economy is glaringly obvious in the face of #automation #paulmason]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Y1LAsX8p9L #economics #workerproductivity #Fightfor15]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/hrq2c6ATkG #globaltrade #bankunderground #economicforcasting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pauldclynam star wars first released, a great year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/ynmPHG000k #evonomics #rethinkingeconomics #entreprenurialstate #publicvprivate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keynesian economics: is it time for the theory to rise from the dead?

https://t.co/c8isMbaRSQ #keyensianism #globaleconomy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/bFgcu8z5B3 good to see @TheEconomist questioning conventional thinking in #Economics #rethinkingeconomics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/LAP0iLKIEX his the nail on the head I hope the @TaxInstituteIrl take note. We can have tax cuts or a fair society not both.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/lG69bKAOtV @EvonomicsMag #rethinkingeconomics #economics #neoliberalism #econ101]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Al lethal combination of low spending and USC cuts have put our public services and infrastructure at breaking point https://t.co/72d5RvqnuD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/QaB1f7bbi8 via @fusion #mentalhealth #PTSD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/cul6Kz50u5 Austerity has killed investment and demand in the #Eurozone,  #globaleconomy. Case for new direction overwhelming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Ireland while #Virginmedia is down @virginmedia https://t.co/lZODKJPymP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/3QEN5sww7F  #neoliberalism is leading to deficit fetishism and holding back #Economic and social progess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/3dOzOb6IiF relevant as ever to #Ireland too, the #Economy needs to be rebalanced from profits to wages and from market to state]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@labour @BrendanHowlin why did you support the Fiscal Treaty in the first place knowing what the rules implied for spending and investment?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/9oReTXYs3p even #theeconomist admits Ireland had low taxes. @taxinstituteirl should stop claiming otherwise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dublinbusnews appreciate that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/pNWJO7oB8W #evonomics #globaleconomy #neweconomicthinking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davemurf83 @KevinHigginsIrl the struggle is real]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davemurf83 @KevinHigginsIrl fair enough thanks for clarifying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darkagesreturn I said nothing about anyones weight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is a good day for #Europe the people of #Austria have done us all a service in halting the March of the far right #Austrianelection]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DubMetro Great initiative, fully support.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AAA_IRE there is not a Hope that the #AAA would support #Sanders if they were American with his "reformist" this is a charade.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free Water announced the same day as Bertie's return, a coincidence?#makeirelandceltictigeragain #IrishWater #Right2Water]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaceyDermot @PaidiCole present company excluded in every way Dermot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaidiCole by all means #copyleft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaidiCole I still think you're a decent bloke with good politics differences aside]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaidiCole secondly I was subject to subversion, vilification and petty insults when I tried to raise important discussions at board level.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaidiCole what was I supposed to do after getting Co opted not re run for my seat?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conisme @PaidiCole @activedan I'm the last person who needs to explain myself given my years of patience and service, but enough is enough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conisme @PaidiCole @activedan I ran as a candidate during its worst time and remained until after the GE, I earned the right to bow out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaidiCole @activedan @labour in plain English mate, what does that mean?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaidiCole don't run away from the purple light comrade we are ready to pull you in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@activedan he's no Justin Welby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HazelJN #BrexitBritain becoming a bit of mad house?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Francois Fillion will be the candidate the left has to grin and bear to keep Le Pen out. @partisocialiste are to blame #frenchelections]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rest in peace #Fidel Long live the revolution. #Cuba

https://t.co/3h3phzAxsb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/0s9fw3v3ig #economics #rethinkingeconomis @EvonomicsMag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/8akNjdVfe8 great interview with @1GaryGannon sets out why #Irishpolitics needs a movement like the @SocDems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The number of homeless people is beyond a tragedy, it is a National disgrace .Fine Gael's anti Public Housing agenda to blame. #dublin]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>