<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarinkaNYC  It is flooding our news over here (Sydney). The world has gone mad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srpeatling I had to google 'corflutes'. Forgive me, I'm a kid's writer now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@truongthomas Fine. You created them, pay for them, raise them. Take the chocolate, buy some more tomorrow. Or don't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What an astonishing story, what a gutsy guy - how white supremacist Derek Black grew up and left the fold. https://t.co/xIbgSjgz5L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@James_Jeffrey Awwww these are beautiful, and cheering me when all the news around is truly wretched.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexadsett Absolutely not. The little notes on the fridge with stray apostrophes will drive you nuts, otherwise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@msmisrule Like you, I have a certain grudging admiration for the Joyce. At least he says what he means!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@msmisrule No - then he'd have to characterise himself as a dullard without ideas, and he certainly wouldn't do that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@msmisrule They don't enjoy a debate. They just vote!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@msmisrule I take your point, but think he was saying most people want strong borders and those not in the inner city r too polite to argue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@msmisrule With all due respect, I don't think that's what Joyce was saying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For me, the only bright spot in that election was finding @ananavarro. At least the world gets 4 more years of this: https://t.co/YPNFDLyfpL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pryorlisa I feel sick he won't even be able to get the detention centre deal done now, and it was a breakthrough. What will you write?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pryorlisa At this point, I just want to put my head in my hands and weep. This is all really, really bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hornery I feel it's worse than that. I worry what it means for the freedom of the press under his presidency.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@murpharoo Kellyanne has taken back the twitter account]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@James_Jeffrey I laughed, but I'm actually terrified.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@James_Jeffrey He's already tweeting against the right to protest, and the media? His presidential pose lasted what? 30 hours or something?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pryorlisa I could go on, but it's all been said. I only hope it doesn't happen here and we can hold to the dull and sensible centre.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pryorlisa People are trying to normalise this -  too scary otherwise. He rants, makes threats, doesn't respect rule of law. Facism 101]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamHarrisOrg Thanks, this is riveting, but also terrifying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srpeatling Taken with salt. How would he know, or anyone truly know? It's speculation with a loose cannon like DT.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justinjmoses I know, meant, of course mood grim in Bk and manhattan. bet they're celebrating in the rustbelt! I think that's a good impulse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justinjmoses Yeah it's bk. No one in bk wants this. Outside bk it's lots for Trump. Does it make you want to come back to Aus?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justinjmoses How is it there? I see a protest on 6th ave, and the appointments in this crazy government beginning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pintadoguy not known yet. Struggling here. Feel the things we take for granted - rights of women, minorities, free press - under threat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WazMan01 I mean, wtf? I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pintadoguy I am having a very, very bad day. Wha? How? WTF???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmilyGale You are a hard, hard taskmaster]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmilyGale I like your trophy and award system. I might adopt it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNN starts the election marathon, I wonder: do the commentators wear adult diapers? If I had to talk for hours sans break, I'd want backup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katedetweiler we're half a world away but watching with bated breath! Tomorrow our daytime we bite our nails as the returns roll in. Oyyyy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exactly! Who is going to want to ride this again? https://t.co/Vb4tbStsQn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srpeatling @ALeighMP @ellinghausen He obviously sprinted in after training. Go Andrew!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raspratt brilliant - wish I'd witnessed that, and the skulk back with the wrong chicken.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rglover702 @BernardSalt Seconded ... although why 'smashed'? Does the extra 's' allow cafes charge to $5 more vs 'mashed' avo?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raspratt I know I'm asking for it ... but wha -? Now you have to tell the damn story.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srpeatling Why is he looming behind her so often when she speaks? It's creepy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JacquelineHarve I can imagine she was. And just so normal. No bullshit, no apologies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JacquelineHarve I am so ridiculously damn sad about RW. Didn't know her personally but adored her on TV, and she was always in our local.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katedetweiler ITA. That red is terrific.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am so very happy that Clinton is wiping the floor with Trump. So very, very pleased.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WazMan01 Way to talk yourself down, Brit! :) Come on, big yourself up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full text of Lionel Shriver's excellent Brisbane Writers Festival speech she's getting flak for: https://t.co/1RLxWfaSkV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@srpeatling my fave frock of the night. Bishop's was more glam but also more safe. This was terrific.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Milingimbi Sustainability project is worth a look. Their Art Centre needs funds - Project https://t.co/MfXCpF26F3 via @gofundme]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suzanne_leal Running well, badly, who cares? You're a writer, not a runner. And @DavidDyerAuthor is indeed one of the loveliest!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suzanne_leal a) I am so impressed you are up at the hour the sun suggests b) I am so impressed you are up at that hour AND running!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@altait No you're just gorgeous. Take that compliment. TAKE IT!! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awww, heart officially warmed. https://t.co/mQQuLEfscx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vile night in Bondi, but worth venturing out for Nib awards talk with @obmmusic @ErikOJensen and @jemmabirrell https://t.co/ZUfyxC1GX5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rglover702 @MichaelPascoe01 Thanks! Just the bracing kick I needed after Brexit-bingeing and election-stat staring.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent Gladwell podcast Revisionist History, Ep 1 linking former PM Julia with painter Elizabeth Thompson https://t.co/2jPejvB8zQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Razor-sharp piece about Farage at the EU from Marina Hyde - https://t.co/a27uoHkf8M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pryorlisa excellent take home I say, esp if it tastes better (which I bet it does). I find those healthy branded things usually taste bad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pryorlisa I hear you. Is it the carrot in the title that is irritating you? feels muffinlike. Although muffins also cake. All cake. So sad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pryorlisa but .... it is cake. Sort of to be expected with cake, isn't it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katedetweiler I need this. I can always manage 400 minimum but never break 2000. You are amazing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katedetweiler 6000 words??? How is that possible??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JacquelineHarve Looking/not-looking forward to reading that one and sobbing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JacquelineHarve too easy to adapt, yr story was a delight. Got teary at my desk when I adapted Chap 16 where Hephz takes off her veil!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suewhiting4 @JacquelineHarve Hey I was honoured to be asked to write the first episode! It's going to be terrific!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WazMan01 Oh sorry to hear it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pintadoguy you will totally rock it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pintadoguy Not gauche, love it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #Ghostbusters trailer looks terrific - why all the hate? https://t.co/FwS9dNCwvR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anthony_mcgowan and lovely pronunciation- 'zs' in Hungarian is 'g' sound from 'genre'. Child of Hungarian, my fave doll was zsuzsi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks Five Paddington for the wrap dress - you got it just right! I feel like a 70s babe. https://t.co/bDhodf20K0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The people who turn up at Sunday soccer ... @TurnbullMalcolm #abcdeFC https://t.co/x7ui21xxW6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WeathermanABC sorry to hear it, good luck with such a difficult situation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm slapdash with my gin &amp; tonics, and I appreciate this couple's thoroughness. Would love to drink at their house https://t.co/xEocbJWPtQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Regardless of whether you care about golf, this Tiger Woods feature is a must-read - spans identity, grief, failure. https://t.co/ueZz6UjD2u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suewhiting4 Congrats! Wonderful news!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terrific New Yorker article about schizophrenia by Pulitzer-winner Siddhartha Mukherjee https://t.co/L02sL1ABje]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katedetweiler I KNOW, RIGHT? There can never be enough RZ as Jones in the world for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pryorlisa but now I reread my response, it's also ambiguous, can see why you weren't sure. Tone dammit. I did buy the tee though, sriously]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pryorlisa yes, yes I got that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pryorlisa clutch your pearls - bought the 'how ya going?' one with koala for myself, in a size 14. I need the koala/Lolita glasses next]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WritersCentreAU Really really good. Please that this exists and want to spread the word!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just perusing the https://t.co/lozk6zbCHr site for readers, teachers and writers of Australia YA - terrific resource. #LoveOzYA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gripped by Niki Savva's #RoadtoRuin. Seems hastily written and the prose is sloppy, but still a page-turner. She's the Australian Suetonius.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glad this is happening... https://t.co/PeCmba2tKt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[:O When you ring Medicare and hold for 34 minutes, then accidentally press the END CALL button instead of switching out from speakerphone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My #StellaSpark? Kate Jennings' Moral Hazard - whole thing is startlingly good, but never read an opening that grabbed me more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WilkinsonCarole And Sydney! The train is $17 one way!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndieHensley thank you! Ate way too much again but had a blast!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ozbluey Didn't realise you were a fellow knitter! This jumper is stunning. Must talk yarn one day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndieHensley True it's hard when it's just you and kids. I tend to leave them to it and grab a book, sit beside them while they lego]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Darning, drinking tea as I disappear into Carlin's amazing @HardcoreHistory podcast. Stacks of books with time to read. LOVE early Jan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndieHensley Here now - you about? Dinner? Daytime?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndieHensley You both look exceptionally cool!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrigidWD when Cameron was in Egypt's land .... Let my Cameron go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WilkinsonCarole I'm so sorry. I don't know you, but that picture of your dad touched me. Handsome dude.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@frescolicense Sure, most welcome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ozbluey I am shattered for the poor owner...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ozbluey hey bluey, reckon that car is ruined?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Out our front door at Paddo. Sigh. #sydneystorm https://t.co/Iro1ZbbUr1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transparent Season 2 - thoughtful, heartbreaking, shimmering. Best TV show I've seen.  https://t.co/vvhCqdTCch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love amazing writing? Interested in terrorism in the Philippines? Must read @MattThompson777's Don't Go To Jolo https://t.co/6lnhIFa8u7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WazMan01 woooot! Congrats! Now I need to cosmically influence the tv producers I want to work with]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>