<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyanRMUFC 3 nil win with 10 men. Decent day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Up the reds https://t.co/1Ph0QCd2Sh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gary302 away to Arsenal in 2009 on the breakaway was a memorable one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bealymufc any two together if possible man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bealymufc ah cheers man. Thanks alot.   Really appreciate it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bealymufc sorry to annoy you pal.  Heading over to Manchester in February.  You wouldn't know anyone with a pair for Watford? Cheers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pat Dolan tipped Reading to beat Utd today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bealymufc club was too big for him.  He bottled it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schneiderlin will go down as one of the worst signings in Utd's history]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forza shelbourne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shelsfc stick a half decent sponsor and it's ready]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@doyneamite no complaints from me so far.  Lovely top]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's a decent Shels top.  Don't mind no sponsor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@doyneamite looks like it's already to purchase. No sponsor it is so]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@doyneamite looks like a training top. Any word of a sponsor?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Callum Best turns up on a z lister show for the 142nd time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy new year cunts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Danny_McMoomins happy new year bud.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maclaithimh @RTEOne @rte jools Holland on BBC not too bad bud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fucking scenes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Credit to @WeahsCousin tonight.  Great laugh with a few tins.  Roll on next year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WeahsCousin big Phil all the way.  Using two of his kids in one "didn't happen"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WeahsCousin @beth_drakey @edebellauthor ha no pal never finish it.  I need this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WeahsCousin @beth_drakey @edebellauthor you have created a monster with this didn't happen.  Great scenes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So glad I'm not on Facebook.  Say it's riddled with profile pics of George Michael with the French flag in the background]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems alot of people on here knew George Michael personally.  May he rest in peace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DjAzzIreland sound buddy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DjAzzIreland few beers later]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Christmas folks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seidodge merry Christmas dude]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Conjob123 happy Christmas bud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warwick Davis, Katie Price and Christopher Biggins on Catchphrase, sounds like the start of a joke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Realbarneycarey ha know what you mean.  My missus ain't here so thought I'd treat myself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_weedimples ah yeah I know.  Just leave your bags in ballyfermot and hit the town ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_weedimples ballyfermot ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚. Not the best place to go for your first time in Dublin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_weedimples no way.  Where you staying? Hit temple bar and you're sorted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_weedimples the place to be]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol at Ian Holloway.  Hope he never wins a match again the cunt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a pub full of bohs fans. Hope the roof caves in if I'm being honest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Up the fucking reds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noriordan he seems to fascinated with bus stops]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maclaithimh Chisora the winner for me.   Delighted for Katie.  Eddie Hearn is a cunt.  My takeaway from tonight's boxing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maclaithimh it's a disgrace tho.  The undercard is why I watched the event]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maclaithimh it's what Joshua fights. Boring as fuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bealymufc defo man. Really enjoyed that. Fair play to both.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bealymufc Terrible decision tho.  The draw or Chisora]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joke. Chisora or the draw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a fight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Zealand are dirty cunts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a fucking strange man https://t.co/jFmkvVMNo6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wales are an awful side. Delighted we got them as a top seed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a fight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well deserved. State of Austria. Worst team in the group]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scotland are utter shite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A @SRowntreeNews tweet has nearly 150 thousand retweets. WATTBA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gary302 he's a disgrace.  Smiling and laughing while swapping shirts.  Unforgivable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gary302 hard not to name and shame Smalling tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichieSadlier wasn't too long ago they were watched by about 50 people when they nearly went out of football]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 points from 18. Horrendous stuff from Utd.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mourinho tactically outdone Klopp tonight.  No plan B from from him . Spoofer Klopp, too concerned with how the media views him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome to the graveyard Longford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarryECrossan @RadioCleary @gerry_deane @ConorBroderick1 Adrian Kennedy must have got into their heads.  Garbage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RadioCleary @JamieMoore98fm @shelsfc @derekryan see last tweet.  Didn't even listen to the podcast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamieMoore98fm @shelsfc @derekryan @RadioCleary the highlight of the word scumbags. Wouldn't even bother listening to the podcast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[State of this https://t.co/zogbPge8E9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Decent pyro by the rovers mongs but yeah.. https://t.co/4PbdAE2F5M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Crazy_Cole79 I'm more worried about the people that keep retweeting the table]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Martin O'Neill and @Corktod  should just get into a ring.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was the worst goal I've ever seen in my life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hoolahan has to come on. Ireland are shite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DjAzzIreland mikhatarian still not match fit though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DjAzzIreland you on the gin bud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hasslebank looking for 55 grand for a speech.  Cunt can't put two words together. Should be thrown in jail for that alone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarryECrossan pure 'bantz', paddy power are all over it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's embarrassing that people are comparing the Utd and Dundalk results]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a Shels jersey in a West Ham bar in Lanzarote. Up the fucking reds https://t.co/W4ALxFUgiW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice place to watch the celtic match https://t.co/PoILLwURiK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off work for two weeks. Lanzarote on Monday. Cans. Forza Shelbourne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Conjob123 @SpursOfficial Yeah suppose pal. Ferguson hated him. Can see why now. Awful to deal with I'd say.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Conjob123 @SpursOfficial can't stand that cunt levy tho. Sitting there counting his coins until now. Top shithousery tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[State of Jim White pretending to get messages on his phone live on Sky. As if anyone would tell that cunt what's happening]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alancaw it is what it is. Glad to see you're going great in the media world. Good egg ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alancaw it's all gone wrong. The excitement we had when we were signing a young Alan Cawley from UCD ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alancaw what's happening with Shels Al. Heartbreaking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alancaw Al, i haven't much interested in the gaa but are you upset that Dublin won?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Conjob123 unreal pal. Couldn't believe it when I heard it. Shame on everybody.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarryECrossan quality pictures them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ciankavanagh12 fair enough bud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ciankavanagh12 lucky I didn't see the game but not sure how many "positives" you can take from being beaten by Waterford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anytime you think Shels have have hit rock bottom another floors breaks beneath them https://t.co/fdyFiCmNPe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shels are a fucking disgrace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck the FAI @FAIreland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FAIreland shame on you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shelsfc will the game be streamed later?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BOHSCONNO Yeah I'm due to be paid the 23rd so get it on the Friday instead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BOHSCONNO it be Friday then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DjAzzIreland love him pal. Better than Cantona ðŸ˜˜ðŸ˜˜ðŸ˜˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ufc is fucking awful. Not sure why I woke up for it. Bed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see plenty of flares at the gig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just put the women's team out next week lads @shelsfc]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>