<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill Please!!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump and Staff Rethink Tactics After Stumbles https://t.co/UdUG3Dr8Wm. This hardly seems like governing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Can you please direct Homeland Security to check incoming presidents VERY CAREFULLY.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @nytimes oh brother.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MSNBC But he does not respect the rule of law, the media, most racial/ethnic groups, women, US allies, the American people, . . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisHarrisJr The best in the world always do. A worthy successor to Denver's SB 50 win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@USATODAY We will be seeing this catch video for years to come]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill I hope Trump is watching the commercials]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome half time show]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@politico When will Washington hit rock bottom?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN So Trump is God's gift to the world? Because, of course, God has no better things to be doing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Terrell_Davis Congrats TD. There are a lot of TD fans who feel the same way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Broncos Truly deserving in terms of on field and especially off field performance. CONGRATS!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill This comment takes your breath away. In one fell swoop DT rationalized a host of illegal and immoral behavior. Unbelievable!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A big congrats and a heartfelt- FINALLY- for TD, 2017 NFL HOF!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Sorry but we are a nation of laws that even you must abide.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaraMariaMTV @MTV @ChallengeMTV Greetings from Helena. The last three seasons are terriffic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MSNBC Of course the burden of which always seems to fall on the poor taxpayers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MSNBC Oh this will end well. Last attempts at financial deregulation led to two recessions, an S&amp;L crisis, and the Great Recession.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill What a load of crap!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BuffieCEPR @ceprdc Thanks. It is an interesting trend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BuffieCEPR @ceprdc Is this labor force less likely to relocate for job opportunities?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNBC Of course, but does this order make us safer?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FortuneMagazine How does the carbon footprint of electric cars compare to non-electric? Forty plus % of electricity comes from coal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BuffieCEPR @ceprdc Is there much slack in the prime employment labor market? If so, is it largely skilled or unskilled?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TIME The question is are we making forward progress?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill The south China Sea is of importance to China and the US. Australia  stands to play a key role to stabilize the area.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reftpt @DeanBaker13 Infrastructure investments would also greatly increase productivity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnForce_FC John, the place would never be the same]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Slate I suspect the fake news will morph into fake numbers. He  has alluded to not trusting economic data over the last couple years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Grindin_59 The Broncos miss you Danny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MSNBC Yes, when Uncle Steve says he can]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kayvonwebster @c10anderson @nflnetwork @champbailey  Yessiree]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill Count me in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill Yes, tote the party line or else . . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wef @hpatrinos There is much we can learn from other countries whose educational and health care systems are better than the US.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill ACA isn't perfect but can be improved. Good move.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MileHighReport @Jezru It's just a matter of time for TD. There are too many positive accolades from his career for him not to be enshrined.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Newsweek I think it is fair to say that the US relationship with most of the World are at all time lows except for Russia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ABC Safe from whom? You?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ABC Tolerance?! Where is your tolerance for anyone other than your sycophantic followers and yes men.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Salon Trump will get around to the LGBT population soon enough. He'll attempt to legalize discrimination against a wide variety of groups]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill His insecurities are embarassing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ABC Diplomacy and trade are not a zero sum game where one party wins, one loses. If viewed as such, ST gains exact heavy LT consequences.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill uh oh Canada also needs to be put on notice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Bush's lie got us into a deadly and costly war. Learn from his mistake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You in a nutshell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricSchmittNYT @nytpolitics @nytimes The article didn't say whether the computers and laptops that were sought were retrieved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost Another of Trump's favorite words. What would you get in an Iranian deal? A Monday morning QB with no clue of issues.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MSNBC Perhaps Trump should deport rain clouds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Reuters What is this guys Muslim fetish? Who will he target next?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thenation The order would respect religious freedom when condemning huge swaths of the population. No way this would be constitutional.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill Without sufficient intelligence! This sums Trump up nicely. 
This is what happens when decision making is isolated and political]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HuffingtonPost Trump is nothing more than a fear monger. Preaching false fear to sell his oppressive policies. Where does this end?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@business Two troubling trends. Our economy lives and dies by our productivity rate. It has been trailing historical levels for a while now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@politico @mike_pence the administration gets what they deserve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill PLEASE!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN she is afraid she will be deported so she is laying low]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill Yeah, so are many of us poor taxpayers waiting for Washington to fulfill it's promise to us and our kids.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump The US agreed to resettle 1,200 refugees in a multi country pact. I suspect the a US has bigger problems.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I hope it's written in crayon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You don't allow free speech. Your private security oppressed many protesters during the campaign and transition. Hypocrite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidCornDC Very similar to the 2008 republican strategy to oppose every action taken by Obama administration. Boohoo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill Yes, Trump also was paid more than  $2 million a month in salary along with his kids during the campaign]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ABC and a romantic dinner  or two afterwards !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ABC a The DOE? Is the DOE now a homeland security agency?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Bad people with bad intentions like you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN It seems that Cruz maybe mimicking Trump's behavior.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nytimesworld @nytimes So who is going to protect us from the protector?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nytimesworld @nytimes From threats real and imaginary!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarketWatch I don't think it matters anyway.  Trump will lie about it to fit his agenda anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@USATODAY A man of his word who routinely lies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hardball Thank God he didn't nominate Steve Bannon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@voxdotcom The immigration ban is just the start.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill Didn't the Republicans fail to hold hearings for Obama's nominee? It seems they established a dysfunctional precedent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost Governing by fear and animosity is not leadership. Howard Stern shock jock tactics only seek to create choas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN With so many Trump statements over the past year plus about banning Muslims, does anyone believe the denials?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SteveDaines #BetsyDeVos will defund and destroy public education. Our public schools need a champion. #DumpDeVos
https://t.co/ONpnKeZ1ds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Of course blame someone else for your poor choices and improper vetting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MSNBC Hell of a way to out!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MSNBC Trump's Monday night massacre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hardball @chuckschumer @realDonaldTrump we have serious but solvable problems. We need a leader to build consensus and get the job done]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulkrugman  The stronger dollar and further and expansionist policies will drive inflation/interest rates higher, checking off growth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN it sounds like many have alreadt resigned en masse. Scary to lose such deep institutional knowledge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill Sad but true. Where does ineptitude fall within the definition of high crimes and misdemeanors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump By specifically doing what?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who are you picking to win #SB51? #MyMaddenPrediction = #PatriotsWin. @EAMaddenNFL's Prediction drops Wednesday!
https://t.co/ES56XdRvux]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amanda_m_macias @businessinsider 
Of course. It takes months to work changes through the various systems. Just another Trumpism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN Decisive, yes, leadership, no.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill No he really doesn't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@politico @SenSchumer How about the letter "g". Hummmm, what word starts with a "g" . God perhaps!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@politico @SenSchumer Donald, you have way overused the "d" words like disaster, now the "f" words like fake, move on to a new letter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@businessinsider He must be referring to th he West Wings of the White House]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump What represents the greatest threat to th he US? Of course, that is a rhetorical question that you don't need to answer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@politico @realDonaldTrump Really????!!!!! What an absolutely ignorant thing to say. Have you no shame? Embarassing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost The new abnormal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@businessinsider @POTUS then why is there a region test?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewYorker Isolated by lack of experience, lack of understanding, lack of caring about the consequences of actions, lack of empathy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Salon Very well said! Magnificent letter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@businessinsider oh yes he does]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>