<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Painting Paradise at the Queen's Gallery Holyrood. I especially liked this zany work. https://t.co/aPlb9OfLOM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turns out @AmazingMorph is a Rovers fan. Who knew? https://t.co/XvJOpioELp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Bell on Donald Trump at the National Prayer Breakfast – cartoon https://t.co/dLlHU726zK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course, you know the sequel...dissenters are "betraying the will of the people". https://t.co/lVPG51Dq82]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leilabilling I forecast a revival in the next 4 years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious https://t.co/eImmue7Vef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shameful performance in #HouseofCommons by #borisjohnson - flippant, complacent, self-regarding. Wrong day for the Bertie Wooster act.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good tag line for #Knocale @jacklord ... https://t.co/S4c0eg7Bpl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...make that 600k signatories - support seems to be accelerating
https://t.co/e2HOszZIy8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the time you read this the petition to deny Trump a state visit will have passed 500k signatures: https://t.co/e2HOszZIy8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you with Mo or Trump? Predictable payback for May's 48 hours of pathetic grovelling: https://t.co/2QsOTzmDs7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The marvellous Blackfriars pub https://t.co/0aT5Jvq3m0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sean Spicer is a Groucho Marxist, asking us not to believe our own eyes https://t.co/bwSr3IthQf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good enough to eat, but actually quite indigestible https://t.co/mISPJhm5sU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This beggars belief. Truly terrifying. https://t.co/va0cthxl3h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seen @Gagosian Gallery King's Cross https://t.co/KDa6Jx2gZE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 1917 Caporetto offensive sketched on a wall @Estorick Collection #WarintheSunshine https://t.co/HsjKvaALHM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Richard Serra @Gagosian https://t.co/fW9HAZbhfq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1000!!! Amazing response to our survey on community engagement wth the @ScotGovPlanning planning system. Do it now: https://t.co/HlIJXv5u0d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good piece by Andy Beckett: decades of urban triumphalism missed important demographic and electoral realities. https://t.co/H2MMsozqBD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want a @ScotGovPlanning system that is more engaging for communities? Tell us how with this 10 min survey: https://t.co/HlIJXv5u0d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here you are @robincph - as soon as the weather perked up old Finn would haul his favourite sofa out to the carport. https://t.co/i5tg3JzHPW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Tivoli. First class. https://t.co/OKrvV3XK9Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today in Copenhagen with @robincph we visited the Indian Embassy (!) and walked for miles around Holmen, Christiania and Christianshavn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bit of essential reading... https://t.co/9UGWxLODMQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant day in Copenhagen area with @robincph - Finn Juhls Hus, Ordrupgaard, Thorvaldsens Museum.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leilabilling @wendylord We figured that short stories would be the perfect format!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here you are @PeteLordAardman @bbrighid1 - modest but very nice in Perthshire https://t.co/ihUGyZhxEx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...and this is one of the best sites https://t.co/kDfVMCs5ki]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice to meet @planningclaire in Aberdeen at tonight's feisty meeting on engaging communities in planning. Lots to think about.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In case you're thinking he might not be so bad really... https://t.co/sloSmgS7MN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nattrustjobs ...and to raise the bullshit bar to a new high]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is Nina Simone singing Suzanne. Astonishing. #LeonardCohen https://t.co/vMCeOmuSPQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeteLordAardman @wendylord How about this? https://t.co/Vrn2IDxjfl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeteLordAardman @wendylord Big Mamma was all very well, but... https://t.co/x0XaYZKoZN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'll enjoy this https://t.co/nVAZ25sMfH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is very exciting. Had to flag down the train at Tonfanau earlier - and ask to be set down there on the way back. Hope that works.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First visit to lovely @momamachynlleth - really enjoyed Ffiniau: four postwar Welsh artists in Raymond Williams' Border Country]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heard in cafe: "Every year Auntie Wyn could send a crab in a shoebox"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you liked the headgear @annielord what about the dress? https://t.co/4p8XT3pw5R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pembrokeshire has weapons grade heritage https://t.co/p6Ni3WJM6Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here you are @PeteLordAardman - we're doing everything we're supposed to. https://t.co/ArQvG7eIbf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's @wendylord on the beach at Newport https://t.co/XZNRJqmW0r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fine fungi on our walk this morning https://t.co/CluEPwD9UL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today we visited Christina Shand's amazing garden at #DyffrynFernant https://t.co/RDWeaDrp9V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IMcMillan Have you also read his "Does Your Rabbi Know You're Here"? Also great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annielord  - in Newcastle, might be interesting https://t.co/7pzMa3qT4Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bboptimist On our way to Pembrokeshire yesterday we passed close to Dolaucothi gold mines, prompting a nostalgic pang or two.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yew tree arch at Aberglasney https://t.co/lSAoEuesen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant weekend in Monmouthshire. Pembrokeshire next.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facts Not Opinions. I was just obliged to remind @wendylord of this important distinction. https://t.co/HRLzgiJ7B1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We’re killing national treasures and closing our minds to great art | Laura Cumming https://t.co/RbZMKCuImV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeteLordAardman Have you been to Partrishow church? Black Mountains, middle of nowhere, top of an impossible hill? https://t.co/YKDqfDCEAw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now we're in Blaenafon. Fog clearing. https://t.co/Sy1u8k087I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Victoria Place: a surprise in no-frills Newport https://t.co/3pJZkMJzXu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Special holiday treat for @wendylord - Newport County v Plymouth Argyle https://t.co/IjAsOsFEFT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's apple pressing day in Abergavenny. https://t.co/28UyL7wbLw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Out of town unfortunately but go if you possibly can https://t.co/uvqLzJ6cYO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Bell on x-rays and checking teeth – cartoon https://t.co/hioLSywiuJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No doubt someone @TheBotanics thinks the 11th hour announcement of Inverleith House closure is masterly news management. It's shameful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@InverleithHouse You mean "before the gallery closes for ever", so why so secretive?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not good enough to hear on Wednesday that one of the capital city's cultural gems is closing on Sunday @TheBotanics @InverleithHouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No word of #inverleithhouse closure on @TheBotanics website. Late announcement seems designed to close off discussion/alternatives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LauraCummingArt called Inverleith House "the most beautiful gallery in Edinburgh – if not Britain". It's closing: https://t.co/c5ycFOQnIs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@willlord "HOUSES IN NICE PLACES TEND TO BE MORE EXPENSIVE": BOFFIN'S SHOCK CLAIM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terribly sad. A beautiful gallery with a consistently excellent programme. https://t.co/lAIMPYSxVp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting. https://t.co/dHm6MnnPxz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is extraordinary... https://t.co/beVPpIpSfl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Inverleith House https://t.co/htVJOHXwEH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MindLint Where can I place an order?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a really important - and shaming - graphic. Look at Glasgow, Dundee, Hull! https://t.co/b8q61fzRvz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really looking forward to Paul Nash retrospective @Tate - but they'll be hard pressed to match 2010 show at Dulwich https://t.co/19UCtXSXtK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quite often these days the news makes me feel physically sick... https://t.co/gC7T8RzfbS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'll be pleased about this @jacklord https://t.co/xvtNGP7UxK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NetworkRailSCOT @networkrail That's very encouraging: joined-up thinking in action]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remind me @networkrail @NetworkRailSCOT wasn't Queen St just closed for months on end so that the infrastructure could be upgraded?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Classic planning speak: "the town centre lacking the resilience to act as a catalyst in regenerating itself". Whatever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello there @networkrail - on a train stranded outside Glasgow Queen St. The guard has no idea what's going on. Do you? Like to share?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blimey! This is brutal. https://t.co/nONDg8Thz5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a very fine long editorial in today's @observer - this is the nub of it... https://t.co/fIbbUQU7na]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The UK was split 52-48 but our fate is entirely in the hands of zealots, ideologues and nativists. Scary. https://t.co/0n3Jw02U8M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This beggars belief. No, on second thoughts...Government bars foreign academics from advising on Brexit https://t.co/rv82imKLsn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["On Margate Sands.
I can connect 
Nothing with nothing"
That was before Margate became Hoxton-on-Sea of course #NationalPoetryDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deeply unpleasant cameo appearance from the deeply unpleasant Neil "brown envelopes" Hamilton on @BBCNews just now #UKIP *disinfects TV*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AkikoMaK @wendylord @AnaMiret My home town - and a fantastic city!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you considered mudlarking @MindLint ? https://t.co/OANlzVC9vS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Figuratively only, as far as we know" - lovely line from @Uniformbooks excellent The Keatons by John Bevis https://t.co/duRaWtbGqw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice review for @Dingsich performance in Manchester: https://t.co/G7evvti55j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had some innovative jam on my toast this morning...the marmalade (made from UK-grown oranges) was a bit challengi… https://t.co/jzRNzErm9q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoever had the idea to perk up #birminghamlibrary with those crappy lights should be summarily dismissed. https://t.co/ORsB5akGd3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious. No idea. https://t.co/6iFfwYx7th]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A message to tell me my Flickr pic will be used on a website that "promotes tourism in the trekking space". Sounds like a bullshit space.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Autumn at the allotment https://t.co/pSsMXExLEn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also had a look at Womersley's Church Square #Galashiels https://t.co/m1DMrV9DtB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #Womersley grandstand is lovely: concrete origami. The setting could be improved... https://t.co/MxFtz3odWn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally saw the Womersley grandstand at Galashiels. Came across a party from #RIAS with their backs to the game. https://t.co/Zd8T6Kl09s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of people called in to see @GroveEdinburgh in its new home at Harrison Pk. Thx to @gavincorbett @Edinburgh_CC https://t.co/xvwYx3DEt7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liked this spoof blue plaque in Margate Old Town https://t.co/1u5WpBeOcv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also a chance to revisit Margate https://t.co/fgzeDiaWlp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On duty with the Historic England urban panel in Ramsgate, where they used to observe local Mean Time https://t.co/S5DbKxw4Zf]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>