<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[This will keep me awake at night. https://t.co/ljLghUujhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good to know: the keeper still gets a BOOM! at BC Place, @JoeCannonGK1 !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could hear the horns out at Production Way Skytrain station today! https://t.co/lJze7ozm6e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trudeau the Elder https://t.co/DMZMmag8jT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The universe is shaped exactly like the earth: if you go straight long enough you'll end up where you were. @modestmouseband #mixtape day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I probably started counting when I lived in this neighbourhood, so I've come full circle! 40,075km #circumference… https://t.co/oMZskhPXEs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's here, it's here! Norse Mythology by @neilhimself arrived early. However, I showed it to my 10y-o and he won't give it back!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A change of pace https://t.co/3GSWwEz5ZG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking up "questions the border patrol can ask" as an afternoon activity. Though any advice is probably obsolete now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hold to this truth. https://t.co/j7nPFhKMKO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The score levels in the 2nd, making for a close run of play, but Dynamo put together some fine passing (w our centre mid!) and take it 3-1!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pressure pays off as @CMFSC U11 Dynamo net the first goal on a bright grey morning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Playing an old mix. 25yrs ago, we sang out @billybragg's "you're a dedicated follower of fascism!" with irony. Now: not so much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AltNatParkSer Our family road trip to @YellowstoneNPS last summer was truly great, thanks to the people of the NPS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can still wear my @WhitecapsFC jersey! Koffie is 28 again. https://t.co/HSqI7AWucw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Second half goals delivah a thrillah for Dyanamo to overcome an equally matched Lyon side! 2-1 final, and one of the best of the season.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back to @CMFSC play on a cold morning! Dynamo are up 1-0 at half in a tight game, as the showers slide down from snow-topped mountains.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nope, nope! Boycotting all political coverage today!  (I hope all the good memes survive until tomorrow.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PLEASE PLEASE PLEASE! RT @RealGDT: Informal poll (let's see how many votes we get in 24 hours)
Hellboy III]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giving poutine a bad name!
But I am hungry now. https://t.co/0RlbqAs8RS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait a m-! * squinting* https://t.co/X7VOJTciDR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another glorious failure! https://t.co/xwukHpd7Fp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guaranteed: full coverage of the woodwork and he'll catch every drop. https://t.co/HV3XJmfDB1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like roller coasters but maybe I'll give this one a miss. https://t.co/4yFkylrWAx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 minutes, if you're still walking in a straight line. https://t.co/rmBjD9NSqc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to Weezer's Pinkerton and the 10y-o catches the Green Day AND the Public Enemy name drops. Three hits for #indierockdad!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West coast winter hack #42: park in the underground lot while grocery shopping, until the snow &amp; ice melt off the car.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wave your hands in the air
If you know the song
Like you just don't care.
 https://t.co/AUqshQ3CKv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sir, your reverie of meat has been epic this eve.

But truly: are you a quitter?

A quitter of meat??

 https://t.co/p5uxNEUzYk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And a couple personal additions. https://t.co/6yItUSZQDq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I checked: from Wishful Drinking. https://t.co/CGNXlX1n8p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can it NOT be Bill Murray?? https://t.co/Dmf2TFRI9S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Medicating this cold with Christmas candy and coffee at the office this morning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The snowflakes are getting big and fluffy.
"Like kittens, falling from the sky."
What?!?
"Hey, you asked."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Party on! (For engineers) https://t.co/92ErPscQbu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The crux of the dilemma. https://t.co/802MqaHS9z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas fear. https://t.co/Hz48iw3tW6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The etymology of "gas lighting". https://t.co/eZZEcpbNCZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life behind bars.
Decent commute though!
#bikeyvr #bcstorm (#notreally) https://t.co/gBhVYTlAjs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then the rush wears off...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Busy morning, so put off my first cup of coffee until 12:47pm.

WHAT WAS I THINKING?!?
I'M NO QUITTER!
MOAR!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the bike riders in the office say, Yeah!
#bikeyvr  #snowpocalypse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retracting brake caliper on the Jetta in rain and failing light. Reminded of Clive Barker's puzzle box in Scarlet Gospels. Coincidence?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our forward went down hard in their box just before the half, as the Dynamo put together another goal. Up and at it again for 2nd half!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great passing and overwhelming pressure put the @CMFSC BU11 Dynamo up at the half. Again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not through the Burrard Inlet. https://t.co/6eO0aWcX57]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I need to wash the car. It's gathering some dirt. https://t.co/cXuZVvseT8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @CMFSC BU11 Dynamo press their advantage in the 2nd half, scoring 2 more to finish a cold &amp; wet game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Dynamo are held 2-1 at the half, versus a tough @CMFSC Celtic side. Push on, lads!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey neighbour... https://t.co/gJ0gPb38Mt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gonna be sick of fish for dinner... https://t.co/Il2ocog4TI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sure-fire way to get square with the Bureau for messing with the election: Presidential pardon for Leonard Peltier this year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I remember having breakfast in Kaikoura. "State of emergency declared in town cut off by NZ earthquake" https://t.co/cdbYvsJLJs Best wishes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making a list of news organizations to support, like I would for charities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Dynamo keepers earned their clean sheet today, as the forwards' pressure deliver a 4-0 victory against a stubborn opponent!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our keeper pulls out a big save to hold the score 1-0 at the half for @CMFSC  BU11 Dynamo! https://t.co/EM3Tke1QeI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Game on, Dynamo! And the sun breaks through for @CMFSC BU11 this afternoon. https://t.co/0lRAyo0Oyn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we ask every Rep voter what they expect the new gov't to achieve, then see how it pans out in 4yr, can people learn something? Finally??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good to know. https://t.co/uGGPNUFMnZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can hear the Harvards flying overhead, some distance away, echoing in and out as the wind changes. #lestweforget]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some good news https://t.co/kS5V0hFE46]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not reassuring anyone.
Fair enough. https://t.co/qoVaf0w85B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FFS, America...
No. I got nothing to say to you right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're going to drive a tricked-out BMW, be like this guy. https://t.co/VWKKRfK9FP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel bad. Just finished cursing out the salesguy, said there were Revellos in the freezer. He wasn't "lying"; he was "selling". My bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think you can full stop after "...no idea."
 https://t.co/1q2KRkyz1N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @VSOrchestra is rehearsing before screening Raiders. The horns played a snippet of Indy's theme and I- I got the feels.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introducing the kids to Indy with the @VSOrchestra for Raiders of the Lost Ark! https://t.co/riYYbLDDuo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A handy reference to English Facebook! https://t.co/FElUqVjPnh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The most interesting information comes from children, for they tell all they know and then stop." - Mark Twain
https://t.co/dT733E6GkU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoyed the tourtière by @chefenrick for dinner on a rainy night! And the chicken pie earlier this week. Recommende… https://t.co/5E5g8gJ4RU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2true, @FatMike_of_NOFX ! 'All my secrets are out there, I've lost all pride&amp;shame, 2 things no one should have' https://t.co/I4AXBTG94B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bit of rain on the mountain for @CMFSC  BU11 Dynamo today. Hustle, hustle, boys! https://t.co/5YVyb9OydD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The long precursor to this chaotic US election by @SKendzior https://t.co/FhJET47Irt https://t.co/Jg3knJ0YSV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome. It waited 5 minutes after practice started to start raining. #thatsfootie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Belated thanks for playing @gorddownie's "Seven Matches" for the morning drive, @evolution1079 . Started the day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've spent the whole work day in my cycling gear. It's as if, subconsciously, I'm ready to drop tools and run for freedom at any moment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter, tonight. https://t.co/eiBqRnskOr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guy at work described Hallowe'en terror: his 15y-o daughter dressed up as Harley Quinn.

I've no doubt she will use that bat!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wearing my @Powells tee in honour of@SnarkySteff as she begins her 2nd year as a nomad, travelling the world!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting his @David_Ousted on, building the wall in the rain as they practice free kicks! (Tak, David!) https://t.co/nRDUdacFxm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally made the Ironworkers' sidewalk navigable, now someone decides it's too much to provide access!! #bikeyvr 2/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Btw, who decided to close half the Ironworkers' sidewalk to cyclists?! #bikeyvr 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Decent commute to meet my new #UBC mentoring students this evening! Extra bonus: introducing them to Benny's Bagels. https://t.co/TRUV4lh5PE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With a sprinkling of dignity over top to sweeten that season-ending swallow of pride. https://t.co/8EopZcbbGq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pretty good way to end the season, @WhitecapsFC ! Thanks, gentlemen. #vwfc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoy a glass from one of the Okanagan vineyards, @ericidle! https://t.co/FK599erMUn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There was an Indiana Jones treatment based on this but Harrison Ford "didn't want to return to Hoth". https://t.co/1leOmxZBZO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where do I sign the petition? RT @NEWS1130: Cycling group pushes for "one metre law " in BC https://t.co/hO2R2xFH8M https://t.co/zam4mTcSV4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Start with the rule, for safety.
Then drivers can lobby WITH cyclists for 1m lanes, for new infrastructure. https://t.co/Y5b8aIvonE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two rockets in the opening minutes put @cmfsc BU11 Dynamo up early. Now into the second half, and our opponents are pushing back!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walking laps in the rain, listening to #Soundgarden's Birth Ritual on my Seattle Soundtrack mix. Apropos. https://t.co/9Sr3MeRH3p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creeptastic! ITSAZOO Invites Audiences into Their Own, Personal Horror Film: Theatre Event: - Hidden https://t.co/UBN0O30z3j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So is he making a joke ABOUT the democratic process, or making a joke OF it? #notfunny #debatenight https://t.co/mWHEDOlBBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EmmMacfarlane: DONALD TRUMP IS PREPARING HIS NEXT ANSWER. #debatenight https://t.co/051nE1mxBg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you would, @TheTyee, it's a US tug in BC waters.  https://t.co/sA7hE04VKv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What are they filming at @zulurecords tonight?! Trucks &amp; lights on 4th as I rode home tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...Flattering and all but hey,
I'm not your type! I mean,
Married.
Kids.
And dude, I'm a DUDE!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Riding the Kawi home from UBC, an Acura starts flashing lights and bipping his horn.  Uhm, is that a pick-up line, or...? 'Cause, dude...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We still have a crack at this?! All right then! https://t.co/8B4HEbR8r3]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>