<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada’s "Alt-Right" Mosque Shooter, And What He Means For Right-Wing Media https://t.co/tHEhSHnZx9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senate GOP Bypasses Dem Boycott of Mnuchin, Price By Suspending Rules https://t.co/f16hSfzopP via @TPM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-Bush speechwriter: Dumping Steve Bannon won’t help because Trump attracts ‘bad characters’ https://t.co/TMpWdDrixs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Melania Trump may permanently stay in Trump Tower and not move to White House: report https://t.co/aUVyLVQwIC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senate Finance Republicans change rules to approve Price and Mnuchin without any Democrats present https://t.co/D7xHF9KYpc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters orders reporters to cover Trump like an authoritarian regime: Expect ‘physical threats’ https://t.co/ABJDH4QqjU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's antics are triggering an army of first-time protesters https://t.co/NBuqczzjNs via @HuffPostImpact]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Breaks Promise To Reduce Drug Prices | Crooks and Liars https://t.co/HcrZmXLrgf via @crooksandliars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Detroit family caught in Iraq travel ban, mom dies waiting to come home https://t.co/XsjTaQwVcD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch Dianne Feinstein eviscerate Jeff Sessions in savage closing argument https://t.co/MxrjmNzWoU via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FBI afraid to share information with local police because white supremacists have infiltrated departments https://t.co/akyqSkRsOg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DeVos Apparently Plagiarized Parts Of Her Responses To Senate Questionnaire https://t.co/g4OHdJEEOc via @TPM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘He is running a cabal’: White House leaker says Steve Bannon runs ‘shadow NSC’ with no paper trail https://t.co/ySPx63nBUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Family History: Donald, Fred, and the Ku Klux Klan  https://t.co/0mIsptqHbR via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama weighs in on President Trump for the first time https://t.co/rn8VxTzorm via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The FBI has quietly investigated white supremacist infiltration of law enforcement https://t.co/iZZCNVaJzF by @alicesperi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mystery Convoy Of 'Military' Vehicles Flying 'Trump' Flag Spotted In Kentucky https://t.co/j3xgiqcFBY via @TPM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump's first 100 days as president – daily updates https://t.co/8Ztpkb8RTP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. diplomats drafted a "dissent memo" against Trump's Muslim ban ➡️by @christinawilkie https://t.co/5MYDtHmcOp via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Denver Police Tell Protesters To ‘Stop Doing Anything That Could Be Construed As Free Speech’ | https://t.co/rlyGezIg58 via @crooksandliars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After Court Rejects His Policy, Trump Moves To Undermine Judicial Branch. https://t.co/gPvpwn4Rn0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING- Steven Mnuchin Lied During Confirmation Hearings- Help Needed- Vote Is Today! https://t.co/lAaC5byFqn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Resistance in the Heart of Dixie https://t.co/7JU1GTrIzc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It took Donald Trump eight days to bring the U.S. to the brink of a constitutional crisis https://t.co/Z2LepJ1cZb via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bannon's Blueprint. Read it for yourself. - Democratic Underground https://t.co/NTnsme5a6x via @demunderground]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Antagonizes America and the World https://t.co/FwYW0vkjde via @theworldpost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Orwell essay that's even more pertinent than "1984" right now https://t.co/I7YtVhb3zp via @HuffPostArts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time's powerful new cover reminds the world the resistance to trump has arrived https://t.co/o2J0OioZcE via @HuffPostWomen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pope Francis Just Called Out Trump For Being An Intolerant Racist – Awaiting Twitter Rant https://t.co/IAsq6rmvSg via @Bipartisan Report]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republicans largely silent as Trump bans refugees, immigrants from U.S. https://t.co/16lsehcPmt via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘This is about a guy who never brought a woman to orgasm’: Bill Maher tackles Trump’s ‘crowd’ https://t.co/xsuPPg1CfS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Omits Jews From Holocaust Remembrance Day Statement via @politicususa https://t.co/pS7MLNpHCN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report: McConnell Shot Down Trump's Proposal To Abolish Electoral College https://t.co/HHy6MEYORv via @TPM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘We’re not going to shut up’: CNN’s Christiane Amanpour slams Bannon and Trump’s ‘totalitarian regime’ tactics https://t.co/wQdm6OTSHT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Trump already looks like the worst of Richard Nixon https://t.co/hmQRsCjwY4 via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GQ totally trolled Donald Trump with this presidential makeover https://t.co/bBFAfV1x6m via @HPLifestyle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making It Up As They Go: Trump Team Now Pretending They Never Proposed 20% Wall Tax via @politicususa https://t.co/pKWIFu6jJI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's Presidency Is A Train Wreck Because He Is Getting His Info From Fox News via @politicususa https://t.co/2opOWwcqXx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Press Says Transcript of Trump's ABC Interview is 'Bonkers' and 'F*cking Nuts' via @politicususa https://t.co/k9e7DH7DGQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In first interview, Trump confirms things that aren’t “tremendous” are “disasters:” https://t.co/nwJoNYw4Yt via @slate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CDC's canceled climate change conference is back on — thanks to Al Gore https://t.co/MSnkzQQpLp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girls start doubting their own brilliance as young as 6, researchers say https://t.co/DkVDh2VBKr via @HuffPostEdu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Donald Trump made the cable news chyron operator a Washington power player https://t.co/PHnUrfnMDU via @HuffPostMedia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilipGNews Ashes to Ashes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump reeeeeally needs to stop using an unsecured Android phone https://t.co/HQGhCjOO8K via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump cries voter fraud, while his chief strategist is registered to vote in 2 states https://t.co/XU1cZwgNTR via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No White House Leaks Like This ... Until Now https://t.co/3bJXp6ZmDr via @TPM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CIA folks are worried if they find dirt on Putin &amp; tell Trump-Trump will blow up their source's spot https://t.co/6IheoJ73ac @demunderground]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federal workers told to halt external communication in first week under Trump https://t.co/b5Pj6q69Dw via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is American Democracy Strong Enough for Trump? https://t.co/4oHvo6Umr1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Trump troll accidentally organized a solid women's march https://t.co/TmykVpdc3C via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course the CIA gave Trump standing ovations. He never let them sit. ➡️ by @svdate https://t.co/NyxKWObKjt via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump's laugh track is tricking America https://t.co/sJ4rku8Ego via @HuffPostMedia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump signs anti-abortion executive order surrounded by men ➡️ by @aterkel https://t.co/jnVXkLIumD via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doomsday Prep for the Super-Rich https://t.co/onkxvFXvMM via @eosnos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump and his press secretary flagrantly lied on their first day in office. That matters. https://t.co/LWGPN8NznR via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chaffetz skipped meeting with ethics chief he threatened to subpoena, emails show https://t.co/tovPpZu7cP via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phillip Roth's 'The Plot Against America' Is Fast Becoming Reality https://t.co/dJP8tSwa3I via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[G.O.P. Lawmaker Hints at Investigating Ethics Chief Critical of Trump https://t.co/VT6SUFckEQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOP Prohibits CBO From Reporting How Much ACA Repeal Blows Up the Deficit via @politicususa https://t.co/flFz9UhuV5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trumpsters On ACA Don't Know Obamacare Is Same Thing? | Crooks and Liars https://t.co/pdM4MpVssd via @crooksandliars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Evan McMullin Goes After Trump's Treasonous Attack On Our Intelligence Community. https://t.co/umj7p1YgGt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[N.C. Guv-Elect Cooper Sues Over Elections Law Stripping His Powers https://t.co/uEkH5WuBm4 via @TPM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It Wasn’t the Russians: Hillary Lost Because She Blew Off Sanders and His Voters https://t.co/gfEA17qibD by @NatCounterPunch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North Carolina is no longer a democracy: report https://t.co/QOwMZOYmjQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 10 best TV shows of 2016, from 'Westworld' to 'Game of Thrones' https://t.co/Xsvebn1BC7 #Outcast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peevish, petulant and petty to the end: McCrory puts an exclamation point on four dreadful years https://t.co/mva3LAAczd via @ncpolicywatch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John McCain says Obama has "no strategy and no policy" on Russian hacks https://t.co/BCW8Q1aA9O via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Majority wants Monday's Electoral College vote postponed in wake of Russia scandal https://t.co/3C4zLqZSD1 via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump says his supporters were "violent," but they're "mellow" now he's won https://t.co/Rsj0AYKhWA via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Defeated North Carolina governor signs bills gutting successor's power ➡️ by @juliacraven https://t.co/6ApAyFGUSh via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-Hill Staffers Put A Spin On The Tea Party Playbook In Anti-Trump Guide https://t.co/Y1Fe11nUlu via @TPM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joy Reid's Panel On North Carolina GOP's Craven Power Grab: 'It's Like A Cry Of Rage!' | https://t.co/47M5NZge2Q via @crooksandliars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McCrory Is Having Citizens Arrested For Protesting His Disgusting Coup In NC | Crooks and Liars https://t.co/srpaXWWCSX via @crooksandliars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kurt Eichenwald Takes Tucker Carlson Out On His Own Show | Crooks and Liars https://t.co/derlc92PuA via @crooksandliars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North Carolina’s new governor is prepared to sue state Republicans over bad laws https://t.co/WNanen3EXe via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North Carolina Republicans push bills to hobble incoming Democratic governor ➡️ @juliacraven https://t.co/EY4ZiHyUlT via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North Carolina GOP shreds democracy, acts to strip power from new Democratic governor and high court https://t.co/oLO0JBDinL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NC Legislature Calls Mystery Special Session With Just Hours Notice https://t.co/88W0h63nnO via @TPM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch Fox's Shepard Smith Debunk Trump's False Claims Scrubbing Russia Of Involvement In The US Election https://t.co/MX5MybrkZt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NC Legislature Launches Special Session To Strip New Dem Governor Of Power | Crooks and Liars https://t.co/tm5DCFigqi via @crooksandliars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vladimir Putin's popularity is skyrocketing among Republicans https://t.co/yItTV5sEUm via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report says Putin was directly involved with Russian interference in U.S. election https://t.co/jrVqdstC6U via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Russia Also Tilted Key Congressional Races | Crooks and Liars https://t.co/3hWE3CperY via @crooksandliars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOP leaders ignored repeated requests to go further in condemning Russia's hacking https://t.co/DENMyUOtxe via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump, McConnell, and the Triumph of the Will to Power https://t.co/RwDWQ4dJup via @intelligencer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With Russia Probe, Obama Finally Hacks the Hearts of Defense Hawks  https://t.co/id8zOSJyzM via @thedailybeast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The CIA concluded Russia worked to elect Trump. Republicans now face an impossible choice. https://t.co/oVau4w4fmW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia Hacked Republican Committee but Kept Data, U.S. Concludes - Democratic Underground https://t.co/9kvUI8FO2L via @demunderground]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Secret CIA report says Russia aimed to steal White House for Trump, Washington Post reports https://t.co/GVFA4uj0HU via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are Republicans Crazy Enough to Go After Social Security? https://t.co/0SWNM4NWV7 via @intelligencer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Secret CIA Assessment Finds That Russia Helped Get Trump Elected via @politicususa https://t.co/nucZyYwl3U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Treasonous Mitch McConnell Refused To Oppose Russia Election Meddling For Trump via @politicususa https://t.co/yzBcRXj3rr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Pat McCrory Lost and Wh... https://t.co/pm2jhGD9qQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pentagon buries evidence of $125 billion in bureaucratic waste https://t.co/0eOQp9Yw0a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As the Labor Movement Dies, Does the Middle Class Die With It? https://t.co/5TgQODNlR7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why the Rich Don't Give to Charity https://t.co/VJNtAfiHMI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blue-Collar Democrats To Party: It's Still The Economy, Stupid https://t.co/eVqtXHXzgV via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading Dostoyevsky For Thanksgiving https://t.co/NiDWfs0Jhy via @BillMoyersHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neil deGrasse Tyson (@neiltyson) explains 2 things most people can't grasp https://t.co/ebj9ewsdAG via @HuffPostScience]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>