<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[What fascists and antifa have in common is that to both of them I'm just a liberal cuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes the gayest wrestling moves are the most effective, but cis wrestlers are to sexually insecure to try them. Sad!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not an organ donor because I need my kidneys in heavenðŸŒ¤ï¸ðŸ™ðŸ™Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I read the Economist because I'm better than you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've developed a strong bond with the repairman who's been fixing my shower irregularly through the hours of 8-5 this past week]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If anything, globalism promote freedom and equality]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want whatever Alex Jones is having]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Food $200
Data $150
Rent $800
InfoWars DNA Force $3600
Utility $150
someone who is good at the economy pls help me budget my family is dying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SullivanBobby this will be better because it's real]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't watch the Superbowl, but I will record it and not go on the internet for 24h. This will be my greatest accomplishment if I succeed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cinnamon_Bruns you can fight back, but don't be an instigator]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1) use violence because you think you are right
2) the other side thinks they are just as right as you
3) both sides use violence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[anthony fantano was my right in on  Nov 8. and I didn't even vote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey

Look that muscle

Nice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jcornithwell that would be truly abhorrent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free speech guise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are people protesting Milo, he's like the least controversial controversial person]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely wild 

https://t.co/4hZarn45r5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am very good at cooking steak. Not as good as the goons over at Ruth Chris but good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michael_olmo @dan_the_ram_ @BrandonSykes69 I thought Toys R Us only had big box storesðŸ¤”ðŸ¤”dont rt guys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have never been more excited for a podcast #6MonthsofRationsandAAbatteries https://t.co/9yCA3Fsh4I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@STREETWOLFFF https://t.co/l984JTjURJ it's been on repeat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which is 8% of an olympic size swimming pool. Not good obviously just some fun contextðŸ¤ ðŸ¤  https://t.co/7jUSOYH9hK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really hope @JustinTrudeau goes to someone's private island who likes electoral reform]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this what Spotify thinks of me? I associate with this? https://t.co/WHRbrVsaaY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsafshar the only thing harder than spelling entrepreneurship is copyright laws*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsafshar If it's so easy, why don't you start your own company then ðŸ¤ ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing harder than entrepreneurship is spelling it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YABOIMAXXX she can't see it from here, but I pray I go into her binder full of men]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The girl sitting across from me's flash went off, I hope it wasn't an accident]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breakfast is not the most important meal. Lies from the parent lobby...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can think of so many inefficient solutions to so many problems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I d-don't think Rex Tillerson will be terrible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chance consistently hates on vegetables in his music]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spaghetti nah, you did a good job. Appreciate the tweets, makes a lot more sense now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nyro_lol thanks, cleared it up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spaghetti let's compare a doctor to a truck driver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To the communists: why should someone working a very difficult job get paid the same as someone working a simple job?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HHHGignac I thought they leaked some documents but they actually just linked to their already released archive. I was double wrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@2008recession nevermind they also released Le Pen's stuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting how Wikileaks only leaks information that benefits RussiaðŸ¤”ðŸ¤”ðŸ¤”ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TBQHFam my third eye hurts all the time too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wow I can't believe university is hard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@flanvoyage @bound2yeezus in the mood for pumpkin pie? https://t.co/8ex0sQ639X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kofi Annan in the seats , cocky anon on the Internet forum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sidstacks this guy fucking knows what he's talking about]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Industrial purposes, just for fun, tax purposes... 

Don't tweet unless you know what you're fucking talking about https://t.co/2jCFHDFbXq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got too hopeful, still not loaded https://t.co/KKHwKGIdbT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When it takes 20 minutes to open up a word doc &lt;&lt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People are going to be listening to Joe Rogan in their philosophy classes in 2000 years ðŸ˜…ðŸ˜…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ben's, it's time to rise up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'm not afraid of voodoo"

but too afraid to send ziploc bag of hair and piece of my shirt to west africa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[place that head on your pillow, fill up that nyquil enma bag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ben, you idiot, you need to wake up early tomorrow, wyd retard? get your ass to sleep, let's keep that circadian rhythm in check]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just can't get tower 7 off my mindðŸ‘½ðŸ‘½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[cut twice measure once word to the smart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[trillary clinton is such a hufflepuff, love itðŸ¤ ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarelyOnTime ya, I don't even know how someone can reach authoritarian right unless you are literally Hitler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarelyOnTime some of these questions are a little weird but this makes sense https://t.co/tmDOuP0Jg0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i want tomi lahren to liberal bash me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why aren't there any rabbis steering me in the right direction]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nontolerantman what about foreign embassies?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying to find a girl straight out of a Tim Burton movie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This shake is thicc in the worst way possible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@moastdeph needed a subtle Biden reference tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChristianMingel worf it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 Chainz re-released Good Drank as a single. Please appreciate it everyone, he knows it's a good song and is trying to get it to number 1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[someone needs to make a tournament on who makes the best skr skr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[rt if you allowed offset to fuck your wife before bad and boujee came out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[your mcm looks like he was on games done quick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actia;;y think they have the right to free speech. Just pointing out the hypocrisy on the control left]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I find it appalling that someone can support the ACLU while they openly defended the rights of neo-nazis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After Iran violates the Nuclear Deal, I feel safe knowing Steve Bannon will be there to respond with appropriate action]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring on those sanctionsðŸ’¯ðŸ’¯ https://t.co/gzkBeBfKjp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a postmodernist, #FactsDontMatter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@canubian @imraansiddiqi @EyesOnTheRight @intifada I don't agree with them, but it's useful at countering their arguments]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@canubian @imraansiddiqi @EyesOnTheRight @intifada Im on your side, I just like hearing what they have to say. Doubt the suspect is the case]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EyesOnTheRight @imraansiddiqi @intifada you know what I was getting at]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@imraansiddiqi @EyesOnTheRight @intifada I follow the same pages, yet they haven't inspired me to commit terrorism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think for every one regulation they add, they should add three more on top of it https://t.co/tY0uXRjL72]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh no, this person is making their bitmoji look much more attractive than they do in real life ðŸ˜±]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely https://t.co/hOzpRuF2CP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016 was Anderson Paak's year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grt8ness2017 why not real]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I tweeted before Trump today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChristianMingel @wokieleaks1 i only read the pic not the quote, my bad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Folgers crystals but meth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a couple seconds of pondering, not doing it https://t.co/1w8Fz6cY8W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[can you justify wearing thrasher if you are a monster truck driver ???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Bannon looks like the kind of guy to think that some races are inherently superior to others lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamHarrisOrg should have used squarespace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoutout to me for doing well on my exams except for one but it's okay https://t.co/ko3cdwOqf8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FIabbergaster @HHHGignac everything is crumbling downðŸ˜¤ðŸ˜¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spaghetti I just think it's better to have good people try to engage him than not engage him at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spaghetti I like having Musk whisper good things about renewable energy in Trump's ear. Better him than a coal CEO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber's CEO is on Trump's advisory board, just like Elon Musk. Weak anti-Uber argument guys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please sponsor me @HormelFoods, I'm your biggest fan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My dog just turned on a podcast with his nose. Loves that Freakonomics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump reconciling his colossal fuck ups through a couple tweets &lt;&lt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Oh yeah", I say, as I passionately clap to Bill Maher]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>