<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisdonia @strongmisgiving @hiddendoorarts we're borrowing them for hidden door]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisdonia @strongmisgiving @hiddendoorarts yeah, that is basically the same]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DougGarryPoet @FredRAlexander yeah it's pretty decent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cww_george @periwinklewine chortle Chris. chortle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[white people are awful https://t.co/LDfV4DtrsW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emotionalpedant not sure first and third ones are compatible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bart_owl this is our watergate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile, in Edinburgh... https://t.co/EEYIGDWRKw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving Meadowbank has that effect on people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving how is the bus?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there a word for the lag time between logging into Twitter, seeing all the stuff about babies and bombs, and working out wtf happened?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving i am disappointed by the second sentence there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last ever Blind Poetics was great. An unsung hero in the Edinburgh poetry scene. https://t.co/2v0Ma3R08E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeylaJosephine1 it can be excruciating depending on circumstance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving Okay. What information do I need to know that makes this comprehensible?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SKBwrites cheers! i hope i get to read the rest of your story.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edmorrish it's forever teetering on the comedy/tragedy divide down there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stugone I feel like I should buy you one of these https://t.co/CPVkLE2ays]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edmorrish have you ever read the customer reviews on that site?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeatherParryUK Likewise, though I got nothing on the nickname front.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If someone asks you to do a gig at @InterrobangEdin, do a gig at @InterrobangEdin - great line ups and audience. https://t.co/rsD4AtS5yf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisdonia we do blur into each other]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@poetryshower69 likewise, clocked you and @weecalrobot but I still haven't got the hang of basic human interactions like saying hi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@poetryshower69 is there a Milletts outdoorsy type shop near you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving @clramc noted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@denofgeek you should look at @moriartyenterto if you haven't already]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thermoso I'm so happy it is a thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is like the sweet spot on a Venn diagram of my interests. https://t.co/yiZsS3Jahf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving @Josherick3 shark backs are shiny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving interesting, I wondered how far you'd have to go to jump the shark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@freelance_liar see @InterrobangEdin for updates and that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a thing I'm doing on Saturday in Leith with some people who are really really good at readings things out https://t.co/XYM6w6NcWG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@panieldiper compare it to a failed relationship that you aren't fully over, add a dick joke in before a moment of pathos, done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going to this because it is relevant to my interests/looks mint. https://t.co/N9NDoKmmDF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarianneMacRae have reserved them at the library.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarianneMacRae I will look these out at the libraries. Dave described the winner to me and I eventually went 'Meh'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davepoems @FredRAlexander @strongmisgiving @BexFoxwood @Josherick3 esp. Compared to the moral + physical reality]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving @davepoems @FredRAlexander @BexFoxwood @Josherick3 that is not the bad boy way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving @FredRAlexander @BexFoxwood @Josherick3 but with bad assery as a judging criteria]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is on, niche interest style https://t.co/HOMchncvpg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ringo_starrrr are you looking forward to the shoegaze tinnitus in your 50s?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Considering forming a political party called "We are actively trying to kill you" just to see if I'd get my deposit back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Edinburgh Watch never boils.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving @CJMacBeathW @BexFoxwood and that Edinburgh watch rose again on the third day according to the twitters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@poetryshower69 @mitchellljade @KevinPGilday you should do that. with props.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davepoems Kate Kellaway: the origin story #possiblepamphletnames]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamiesmart if you ever feel ready, I think it's also on Netflix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamiesmart do Sing Street next]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving mind that joke we had 'In a war between page and performance poets - AND IT IS A WAR']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last night I had a dream about buying the wrong size of cross dowel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@triplebozzmun it's worse than Shark Zone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stugone I can't make that promise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stugone I expect I will not be the last, but only if ross is reading this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stugone I can wait for you to pretend block someone else first if you like]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BexFoxwood no, but if you like crying it has its moments.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving that would be cheaper, certainly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving no, but we should make this film]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BexFoxwood have you seen 'A Monster Calls'?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@freelance_liar after about eighty minutes it becomes clear that what this means is, in fact, the sea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The worst film I've ever seen with the word 'Shark' in the title is called 'Shark Zone'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are going to watch a film called 'Shark Exorcist'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving haven't we all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never felt so close to self service checkouts as when they repeat "Awaiting approval"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FredRAlexander #joebidenmemesagainstthedyingofthelight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dohoodle I like the one where he fights wolves. This one is also good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dohoodle I think I've seen that. It's got a surprisingly good cast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Working title: 'Miserable Bastards in Space' https://t.co/M8E87zocuP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thecolleencg you should get Hattie Hayridge in to record that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EddieRobson have you read this interview with Morris about Cook? https://t.co/wpqdm9ByaJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thecolleencg imagine fire alarms were changed to a barrage or urgent whispers tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davepoems @adfinnes 'in a very moving eulogy, up to seven of Al's friends mentioned times when he had "somehow made things worse."']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adfinnes how have you made this worse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alantwentyseven some of them have evolved beyond blood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@freelance_liar this is actually quite an optimistic tweet because it presupposes a lack of nuclear armageddon/the collapse of civilisation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The year is 2046. Scott Brown has come out of retirement. Strachan thinks this is our year. We fail to qualify for the 106 team World Cup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@callumjodwyer we'll be dead by the time this escalates into bloodshed, but its our future generations I feel sorry for]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinPGilday have you found the belgian beer for about 90 cents a bottle in the supermarkets yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@empowermint they're great fun but they've also generated their own cliches pretty rapidly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving @Josherick3 @etherwaves especially gallus weegies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@empowermint the MCU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sigourney Weaver is doing a Lis Sladen impression in A Monster Calls. There are also many other reasons to watch it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davepoems a short list poem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davepoems things I learned through PAH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davepoems no, sorry, meant to be this https://t.co/OYPv4D6u0l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davepoems relevant to your interests]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robleane ask Simon if you can serialise it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ayetunes yeah, but I got nothing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving @stugone did neeson not do the taken speech then?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bored on the bus, picked up the Metro. The next day on page 3: "BORED MAN PICKS UP THE METRO" #LossLit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Josherick3 he's opened my eyes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I saw Coolio working in Spar. He was arguing with his manager about the mark-up on salt and vinegar twirls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The bus driver refused to let the sunrise on, working to a timetable and besides there wasn't space #LossLit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come to think of it, before Jeff moved to Midsomer, he did have a sort of cloying melancholy to him #LossLit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just found my diary from 2013. There's nothing in it. I can probably spin a fringe show out of this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@freelance_liar I used to do stand up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's nothing on the telly. Literally nothing. It yawns. It becomes so attractive your neck snaps in its pull. #LossLit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Due to inflation, forty winks only actually worth twenty nine of your parents' winks #LossLit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving @stugone evocative, certainly, but it's not that good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving schedule this for loss lit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving everyone else around the fire continues weeping for their lost futures]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>