<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Only cats could lead to me having a casual catch-up with friends over twitter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bionictoaster Ray no longer there all the time!? That's heartbreaking &lt;/3 Daisy I bet is still cute- does she still do the window thing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LizzieWilliams8 of course!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bionictoaster Exactly like why are you clingy if you're also going to be a sod; love me or leave me don't do this - how're the other pets?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bionictoaster I know, he's mental, he'll attack my leg and be such a sod that just wants food, but I miss my little fluffy face nuzzler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bionictoaster I fully understand this - going home on Thursday and all I can think is I get to see Georgie boy again soon haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People who think my friends and I joke about HSM nights, do not even deserve to appear on my radar. Be gone, why would I joke about that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some days, I really would love to just scream at people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so our buzzer went off but no one is downstairs...time to lock the doors and all windows and be terrified]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just walked into Chloe's room and asked her to read some Burns poetry as standard on Burns Night]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm calm, I can remain calm and go back to studying climate change and all my lovely geography stuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I watch Fresh Prince to calm down and escape from the world for a bit. And then Donald Trump is a guest star and there goes any peace I had.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've done literally no work since getting back like an hour and a half ago I've just annoyed people what is life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm an awful human being, I am aware. But it's still really funny because now I know the songs are stuck in her head]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of my favourite forms of amusement is just sending Bronte clips of Oompa Loompa's singing because it makes her rage so much it's great]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somedays I really want to explain to people a different opinion, but I know they won't listen and it's so frustrating]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter really is one of the most negative places at times...:/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cold cold cold cold cold cold cold. Edinburgh, you're cold.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish I didn't feel so awkward cooking dinner with other people who aren't in my flat in my kitchen...always think they're judging me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I should just learn to not watch the kids react to stuff I know on the Fine Bros channel because I just get upset and feel old]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeling so low, but virgin just told me it's 12 days til I see Mum again so I'm psyched]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I also realise my friends from high school would probably be surprised at how excited I am for Arctic Monkeys props night, how times change]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A moment to mourn my Night Owl Eyeliner, you have been incredible. Now time to get my next one from the cupboard because I got sent one &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean, you'll also find out you want to do a degree that'll help you save the world, so you know, we had a bit of a big turnaround]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...and there'll come a day when you realise that even though that was your darkest hour, it allowed you to find a much brighter future.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...you will learn you are better than the people who drag you down, and you will keep running for your goals and smashing them every time...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...you'll hate your mum and what you look like and detest the world for what it's done to you. But, 13 year old me, it gets better...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...you are about to enter the toughest point of your life it will be grim, and you will feel darker than you ever have before...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Realising that I probably wouldn't want to tell 15 year old me anything, but I do have a message for 13 year old me...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're going to find people who actually do care, even if it's not in the town you come from. You are strong. #WhatIWouldTellA15YearOldMe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean I have gotten out of bed to make tea...that counts as being productive right? Can't believe it's back to uni Monday &lt;/3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's cold, it's cold, it's cold]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rosie and Christie just having me in hysterics I love this holiday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, I still can't handle goodbyes, I feel we just need to admit I'm 20, I'm probably always going to cry at them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had the best day with my crazy mum https://t.co/pdlKVDFHEP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brendonburieto "it's better than echo falls" professional wine taster right there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just introduced mum to the 'Fresh Prince of Bel-Air' and she loves it see my choice is amazing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's been meowing for me, my little kitten (although he's a large cat now) â¤ https://t.co/fnbAjbaN6g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want my cat already ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mum's saying the train journey is all a big adventure and I'm here like I've taken this 4 times in 2 weeks it's just dull not exciting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To think this time in a week I'll be in Copenhagen...ahhhhh!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never clicked on a video so fast, the lyrics are incredible &lt;3 #TheScriptUnite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's -7 outside and I just get an email from forever 21 talking about swimwear previews- no thanks I don't want to die from the cold]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My new dentist is lovely, so happy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a new dentist, let's hope I don't end up freaked out again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hahahaha time for the dentist who I don't trust hahahaha fun times]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LizzieWilliams8 dont be so modest, you know youre the best]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stay positive Smallwood, stay positive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only drama I want is the drama in my sims games and the books I read, thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can people crave drama like literally all I want in life is some bloody peace and quiet stop with needing drama just relax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much needs to be done to make sure we don't destroy this planet, why don't people realise this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading the news and realising one of my big fears for 2017 is Trump dismantling all the work that's gone into combating climate change]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vicar of Dibley ended 1st January 2007...ten years ago. I'm old. So old.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tristan in Vicar of Dibley is Peter Capaldi, why does no one else realise this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everytime we watch the Christmas lunch incidient in the Vicar of Dibley, I have to convince Mum it is Peter Capaldi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two hours to go ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amelie_elyse come to Edinburgh I will teach you the way of alcohol and dresses]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kay pokemon moon, time for you to save me...3 hours to go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This train is hurting me. Not because the train is awful, its nice. But my hangover is awful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone in my flat is so drunk, I mean I'm drunk too but this is ridiculous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amelie_elyse HAPPY NEw YEAR YOU BEAUTY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[happy new year guys have a good one xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HAPPY NEW YEAR YOU BEAUTIES I LOVE YOU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is my party, so why do I get the feeling I'm going to completely hate every second of it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still can't get over that; never had someone refuse to move before]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sorry but the reservations do apply I need to charge my phone time to ask them to move or battle this out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People on the train refusing to move even though others have reserved those seats. Twats.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have my latte and panini all is well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the train driver tells us to move further into the carriage at university I'm gonna scream]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah, you have to love it when the London Midland train feels like the tube at 9am...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My suitcase is packed and consists of three things: makeup, going out clothes and pjs. My kinda weekend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@QDtalksjunk I NEED TO KNOW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every few minutes my brother talks about stuff that happens later in season 6 like shut up and wait 3 hours we'll get to that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I drink and I know things" - Tyrion is still the best thing about GoT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Some people without brains do an awful lot of talking" - still one of my favourite quotes from this film]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We got to the DVD title screen and he left, new record]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally defying my brother and watching Wizard of Oz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So many animals at the brink of extinction :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fact that cheetah numbers are crashing just about breaks my heart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas world, it's wine time for my family now! https://t.co/J5RIxKmDYI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As soon as I'm back home I just enter a perpetually hungry state...FEED ME]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy cat ðŸ˜ https://t.co/nNjWUMTgWR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MadeULookbyLex  thank you so much for the day 12 box, it's so incredible to get just before Christmas ðŸ˜„ðŸ’•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT'S ARRIVED!! https://t.co/4guzn6jWjl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy to be home with my mad hatter mother https://t.co/3zjQAJNdbd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarynCanFly you can never have too much pizza]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FREEDOM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kay Smallwood, you can do this. One more exam and then after that you can collapse and not move until you need to pack. You got this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please be a nice paper tomorrow please be a nice paper tomorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amelie_elyse Thank you &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe I'm just really run down...revision is stressful. I think I just need a break. One day left.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the plus side this time in 48 hours I'll be home with my cat ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ https://t.co/dLuaZhqsuA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had a nap. Day before exam and I'm napping. Dying of the plague is great for stress! Not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClarkThea Thank you!! I want to go home so bad, just one exam left]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClarkThea so much worse today, definitely think I have the flu ðŸ’” any other pieces of advice? X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh Smallwood you sure know how to pick 'em]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Um since when was Wychaven considered the third best district in the UK? Okay, it's pretty. Still got out of there as fast as I could]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So bored of proxies...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two days left of revision, I can do this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My christmas queen @brendonburieto https://t.co/9xNHoNJXHQ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>