<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@mathie_tremas I can never remember the rule - is it always pigs before fish?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonCT @TweedySean Gone an age ago, its novelty tee-shirts now ghosts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shinyford @bigfinish Correct answer! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graceless title sequence by clever Tom Saunders. https://t.co/NRndNrVf2g MY NAME IN BIG LETTERS. @bigfinish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ctokelly Too bloody right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ctokelly An episode of Buffy the Vampire Slayer has a snot creature from outer space, so there is a precedent in science.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ctokelly But sir, in what medium were the weeing fish suspended as they weed? (It is a mighty long time since we bickered in philosophy.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barnabysalton @newscientist a wee bit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NothingLane @WhoSFX ha! Excellent knowledge!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You’d never see homo sapiens behaving like this. (Care of @newscientist.) https://t.co/G6gjNP56ai]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonCT Perhaps @pauljmcgann could be the assistant to the lady Doctor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LondonConcrete @mwrightwriter @20000streets My son does not allow me to sing any more. It sounds wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidwhittam @20000streets Shocking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LondonConcrete @20000streets It's the lovely moment mid-February when I'm free of some sizeable deadlines I am living for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LondonConcrete @20000streets It has been an extremely long January.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidwhittam @20000streets Yes, but when have you been a good example of anything?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonCT @20000streets I've had at least one of those today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LondonConcrete @20000streets Right in the midst of it, but in reported speech.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grahamsleight Twitter would be much improved if it all had to be run past @20000streets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In what is surely a sign of the End of Times, steadfast sub-editor @20000streets has allowed me an exclamation mark.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WJHayesJr And the Doctor's fondness for fishing in The Androids of Tara and A Christmas Carol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philippa22 @thejimsmith I'm so sorry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thejimsmith You have clearly never worked in development.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thejimsmith Hand mines &gt; Clams &gt; Goldish on wheels &gt; Dalek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THIS IS HOW THE DALEKS STARTED https://t.co/VAccHbLt9X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@E11iotChapman Elliot, have you been seeing *other* writers?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LondonConcrete @drwhofan_194 @The_Cybermatt @thejimsmith @getfandom I hope you have nightmares.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LondonConcrete @drwhofan_194 @The_Cybermatt @thejimsmith @getfandom If you listen carefully, the Seethe are saying "Neil Corry is a poo."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amycockram my pleasure - and me too! A great convention]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“You’d think you’d get used to men yelling, but you never do,” says Call The Midwife, sadly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stuart_manning @AbnerBrowne I used to be teased at university for sounding like Worzel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stuart_manning Lord of Chaos bewitched by the weirdness of the pictures https://t.co/xyqTPEvwYN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stuart_manning @AbnerBrowne His folks were in Kings Somborne, on the road to Romsey (where I was born) and Brashfield.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Execcer The Scientific Secrets of Doctor Who.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AbnerBrowne @stuart_manning Yes, me, too. Though not nearly as traumatising as the Mara.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AbnerBrowne @stuart_manning I believe my best mate’s house can be glimpsed in some episodes - but have never dared check.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AbnerBrowne @stuart_manning It’s like The Wicker Man for kids. And filmed down the road from where I grew up. Brrr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AbnerBrowne @stuart_manning So much of it is eerie. But it’s him falling over at the end of the closing credits that cut through me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What an absolute delight is The Worzel Book by @stuart_manning - though the show till profoundly terrifies me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Execcer Hello! Yes - and I meant to say how much I like Strangeness in Space.  :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(TARDIS by @themindrobber’s dad.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fwhiffahder It can do - I tried to leave it open so it’s up to you :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fwhiffahder More to come. I’m meeting @mwrightwriter in a few weeks to discuss exactly how it might work…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@claytonhickman @WhoSFX In “The Switching”, the Master fails to steal the TARDIS but alters the interior settings to annoy the Doctor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fwhiffahder Well, that’s very kind of you! All credit to @TheLisaBowerman, @mwrightwriter and an amazing cast :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnJJohnston @jonnymorris1973 @wavenode @Andr3wSmith @nimbos Marco Polo and The Romans also bodyswerve historical evidence :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wavenode @Andr3wSmith @nimbos Particularly pleased to get a like for that from @JohnJJohnston. You see? Sometimes I listen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonnymorris1973 @wavenode @Andr3wSmith @nimbos So Pyramids of Mars is a historical?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wavenode @Andr3wSmith @nimbos Strictly speaking, they need to be set after the invention of writing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhoSFX @thejimsmith @LondonConcrete That is exactly how the Eleventh Doctor would go about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nimbos It is true. Calling the story 100,000 BC imposes that on it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thejimsmith @LondonConcrete @WhoSFX “… go to a naked foam party, in a nightclub run by the Ice Warriors.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LondonConcrete @thejimsmith @WhoSFX The with sounded more Craig.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thejimsmith @LondonConcrete @WhoSFX “So, Jim… Don’t share this with anyone else but Mike and Sara and the Valeyard…”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LondonConcrete @thejimsmith @WhoSFX Aw, imagine the radiant delight Craig would have found in that picture.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thejimsmith @WhoSFX Me, too. I bet mine is the more ridiculous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nimbos @JoeMacleish Doctor Who will sneak off to smoke some weed, and get into a rumpus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thejimsmith @WhoSFX Leaving Sara Kingdom and Mike Yates to save Earth from the New Mechanoids.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nimbos @JoeMacleish THIS IS EXCITING]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@claytonhickman @WhoSFX FACT: My first ever professionally published work of fiction explains why the TARDIS looks like that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bluebox99 @robstradling It might save your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robstradling @bluebox99 You haven’t heard my singing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdSalt @LondonConcrete @Gary_Gillatt @jonnymorris1973 Ooh! Ah. *fireworks fizzle cheaply on video*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LondonConcrete @Gary_Gillatt @jonnymorris1973 But @marekkukula may have other ideas. He’s quite good at this stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LondonConcrete @Gary_Gillatt @jonnymorris1973 lots of chemicals can produce green: boron compounds, copper sulphate (used in fireworks)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LondonConcrete @Gary_Gillatt @jonnymorris1973 well, it suggests different physical and / or chemical properties to N-space.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sshabein beats working for a living :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sshabein Filler?!? This is quality core content. You should see what other nonsense I wrote.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Six years since the publication of my finest contribution to Doctor Who Adventures. https://t.co/QWHg0bwV4X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamiraAhmedUK Then don’t do it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andychulka @RadioFreeSkaro You belong to us. You will be like us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marekkukula @ChristelDee @gossjam "Let me show you an experiment in the relative motion of bodies," he said...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChristelDee @gossjam @marekkukula I wouldn't trust my tangerines with those two.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CouncillorEd @planetmondas @CiaraJanson @LDoddington @bigfinish You can give any old toot to a cast like that and it'll sound amazing :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CouncillorEd @planetmondas @CiaraJanson @LDoddington @bigfinish Thanks, Ed! So glad you enjoyed it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rudemrlang That's nothing. My writing is atrocious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nimbos @theotherdebs Ooh! I went with some friends when it was there before, and concluded it would be better taking children :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ythos @unamccormack @EddieRobson I’m scared of her, too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@unamccormack @EddieRobson And does he obey??? I’d marry @ythos for that. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@unamccormack @EddieRobson Mr Tickle can, while still in bed, reach an arm down to the kitchen for a biscuit. He’s pretty much perfect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading this at the moment. It’s horrifically good. https://t.co/w4IK8cvo2S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamiraAhmedUK Christopher Plummer and David Warner as Shakespeare-quoting Klingons!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamiraAhmedUK I adore that film - and often use the soundtrack when writing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FernRiddell Also the War Doctor. Happy birthday Fern!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philip_ayres @TravisinaB7 Ha ha! That’s fab!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edwardrussell @bigfinish @unamccormack Literally from the sublime to the ridiculous :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamiesmart And me. The thing that dates it is now little the girl has to do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dmgutierrez “Fat bottomed dinosaurs” doesn’t fit the tune.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NothingLane @claytonhickman @JonPreddle @Andydrewz That picture quickens the beat of my old heart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nyssa1968 exactly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CameronKMcEwan Do you think he learnt this from Iguanadon - The Dinosaur With The Fat Bottom?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now this is how you grab a reader’s attention at the start of a book. https://t.co/IxtPTBysXq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamiesmart yes, massively. I love that film - and have been much teased for it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arrroberts The Spice Girls. #DunePop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StatusAzure @RadioFreeSkaro @MrsSteveMOBrien @benmorrisillo Hooray! But we are all in the shadow of the 1975 Doctor Who Monster Book :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@2cajuman2 @marekkukula @ThomJacksonWood impecable taste! Happy Christmas!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Siskoid It was an entry qualification]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’ve had freelance gigs like this. (At Charles Dickens House Museum) https://t.co/Qf5g3zl4Nz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Among the sacred relics - a window frame - at the Charles Dickens Museum. https://t.co/XhlyJOeTAH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benwoodhams Innit.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>