<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@harrismint Jesus I thought I played a lot of video games but boy I was wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like the @Dove approach to body image :) https://t.co/4gbXdyBvqG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My home girl @JCHart's new book is up for preorder - https://t.co/N0dOapjl3h. I promise not to tell you how it ends… https://t.co/UAacFdtskR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PSA to all my friends with high pressure jobs and a lack of sleep... https://t.co/1BZJU1mzzc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My home girl @JCHart is going to be here - rare opp for an IRL signature edition. https://t.co/ZDyI8h1OkE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MioneSparkle I wish I could help thru mansplaining but I got nothing. Blame the hormones in chicken..?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xkcdComic kills it with truth: https://t.co/1hHpAi477C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finished final @witchergame expack last night &amp; @CyberpunkGame isn't out for a while - time to go into cryogenic storage for a bit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When did video game trailers get this awesome? https://t.co/QqwMlXzJfE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@docjamesw fyi @TuataraBrew has expanded their line since you were last here. Just sayin'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@harrismint product place that flag, motherfuckers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New 1x2m whiteboard surface for the office. Oh, the characters that will break on this wheel. https://t.co/5iP21yBz6a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erin_ratner I think there's a statute of limitations on responding to ancient tweets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrentfromNZ at least shitting is a biological imperative of sorts :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrentfromNZ everyone loves having an opinion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Just go up and talk to them." https://t.co/N4jsVWJe8S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Frances_Duncan @JCHart that's some fifth dimension shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spend some time with baby piglets and you'll never eat bacon again. https://t.co/uteysigsof]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know what it says about me but I think I have all the things mentioned in this video in our home bar already https://t.co/ud1bJRdj5H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ready to rock: @masseffect #Andromeda pre-orders are up on the @PlayStationEU NZ marketplace https://t.co/GKbCsVdojW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adklepto depends on cost/features of unit. Also if new one does better e.g. HMDI 2.0a that you might want.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@harrismint she doesn't know you well. Not as well as us, precious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those assholes at @lifehacker dug this hole on the Internet. I fell in and haven't clawed my way out in four hours https://t.co/pTkzIXyAxd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@harrismint they watch too much Mr Robot, clearly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching Batman v Superman while doing my NY #bedrockstrength workout. This sweat pattern is not coincidence… https://t.co/An4qnUunVR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lukaszfromwelly it's hard to drink Kool Aid about washing machines.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think the sales guy @ Kitchen Things was on our level re: hatred for old Satanistic Samsung. https://t.co/atiE93HGkR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have an amazing 2017, everyone :) https://t.co/obZiVeKUAe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MioneSparkle white is the new white.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas everyone. I'm specifically looking forward to the kids' table. https://t.co/uxZr8Tqt0G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take two: I'll admit, I'm fairly pleased with how my New Rock playlist turned out. ♫ https://t.co/BkOtUBRISs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@harrismint It's as open as it can be at this end - let me try and share directly from inside Spotify. I even checked using inPrivate! FFS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beware conversational traps with the younger set over Christmas dinner. Prepare yourselves https://t.co/su0CSHL3lR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jensinkler @jvbfit https://t.co/V4iooDbyIc also the resistance band belt jump squat is sublime.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll admit, I'm fairly pleased with how my New Rock playlist turned out https://t.co/QOwUwmIRVM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love @jvbfit &amp; @jensinkler even more for introducing me to the kettlebell superband swing #newtoyforchristmas #bedrockstrength]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My wife thought my @fitbit should be more festive. https://t.co/zbLFOEKY3Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to head into town for a beer. My 3pm phone conference will become more epic as a result. https://t.co/UoQivNOcS8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My friends at @supplementsconz have an excellent stay-moving article for the Christmas calorie apocalypse https://t.co/7qc5tIO1nC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rogue One is spectacular. K-2SO for prez.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@harrismint do you have anything stronger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@harrismint that's actually a phot journal of your kitchen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Summer BBQ PSA (for those south of the equator) https://t.co/tGHeq1BjVl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrentfromNZ I don't think I have anything in Thursday PM's calendar.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisdbanks @ProWritingAid spectacular, thanks :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I purchase @ProWritingAid say for a lifetime will I be able to install it on both my desktop and laptop?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/aZIbHBs3DD this PSA brought to you from the very brink of system failure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obviously I need to build up my salmon mousse skills for the cat https://t.co/On6dgwiwZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel virtuous having just gone outside before watching this https://t.co/7mHZXIzcST]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it weird to get excited about new protein powders to try? https://t.co/pX3Lc1zziR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JCHart sing it sister ... we need to start a recovery group. Separately. In our own homes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@watchdogsgame thanks for that epic ride :) https://t.co/45yqSqfkqu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Frances_Duncan was it a white guy? Was there mansplaining?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Frances_Duncan about saving money vs one that said"we should spend the money because it'll give amazing service" 2/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Frances_Duncan that sounds like someone who doesn't know what the fuck they're talking about. Yet to see a business case that wasn't 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JCHart 515 is awesome if you're a) alone and b) not there thru failing to sleep.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MioneSparkle I now have a new name for them! #pancakeswithabs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lunch today was a waffle burger on a waffle omelette. #winning https://t.co/OgYzXzOeYy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@harrismint I thought something similar but my word started with a C.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Presented without any comment other than, "This is cool." https://t.co/YmeLMboA37]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElliottKaybooks Sing it, brother. Noise cancelling headphones are a cornerstone part of my "festive" season sanity retention strategy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jvbfit @jensinkler also sweat angel says hi https://t.co/xFuhnAzT7g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's face is brought to you by the Jefferson deadlift and my Bedrock friends @jvbfit &amp; @jensinkler. https://t.co/0rH211Mskw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What fucking sorcery is this https://t.co/GsU38vroIH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/MVY07GAmGY I can't stop clicking https://t.co/u6If7gOQn6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[House still smells of pressed cake, uh, I mean chocolate waffles. https://t.co/ixyFRn0rvU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miss__haley I have been catching up on Autobots vs Decepticons (techno vs EDM). Some v funny videos on this out there :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miss__haley I'll take what I can get. I more or less want euphoria as my brain is compressed by the tones coming through my 'phones.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would like some fresh new EDM @miss__haley what do you have on your device right now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Frances_Duncan @JCHart I get the best out of the deal! Will never understand why someone like her would sign on with a mug like me 😀]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@harrismint she had nil by mouth there ... untrusting sort]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The cat likes @watchdogsgame https://t.co/BBJ6iQ9OG8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JCHart so do I nothing gets done around here without her]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wife is sick tonight so dinner for 1: poached eggs on egg/broccoli waffles. My wife doesn't eat eggs. Embrace those… https://t.co/wLMgVNB2zd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DillingersBar may be the best new coffee place ever. I feel like I'm home, mostly because they never throw me out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stufox Nah bro they were actually pretty light, too light really - need more substance. And by "substance" I think I mean "fat."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm enjoying this supercreativity series :) https://t.co/Yls0I8PAkG https://t.co/dxrpRgv5r6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrentfromNZ I'm obviously a flower child then because I take almost none ... which is why I look like a munter in most of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@twytnotist Possibly, never.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protein chocolate waffles, take 2. Much better structure, but now has texture of fibre cement. Taste is fine. https://t.co/4AnXP4nQ8z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Practicing not looking like a cave troll in selfies. https://t.co/EoTm3MEplC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JillFit excellent you have given me a path to a staple-free head]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JillFit I have to know before I die: what magic over-ear headphones do you wear that don't come off?! I've tried stapling to my head but...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrentfromNZ @stufox 2nd batch with fibre was better ... in all ways.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoever said you can 1:1 substitute protein powder for flour in baking was a lying motherfucker. https://t.co/cKoC1FIDSh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrentfromNZ @jvbfit @jensinkler would you believe it's been trimmed: Rarotonga heat says "no" to anything over about 3mm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No idea why I'm smiling, week 2 of @jvbfit @jensinkler Bedrock Strength. Everything hurts. The face is pure tramadol https://t.co/jb0HZWHAnw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C'mon 2016 this shit has to stop. Shepherd Book was great :( https://t.co/ySOu4ptm5n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Frances_Duncan @MaccasNZ there speaks the desperation of a vanilla thickshake unrequited]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EpicFreya Varric needs his own spinoff :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jenniferblake33 @jensinkler also what is this Full Contact Landmine shit I feel terrible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EpicFreya maybe I should try the switch - it's intriguing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Working my way through Bedrock Strength by @jenniferblake33 &amp; @jensinkler - diversity by default is excellent. https://t.co/aGzLdS8ryE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EpicFreya Ah, a repeat and serial offender, I like it. I have finished it twice now, but managed to do it more or less the same twice #fail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EpicFreya how far in are you? It pretty much gets better right the way through.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JCHart "I have to go to the hospital!" Might work..?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Frances_Duncan @kristinluck @Flipboard it's probably for the white dudes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonder Woman keeps me honest about my characters, especially the other 50%. #amwriting @ScrivenerApp https://t.co/mjBmPIXCNl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MioneSparkle "empathy" is a very chic word right now. People wanna be hipsters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JCHart have you been watching The Man in the High Castle?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>