<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[A Mystery AI Just Crushed the Best Human Players at Poker via Digg https://t.co/9rnGfehcMt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your life does not get better by chance, it gets better by change. - Jim Rohn #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't wait to see the cover designs for my next novels. I always consider the cover as Page Zero.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The wonders of #space https://t.co/IpiA9ZJ6RT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Booted up in 1993, this server still runs -- but not for much longer via Digg https://t.co/8ltcQtzjSQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A review of my new Samsung curved TV: I hate it so much via Digg https://t.co/Cv7Ec1P8Sa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NASA Hosts Media Day for Colorado Study of Snow-bound Water Resources via NASA https://t.co/p8gqEzPdCC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If silence was her shield, it was also her weapon. #Hopebreaker #Fantasy #Quote https://t.co/lLeffXCcwZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The miracle is this, the more we share, the more we have. - Leonard Nimoy #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They continued this deadly dance across the battlefield, played to the music of gunfire. #Hopebreaker #War #Quote https://t.co/akXslUyeBe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla’s Battery Revolution Just Reached Critical Mass via Digg https://t.co/YtnJIo4Qjj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hackers Locked Every Room in This Hotel Until a Bitcoin Ransom Was Paid via Digg https://t.co/nFRQ2X1zmk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success is normally found in a pile of mistakes. - Tim Fargo #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Data That Turned the World Upside Down via Digg https://t.co/xn64lYPuMB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the currency had changed to sugar cubes, I might have opened a candy shop. #Hopebreaker #Steampunk #Quote https://t.co/rnLHFlyI0o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Become a Legend. Get 21 #UF and #PNR #Books for just #99c on #Nook here: https://t.co/CbrMhZgo5F | #IARTG #RT https://t.co/0zI2r6Fqxq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SpaceX Faces Challenge Over Astronaut Safety via Digg https://t.co/X2GZCc0xlK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The wonders of #space https://t.co/W2axvI5pKY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be afraid to give up the good to go for the great. - John D. Rockefeller #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lyft donates $1M to the ACLU, condemns Trump’s immigration actions via Digg https://t.co/IEG3Wu02vT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fairy tales are real. It's humanity that is quickly becoming a myth. #Skyshaker #Fairtytale #Quote https://t.co/B2xFdsX76a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mark Zuckerberg Decides He Won't Sue Hundreds of Hawaiians to Secure His Property via Digg https://t.co/tmGYI1nrQ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Change is automatic. Progress is not. - Tony Robbins #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Focusing light through frosted glass leads to new 3D display technology via Digg https://t.co/6sr24QyVh8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PCMCIA History: From Laptops to CableCards via Digg https://t.co/7BGt1rOctS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Become a Legend. Get 21 #UF and #PNR #Books for just #99c on #Kobo here: https://t.co/z5Bu9ILlNj | #IARTG #RT https://t.co/x1JqHtgRJG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turning and churning slowly, like a grim broth stirred by some sorcerer in the sky. #Skyshaker #Steampunk #Quote https://t.co/4SoUcwqP88]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there really a greater good if we sacrifice the little goods for it? #TheRoadtoRebirth #Books #Quote https://t.co/mGW3HNX4mx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join the tour for exciting games, #goodies and #giveaways to meet your #UrbanFantasy itch! https://t.co/332g6cRy6C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You never know what worse luck your bad luck has saved you from. - Cormac McCarthy #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#SciFan Magazine is celebrating our return. Come join us for games, giveaways &amp; prizes! https://t.co/AVfN7IAfqR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ounce of action can crush a ton of fear. - Tim Fargo #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Venus Through Water Drops: Now the brilliant "star" in planet Earth's evening skies, Venus is captured in this crea… https://t.co/LxwKyGC3H7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Become a Legend. Get 21 #UF and #PNR #Books for just #99c on #iBooks here: https://t.co/v8wucAIRq0 | #IARTG #RT https://t.co/B2fS73R5eD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A politician employs the Memory Magus to wipe the memories of voters in this #instafreebie story: https://t.co/9xZY4JywZu | #fantasy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple has filed a patent for some sort of vaporizer via Digg https://t.co/qOgwfymSwx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get #fantasy novel The Call of Agon for #free thanks to @instaFreebie here: https://t.co/ht6JcCbeq9  | #instafreebie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adam Savage Transforms An Old Leaf Blower Into A Legendary Ping Pong Machine Gun via Digg https://t.co/a2FJTYd7sT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t try to be original, just try to be good. — Paul Rand #quote #startup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NASA Invites Media Behind the Scenes of Volcano, Coral Reef Research via NASA https://t.co/s91KyTv8Uj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last days to get this #bestselling #boxedset for only $.99c! #fantasy #scifi #amreading #iartg #amazon https://t.co/LVifiTWFK5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rhythm of the pumps, the revving of the engine, and the fuming of the furnace. #Hopebreaker #Steampunk #Quote https://t.co/afpyFKSKyG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[KZ-ATE Hi-Fi Earphones via Digg https://t.co/dsFQGSx0iY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive: The Super Secure Presidential Phone (That Trump May Not Be Using) via Digg https://t.co/TvWHrMnekj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Click Here to Kill Everyone via Digg https://t.co/bEMLYXA2Os]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Focus on where you want to go, not on what you fear. - Anthony Robbins #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bad Wi-Fi Will Die, And Other Facts via Digg https://t.co/z1DVJtyGIf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Make America’s Robots Great Again via Digg https://t.co/yD7w28eZ9K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where the gods cowered. #Skyshaker #Fantasy #Quote https://t.co/s6m5NKdHVh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man with Bionic Penis Must Endure Two-Week Erection to Finally Use It via Digg https://t.co/iXMcQhvKBb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What It's Like to Be a Millenial In the Amazon Rainforest via Digg https://t.co/Zlnpx7Rl0V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You gotta learn some manners, boy. Here, let me teach you. #Landquaker #Manners #Quote https://t.co/TYEGsH4kgw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Goldfish Can Steer This Little Car By Swimming To Different Corners Of Its Tank via Digg https://t.co/TR3lJAkQCy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[January 1986 - Voyager 2 Flyby of Miranda via NASA https://t.co/NUOwoButP1 https://t.co/t6BjTWwL0a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every exit is an entry somewhere. - Tom Stoppard #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lawyers are being replaced by machines that read via Digg https://t.co/9Tz1AU1KhP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vanishing point: the rise of the invisible computer via Digg https://t.co/932QJATjyr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The wonders of #space https://t.co/pm4Sx2vVeO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cassinis Grand Finale Tour at Saturn : Cassini is being prepared to dive into Saturn. The robotic spacecraft that h… https://t.co/2fKpKzcYQG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the preview of #scifi #western novel Coilhunter for #free thanks to @instaFreebie here: https://t.co/yHHVW6X3IF | #instafreebie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another good #miniatures #boardgame on #Kickstarter: https://t.co/hvqCYRpnSs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NASA Remembers Its Fallen Heroes, 50th Anniversary of Apollo 1 Accident via NASA https://t.co/RxU23czH1K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Juno’s Close Look at the Little Red Spot via NASA https://t.co/k873ZGzw1j https://t.co/k07SIYL81t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The End of Terrible Wi-Fi Is Near via Digg https://t.co/O3NRfzMNvU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The horrors of history stalk us all. #Worldwaker #History #Quote https://t.co/WFK7xXiAax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[D-Wave: Scientists Line Up for World's Most Controversial Quantum Computer via Digg https://t.co/Eq120LOxW4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can normally tell how intelligent a man is by how stupid he thinks I am. - Cormac McCarthy #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The slippery slope of Bluetooth trackers via Digg https://t.co/uPtOnMkRVU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need to break them like machines. #Skyshaker #Steampunk #Quote https://t.co/A0GQP3koKI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mossberg: What’s up with Firefox, the browser that time forgot? via Digg https://t.co/4DDRuwYc6B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not what you look at that matters, it's what you see. - Henry David Thoreau #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You May Not Like Technology But It Likes You via Digg https://t.co/hFn5olme1k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What would Steve (Jobs) do? He sure wouldn't eat humble pie as the Trump era dawns. via Digg https://t.co/EBXOJ2kmpQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[M78 and Orion Dust Reflections : In the vast Orion Molecular Cloud complex, several bright blue nebulas are particu… https://t.co/iSNcqeDxBj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Take Screenshots of Anything (Even When They're Blocked) via Digg https://t.co/uqtWjHvJTw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great #steampunk #miniatures in this latest #boardgame from CMON: https://t.co/9yGmYyiDF0 | #tabletop #gaming]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dynamite is loyal to the one who lights the fuse. #Skyshaker #Action #Quote https://t.co/HkR1hc55U8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Night Shift Coming in macOS 10.12.4 via Digg https://t.co/WX615G44LO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experience NASA at Super Bowl LIVE Fan Festival in Houston via NASA https://t.co/EcxAeZ2di5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get this 21-novel #boxset of #UrbanFantasy and #PNR #books for just #99c on #Kindle: https://t.co/4vzWc9o1NQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cvr_2_Cvr I can send you a 6-chapter preview of Coilhunter. It's due in mid-April.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cvr_2_Cvr Two new series in the works. Urban fantasy series set in Ireland. And The Coilhunter Chronicles series, featuring Nox.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get #fantasy novel The Call of Agon for #free thanks to @instaFreebie here: https://t.co/ht6JcCbeq9 | #instafreebie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there any one so wise as to learn by the experience of others? - Voltaire #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Walk Around While Looking At Your Phone via Digg https://t.co/QhBCdJtaK1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get 22 #scifi &amp; #fantasy novels in the Dark Humanity #boxedset for #99cents #amreading #ebooks #steampunk https://t.co/YsB7sYWJhZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I might have to become the Devil. #Skyshaker #Books #Quote https://t.co/RNOulOxHVo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NASA Simulates Orion Spacecraft Launch Conditions for Crew via NASA https://t.co/U8JyU1ef7C https://t.co/MrSZTztGNc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the World’s Second-Biggest Start-Up in Trouble? via Digg https://t.co/SEAnPkZFbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“A book, too, can be a star, a living fire to lighten the darkness, leading out into the expanding universe.” ― Madeleine L'Engle #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How artificial intelligence can be corrupted to repress free speech via Digg https://t.co/2Y9qNcl4F6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A really obscure forgotten audio format: “Talking rubber” via Digg https://t.co/ob6ebv7GGv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The wonders of #space https://t.co/4I0M3dtBsB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Happens When You Mix Java with a 1960 IBM Mainframe via Digg https://t.co/ssRBRnpg2P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Raspberry Harvester Machine To End All Raspberry Harvester Machines via Digg https://t.co/1DgkQ6gL6f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A history of the Amiga, part 10: The downfall of Commodore via Digg https://t.co/9FyehMflpN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facial recognition systems to replace passports at Australian airports by 2020 via Digg https://t.co/UDowpvzQhT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NASA TV to Broadcast Cargo Ship Departure from Space Station via NASA https://t.co/WFlWN7Yqyi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is always room for the heart to grow broader. #TheChainsofWar #Literature #Quote https://t.co/pgDgRIAxKA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret to success is doing the stuff other people won't do &amp; doing it for a really long time. - John Jantsch #quote]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>