<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@SASRpearson081 @JustGiving we have indeed and have a bag pack booked in :) well once I send back the paperwork :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friends this is how I spend my weekends, funding is very low, volunteers r using their own money to keep it running. https://t.co/eDPbHxJd4f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I spend my weekends volunteering from10pm-4am providing firstaid and welfare on streets of Edinburgh we need pennies
https://t.co/eDPbHxJd4f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RachieBear1987 congrats Mrs Cook]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NuffieldHealth hi could I DM you to ask about memberships please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Laslo_Panaflex it's good :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vitality_UK I did this hours ago but still no reply]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vitality_UK done thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Laslo_Panaflex Pauls having people round to play games etc tomorrow for his birthday of you wanna come over]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vitality_UK @VitalityAdviser I get this message when trying to set up and sing into my account, help please :) https://t.co/Of3DhoL1K6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ninja_kate yea the guy was saying that but hey it's only an extra £10 :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ninja_kate haha yea think we are going to go ahead and get it ordered and hopefully delivered for us getting back from NYC :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ninja_kate what one did you get if you don't mind me asking? We are just here trying some now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ninja_kate hey did you get a mattress from ikea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Laslo_Panaflex don't fancy him just want him to be my best friend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hm_custserv I recently returned some items and wanted to check the status of refund.
ORDER NUMBER 
114964988]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edinhelp my grey bin appears to have only been half emptied today, please could it be emptied!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ninja_kate something up Calton Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScottTsukuru Paul left 3 for o2 as the three signal wasn't great]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SPEnergyNetwork just back from holiday and find this in my garden? This acceptable? https://t.co/wZ4mDHB4KS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edinhelp @Edinburgh_CC hi, could someone please fix this hole on Hawkhill Ave before before someone bursts a tyre! https://t.co/clu9UWVZb5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Colin_Cloud I also wanted to ask if you are able to do short shows for charity nights at all and who I would contact?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Super excited to see @Colin_Cloud show tonight at the Edinburgh festival!! Gotta love a bit of magic!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markagorman @ronabluebell haha no that's on Easter road lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Colin_Cloud couldn't make summer hall so had to secure these ones :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Colin_Cloud bought :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcstamper we are always around xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcstamper sorry to hear this hope you are all ok. Thoughts are with you all xxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davescook we are popping up soon...need any supplies from the outside world]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CitizensAdvice hi, can volunteers be unfairly dismissed and call up the charity on this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RhonaAhmed1 @weebaskets @safebase_edin @Libran_Chick @EdinSafezone what a lovely tweet from someone in the management team]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donaldnurse999 @EdinSafezone interesting how some troll hadn't been blocked by them though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donaldnurse999 @EdinSafezone me too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcstamper I'm more concerned how you would even know that lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@weebaskets @donaldnurse999 @Rpearson081 @forthone @WeAreSTV @Ed @EdinSafezone wow classy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ninja_kate yea pretty much they sell them normally in the glass juice bottles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ninja_kate take a bottle of it down with you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well hello London! https://t.co/qrI4wUSl3H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VirginExp hi. I received a voucher in the post for an experience but I have just over house and lost the voucher, are you able to re send?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Footgolfs first victim! https://t.co/tSWVWlSAFv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OVOEnergy ok. I had to put it into emergency credit as I didn't have the time to top it up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OVOEnergy hi I recently switched to u and got new card for gas. I topped it up and put it in the meter but it says card not recognised...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Natasia_Aitken royal high teacher Robert Watson was on Ninja Warrior today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@O2AcademyGgow I am accompanying people to BFS tonight with disabilities, are we able to come stand inside before doors open?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We at https://t.co/n5hFCNLhWb are currently recruiting support workers :) many hours going get in touch if you fancy some hours :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@easyhotels thanks i have sent along]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@easyhotels 3 amounts for my stay seem to have been taken from my bank account by easy hotel can I speak to someone ASAP to rectify this?!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@easyhotels hi I have booked a London hotel but after reading reviews about hot rooms I'd like change one with a window. How can I do this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@east_team @edinhelp due to the amount of dog walkers who use this park I feel for safety it would b gd to use who can I talk to about this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@east_team @edinhelp as there are lights there could you not just reconnect them as this would save them being their ant not used]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edinhelp hi there is there any update on this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edinhelp thankyou is there a case number so I can chase up at all?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edinhelp thanks so much]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edinhelp ok no problem, will it be a reply from you guys tomorrow or another provider?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edinhelp yea it is the walk way that goes round the loch inside Lochend park. There are lights there but are not turned on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edinhelp any chance of a update on this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So....new year new hair colour :) https://t.co/TGhJSFOFBn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Natasia_Aitken it's a living miracle that they ate curry!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edinhelp hi there are lights in lochend park but they are not on in the evening could you advise why? Dog walkers would appreciate light :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Natasia_Aitken I love this!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edinhelp done thanks :) also we are struggling with the grey bin is there an option to get a bigger one at all?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edinhelp thankyou very much for your help :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edinhelp there isn't a brown bin option there :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edinhelp hi. Someone has half inched my brown bin so wondered if I could get a new one?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ness_Edinburgh hi yes I can email. It was bought from the ocean terminal sore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ness_Edinburgh hi I received an item for Xmas and don't have the receipt but would like to return it, tags still on, is this possible?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ness_Clothing hi is this Twitter used at all?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcstamper @Paulvfinch hope u guys and the kids enjoyed their gifts X X happy Xmas X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tngrewatch what's up X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JandTPodcast oooo what is it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy family X @marcstamper https://t.co/36Pc7eJYQn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcstamper I'm ok with that lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcstamper @kirstystamper both my friend both!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mhansen0207 @marcstamper I'm sure we can all Skype u xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mega looking forward to seeing @marcstamper and @kirstystamper https://t.co/DBbUTejPLG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Edinburgh_CC bins here been like this for 2 weeks, I c they have put general waste in recycling but it need cleared https://t.co/aVEVrGU5gK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcstamper manager of a care company :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YHAYork hi, are you a pet friendly hostel? Emma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaffaStar I'm good been really busy at work, just bought a new house so all go lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love how some people have nothing better to do than worry about what other people are doing...how about worry about ur own life !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tanz_g who....me :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tanz_g I'm pretty sure iv done all the above.....well minus the babies but defo the wine and Queen :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maxjoseph saw this awesome trailer at the cinema in Scotland last night :) #WAYF http://t.co/osPl07VkYz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ninja_kate u up Edinburgh this weekend?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just hosted three back-to-back guests on @airbnb! Want to be next? Check out my listing. https://t.co/W7p2CTIdgV http://t.co/naJPDxWwoN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ninja_kate saw this in the shop today and thought of you! http://t.co/8R9DbHEkgw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tngrewatch @marcstamper let me know if and when u buy tickets, we might come same time!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcstamper :( think ull make.it up this end of the woods at all this year?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Edinburgh_CC Clean up on Albert Street any time soon? http://t.co/GrgNswL6zk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Colin_Cloud loved the show, panicked when I couldn't unstick my hands thanks for helping!! http://t.co/pqVg353Ike]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdinSafezone cool. Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdinSafezone cool, think I might have some people that can help :) is there a date?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdinSafezone is it for a raffle or auction kind of thing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdinSafezone #coffee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's me home from working away the last week and in catching 40winks beofre heading out to volunteer with @EdinSafezone  tonight :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Laslo_Panaflex go see the tree house :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdinSouthPolice @EdinburghPolice especially on Easter road]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money or morals that is the debate of today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahhhh wish some people would just get a grip!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gamewank @Laslo_Panaflex I Remeber the day at mirage when you played the me the new intro for gamewank before it was officially used!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>