<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Exploring compositions for my next large painting :) https://t.co/1vGebMmNZ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Makin some Jon Shaw art with some Jon Shaw markers :) https://t.co/dYngjJbwcp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brightening up colour layers and starting to add the small brush details. This stage is great for a very chill... https://t.co/W6oaNTs9Po]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new studio is big!! Just had some sweet 60" panels delivered by my mates in  1000 Parker. Planning out next... https://t.co/ybPPLDhZti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adding in that second layer of ink lines. Defining bricks, adding randomness and fun additions - name of the game... https://t.co/hb58cgIuVY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital sketch exploring various graphical elements and different places. The studio at 1000 parker meets... https://t.co/OzBn9vM5Nh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah yeas, laying down a colourful underpainting on all those lines :) #art #painting #drawing #city #urban... https://t.co/SMnft3HUmG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I spent the past 11 days in Ontario and discovered/photographed some amazing urban landscapes/decay in St.... https://t.co/kFeSGlnGgi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I spent the last 11 days in my home town in Ontario and while there I scoped out some AMAZING urban... https://t.co/XJiu8APuQO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me and my self portrait from art school days. Circa 2006. Personally I think I've improved a LOT https://t.co/2vUQXil3CZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very cool trash found in St. Catharines, ON. I'm always hunting, documenting the beauty of urban artifacts https://t.co/9IwW7QbpcQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With a final coat of varnish, "Honey Circuit" is off to its new home :) And I'M off to Ontario for 11 days :)... https://t.co/BGguTYbFEz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Progress, progress.. #art #drawing #artstudio #contemporaryart #city #cityscape #urbandecay #urban #line #lineart... https://t.co/egDJK2xGCw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New paintings, new studio, new year. Always begins with some basic lines and colour washes! The meditative... https://t.co/hPFmT2Dgv6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Step one in my next painting. I compose digital mock ups based on photo shoots in specific locales. Here this... https://t.co/RL3Lxkwrfc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starting 2017 off with some bright and colorful marker painting in a cozy West End coffee shop! The little joys... https://t.co/H97GqA7Z05]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Since it's NYE I will thank everyone who supported my art career this year through coming to shows, buying my... https://t.co/jEpUGs2qi5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Classic pic of me and Carrie fisher with the painting I made of her as Boushh from Return of the Jedi...she... https://t.co/6Hp4yLBo7c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Installation shot of four Jon Shaw prints framed and hung, looks pretty awesome! Thanks Chris for sharing! #art... https://t.co/PxYEdVb3zT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure what it is but it's certainly a lot of fun!! #artbugs #painting #vancouverartist #abstractpainting https://t.co/uVqbuYBdr8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's so empty!! So long art studio no. 4, moving into no. 5 (orange!?) #art #artstudio #vancouverartist #1000parker https://t.co/d0oMGzveZI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't believe it's done! Four days of @makeitshow and three overall shows in the past month. And to wrap up the... https://t.co/mo6hyh1VZS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After 10 hours of exhibiting @makeitshow , the ginger is tired and ready for Jim Beam. Show hours tomorrow:... https://t.co/hasgpbMVVK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another new 8x8 painting of beautiful BC landscape! If you are interested in it, I'll have it handy in my back... https://t.co/D7ldVJ8rOC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My last show of the year, Make It, starts on Thursday! This is an amazing place to get holiday gifts for special... https://t.co/JlzkhEhEA6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Working on new painting of a colourful and whimsical arbutus tree :) available at @makeitshow starting Dec 8 :)... https://t.co/zNemSPSlbe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Newest 8x8 landscape finished to be offered for sale at @makeitshow starting December 8 at the PNE, Vancouver.... https://t.co/VqO0PRTvRJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starting work on new batch of small, original landscape pieces to show/sell at @makeitshow starting December 8! I... https://t.co/5ntfrSH9NN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huge thanks and admiration and appreciation to everyone who came out to the Culture Crawl this year! I've just... https://t.co/kF1onTsexF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well check that out! My latest delivery of custom Lumocolor markers from @staedtlermars @staedtlernorthamerica... https://t.co/xMGySR8U7u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's a wrap!! Another AMAZING year of the @culturecrawl at studio 230 in the Mergatroid Building...I love this... https://t.co/3ClgetF9UR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three paintings sold in two hours yesterday! The big pieces are going fast down in the studio at the... https://t.co/SjVLQlvY20]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That moment when you arrive 30 minutes before the @culturecrawl opens and there's already five blocks full of... https://t.co/uBHPrPRTQT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day two of @culturecrawl at our studio!! Open tonight, 5-10pm at 975 Vernon drive (the Mergatroid Building). Day... https://t.co/dQqFU06IKS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out my ad for @culturecrawl in the @georgiastraight !! #art #vancouver #culturecrawl #eastvan... https://t.co/tgbuPxFtPV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Show time!! Ready to go. Culture Crawl starts in 40 minutes :) https://t.co/cGmHCt75cD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Setting up for the opening night of the @culturecrawl tomorrow! More to do but it's looking mighty fine in here... https://t.co/uwraBZpd0e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's that time again! The 20th East Side Culture Crawl begins tomorrow!! This is my favourite show and event... https://t.co/CCHy4yPh9d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The random draw has been made!! The winner of this original painting from Fan Expo is @kayleighley !!!! Let's... https://t.co/Rn26KGefc2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spent an amazing weekend at @fanexpocanada here in Vancouver, exhibiting my R2 painting and promoting the crap... https://t.co/bFYU10SsoJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day one of three at the Vancouver Convention Center was friggen PACKED!! Much love to so many people who greeted... https://t.co/tpriiH3FM4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All set and vending at @fanexpocanada at the Vancouver convention center! Here all weekend, come say hi if you... https://t.co/qdjwOQH2s3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Setting up at the convention center for @fanexpocanada ! Not even done unloading and I've already sold six... https://t.co/XSez6042m5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making marks during tonight's class, I'm starting to think that I should really turn these small studies into... https://t.co/NlxswPB5YR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fan expo is this weekend and I'm looking forward to showing a large painting and more than anything just having a... https://t.co/aRIzYDCg4s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next weekend I'm exhibiting my large r2d2 painting and selling prints at @fanexpocanada at the Vancouver... https://t.co/o7aZy1EHdh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlistairCalder the post is on my art page you can view it there: https://t.co/Tkk0Zzj3KJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlistairCalder try again? Works for me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I was in art school, we didn't learn to use digital media, as essential as it is. If you are interested in... https://t.co/ia1mqsPTA8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brainstorming my next move. What's happening here? Half of me knows, half hasn't a clue. Journey = discovery!!... https://t.co/9klQrq6TB1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm excited to start integrating these watercolour paper cutouts into some paintings. I often draw and paint... https://t.co/ulnMCPaHxr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was away in #pemberton this weekend relaxing and sketching ideas for. Ew art projects. Everywhere I go I study... https://t.co/MSKjyweJIH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's almost time! In just a few weeks is my favourite art event of the year!! At the @culturecrawl you get to see... https://t.co/ZHurH6I8CG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Throwback photo to my May the Sith art show :) What a great night! I'm now looking forward to the @culturecrawl ,... https://t.co/Qau7Oy4PZw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had an amazing first class with new students! Wednesday nights have become such a joy at the studio when I get to... https://t.co/tiETXxOeCO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a big fan of drawing my urban surroundings. Here's some Saturday sketching facing yaletown from south side of... https://t.co/vNcUYh8zXC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight was the end of the second 4-week batch of teaching at my downtown studio! These fine lads and lasses... https://t.co/TCelJuqjE5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arbutus tree - to be painted ASAP...sweet memories of the Gulf Islands :) https://t.co/QWSCGy13Rv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey friends! I'm presenting with two other buddies this Thursday at the Beaumont on our artistic practices, and... https://t.co/Uk0hNja354]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some newer work and one spyin' redhead https://t.co/HVrklnodL5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My #pokearthunt continues in Toronto this week.

This painting will be planted around 5:30pm tomorrow at... https://t.co/SHx1UH0UyT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing - found my work hanging in one of the studios I visited this weekend during the Gabriola Thanksgiving... https://t.co/Kxh3HK1eSt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time for another couple of 8x8 landscapes. It's really interesting to go from a 5 foot piece, to less then a... https://t.co/9nfK9ywPO4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/9gnvJIugVY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Detail areas, abstract marks mixing with tight lines https://t.co/KgcLSpymKw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This painting is taking good shape here in the Mergatroid Studio :) https://t.co/8CwPhn1eNh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Left to dry flat overnight, lots of work to be had today :) https://t.co/hf9RQC1JrJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello friends! My second teaching course starts TONIGHT! The first batch was amazing :)

I have a last-minute... https://t.co/HZc2vCmGaK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[48x60 underpainting. Not bad for a day's work ;) https://t.co/Zi529MAPcl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Various paintings at various levels of completion! https://t.co/C1ey8U5gPQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This painting is now finished! I really like the 48x48 scale of it. I also really like the several new techniques... https://t.co/YO1la6694a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New mockup for my new painting, starting tomorrow. It will be the biggest one yet, at 4x5 foot! I'm really... https://t.co/qEgmA77LyO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adding all the final details! It's come together really well and really quickly! I'm super excited about this new... https://t.co/xco6D5Bpev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Monday! Adding details over here in the studio. Hope you have a good day! https://t.co/ZxVg2lSTMy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First layer. This piece is larger then I have worked on for my cityscapes so it is VERY exciting (48x48). Also,... https://t.co/jpZWqgwZzO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Final documentation shot of my latest painting, "Mermaid Hustle"! 36" x 36", lots of fun hidden details!! Def one... https://t.co/3g3ABXn8QI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CLASSES ARE FILLING UP FAST!

The first two 4-week courses taught out of my studio are full, and the third set... https://t.co/GF61Ohf6Jp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Class 3 of 4 wrapped up! Thanks to my students for letting me take this working photo in the studio tonight! We... https://t.co/AMSbj4Ui0v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adding small details..picking out little paint globules and turning them into sectioned bits. Like an art puzzle :) https://t.co/VKDFmTd0Nk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frog Fridays! Happy Saturday everyone! I had some amazing inspiration last night at The Gam and KIMOTO GALLERY... https://t.co/RwM7pihZQ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the digital mock-up for my next painting. Based on photographs my friend and I took in the West End. I... https://t.co/TmSeKD6Ybo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I finished my newest cityscape painting! It is nicely detailed and full of fun bits! Nice sunny day, new art.... https://t.co/A88NJwmiNE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Wednesday everyone! I drew these frogs yesterday and am starting to paint them today...until it's time to... https://t.co/Bhb2IG2lpM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a Slowpoke for the #pokearthunt !! It will be placed somewhere in Vancouver tomorrow for you to find.... https://t.co/MX7CvjGUUQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm spending my labour day finishing up this Vancouver-inspired piece. It's almost done and looking really great!... https://t.co/WbVVWdjUGU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Working on several new Pokemon pieces for my #PokeArtHunt project! Off to the beach now to finish the bottom... https://t.co/AKurf0GrcM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anybody interested in taking art classes with me at my studio?? The current four week batch is full, and the... https://t.co/DC0a0mky7Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shipping one of my recent large alleyway pieces to its new owner in Toronto. It's always bittersweet to see the... https://t.co/OmLpKtpCS4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Studio is set up for my first class tonight! This four week course filled up fast! The second batch of classes,... https://t.co/W9uqKuV6ZJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeling good and smiley after completing this orca whale painting, now hanging on my studio wall :) :) https://t.co/7rix3WLAKn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Detail work with my custom drawing markers :) my friends at STAEDTLER have been very supportive of my art career... https://t.co/uWkxuGeds9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All finished the ink/drawing layer! Time to get to work painting. Goal is to complete it by Friday :) I feel like... https://t.co/ofthxkBsVI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Cubone painting is stashed and waiting for a new home in Squamish. Details to find it on Instagram: #pokearthunt https://t.co/MB5JbgczXd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBC @gillybeanmartin @CBCNews may I stash one in the CBC building to be found next week?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will be planting this #cubone before dinner time today but headsup it will require a bit of travel! #pokearthunt https://t.co/CmQupvEycW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I finished this painting about three weeks ago and never actually posted the final
Image! How silly of me :p 󾆾 https://t.co/gsUEUTB1Db]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My alleyscapes always start with a digital composition based on photographs that I take in and around Vancouver.... https://t.co/plGpmLFNns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Planting this Lapras painting today at 6pm. Wherabouts to be posted on my instagram: @jonnieredbeard #PokeArtHunt https://t.co/PzRmlH8qwe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello friends! My first 4-week teaching course starts next week!

The course is 4 weeks long, Wednesdays from... https://t.co/WA6uCFdHhS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Newly finished painting! 30" x 30", and rather experimental with a few new techniques.

I pushed myself into... https://t.co/oB0FDhB7FV]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>