<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes I wake up every day dreading what horrible thing T is going to do that day. Or what awful thing he did/said while I was asleep.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KThomasDC @NickBaumann and his wife, I mean daughter, went with him why??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ddale8 can someone ask him how he can sleep at night?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasoninthehouse trying to distract us from your unwillingness to do your job won't work. You will be voted out soon enough. #hypocrite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TechDaddy @BrianTheLady @POTUS but I thought he knew all the things and had everything figured out because he's so amazing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ErikViker @ddale8 @Reddy thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ddale8 @Reddy is this even legal? Are these NDAs subject to the FOIA?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcuban @deniseoryan @POTUS no way, Mark. You're delusional if you think that. There is absolutely no evidence he will change.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yashar he's a delusional, narcissistic psychopath.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaroleRadziwill if you follow him, you'll know the former Mexican president has been outspoken about Trump for a while. #truth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I keep thinking it can't get worse. Yet, it does. He's a worthless POS. https://t.co/ADuSj3ulFd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisCuomo @washingtonpost I think you mean "another lie."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ACLU @chrissyteigen YES. This would be fabulous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lisarinna umm, I think Kim R. uses them on a daily basis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ddale8 how many times has he said "the president's been clear about" xyz?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasoninthehouse @GHughes51 @utahsenate @UtahSenateGOP let's hope their first order of business is getting rid of you. #hypocrite #unethical]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimsciutto #FactCheckTrump #FactCheck #alternativefacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@voxdotcom Instead of talking for five minutes, he could have just told us Trump has a small d*ck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@repjohnlewis you are amazing. You are a godsend. You are needed. Thank you, thank you, thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justinhendrix this is my fave https://t.co/UsCdkSgFGQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BFriedmanDC @jaketapper @MountRainierNPS and so it begins.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VanJones68 @realDonaldTrump @dozerpower23 Van, please don't say that. I need some hope today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasoninthehouse you, the supposed ethics guy, actually posted this? Totally unethical. You are a disgrace to our country. #hypocriticalPOS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ezlusztig @jasoninthehouse @thehill he is disgusting. I wish I could vote him out of office. #fulltimehypocrisy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes why would he? It seems no one with any authority is going to do anything about it if he doesn't. We're screwed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisCuomo @tommyxtopher @JohnKingCNN @Shareblue well his campaign undermined the democratic process. Not much to respect about that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasoninthehouse let's hope they vote you out soon! Your hypocrisy is disgusting. #noethics #doublestandard #EmolumentsClause]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ezlusztig this makes me feel so hopeless as an ordinary citizen in a state where my senators and reps are republicans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tedcruz you're a sellout with no morals. I'm embarrassed you're my senator.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomcolicchio @sssssss12332144 you're awesome for so many reasons. This is just one of the many.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuddLegum thank you for all of this. You wrote there "was" an investigation. Does that mean it's over? Or is it ongoing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost disagree totally. I fear we'll end up in war with another country because he's a moron who can't keep his mouth shut.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes @PaulBlu isn't this insider trading? And isn't that illegal?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasoninthehouse @FoxNews buddy, you might think twice before talking about hypocrisy. Pot, meet kettle. You are a disgrace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomcolicchio @Parker9_ she terrifies me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deray this was painful to watch. How is she even an option???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richardwakile and unfollow now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid yeah well you're not a narcissistic, delusional asshole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AC360 @GloriaBorger @CNN no way. I refuse to normalize their corruption. Being pretty and using complete sentences doesn't make her better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@armandodkos @deejay90192 @dailykos but will anyone with the power to enforce it actually do something about it??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justinhendrix can he ever speak in complete sentences?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisCuomo he's made a mockery of our govt, the presidency, IC, &amp; his fellow citizens - acts like an entitled jerk. I can't respect that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mindyfinn @jasoninthehouse @politico because he is a hypocritical person with no morals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KFILE @politico @jasoninthehouse Jason you are a despicable human being and should be ashamed. I hope you're never re-elected.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomcolicchio @RepTimRyan Thank you both for speaking up and advocating for equal rights.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidCornDC @MotherJones are we surprised? This guy is a narcissist who thinks he can literally get away with murder. He may not be wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johniadarola @cenkuygur I'm horrified and I'm just a regular American citizen. #terrified #trumppressconference]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He is a disgusting, delusional, narcissist. I have never hated anyone in my life until now. #resist #treason… https://t.co/8dWVB5XzNA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're screwed. #TrumpPressConference #resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Signed! Contacted my senators! #stopsessions https://t.co/drLFUDq3Vt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#demforce #NoEthicsNoHearing https://t.co/VOOhE02F1j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuddLegum why isn't this treason?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesFallows @Martina @Acosta @jasoninthehouse Chaffetz, you going to do anything about this? Or are you that much of a hypocritical wussy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pondicheri @JuanHtheGreat love this man!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GOPoversight @jasoninthehouse get a grip. Do your job. Investigate Trump. He is a walking conflict of interest yet you don't seem to care.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bakari_Sellers impossible to translate unless you speak the Moron language. #cannotbelieveheisthenextprecedent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasoninthehouse don't you have bigger problems to worry about or do you not care about Trump's conflicts? #hypocrite #priorities]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnKwue @rol3c @jasoninthehouse couldn't have said it any better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasoninthehouse isn't this your M.O.? Please do your job and investigate PEOTUS' conflicts and Russia meddling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump can you please stop this and pretend you're presidential? I know that would be unprecedented for you, but give it a try.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lisahochstein you're joking, right? Try educating URself on the matter. And you might discover that he's still on the job even in Hawaii.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasoninthehouse We're waiting for you to do your job and investigate his "unpresidented" conflicts of interest... like you said you'd do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomcolicchio @TheYoungTurks @YouTube well we all know risottos can be terrifying. Priorities, people!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VanJones68 @KellyRipa this is the only way I'll watch this show! Pick Van as your permanent co-host, please!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abigailspencer you were outstanding in every episode of @Rectify. Between this, @Suits_USA, and @NBCTimeless, you are top notch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rectify series finale was absolutely beautiful. I am devastated this series is over.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vika7 love decorating for Christmas! https://t.co/8TmkS9U6dG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasoninthehouse when are you going to investigate PEOTUS for his conflicts? Stop being a hypocrite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasoninthehouse it is your duty AND obligation to investigate PEOTUS' finances for potential conflicts of interests.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brianstelter @CNN why not focus on his continued involvement in his businesses and his children's involvement on his team? Real issues!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@candacecbure @TheView stop normalizing white supremacy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrissieEvert this is not the least bit surprising.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CharlesMBlow had to try to explain this to my 3-year-old twins through tears today. #devastated]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bakari_Sellers words of wisdom, please? I'm freaking out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@briankoppelman I'm speechless and devastated for the future of our country. I am in tears.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bethenny how much wine is inappropriate to survive this tonight?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomcolicchio @JoyAnnReid I stopped counting. Counting my tears would be easier at this point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomcolicchio whether you talk about the future of our country or TC, I'm a fan and like your commentary. Haters can piss off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kurteichenwald I live in Texas and am pretty scared. I plan to stay home with my little kids that day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcuban can you help get the @ApprenticeNBC tapes released? https://t.co/vvX8uIyQGM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just told @nbcwashington who I think is winning. Cast your vote now! #Debates #NBC4DC https://t.co/0POEtZnHwg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomcolicchio pretty please NEVER stop tweeting about whatever you want!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ananavarro why is no one discussing his upcoming child rape case?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuddLegum why is no one discussing his upcoming child rape case???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuddLegum thoughts on this? https://t.co/g9ncp6Rez7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brianstelter thoughts on this? https://t.co/g9ncp6Rez7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bakari_Sellers thoughts on this? https://t.co/g9ncp6Rez7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuddLegum @thinkprogress and this surprises you??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bakari_Sellers how do you keep a straight face talking to Trump's misinformed and ridiculous surrogates with @donlemon?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bakari_Sellers @Kaepernick7 @realDonaldTrump maybe a bulletproof bodysuit would be wise underneath your clothes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomcolicchio @KellieAnn0214 @ChefAction You can register to vote in person. Find ur local office here: https://t.co/GlyFeoRGju]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuddLegum seriously?? He let Trump talk over him and let Trump repeatedly interrupt Clinton. He did almost no moderating.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@halfadams how is anyone NOT with her. He's a disastrous bully who knows nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smerconish are you serious? He let Trump interrupt her constantly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CharlesMBlow I hope the media and everyone doing post-debate analysis don't allow him to get away with this. Call him out on his BS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DebraMessing @AlbertBrooks he's trying not to vomit from the smell of his own bullshit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CharlesMBlow I thought the same thing!!! I think they did endorse him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pattonoswalt @The_RobertEvans he's trying not to vomit from the smell of his own bullshit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Andy he's trying not to throw up from the smell of his own bullshit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CharlesMBlow Lester needs to grow some balls. He's letting Trump walk all over him.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>