<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["I voted leave because I go to the supermarket and a banana is straight." 

#bbcqt https://t.co/pH7ZjCfxEg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ScotLab would rather the budget failed and see another election. Truth is another H'rood election would bankrupt them. All bluster &amp; hot air]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fracking could boost petrochemical industry, say SNP ministers

https://t.co/pGPdCr99mX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YvMcL Feel free to. But, despite what it says on my profile photo, don't use lard. Unless you're using it for swimming off Ayr beach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell the Scottish Government to #KeepItInTheGround 

https://t.co/FJBFaYZZCP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bookings for Scottish Greens spr. conference are open: https://t.co/MlK0bAmKl2 

Forgotten your Green ID? Contact info@scottishgreens.org.uk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SimonFRCox @Stuart_McDonald @richardshughes @BritCits I echo this sentiment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't normally sign petitions but...

https://t.co/YCnxSYouIt

Prevent Donald Trump from making a State Visit to the United Kingdom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Green Party T-shirts featuring Spirit of Indy design by Stewart Bremner, are only £6.75 this weekend!… https://t.co/M0SfW8zvbD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Edinburgh housing: Family of four forced to live in one room

https://t.co/PfBwSlW9Io …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@green_scotland I like the sound of biodiversity hotpots!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[25% off Green Party t-shirts and lots of other cracking deals too!

https://t.co/QGid62I6qn https://t.co/HzdxrZ9p1T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@F_Psychiatrist @scotgp No. Just add a note to order saying "hoodie only"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Special offer of the week: A copy of Caroline Lucas's Honourable Friends worth £12 FREE with every hoodie ordered!… https://t.co/JmlhQ2McfA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@freedomforalba That's the England &amp; Wales Green Party.  Scottish Green Party:  https://t.co/1NBCnblLVc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep warm this winter.  Green Party 'green hoodies' are on special offer at only £15 at the moment!… https://t.co/67mfH387Aj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indyref2 can be won with a radical agenda say Greens

https://t.co/T6mLpOX3ij]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm all for free movement.  I believe you should leave Labour and join the Greens 😀

https://t.co/1NBCnblLVc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stewart Bremner's Early Days of a Better Nation &amp; Scots Sayings calendars are only £4.50 each!… https://t.co/4Jmy8sVsPu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stewart Bremner's Early Days of a Better Nation &amp; Scots Sayings calendars are only £4.50 each!

https://t.co/QGid62I6qn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stewart Bremner 2017 calendars HALF PRICE at only £4.50 each!

https://t.co/QGid62I6qn https://t.co/XIcxk1wFCD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great substitution!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's still time to order your 2017 Stewart Bremner calendars.

https://t.co/QGid62I6qn https://t.co/jETdg6F6d1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What better way to start 2017 than by reading The Early Days of a Better Nation? (foreword by Lesley Riddoch)… https://t.co/QDWV1btevM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's the last chance to order Stewart Bremner calendars if you want them in time for Christmas!… https://t.co/2Lpn9vJbcG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is the last day to place your merchandise orders if you want them in time for Christmas!… https://t.co/3m2jeb8hVK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas cards from only £1.75 per pack. Final orders go out tomorrow!

https://t.co/QGid62I6qn https://t.co/TKgy74rRsO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow is the last day to place your merchandise orders if you want them in time for Christmas!… https://t.co/UtqFC6HWH3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow is the last day to place your merchandise orders if you want them in time for Christmas!… https://t.co/dhn7bbQjtD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow is the last day to place your merchandise orders if you want them in time for Christmas!… https://t.co/pfSuoZ4lh7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow is the last day to place your merchandise orders if you want them in time for Christmas!… https://t.co/gYO2seq2H4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friday is the last day to place your merchandise orders if you want them in time for Christmas!… https://t.co/owVph0qDe0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friday is the last day to place your merchandise orders if you want them in time for Christmas!… https://t.co/dWvHvA04W4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chris_Freeman01 @scotgp We did have a limited stock of 2XL hoodies and t-shirts but they sold out fast. Will prob order more next year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friday is the last day to place your order if you want them in time for Christmas!

https://t.co/QGid62ZHhV https://t.co/ENTz0j23sl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This week's special offer: Only £15 for the very popular green hoodie. Offer ends this Friday so be quick!… https://t.co/DFbUXZX3lR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time's running out to order your Green Christmas cards! Prices start at only £2.50 per pack.… https://t.co/PCG6gUtZZk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bilco62 @MhairiHunter  why couldn't David resist a £3,500 Richard James suit from Savile Row?

https://t.co/gZ6LLQTneE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas cards from only £2.50 a pack
Hoodies only £15
Mugs from only £3
Calendars, books, posters too.… https://t.co/MLb19VFwiH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This week's special offer: this large Americano thermal mug is only 3 quid!

Offer ends Sunday 11th Dec 2016… https://t.co/sztz1zrR3e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas cards for sale from only £2.50 per pack. Designed by @scotgp members and printed on recycled card.… https://t.co/C8lBBCwvZX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stewart Bremner calendars and books. During the indy campaign, Stewart was the digital artist for Yes Scotland.… https://t.co/wnkUonfSSt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More than one third of SNP and Labour supporters backed Brexit, finds survey

https://t.co/cQuw6eGK7T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Scots Sayings' calandars are back in stock! Only £9.  Free P&amp;P if you buy 2 or more calendars.… https://t.co/6JBu4KafX2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep the flame of independence burning with this Early Days of a Better Nation book 

Free P&amp;P!… https://t.co/wHNaHtqPXq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas cards for sale from @scotgp 

https://t.co/QGid62I6qn https://t.co/8bRdosNQfq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brrr, it's cold outside! Keep warm with a @scotgp green hoodie. 20% off special offer extended till Friday!… https://t.co/Qmy0d3ibRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a fucking game!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Green campaigner calls for all South Lanarkshire Council debt to be written off https://t.co/fliVTTMV9y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only one merchandise pack left!  Just £6.99 for a large thermal coffee mug, pen, keyring and shopper bag.… https://t.co/9s9u4OI1Qo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas cards for sale from only £2.50 per pack. 

https://t.co/QGid62I6qn https://t.co/oTr5szVaTp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep the flame of independence alive with this Early Days of a Better Nation book from indy artist Stewart Bremner… https://t.co/53pbAKALPR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep the flame of independence burning with this Early Days of a Better Nation calendar.

https://t.co/MnPa58pqAZ https://t.co/Hi9ZN8s3Br]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for a great Christmas gift? We have calendars, books, t-shirts, hoodies, mugs, badges...… https://t.co/pR7lYKm9WB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep warm this winter with a green hoodie! On special offer at the moment at only £18 inc. P&amp;P… https://t.co/kYmcfsds5q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very special offer: get a large thermal coffee mug, recycled pen &amp; keyring and cotton shopper bag for ONLY £6.99!… https://t.co/5v2fEt0VJw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrate St Andrew's Day &amp; keep the spirit of indy alive with Early Days of a Better Nation &amp; Scots Words calendar… https://t.co/rpSUHKRXMj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrate St Andrew's Day tmmrw &amp; keep the flame of indy burning with a The Early Days of a Better Nation calendar… https://t.co/dPxx7MwdN4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caroline Lucas's book 'Honourable Friends?'  is only £8 on the @scotgp online shop.  That's a third off!… https://t.co/RuMzNSlmY5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep the flame of independence burning with this 2017 calendar designed by Stewart Bremner. Only £2 P&amp;P… https://t.co/QpQMlKNbZz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time's running out to order your 'green' Christmas cards! Order now before it's too late.

https://t.co/QGid62ZHhV https://t.co/LgUAk0tIDY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YESthatcherDead Which country?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very special offer: get a large thermal coffee mug, recycled pen &amp; keyring and cotton shopper bag for ONLY £6.99!… https://t.co/umKhCtivNQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Xmas cards from the Greens, recycled card, designed by @scotgp members. Orders yours before they're all gone!… https://t.co/6ErUxsXzCq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stewart Bremner calendars! Early Days of a Better Nation and Scots Sayings. Only £9 each.

https://t.co/QGid62I6qn https://t.co/OJAZx8xaol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Doherty_RA @sgpkev And on tonight's Crimewatch...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[50p in every pound of council tax spent paying off old debt (Edinburgh)

https://t.co/wsym1DHM3d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only 31 days until  Christmas! Card orders going out every day. Order yours before they're all gone.… https://t.co/H4Wjrc2rEK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Explore the @scotgp online shop where you can find lots of goodies, including bags, mugs, t-shirts, calendars etc.… https://t.co/FO2Czc0gZ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get updates from the Scottish Green Party online shop: 

https://t.co/p02bT3ObBt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chris_Freeman01 @scotgp Size guide has been added to the item on the online shop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chris_Freeman01 @scotgp Hi Chris, there isn't an XXL size, I'm afraid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During the indy campaign Stewart was the digital artist for Yes Scotland (features a foreword from Lesley Riddoch)… https://t.co/NA5b0ANaLs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Scots language has a long and colourful history, that stretches back well over a thousand years… https://t.co/FycQTjbB0j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep the flame of independence burning with this calendar by former Yes 
Scotland graphic artist Stewart Bremner… https://t.co/vw4W4jlkTf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LOVE IMMIGRATION mugs
https://t.co/hCHL9AbL1D

Use promo code MUGSALE for 20% off! https://t.co/7quvxPO7Vq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Less than 5 wks left to order your Xmas cards and other goodies! Lots of bargains inc. money off books and posters

https://t.co/QGid62I6qn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jm_stout Once upon a midnight dreary, while I pondered, weak and weary...sorry!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stewart Bremner calendars in stock. And his book The Early Days of a Better Nation too! Order online. Only £2 P&amp;P!… https://t.co/nCjQ131XgQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas cards from only £2.50 per pack. Lots of other "stuff" on the @scotgp online shop.

https://t.co/QGid62ZHhV https://t.co/THyl35WDx7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This week's very special offer: Get 20% off @scotgp green hoodies. Offer ends 30th November 2016. Only a few left!… https://t.co/2mKWABcqSi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Xmas cards, hoodies, bags, calendars and lots more merchandise! Orders going out this week. Best order yours soon!… https://t.co/zztylcPMkV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Xmas cards, hoodies, bags, mugs, calendars and lots more merchandise! Orders going out this week. Order yours soon!… https://t.co/ZnrlT8yeFZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Special offer: 1/3 off Caroline Lucas's Honourable Friends - this week only!

That's only £8… https://t.co/jd6z4Pij9w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[£11.5billion loan debt is crippling Scottish councils with almost half their tax revenue used to repay banks

https://t.co/BuQ8HzAXaH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Less than 6 weeks till Christmas! @scotgp Christmas cards are in stock and ready to be delivered. Order yours now!… https://t.co/eyJ4JjfetV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ScotCan posters, by Stewart Bremner, are £10 this week! 1st 10 customers will receive posters signed by the artist.… https://t.co/cdGMqERuM1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This week's special offer: Buy a green hoodie (any size) and receive a free cotton shopping bag worth £3!… https://t.co/uQQKbQJStA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moon over Leith at 7am https://t.co/25tO5QyIsT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas Cards sold by Scottish Green Party from £3 per pack

https://t.co/1bJoRVezME https://t.co/LTIkuZ1fdr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GREEN HOODIE UPDATE!

The Smalls are sold out, there's only a couple of XLs left. 

Still plenty of Ms and Ls.… https://t.co/IVyDjJKEzi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merchandise pack 2 - incredible value at only £7.99 from the @scotgp online shop

https://t.co/ACHySFX2gy https://t.co/vrZHNezA5V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merchandise pack -amazing value at only £4.99 from the @scotgp online shop

https://t.co/0MzPghE2Yr https://t.co/0xuqyikW0i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Patrick Harvie: We needed a change ... but not this one

https://t.co/XFsAct7GHh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Immigration Mug sold by Scottish Greens.  20% off this week!

https://t.co/hCHL9zUaa5 https://t.co/G0TATGkXdN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the many products on the @scotgp @tictail online shop:

https://t.co/L7FvNptzSp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mickhumph Hi Mick. Yes, members of Green parties can join other Green parties. We have members all over the world, inc. many in England.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join the Scottish Greens today, to help create a fairer, more compassionate and inclusive Scotland

https://t.co/1NBCnblLVc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Americano thermal coffee mugs (large) are half-price today.  That's only £3 per mug. Bargain!… https://t.co/kwU5psshRv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Scottish Gov't really needs to get to grips with what's gone wrong with Police Scotland.  Shocking.

https://t.co/8R20tZDpCy]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>