<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@philtastro will try and get some next time they come through!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hung a CD in the fig tree to repel the currawongs. Now they aren't around, we have (loud) corellas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This out of date emergency sign with terrible grammar also serves as a reminder for RSAA PhD students https://t.co/qT93RT7r42]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Old keyboard died, so now I have a new keyboard and it is even louder than the temporary Sun Microsystems one I was using.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A series of tubes... https://t.co/UsoeT9sebS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That feel when someone is using ur photo as a promotional picture https://t.co/3PUATmPW5C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Edited the data reduction pipeline without breaking it. May have bounced around the office a bit too enthusiastically]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@philtastro @photonhandler this is relevant to our interests https://t.co/Y805eHDWdn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking at results from my work and seeing the paper I'm gonna write coming together https://t.co/K98t1f12dd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I went 2 nights with no server resets. H o w ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My entire life has been a lie. I thought the cheese and gas interacted https://t.co/AcrA1JTRTU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We have had 0 server crashes so far and tbh I have no idea what to do with myself. So much free time for activities]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're officially out of ToOs to look at! On to some SN Host galaxies! https://t.co/PkK1VaTfwy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorJeph it's gonna have to happen soon with ours]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorJeph yep. Those things would never cross our threshold]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day 375: the hot dog shape incarceration continues #freetheshapes https://t.co/Go7mAS6ZBD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@novaric thanks! We had a good night tonight. Hopefully the weather continues to hold out!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@novaric thanks! I'm considering opening an etsy shop but the fact the ink runs if they get wet makes me reluctant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Final galaxy of the night is full of surprises - I can see strong emission in the raw data (possibly SII)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clouds marching across the all sky cam https://t.co/b2YzLsz78w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spoke too soon. Clouds moved in and ruined our 4th target :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On to target number 4 for the night. We're on a roll!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We've been learning about SN nucleosynthesis this evening (in between setting up observations) https://t.co/K3zOaoELAi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right as I want to start observing my targets, the cloud returns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JustinList God damn , I thought you were referring to the image of a galaxy I tweeted earlier! Safe to say this fella is very nearby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JustinList Not sure, but probably 12 or so thousand parsecs (1 parsec ~ 3 light years, and 1AU ~ 8 light minutes)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The aliens have arrived. I for one welcome our grasshopper overlords https://t.co/ZmSUwREIvG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philtastro yeah, it's only like a few thousand parsecs away]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philtastro Yup. I headed out to Andromeda to observe tonight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#observations https://t.co/oGOpTZG6av]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Currently observing a target of opportunity in this beauty https://t.co/MGOLTSb8hk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geddy Lee screams in the distance https://t.co/mKKbvBiT8c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG the clouds might be dissipating. Maybe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DRG_physics oh goodness I'm so jealous! What an awesome experience!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorJeph and it's beautiful seeing here in Canberra.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorJeph if I have to watch clouds blow through until 3:30am I will lose it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting chap - wallaby of some kind https://t.co/DzgDOlL0dz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@astrostew but what will I occupy myself with during my hour long exposures tonight?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I forgot my phone charger. This is a disaster]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Observing ennui. I was too organised and I have nothing to do until I think about opening at 1930 https://t.co/nkIA3tWk4T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm observing tonight and tomorrow on ANU's 2.3m telescope - looking at galaxies where my favorite type of weird supernovae occur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Observing plan coming together ~12 hr before first target rises. First step is "Check the bloody dichroic is the correct one"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have no idea how I did it but I made the TV work by wiggling the co-ax and my flatmates think I'm a witch https://t.co/b9ByY9AyRV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aaaand just as I prepare for the HPC runs they take the damned machine offline for an upgrade https://t.co/1JjYkQ9eZR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ready for Australia Day https://t.co/VOdvGIVIaU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Officemate: my galaxy gave birth to babies!
Me: I don't think that's how cosmology is supposed to work... https://t.co/fMQXtaeYPD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting some neat results from my project right now https://t.co/JRXu7qb12b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Impressive Canberra sky tonight @StormHour (no filter needed!) https://t.co/SUsn4pxgg4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mostly looking good 3 days in. And we have flowers on the tomato plant and chillies growing https://t.co/uO52keErOI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phys Rev now asks you to identify either Albert Einstein or Marie Curie when downloading papers!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's called fashion. Look it up. https://t.co/yMb9RH0zcU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AshleeMParkes I made mine using some white sneakers from Kmart and a fabric sharpie :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When u get blessed by the weather gods (next observing run on Friday/Saturday) https://t.co/j9G35M7kjo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish I had been more imaginative when naming my code tbh https://t.co/xYY3Hq0jxi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's shoe situation: Feynman diagrams https://t.co/WgwVyB1l7R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean sure I could probably build my own plug in, but I actually have real research to do so...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it's a shame twitter's mute feature only works on direct tweets, not mentions, newspaper articles about, retweets...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day 370: no reprieve in sight. Hot dog shape inprisonment continues https://t.co/SBOePZtYHb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@antDigital it may have changed, but I've seen it discussed as a digital security problem (people posting pics of boarding passes)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@antDigital usually need the details available on the boarding pass - surname, booking ref etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@antDigital yup. I recently heard about the passenger reference number one - people cancelling your flight once you've checked in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, stop posting your passport number. You're opening yourself up to identity theft and tax fraud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@antDigital I've seen several on Twitter today. All info needed to cancel booking was visible on boarding pass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If people see your ref number and name, they can actually cancel your ticket]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FYI: if you're travelling somewhere, don't post photos of your boarding pass where your passport number and ticket ref can be seen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dr_dbw this is why I didn't go into experimental physics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh my god it's gonna die anyway https://t.co/Tj4QG7dtkF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dr_dbw well it looked like Rosemary from the side (also turns out it has 0 culinary uses) https://t.co/z4exYfeuMu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me: and I bought a Rosemary plant too
Flat mate: that isn't Rosemary, that's a curry plant
Flat mate: it literally… https://t.co/O8DeXVUoYq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They call them that because you don't particularly want them in your house https://t.co/O0giBTOznH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't talk to me or my daughter again https://t.co/ZwyTF0PMsq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@photonhandler blackcurrant hole sounds a bit... Rude]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@photonhandler I have to go out and buy another 24 now. We do have fairy mass f-loss though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because the original space themed zooper doopers weren't sciency enough https://t.co/daMKCrILy0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mood tbh https://t.co/Sd5uKE9Iv2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fri: never mind. You were right all along. 

We're bringing back the variable adiabatic gamma!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tue: model works 
Wed: model impeded by transcendental equation 
Thurs: transcendental equation has no solution]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@photonhandler: maybe the real funding was the friends we made along the way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorJeph could also be it. That inversion thing that happens around Coona always throws me when I'm observing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorJeph @stevebiddle @MetService I've noticed the Canberra radar starts picking up 'rain' in the evenings. People using wifi?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is borderline COLD in Canberra this evening and it is FANTASTIC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day 367: hot dog flavour shapes are still in the fridge https://t.co/R9LUPZYyCT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I DID THE THING]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philuponscience A coffee can was used to help it vacate the premises]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@photonhandler and the cold taps at stromlo produce hot water anyway in this weather (as I found out AFTER burning my hand)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DRG_physics @photonhandler I've had school kids argue with me that blue stars are cool because that's how taps are labelled 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can now see my CSIRO Bolton and Student symposium slide at https://t.co/BUTFmFXk0I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success! Calculated radiative temperature evolution of an adiabatically expanding bubble!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Running into lots of astronomers out running/in the gym of late. 2017 is the year of the buff astronomer I guess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@astro_jje @Knhannah @CatherineQ @SpaceLauren @BasilLeaf gosh I just got in the car and saw this! Thank you so much for sharing my writing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@antDigital the trouble with a lot of skeptics is they take a fraction of a community and then generalise. Then again, I'm doing the same!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Knhannah same. Christian independent school for 6 yr then into state schools with compulsory comp. religion up to Y11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Knhannah honestly I've only come across this in Aus/NZ. Correlates with no compulsory comparative religion classes at any stage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["But as a scientist you rationally know there is no evidence for God's existence"
"Well someone gave me the patience to put up with you"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You believe in God - you must be stupid"
"Well I'd argue that my BSc(Hons) in physics and half-finished PhD disputes that"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Knhannah @TristanRS @DoctorJeph when we were observing @photonhandler coloured in a pic of the rover for my office… https://t.co/YVM0z5N35a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philuponscience We had one of those incidents a few years ago. Baby brown in ladies bathroom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Knhannah Sorry, I just get so frustrated with some of the cynicism in the scicomm and science community.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicgaston @REasther @Knhannah @DoctorJeph that's always been my scicomm manifesto: Come as you are, take what you need/want]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Knhannah and having colleagues tell you you've been "brainwashed" bc you have religious/spiritual beliefs (which do not conflict w. sci)]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>