<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@annasproul @colindickey @Paul_The_Cote I...went to a prep school in junior high but then was in an IB magnet program so can I hang out too?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colindickey Years ago, my husband got into his doctoral program with a thesis on Dr. Seuss. You two need to meet. @Paul_The_Cote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamchrisscott This is wonderful news. I'm so proud of you and love you. See you tonight. ❤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RadMacawesome I'm just doing 2-3 times a day? That's what my artist told me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But you can also vote. 

You can vote "no" on every horrific appointment and policy. That's also a thing you can do… https://t.co/LwdrAViTlt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@karalearota yes, such robust foreign policy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GingerConstruct I'm doing 2-3 times a day. That's what I was told by the artist so hopefully it's ok.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the brazenly condemnatory wording: "practices violence on innocent people" -- I'm sorry, did anyone so much as touch Milo?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very glad your priority this morning has been threatening a public university because it protested the presence of… https://t.co/Rqm1AP3Btp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give me a relatively low-stakes task (the tattoo is perfectly fine), and I *will* honor it with my life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to see a neurotic person lose her mind? Observe as she gets a small, simple tattoo and proceeds to obsess over its cleaning regimen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rpbp that it even seems possible makes me want to sob.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It occurs to me that when Kanye visited Trump Tower, Trump might have thought he was in fact holding a meeting with Frederick Douglass.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most perfect Twitter post that ever was crafted. Thank you, Ira. https://t.co/ko8IcWMY0j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lubchansky I thought I could trust all furries to be antifa, but I guess I was wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@williamandmary I love you, alma mater, and hope and expect that you will announce your status as a sanctuary campus ASAP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How hard do you think Vladimir Putin is partying right now? Three day bender? Naked horseback riding through the Kr… https://t.co/PUbzwzN2KM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You do not fuck with the power of the Knowles women and their wombs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshgondelman He'd get derailed when he mentioned Kanye because he'd have to tell everyone about how much Yeezy loves and supports him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I used to teach this poem in my queer literature class. It is one of my very favorites and couldn't be more resonant right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helfitzgerald "Every time we kiss / we confirm the new world is coming." Ugh god I love it so much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They don't know
we need each other
critically.

- Essex Hemphill, "American Wedding"

https://t.co/ej2FXzTE9W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aurora_f And maybe don't make an asinine and self-absorbed remark ignoring the horrors POC have endured.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He said during his hearing that he couldn't imagine anything worse than being called a racist.

This is a fucking d… https://t.co/ocKl17wrDA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need a new word that encompasses secondhand embarrassment, disgust, and scorn. https://t.co/Naqt5tATBi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fatgirlinohio it was pretty nice, huh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Current internal monologue: It's late, you should go to bed. Okay, maybe refresh Twitter a few more times. Just to set your mind at ease.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One thing I miss about the Obama administration is going to bed without worrying that I would wake up to Armageddon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GingerConstruct there is a TREMENDOUS amount of Harvey nudity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Checking in briefly as I refill my mimosa to say that The Piano is a perfect film, and I think you all should watch it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@S_Insley_H Yep! I was waiting for a William &amp; Mary person to identify it :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mug filled with mimosa and my favorite movie which I ~have~ to rewatch for an essay assignment. I'm headed to #cope… https://t.co/CWupcHHjbG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fatgirlinohio exactly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I did not expect to be pleased, and wow I am not pleased. https://t.co/klfBG7CCBP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cal_beu oh my goodness poppers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay, time to finish up some intense revisions. Somebody ping me if there's a coup/war/air raid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is especially disgusting because before the shooting suspect was identified, the police referred to the attack… https://t.co/4hNCOjjPFg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(This sensation is also intertwined with my white privilege: I have the luxury of sometimes feeling something other than terror.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@skinnyblackgirl it's extremely rare, weird, and alcohol infused]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aMandolinz @jesslbergman that's a really important one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@afrosypaella yes, I love that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously, one drink and I turn into the embodiment of this GIF. https://t.co/WXCjRmWkwe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AuroraBorealice this is generally where I am. sometimes alcohol adjusts things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All this really means for me is that when I'm drunk I have to brace myself against the urge to send really ill-advised emails.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It doesn't necessarily have to be tied to love. I'm just talking big-gestures-last-shot-now-or-never bursts of emotion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who else is, when they're not furious and/or terrified, feeling romantic in the apocalyptic way?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@esmewang @PKhakpour As I keep telling everyone, I am too poor to register, but live here and hope to see you for meals/off-site events! &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pronounced_ing Oh I really hope we can see each other! I will be around and hoping to catch people for meals and the off-site events.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pronounced_ing will you be here?? I'm not registered, but will be around for off-site events since I'm local.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We knew that bitch was no ally. I'm just too attached to her damn music.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But really, my reaction to T-Swifty's self-preserving silence lands here: https://t.co/r6RlUrlnHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me: I literally do not give a shit what Taylor Swift thinks about politics. It's irrelevant. 
Also me: This is betrayal, you fake feminist!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicole_soojung This is the initial vote or THE vote? Either way, I'm spitting mad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NOT_TomPetty In any case, I hope you guys are doing ok in the midst of our new national nightmare.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NOT_TomPetty You would think. He is either very dumb, does not care, or--most likely--some combination of the two.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pronounced_ing ...and donated to the ACLU &lt;3 #smallacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pronounced_ing Emailed local mosques to ask abt support needed, protested near the White House, blogged abt politics on Jezebel #smallacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annamerlan I just watched the video clip, and she is dynamite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I cannot remember the last time I didn't wake up in a panic, grab my phone, and wonder, "What have I missed? What has he done now?!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh. 

Okay.

I mean, I'm happy if you're happy.

https://t.co/VccY7eRU6V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's very tempting to cling to the logic of exceptionalism, but dangerous. Make no mistake, Trump is behaving like a dictator.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Extremely disturbing shit just went down in the Department of Justice, and I have written it up for you: https://t.co/WXZagLY29b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once again, to all those who voted for Trump assuming he would do little of what he promised: please escort yourselves into the sea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelEdits it truly is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm unsurprised that Trump lied through his teeth re: LGBTQ issues at the RNC, but still: fuck. https://t.co/mQvDolhUDN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@washingtonkate oh man. what a painful memory. &lt;3 &lt;3 &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StassaEdwards Frappuchinos 4 Freedom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annasproul I'm not registering, but I *will* be around, so...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Angela Merkel had to explain the Geneva Conventions to you. https://t.co/DqnPZNDzFc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rpbp you certainly did.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't think it especially deserves the awards, but I also think white narratives need to be pointedly moved aside, particularly right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recently saw "La La Land." If it wins half as many Oscars as has been predicted, the Academy will commit an(other) act of racist erasure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@THBevilacqua lol why thank you, Thomas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apologies for all the times I get too drunk in the near future and quote this line like the clichéd, 90s-obsessed white girl that I am.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For all those who persisted in doubt, Cher Horowitz has the last laugh — as well she should. https://t.co/NMK5Rlwq2S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@k_files That changes EVERYTHING!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh good point. Next time we protest the unconstitutional banning of weary and frightened refugees, let's make it mo… https://t.co/xoJLZkf898]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MoustacheClubUS lol that's cute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ringwraith10 it cut me to the quick, it's true.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always listen to Stacia. https://t.co/UvgmkXuUid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@realDonaldTrump Any thoughts? https://t.co/0lR6znjh2f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*accompanies

Though, oddly, "accomplices" works too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lafergs I always appreciate your support LaToya.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gbrockell I personally don't get it, but opinions are opinions I guess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, I really think MAGA2017 needs a sturdy anxiety med cocktail. I mean, settle down, bud.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG but did you see he said I have a nice ass? (BTW a large image of Pepe accomplices this image because some troll… https://t.co/TYxe8BRlPL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you define "massive success story" as one of terror, chaos, and prejudice -- but I expect Steve Bannon does. https://t.co/2KS1hvrXkk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seekanewerworld so glad we were all together ❤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She can't keep doing this. It's not fair.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sdpowell1 Thank you for having my back. I am dead now, but also happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am both profoundly inside my body and transported far beyond it. https://t.co/KYPAxqNl6z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danitasteinberg thank you!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@haylieswenson Same to you! I'm so sorry we weren't able to find each other. &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm blogging/fretting over the news. Could someone please tweet me a pic of Evan Rachel Wood at the SAG Awards? I would be so grateful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@becagrimm I knew you would be pleased! &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Ludacris Do you know that your music has become the chorus of the resistance?? #MoveTrump #GetOutDaWay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LOL. #WhiteHouse https://t.co/HjN1iviI3o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With @seekanewerworld, @Paul_the_Cote, and other buds supporting refugee rights at the White House. https://t.co/QSMwnEtUhm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one murdered in the Holocaust--Jews, the disabled, queer folk, so many more--should be named so blithely, with so little respect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Millions more innocents were cruelly murdered by the Nazis. But the WH's statement is constructed to reference Jews as an afterthought.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>