<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The names for the strategies here are gendered, but interesting observations. https://t.co/venk5skWFi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PSA: Don't put soluble fibre in diet cola.

Unless you're deliberately going for a mentos-coke effect.

(No questions please)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG what is JBish telling the world? https://t.co/0H5bEXg0BM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[anyone ever noticed how much Paul Ryan looks like Ramsey Bolton? Without the charm, that is. https://t.co/dvxeqkWxqk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColourpurpleGal @BrigadierSlog sorry, stalking your timeline to make sure he was okay! Good to hear you worked it out!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheOriginalTKO @billmaher No, they're Australian, too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billmaher Build a wall, f*cker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Straightjacket for golfers. Fair enough, we know what they are like. https://t.co/7EKNWkuoZJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kelloveslife @FiveFrogsBlog @2FBS Thanks xx He's a bit brighter this morning, but he still needs oxygen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most amusing is the idea of "grimy black and white" video from 1991. LOL. https://t.co/So219hOqB7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FiveFrogsBlog @2FBS He was a bit brighter overnight but still needed oxygen treatment. Acutely aware this is more than some people get.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@John_Hanna @TheNTNews that is fascinating]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SallyRMelb @BecPobjie thanks xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@2FBS and I get a consistently cheerier story from the surgeon than other vets or his nurses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@2FBS He's okay bit he has a feeding tube, a large mass removed, aspiration pneumonia &amp; is getting intensive care o/n with oxygen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davrosz He deterred the draft 5 times, the last because he apparently had "bad feet" https://t.co/gud5o6Papx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davrosz Oh I think he was taking advantage of a loophole during Vietnam, anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BecPobjie Survived the op, but he has pneumonia. Surgeon reported the op went well; emergency department giving him oxygen overnight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BecPobjie thanks x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BecPobjie the waiting for the phone call is the hardest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiting on the vet to ring to find out whether we have a beloved dog &amp; a gaping maw in our finances, or just a gaping maw in our finances.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hm. So pleased 2016 finally ended. 2017's going so well so far. https://t.co/9Xyaw6LqFh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vanbadham "Largest inauguration crowd ever".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RaidersGirl83 @PeitaTweets I am going to try a few methods. Very dilute alcohol and distilled water seems to be the go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this is disheartening. Needs to be more than that. https://t.co/fC4xy9hGj9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BevJohnst @KeithOlbermann I think Trump decided that all on his lonesome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take notes. We may need this #nuclearwinter #trump https://t.co/PgWEZ39YVZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noplaceforsheep and the deal was an attempt to side-step this perception that to gain power a party has to be "tough on border protection"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @TurnbullMalcolm, you know what would be a real show of strength? Shove the ultra right bullies. #Bringthemhere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noplaceforsheep and now that the deal has fallen through, they really have no choice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have been to countless protests over the years and watched the effort disappear like a fart in the wind. Must be more effective ways.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeithOlbermann what do you think - is the GOP going to grow and spine and impeach this monster, or are we all dead?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeithOlbermann Reason Turnbull made the deal is both sides of govt now too scared to treat refugees who come by boat humanely. Cruel &amp; mad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeithOlbermann &amp; they're on Nauru &amp; Manus because then PM John Howard convinced the Australian people in 2001 that refugees=terrorists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@corijomama @seankent @Ebswearspink You're in the hands of the GOP and the law now. Lord help us all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timmaughan @fuddlemark Good. Be good for them to have to contemplate the real world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clairebbbear @zoomosis it's not much of a field but of the last five I rate her best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zoomosis @clairebbbear For all her faults I think Gillard was actually pretty good at negotiating. She got a lot done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zoomosis @clairebbbear oh no, that would be brilliant. There'd only be tiny weeny hands and a sad toupee left.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bugger Keating, imagine what would have gone down if it had been Abbott.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomas_violence Total fuckwit fits nicely though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jurassic_snark_ clowns deserve it, after all. But they (clowns) don't taste as good though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonder what other traps Obama might have left politically. Guess the success of the Affordable Care Act was one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder whether a gathering of neonazis would be a bunch of buzz cut inadequate twats wandering around making cucking sounds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ben_hr @WynRichards Just wondered whether the "thousands" sum was classic Trump inflation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@2FBS when Tony the Messiah comes back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seankent @Ebswearspink Can you fucking do something about him? Plz? kthxbai, Australia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ben_hr I guess "thousands" is a large scope.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Trixie_Boo who are his enemies? I think it's just about everyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BernardKeane @dotrat @rhysam Depends, was it on his unsecured Android?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ben_hr How many are on Manus and Nauru now anyway? It's not "thousands" is it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And by the way, oh great, the fucking eye of Sauron is on us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear @TurnbullMalcolm, you continued the lie of calling these people "illegals". They are refugees. Do the decent t… https://t.co/CWyQJatgFk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onlyapaprmoon Online might be the only bet - as long as they don't think I'm setting up my own still or something o_o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onlyapaprmoon Was thinking of giving this one a go https://t.co/d7XbhqTnXD just not sure about buying the chemicals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewwhiteau @SezClom Nothing spoils in a dungeon. Just sayin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onlyapaprmoon They're all post-1970, so I assume all good. I did have 78s, but those were some that the builders stole, along with Bowie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onlyapaprmoon Some are really quite dirty - great condition until kept in a garage for 20 years, and had builders rifle through them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why doesn't potus have spellcheck? How old is his android?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't even know if that was mine or I just appropriated it from somewhere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Idea for a tv show: hot dog stand proprietor and his psychopathically calm side kick solve crime, called Frank &amp; Fearless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama killed a 16-year-old American in Yemen. Trump just killed his 8-year-old sister. https://t.co/qFsXE4iGYQ by @ggreenwald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is from 2015, but still very relevant. https://t.co/xswSOfx7nU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hippopeteamus @saboteusenik @phantomdiorama Except yours and @phantomdiarama's. They are radpoles.
*You're welcome!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maddythecatlady @ozzmosis does the microfibre cloth leave lint or scratch?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zoomosis I've seen people recommend dropping a long bead of pva, spreading it with a credit card right to the edge, then peeling it off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do people clean their records? There seem to be as many conflicting opinions as baby raising methods.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hippopeteamus That wins everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BevJohnst What horrific times we are living in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AJemaineClement The cult of Baio.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonyschwartz I bet he didn't actually read it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YaThinkN Fundamentally a lack of imagination, I think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YaThinkN Tony Schwartz's law still reigns--what he accuses others of, he's doing himself. It's carnage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adelaidejerks also, when you bite a neck it sounds like an apple.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YaThinkN I'm convinced the plan is to give him enough rope to lose support then tighten noose. He can do a lot of damage in that time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YaThinkN GOP are not happy campers atm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd love to know where Murdoch is on all this, given he went so quiet after he got married.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justtaff That was my guess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnWren1950 and/or US Customs and Border Protection uniforms.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnWren1950 @nzherald There's relatively good evidence that the rogue account might actually be Bannon staff or Russian. Not verified.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WBfromCanberra but I get what you mean.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope that doesn't mean the US will end up with pneumonia after 18 straight shots of whisky at the Whitehorse Tavern. https://t.co/7hs9TLwimA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Troll-like behaviour from "Alt Dept of ED". https://t.co/GvHCmBeewl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dogboy64 Murdoch? (Same thing.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much Australian anti-refugee language being used by Trump now. "Illegals", "weak on borders". What's the link?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cateia97 @laurelatoreilly close to an Australian slang word for Muslim.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swearyanthony a readymade fascist force waiting for a leader.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Weak on borders". Where have we heard this language before? Well done, Turnbull. 😡 https://t.co/RIhKbvYoSI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noplaceforsheep @giddyupbill yes and their simpering arse licking will follow their reputations forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chrisbdg34Smith not thinking about the consequences of their actions is a mistake Trump voters made as well. Just a point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This attitude isn't helpful. https://t.co/n0ypZLL3jn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chrisbdg34Smith Hate doesn't solve problems, it only makes makes you feel superior.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chrisbdg34Smith Sure, but credit to anyone who admits a mistake. Trump voters were brainscrewed big time https://t.co/uE0HN7uuaM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@micklaw @illchangethis @JohnJohnsonson Actually, yes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chrisbdg34Smith Hey, leave off her. She made a mistake, knows it now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SwordfishParm Can I ask what appealed about him? Were you just always Republican, or were you convinced by the lies?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think we have our answer. https://t.co/xUJ1fVFTIR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thisleisa worst thing is when you clap one of those huge ones between your palms and it squirts your blood.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LizDolphinfluff I'm wondering who did it? A couple of years ago Mum would have had a hand in it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mum used to give me plants on the basis that they'd survive but I don't think she could conceptualise a plant not drenched every 2 weeks.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>