<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@dailykos The #Resistance gives me hope.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@haaretzcom Will the burning of this Texas mosque be thoroughly investigated?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RawStory A vote for Jeff Sessions is a vote for a return to Jim Crow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomPerez What McConnell did to the Garland nomination sticks in my craw. Yes, Gorsuch is well qualified, but so is Garland.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glasgow School of Art's ashes turned into artworks to fund rebuild https://t.co/ODcgKrPxL5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keithellison @huffpostqueer For many families in my city, running out of these items is,  at best, a monthly crisis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RawStory is Chaffetz going to investigate the foreign press?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RoguePOTUSStaff Gorsuch is a fine pick if you want a conservative. Garland would be the perfect pick IF you wanted to heal the country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ForeignAffairs One of the requirements of a good negotiator is to be realistic in evaluating one's own position. Trump is unable to do so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Slate One thing disqualifies Neil Gorsuch in my mind: he is not Merrick Garland.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheEconomist @MalcolmNance They stood by us. We need to keep our treaty obligations &amp; stand by them. If we don't, Trump must be impeached.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HindMakki @wjbk Unspeakable &amp; unnecessary tragedy for this family. Kellyanne Conway said this is just temporary. Cruelty beyond belief.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nadabakos @MalcolmNance @BuzzFeedNews By making CIA job more difficult, Trump's Immigration Order puts Americans at GREATER risk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@guardian Hope to see Connecticut join the list of states opposing anti muslim travel ban.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thedailybeast @MalcolmNance Banning spokespeople and surrogates from appearing on CNN shows means less spin &amp; less nonsense on CNN.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Yamiche @nytimes Oh no! Did Sean Spicer lie? Again? Did he just pull that 109 figure out of some mysterious place?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dailykos Jeff Sessions fits the mold of the spit &amp; polish White Citizens Council segregationists who let the Klan do their dirty work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Trump wants Democratic support for his #SCOTUSnominee, he can nominate Merrick Garland.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Slate Note the careful hand-on-butt placement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Maryland girl died in a Delaware facility for disabled youth just ahead of being transferred. https://t.co/Mb3DJ74WGb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FBI: U.S. law enforcement infiltrated by white supremacists https://t.co/2qsPm0ZhzS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like Trump won’t try to negotiate prescription drug prices after all: https://t.co/qhtHPvYMzx via @slate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MoreAndAgain @WillisBonnerr As for example, these fine law enforcement officials made famous by the movie "Mississ… https://t.co/sw75ldr32l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid @crampell @washingtonpost Interesting that Charles Koch came out against the ban, but Paul "Rollover" Ryan supports it w/smiles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkLGoldberg @MalcolmNance @9NEWS Has the Republican Party now become the symbol of cruelty in America?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AGJepsen Please join Washington &amp; Massachusetts in going to court to stop the ban. We are US. #NoBanNoWall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Massachusetts to join court battle against Trump travel ban https://t.co/q3VvR72IkR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickTimiraos @crampell @WSJ If he was truthful, it simply means they screwed people on purpose, while he made millions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chaffetz &amp; others want to give away public land so private interests can profit. Russian-style KLEPTOCRACY.… https://t.co/LJrtTHT8Lv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democratic state attorneys general begin Trump pushback: https://t.co/ZLnquQc9f6 (from @AP)

Stand &amp; be counted https://t.co/iO9HYycgCO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian State TV Praises Trump for Avoiding ‘Democracy’ in Inauguration Speech: https://t.co/bPpNcskc0C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here are all the parts of the Constitution Trump’s #MuslimBan violates: https://t.co/vZuRSS5q0D via @slate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HarleyPeyton @Lawrence It is the women of this country that will bring about the changes we need.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bnkausik @crampell @washingtonpost No Red Line. Power corrupts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SallyQYates #ThankYouSally for taking a stand. Hope you run for Tom Price's House seat. Your home state needs you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oath of Office is to Constitution, not president. No matter how he decorates his apartment, Trump is not the Sun Ki… https://t.co/qGBjzWe74T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's firing of Yates "suggests he has no commitment to the institutional integrity of the [Dept of Justice]." — Prof. Lawrence Tribe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Trump's casino bankruptcies screwed his workers out of millions in retirement savings https://t.co/Q7SJWiuGiO via @MotherJones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would like to nominate Sally Caroline Yates to represent the 6th District of Georgia in the House of Representati… https://t.co/1HyRYa72Qb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Fires Acting Attorney General https://t.co/P5XCefiy1a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNBC @MaddowBlog Remember Nixon's Saturday Night Massacre? This is a time to be counted. I applaud acting AG Yates for taking a stand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jbouie stuff stays with us. The boy did not deserve this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jbouie At 5 I was sent to school day early, waited at stop 2 hrs for the bus that never came. I was scared. Walked 1/2 mi home. 67 yrs ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Kraken has been released from the depths and the Trumpocalypse is at hand. 
https://t.co/wV9zi3Sdmo https://t.co/USa2A1urEO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MicahGrimes @MalcolmNance @NBCNews Ironic that the first mission under Trump's watch does not go well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So horrible. https://t.co/kcXGZjKLmf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Screenshot from https://t.co/G70kg8o9Hf  — Sean Spicer sees a threat to our security, I see a 5yo boy happy to be r… https://t.co/S0583WpX9Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Bannon on the NSC is dangerous. The WH spin is bs. Bannon is dangerous. #RemoveBannon https://t.co/Nngzlg3hSY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RawStory We have an effective defense against 5 yo terrorists (pictured): send in Arnold Schwarzenegger, The Kinde… https://t.co/hicNiF62we]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Media not talking about President Obama's ban on Iraqi immigration—because it's another Trump lie https://t.co/KgBePOgRXz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LoveMeLuLu22 @MsTaraDowdell 
Hey Donald, here's a thought — why not protect Americans from poisoned water?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CivilRightsCntr @splcenter @yawn_meister @MGMAdvertiser These were not called terrorist attacks back then, but that is what they were.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quebec City mosque attack suspect known for right-wing online posts /via @globeandmail https://t.co/cFqxURRN6U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Trump administration’s weekend of affronts to America https://t.co/rdju0q5ukv via @bangordailynews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ancient history is difficult to compile — bits, pieces, detective work and conjecture. We are still finding pieces… https://t.co/n1k6RbLv7e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid @MalcolmNance @MotherJones It is just a coincidence the WN stands for both Wing Nut &amp; White Nationalist. #Resist the WN Admin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bannon is a cancer in the body politic. Must #RemoveBannon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@haaretzcom Netanyahu CREATED the diplomatic crisis between Israel &amp; Mexico. He &amp; Trump are scary similar.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShaunKing @NYDailyNews The protests this weekend are an affirmation that 
'We the People Are Greater Than Fear"… https://t.co/Ui6LIOP2Xu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@EliotACohen: "This is one of those clarifying moments in American history." https://t.co/q4WeEW5Jic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisgeidner @ShaunKing Sounds like sending petitioner to Dubai after application made for TRO was violation of due process, no?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ADL_National @Lawrence @WhiteHouse Yes, others died, but the principle target of the Holocaust was the Jews. No one else wore yellow stars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexisgoldstein @Jezebel This is a horror story. Everything about how this mother &amp; her two children were treated is wrong!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bangordailynews @krauthammer An evaluation of Trump's announced foreign policy by a well-known conservative voice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamilSmith @EliotACohen @TheAtlantic  Solid article. "… but in the end, it is the greatness of America that will stop  him."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Per Cato Institute, as quoted by Fareed Zakaria — the # of Americans killed by citizens from the banned 7 nations frm 1975 to 2015 is ZERO!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Slate Maybe the time has come to formally overturn Korematsu v. United States (1944), considered one of SCOTUS' worst decisions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@prisonculture @ShaunKing Spreadsheet also tells you when they are up for re-election. Let us have long memories &amp; let us vote.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dnvolz @Yamiche @ACLU I doubt strengthening the ACLU was an achievement the administration intended.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@repjohnlewis Like the sign in the crowd: "Stop pretending your racism is patriotism"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamilSmith Sounds like more than one "Senior adminstration official" is massively deluded — unless, of course, chaos &amp; pain are the goal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@voxdotcom Since bases do not travel, might we be better off trading a few bases for a few ships that we can relocate as needed?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aprilsdogs Needless, gratuitous cruelty. Turns my stomach. I know what it is like to be 5, alone &amp; scared. I have not forgotten after 67yrs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@guardian Border agents defying court order should be charged with contempt of court ASAP! Should be held personally responsible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bangordailynews This is the face of the #AmericanRasputin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@haaretzcom Who will they come for next? Who else does Bannon, the American Rasputin, distrust?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattyglesias @jbouie @voxdotcom Bannon, the American Rasputin, and his tortured mind are pulling strings behind the curtain. Rep 4 Putin?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RawStory Nero fiddled while Rome burned. Bannon &amp; Putin celebrating the chaos and heartache.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is heart-warming to see so many  in the Jewish community taking a stand in support of the Muslim refugees. We are us. #NoBan #NoBannon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@resnikoff @thinkprogress The triumph of ignorance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@splcenter @anniecorreal @nytimes The history &amp; culture of my country is made up of the lives of real people. We are us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to @KristilA for calling my attention to 25th. Question: Pence better or worse? Hobson's choice?
https://t.co/tUzlvob5Af]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisMurphyCT @mkslater @RonWyden Hard for Trump to NOT know that most Americans believe his tax returns should be relased.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The protests against the ban announce that we as a nation are better the fear that helped propel Trump into office.… https://t.co/Wnmckh4n22]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Florida restaurant offers ‘Angel Shot’ to help women escape dates https://t.co/fEMZZGLCAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe we got the president we deserved for not guarding well the values of our democracy. Trump woke us up. We must #resist &amp; we must #vote.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamilSmith @jodikantor @nytimes Reading about the welcome this Syrian family received from synagogue members is emotional. My America!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lsarsour @ShaunKing @HuffPostPol This is what happens when the inept rush to impose emotional solutions not have not been properly vetted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Some…believe having districts that are more balanced between Republicans and Democrats would reduce  political ext… https://t.co/s9VwLnpdM3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Texas mosque destroyed in early-morning blaze; cause unknown: https://t.co/JswpJlNUfx (from @AP) https://t.co/oR66CxZ83w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Latest: PM Trudeau says Canada will take refugees: https://t.co/U8g5TWNjms (from @AP) https://t.co/4sfsRwTAeT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sahilkapur @MalcolmNance Not what Ryan said on July 31, 2016. Power is priority over principles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuddLegum @ShaunKing @thinkprogress When I think of terrorists in the US, I think of the Ku Klux Klan &amp; those who commit hate crimes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am thinking about the many refugee who died in Nazi concentration camps because we turned away their ship the St Louis in 1939. Shameful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRoot Is the timing a sick joke or is the new administration that incompetent?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course Trump listens to nut jobs, he is a nut job himself. https://t.co/bvGVBsBLBs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lady Liberty has been betrayed. https://t.co/Y0MaWLTgnJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["…essentially, Republicanism should govern America as a one-party state." That sounds like fascism. https://t.co/ZNczXh0vnU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["President Trump is running the nation just as he ran his business: to maximize his own profits." https://t.co/MLPBguTDBd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Slate Well, Carlos A. Giménez, no need to rush to print with "Profiles in Courage, Part 2".]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>