<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@ABELCIDER with a starter of Kingfish #White-bait #Wellington https://t.co/EjD8KWk6Lr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From roadside trading to hipster supermarkets, how we buy food reflects the state of the economy https://t.co/7iB7Sku669 via @qz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@farmerjase @MichaJohansen well maybe 10 of them. And the still almost bet us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dean_Nimbly @Browncowkiwi Starc was a bugger Muppet trying to go for the glory himself. He is 'The Big Show #2']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trumps going to need a Canadisn boarder wall now too 😂
https://t.co/STjfycPFCS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZStuff about time. That will help with the balance of the side. To often been playing with keepers &amp; 'allrounders'. Need batters &amp; bowlers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dalecooknz @target_focus hope the team is #JuicedUp on some good silage 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deane_ag good point. Media used that word for the Bobby calf story I recall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emily_fear_less Govt doesn't lead innovation usually so not surprised @MPI_NZ use this 13th century word either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emily_fear_less not looking for a ephemism. A word that is relevant to the activity. 13th century 'slaughter' is not fit for purpose IMO.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deane_ag correct, and my point is slaughter is used to discribe other not nice things. We shouldn't refer to our animals bend slaughtered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikeonthehills @TheCountry @nzherald conveniently forget the industry that allow the practices]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annegalloway I can see how policy stuff gets hard with academics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annegalloway that is stuck in tradition thinking sorry.  Come up with a new word we don't 'slaughter' our animals sorry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annegalloway and we don't kill our animals in these inhumane ways that the old world of 'slaughter' depicts. So let's stop using it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annegalloway why stick with a word that's centuries old.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annegalloway is really. Hear 'slaughter' used all the time in relation to terror events and war crimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lewisridge_Farm @MorrisonFarming @m_herbert @farmgeek how did their solar power and insulation policies work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annegalloway lright then. Have this word part of your value chain along side it's use in terrorism etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MorrisonFarming @farmgeek @m_herbert what is it? A swiss - cheese dam?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fowell103 @mikeonthehills @ABC are they doing the same on all BBQs sold and toasters too? World is going mad. Media law vs science.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Set a poor example for ASB classic.
Use it for a travel stop to Australia. Tank in the 2nd round, Carbo-Loading. 
https://t.co/IwsQMjo3Nm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annegalloway 'Processing plants', 'Pocessed'. Don't use that other word]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annegalloway and we still use terms like 'slaughter', while most product is still sold frozen. Reduce the use of both please NZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iangriffin @PhilipDuncan might be able to help ya]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bills less of an isdtue thsn using tge tornament as a travel stop over to Australia. #Tanking #TakingthePiss https://t.co/NHy6zHPpZQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@farmgeek don't blame 'irrigation' per say on NZs slow and poor water &amp; nutrient regulation. Industry &amp; Govt at fault here. Not irrigation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@farmgeek AR a higher value that is more value for regions economy (spending multipler). Also enables downstream processing jobs / value!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@farmgeek Wairarapa in a dry year (most yrs) sell most lambs store at low $ to another region. If irrigation could allow these to leave 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@m_herbert @tutukaus @farmgeek to Will's point. The whole community would benefit. Just look at Ashburton or Timaru vs Masterton past 15yrs!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@m_herbert @tutukaus @farmgeek very good point!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HandsMegan @GrovesCole @NewstalkZB the group dressed as Yellow Seats keep buying up more and more tickets every year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This nonsense, if they do ban glyphosate, makes #Brexit &amp; #Thrumpy look irrelevant. https://t.co/igDclqgIyD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annegalloway @TMKuriger half of carrot, quite a lot of onion and brassica. Clearly not a third of world's for seeds though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LinkChinaGlobal @annegalloway sheep meat looks high for trade. Wouldnt think it would be 75%. Sheep meat moves about around the olace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iconic rural Wairarapa in this video clip #HuricaneLove - #LAWomen. KiaKaha https://t.co/eBtOKPmAXJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Slight shaking'. That was pretty good shaking especially for only a 4.0 https://t.co/gw88aTK0Jl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DairyCowQueen ha. Was going to suggest that...didn't want to offend any dairy farmers though 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahocnz @ABELCIDER yes it is dry, not like other NZ cider which hits you on first mouthful. Tfrom then it really becomes easy drinking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DairyCowQueen just a scary butcher by the looks of those carcasses 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lewisridge_Farm @StuartHusband @ccwnz @bushypark8 @nzherald weren't blaming just stating one such issue on a 'clean river'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahocnz @ABELCIDER it does that. Guess the whole bottle is finished now. Happy days ☺]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gregtheasp Regonal GMO Free, pretty blunt tool @FoxMarama. Food has GMO. Medicine too. Why not let growers have a choice too if available?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahocnz @ABELCIDER good pour there Sarah. Big week was it ☺]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LukeTipoki all NZ getting SA. Their home country going the way Zimbabwe did. Very unfortunate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StuartHusband @ccwnz @bushypark8 @nzherald @Lewisridge_Farm @sciblogsnz cant be that clean with the Carp mudding it up in the lower reaches]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StuartHusband @GrantRowanNZ @nzherald is that 'Ben' Benfield or 'Bill?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WgtnCC water leak at basin round about exit to airport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RozMackenzie what's this 1/3 of the world's food seeds?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZDairyFarmer keep the summer milk fliwing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HotMummyBerry @CharollaisRams Southlanders and their Texels! #SufTex #Tefroms, ....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HotMummyBerry @CharollaisRams why not stay as studs? Be time to sell ahead of mating decisions too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@THmanawatu conferences and shows for everything. Pick ya topic and go hunting the net]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@THmanawatu Ag Innovation Showcase a couple yrs back in St Louis was good. 2010 Nuffield CFC conference in WashingtonDC was great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@m_herbert oats if you after bulk winter feed. Will also be better with the wet than Triticale. 
Late March &amp; April sowing fine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Island, Aoteroa is a pretty special place @FlyAirNZ https://t.co/WEj6E945Ym]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aucklandcricket @lauramcgoldrick @Martyguptill Vincent could have got more....😯]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mavorafarms @Sam_Sheppo maybe next time. Was a bit pushed with flight out of Queenstown. Glad you farming 'Jerseys' down there...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sam_Sheppo @mavorafarms I was across the road at Mararoa Station ☺]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sam_Sheppo 13 tonight. Feels a v warm 13 after today's tropical Mavora @mavorafarms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wgtn evening feels like the tropics after being in Te Anau today! Was a balmy 6 degrees https://t.co/OJaqX6ovop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CentralStags wowza! That's a cracking run rate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blairdrysdale77 should be doing it for seed ☺]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KoanuiFarming good view bit too windy for a 🎣 https://t.co/az4n0236l3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Saarbo1 good question. A few options out there - Agrinet, Land &amp; Feed,  Pasture Coach, FarmIQ, Feed Flo....Then theres @Farmax feed modelin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Might be the next big Entertainment out of Masterton post Jermaine #FlightoftheConcordes &amp; Pip Brown #LadyHawke
https://t.co/eBtOKPmAXJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxMarama @LukeTipoki 2/2 taken for granted until there is no more'. Water has value. So value it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxMarama @LukeTipoki NZ is got a phobia to water 'ownership' tho. 'If you don't value the resource that creates the value, then it is 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxMarama @LukeTipoki a better system is a 'right to use'. Which is more like owning it. It decoupled water from land. Australia has this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxMarama @LukeTipoki some water is traded within irrigation schemes. It's not being 'sold', the consent to take is being traded.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxMarama @LukeTipoki the value the water provides from the consent is capitalised in the land price as you mentioned. They own the land...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hurricanesrugby welcome back @CoryJane1080. Hope your truck tyres didn't get slashed out by the airport while ya were away ☺]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CharollaisRams @m_herbert @willagriseeds pretty silly comparison. They are different types of ryegrass. Italians aren't for summer anyway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxMarama @LukeTipoki. It's not owned. Farmers have a 'consent to take'. Which is more like a lease to use it. So don't own it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@santalasatu @HelenClarkUNDP didn't much of this all start with droughts to the wheat areas in Syria. How's that all looking now. AGrecovery]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GaryMass6 @andrew_hoggard nice. That will help the Feed Wedge or supplement stack. @FarmaxNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jo_moir not sure 'shots fired' is a good segway into a story like this one in this day in age ☺
Looks like Andy Murray didnt hit many shots]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been a bit wet in the south too...Guess that means no fishing 🎣#Mataura #Gore https://t.co/WeNGYGl4w6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blairdrysdale77 sure are. Wairarapa has three. Only 40,000 odd people live there. To many 'elected councillor' &amp; mgmt overheads.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blairdrysdale77 I guess that is what they will claim. All Hawkes Bay to pay for Hastings DC bulls up. Should be only one HB council anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG. Shows that the Regulator (HBRC) is likely sleeping with the Local Authority.
'Polluter Pays' - not in the curr… https://t.co/7kEbgNKZAI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama has 4x more followers than #BigOrange. That's not going to change much when #BigOrange doesn't always agree w… https://t.co/Ow385p7fit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OrganicFarmerNZ @RadioLIVENZ big call...thought that was car salesmen and real estate agents 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikeonthehills @blairdrysdale77 wrong shade of green ☺]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They got the wrong day. Heaps came out the following day https://t.co/aFhLWrvwLs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@veitchynz @nzheraldsport they spanked us over there. If we want their best players we need to perform. Why we playing them again so soon?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proposed irrigation scheme cuts costs as build nears - Rural News Group https://t.co/fibJBP2VXC via @Rural_News]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very true Dean. Can't believe the @GreenpeaceNZ ad didn't get banned. Using Tannin stained water and suggesting it… https://t.co/pszaefpNis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MorrisonFarming @theofficenz @GemmaHain get an rain out of this stuff?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GreenpeaceNZ @mikeonthehills @NZSharemilker @AdamFricker @andrew_hoggard a measure by 'river length is just STUPID!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GreenpeaceNZ @mikeonthehills @NZSharemilker @AdamFricker @andrew_hoggard they are often the same rivers. Plus urban directly into estuarys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RozMackenzie @ballomes @NZSharemilker is that based on the 5km virual weather stations Roz?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blairdrysdale77 your harvester the wrong colour too 😂 🚜 https://t.co/sLrdB1JSns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garry_reymer @Saarbo1 @tutukaus not that keen on resource / pollution taxes. But industry not set water &amp; nutrient limits=Others will do it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garry_reymer @Lewisridge_Farm @bushypark8 @andrew_hoggard @ktmilne6 put it through an AD plant. Make power, then use the dried nutrients.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pregtester @fairleigh_ag built in sinkers.
Can't be killing native Puks tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilipDuncan only 18mm over Tikoki way according to @WoolstonDavid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WoolstonDavid bugger. It's a start I guess. Hope some more makes it your way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WoolstonDavid get some good rain up there Dave?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@4aron_Baker @PhilipDuncan nice Aaron. Good to hear]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>