<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Early start tomorrow &amp; shld be asleep but hve to watch all of John Aldridge @Realaldo474 interview on #RTE.Great memories of a great player.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cris_GamboaCR @celticfc Thanks for all your hard work. We]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is a great time to be a Celtic supporter.Thank you Brendan Rodgers. I haven't enjoyed it so much since Martin O'Neill was manager #Celtic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rachel_Lynchx he is past it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eamon de Valera gave great service to the Irish people. Vandalising his grave is an attack on all of us. I am sad that this could happen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaudineKeane1 Send him back to Celtic!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatMcA sounds like a good plan Pat! Thanks again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Douglas Hyde (born 157 years ago today) made an outstanding contribution to our nation.It's been a great adventure… https://t.co/EIYU1OUHXE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatMcA @Robert_Mauro here it is Pat. hope all is good with you.  Brexit and NI crisis.
https://t.co/zKVpOFsOYT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robert_Mauro Glad you enjoyed it Bob. See you next time you are in Dublin hopefully.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DDGriffin92 @DouglasHyde1 @PresidentIRL Thanks Daniel I am glad you enjoyed it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CelticLisboa thanks for this account. Some terrific memories. Well done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaudineKeane1 what a fantastic player for Ireland.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not exactly Ireland of the welcomes. A terrible experience for these young ladies. And this could do our tourist in… https://t.co/Jl8KMeMkn2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did I write a book about Douglas Hyde? Answer attached! 
https://t.co/Owf4vrF0j8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good review of my book on Douglas Hyde 
https://t.co/xtWyQUOCKE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a load of codswallop! Humanitarian crisis in UK hospitals. Ordinary people can't get in the doors but the Quee… https://t.co/8kGUGDH0J0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Ham must be having a laugh.Dembele is worth double what they have offered. And why wld he leave Celtic for a team who will win nothing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Moorerichardpr yep. The other clubs lack Celtic's ambition and support base. If Celtic were in EPL they would shake things up there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Moorerichardpr Their keeper was man of the match. Celtic on a different level. Dembele is quality, but Griffiths will score more goals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hats off to Brendan Rodgers. Celtic are at another level to other sides in Scotland.  The tribute act are an embarrassment to the old Gers!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK Labour Advisor essentially tells us what Haughey said a long time ago. N. Ireland is a failed political entity. 
https://t.co/jSkxSrBBhR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Delaney would do his public standing a lot of good if he told FIFA where to stick their 1916 jersey fine
https://t.co/EKX5ZS7Lig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amateur Boxing should be turfed out of Olympics. Fining Michael Conlan after robbing him of a medal is pathetic. https://t.co/ygNHsBZoDm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_mickyc_ @eir @Meteor_Mobile i have been having them for two days and they still haven't sorted me out. terrible customer service]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eir @eircare that the issue would be resolved shortly.  a total shutdown on Sunday.  shocking customer service............]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eir @eircare the worst customer service i have ever experienced. i am still without a service, despite being assured on Saturday evening]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So after over 24 hours trying to contact @eir @eircare they tell me to send an email which may be dealt with it in about 6hours #whatajoke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@a_martin33 delighted he also mentioned Forgotten Patriot about Douglas Hyde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eircare an absolute joke of a service. can't contact you online on sunday  because no one is working. and the service fault is on your side]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eircare this is not the case i ring 1901 and it tells me i am not registered with eir. i am registered. you take money off me every month]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dmcbfs i am sure you will do even better,  hope to see you soon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dmcbfs terrific well done]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Internet service on my phone down since Sat afternoon.  No customer services reps working on a Sunday. Time for me and @eir to part company]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am not a regular cinema-goer, but Sully is the best movie I have seen in years. It is definitely worth watching #Sully]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donnchanuig @irishexaminer thanks Donnacha.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reach? They won it and they won it in style! https://t.co/Ihx46hIUav]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SuzieCoog @IrishTimesBooks thanks Suzie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LarryPDonnelly thanks Larry!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Douglas Hyde’s legacy has been particularly ill-served by Irish historians.
https://t.co/Owf4vrF0j8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done Celtic. Far too good for Aberdeen today. Brendan Rodgers reminds me of Martin O'Neill and that is a big compliment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Fidel Castro nearly met Charles Haughey https://t.co/kMvTiQ6Z3Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrainneDaly1981 Not a bad performance in the end!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootballInT80s @Ian_Rush9 what a player he was. Would have loved to have seen him play for Celtic!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArdgillanHist @DouglasHyde1 He was a great man and someone we can all respect. Thanks for the positive feedback.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArdgillanHist @DouglasHyde1 Thank you. I hope you are enjoying it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SineadB_ @DouglasHyde1 great to see you Sinead and we will catch up again soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irelandsocshirt @CollinsPress @FAIreland @okmick sounds like a winner of a book Eddie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rachel_Lynchx @stephenoreg he could not get a game with the mighty LA Galaxy in the end. A great player  but now past it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jamesmcguinne20 @Rachel_Lynchx Would take James McCarthy over Gerrard any day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rachel_Lynchx no thanks. he is past it and will take a huge wage. the players we have are better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annieemac_X @celticfc i hope it doesn't. he'll take a big wage &amp; is past it. he was a flop in LA. the young midfielders we have are better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ireland top of the group &amp; looking a good bet for Russia.James McCarthy &amp; Aiden McGeady must be delighted they chose Ireland over Scotland!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ronanodomhnaill he is the Mike Pence of the operation!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrainneDaly1981 the best in business!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought @DavidMeyler7 was immense when he came on. His best game for Ireland']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a win!!! I have said it before again and I will say it again, Martin O'Neill is a genius!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't go deep Ireland. Do your defending further up the pitch!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ireland one up. Terrific goal by McClean, set up by Hoolohan. Don't go deep Ireland!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gerrard was a fantastic footballer, but he is past it now. Can't get into LA Galaxy team. Why would Celtic sign him? https://t.co/r6cjrTwIsP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonnyfallon I am moving on to Sean T. next.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonnyfallon thanks Johnny. Really glad you enjoyed the book.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Article from the @RoscommonPeople about the GAA's shocking expulsion of Douglas Hyde in 1938
https://t.co/NUHvhcm8Ky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strong analysis on RTE1 right now from @LarryPDonnelly on why so many Americans voted for @realDonaldTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annieemac_X whatever about his posh coffee machine, I bet he won't be drinking Green Tea anytime soon!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annieemac_X the self proclaimed best player in Scotland #ComedyGold]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's been a long time coming. Well done to Ireland on beating the All Blacks. #great]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Nobody won any medals' in this debacle. Strong analysis from @jfjohnston  https://t.co/llhC8cZqzm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annieemac_X Agree. They are charging Ireland retrospectively to justify their row with FA and SFA. Hope @FAIreland tell FIFA where to go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SleevesElliott @FIFAcom pity they didn't take such a righteous stance when Thierry Henry cheated us out of the World Cup!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mrs May shld have said in a democracy there is freedom of choice &amp; individuals shld not be pressurized to wear Poppy https://t.co/3uj83CHtP0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dr_Brian_Hunt thanks Brian. Hope to see you soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ciara_OLeary7 very well done and good wishes to your grandad, your dad and your uncle Pierce, a Scottish Cup winner with Celtic in 1985!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delighted to see Forgotten Patriot, Douglas Hyde book, is number 7 in the national bestsellers list. https://t.co/PzM6fSQjdv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ntwamley @jmkirl thanks Niall!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmkirl thanks Jeanne. You are very kind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ciara_OLeary7 best wishes to all your family and good luck with the marathon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ciara_OLeary7 sorry to hear this news. The O'Learys all great football people in Ireland and widely respected. Hope he is on the mend soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EamonDelaney10 @DouglasHyde1 thanks very much Eamon and hope to see you soon!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MDevineOCallagh @SineadB_ thanks Mary for making it a great success!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SineadB_ thanks sinead. Looking forward to catching up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SineadB_ Sinead great to see you and your Dad. Thanks for coming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to the Roscommon launch of Forgotten Patriot, Douglas Hyde book. Tomorrow, Friday, 6pm in Frenchpark! All welcome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatsyMcGarryIT thanks Patsy. An article you wrote in Magill on Hydr many years ago was a big inspiration. Hope to catch up with you soon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JS_D9 @DouglasHyde1 Thanks very much John. Glad you enjoyed and great to see you the other night!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should be a good night on Friday in Frenchpark. Roscommon launch of Forgotten Patriot. https://t.co/64zvMkHnPI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FeargalORourke May she rest in peace. Sorry for your loss. A wonderful, decent, intelligent lady.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DeclanHarmon Thanks Declan!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great win for Celtic and well deserved! Take a bow Brendan Rodgers!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatMcA thanks very much Pat. Hope to catch up with you soon. B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MDevineOCallagh thanks Mary for your kind support and help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CllrMcGuinness thanks Dave. Hope to see you soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delighted to see Forgotten Patriot is top of the bestsellers list. Thanks to everyone for their support &amp; interest… https://t.co/4jHwTQ3QBs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Loughlin_Deegan unreal. Thanks!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dangers of Brexit. Strong analysis from @jfjohnston  https://t.co/J875gwkWv0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jfjohnston @HydeWhiskey @AlbaImport @irlembberlin @Bordbia it is 6pm!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonnachaMaguire thanks Donnacha, hoping to see you Wed and hoping u are enjoying the book.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donnchanuig @wordpressdotcom he will be sadly missed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vallmeister @Hodges_Figgis @mcculld @KZapponeTD @SenatorMcDowell on Wednesday rather! It'll help if i get day right for my own launch!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vallmeister @Hodges_Figgis @mcculld @KZapponeTD @SenatorMcDowell cheers Aaron,-looking forward to seeing you on Monday.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>