<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@PalmerReport @DailyNewsBin I wouldn't be surprised to find out that Trump made comments on this deal during the campaign and then forgot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rmasher2 IMO 'Trump thinks of the USA only as a theater and of We the People as his audience. #ImpeachTrump #CalExit #TheResistance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NaphiSoc This major crisis getting is getting only minimal coverage on CNN but a  protest at UC Berkeley is getting hours of live coverage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timewarden1 @Slate Trump's "coup" is just a distraction. The Tea Party Congress assumed control of the USA in Constitutional elections.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@machonejack IMO there's going to be an economic meltdown before the 2018 election. #CalExit #BlueAmerica #TheResiostance #RevolutionNOW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrSpock2017 IMO the Demos in Congress should try to block EVERYTHING the Tea Partiers attempt. #ShutItDown #TheReistance #CalExkit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sammypolsen12 @realDonaldTrump IMO, "pro-choice" makes perfect sense but "pro-life" as used by the anti-abortion crowd is total nonsense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AUkeibro IMHO there's no significant difference between "engaging in serious journalism" &amp; "not promoting the Trump agenda". #TheResistance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MtnMD I second that BIGTIME, and IMO the Demos in Congress should also try to block EVERYTHING the Tea Partiers try to do. #TheResistance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rmasher2 I agree BIGTIME, and IMO the Demos in Congress should also try to block EVERYTHING the Tea Partiers try to do.#TheResistance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepMarkTakano Meaning let him wait in limbo till 2020 and then be replaced by whoever the new Demo President appoints.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnWDean It's not just Trump. Similar events in many countries are going to trigger economic meltdowns and revolutions all over the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@punkdinok IMO, it doesn't matter because the center isn't going to hold. We're headed for economic meltdown and eventual revolution.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LouisatheLast Yes! They're just scarecrows. The farmers are the Tea Partiers who will trash them &amp; claim they saved the USA from fascism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IMO Bannon and Trump are just scarecrows. The farmers are the Tea Partiers in Congress, who plan to "save the USA from fascists".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deejay90192 @HouseDemocrats  In the 60's, when some said "We need a revolution," I said "The center will hold." I'm no longer saying that..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA In the Sixties, when people claimed we needed Revolution, I said the center would hold. That's no longer true. #RevolutionNow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DHStokyo @BillieO2 @peterdaou I'm watching the Dollar and the Dow, not the polls at the moment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samueloakford IMO, nothing went wrong. The Trump regime is simply ordering its forces to carry out a fascist scorched earth polic.y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VanJones68 IMO #TheResistance is also defenders of the Constitution against those who no longer follow it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinMKruse @PressSec Everything the Trumpsters say is a lie and everything they try to do fails but they keep right on anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jodotcom People didn't believe Trump because most of what he said was impossible. They didn't realize he's crazy enough to try and fail.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jbouie It won't last long, A financial collapse is coming and after that the Second American Revolution.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MythiliSk @amazinmikey It looks like the Trump regime is trying to scare all Americans into unconditional surrender. No way. We'll fight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NaphiSoc I'm talking about things like immediate increases in state-funded social services and preparations for direct foreign trade.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NaphiSoc The USA is going to melt down before the formal CalExit is on the books. That's why I say we should act now on the economic level.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rmasher2 However, IMO history will be just as harsh on the Demos who allowed this whole sorry mess to happen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA I haven't yet bothered to even find out who Trump picked. His whole regime is marching towards the edge of a cliff anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterdaou And they're not only doing it at breakneck speed, they're blatantly obvious about it. Don't they realize they'll go down too?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuddLegum It's now obvious that Trump is going to continue running his business empire himself and his children will help him govern]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaloneRuth In normal times, government officials keep watch on one another along party lines so the people don't have to get involved]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SusanStoneSalas @realDonaldTrump From what I've heard, it's just as obvious as Ivanka's son being autistic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Christi65580271 IMO both the governments and voters of other democratic nations are less naive about such things t… https://t.co/8OuYaXmlKc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RanchDressingTN I'm 74 and remember all of these Presidents except FDR. Especially things like Eisenhower endorsin… https://t.co/AHOwKYQ5Sq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GiGicmka @groopspeak I suspect Trump will cancel this vacation the same as did the one scheduled for the weekend a… https://t.co/1OmhmA9enm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barrytgoldberg Most disgusting of all even Hitler and Stalin usually didn't handcuff small children being locked u… https://t.co/ajTLfwljBX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BettyBowers Only if he breaks the law, but Trump seems to be doing that right and left. #ImpeachTrump #TheResistance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Emolclause The MSM are owned by the same plutocrats who own the Tea Party GOP through their contributions. IMO bot… https://t.co/5YT0iMnmav]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisMurphyCT @aalali44 I'm wondering how soon we'll be able to chase "The Newt" back under his rock, where he can… https://t.co/OGXHombQ67]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KenRoth @nytimes I assume DT will end up firing them all: the amateur sailor made captain of a big ship firing the… https://t.co/RZnWBrXUG5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NetflixMulhouse IMO, If Britain backs out of a state visit by Trump, that's a sign that he's losing all credibilit… https://t.co/ZieOYMHQpA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DumpTrumpWatch @KatheleenMitro The reality is that America was at it's greatest under liberals: FDR, Truman, Eisen… https://t.co/x2Tal3bkkb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA @KCStar IMO, DT is hoping he can muzzle the MSM and social media before enough info of this type gets o… https://t.co/EWVNdPagSd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@forditude1968 @MybestgirlHolly @nbc4i IMO, Trump's "America First" doesn't mean isolationism, but a form of neo-co… https://t.co/U7Kl6zrSub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McFaul Despots throughout history have replaced the term meaning "opponents" with a pejorative It started in relig… https://t.co/J2BaVKekN3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@montfam ALL government officials from the President on down are required to follow the Constitution. So is everyon… https://t.co/MEfkiJbCCk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annie_sparrow @AP DT seems to believes the majority of Americans are OK with bigotry &amp; fascism. We need to prove h… https://t.co/BVuWuKpSuW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ericgarland Yes! The new captain of the ship has no experience at sea and he's replacing the crew with syncophants… https://t.co/bRuCSbmCaG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarolineLucas @julievonessen I still don't know if he's a bigot and fascist or if he's or just insane, but it does… https://t.co/ezMtiPhlPb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SusanStoneSalas @realDonaldTrump Somebody should post a poll: "Is Trump really batshit crazy, or is he just preten… https://t.co/G4sahQoBRl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer @bannerite As I interpret the Constitution, it's not "should" but "is required to". Trump apparently se… https://t.co/YJ30UUAywR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuddLegum @marcylauren @thinkprogress IMO, Trump expects to use Sessions and the other outright fascists on his st… https://t.co/XHfFA6J3S5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NetflixMulhouse I agree. IMO, we're headed for an economic meltdown and a Second American Revolution, scary as tha… https://t.co/2hpbLCbcCJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AUkeibro I agree with you and actually expect a total economic collapse followed by a Second American Revolution.… https://t.co/corZKaYu2B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tina_donahoo Yeah, I've always been fond of Jerry Brown and wish he'd been nominated and elected back in the day.… https://t.co/olotmw1dh3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@randyprine I'm hoping that both Obama and Hillary keep a low profile as the Trump regime self-destructs.… https://t.co/NQoNNYDsQT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@holachola I'm now hoping that Trump will cause a revolution before the Tea Partiers are able to force him out of o… https://t.co/ByQWjISvX8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonKander If the economy tanks, as now looks probable, Trump's appointments and executive orders are going to be… https://t.co/vIxtSAQepJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carmenlynn1970 @TeaPainUSA @realDonaldTrump Nah, Trump applied for the position of AntiChrist but the Devil told h… https://t.co/roXYMBqCO4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@existingtoday @peterdaou Yes! The Dollar is falling and so is the Dow Jones, so it may be time to call for a Gener… https://t.co/cPYgpPfM0T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vox_corvi IMO there's more to it than looks. Bannon is also the guy who got thrown out of the homeless shelter for fighting. #ImpeachTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IMPL0RABLE Every new room I enter these days seems to contain still another ticking clock. Is the explosion days a… https://t.co/qQVaBheidN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gollum1419_g @tina_donahoo Yes! And I wonder what affect this Monday Night Massacre will have on the monetary exch… https://t.co/VXM5jdsiK7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RicknShira IMO Trump's "basket of deplorables" may have morphed into a bucket and will start leaking soon.… https://t.co/H62y14enS3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA Yup, it sure is. But I suspect if you do a poll on "Will trump use nukes?" it will yield results that a… https://t.co/D5WfVgxS9M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NaphiSoc Yes! The Dollar is in free fall and the Dow Jones may soon follow it. Is this the beginning of the crash… https://t.co/HJR2ac3Vbr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterdaou Yes! Patriotism, moral integrity, and plain old common sense. #ImpeachTrump #BlueNation #TheResistance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NaphiSoc That doesn't bother me. I'm just hoping that he doesn't also have the most chaotic END of a presidency in… https://t.co/X3jlaB2w0U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SheWhoVotes Or for that matter, a powerful argument in favor of the "pro-choice" movement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA @realDonaldTrump Yes, and Nixon was also a skilled professional political leader, though somewhat on th… https://t.co/ps8kRhXAST]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@soapboxsteve Yes! Take away his mike and headphones and he looks like a guy who got kicked out of the homeless she… https://t.co/773GYXnTVD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pikminister @TeaPainUSA @intelligencer I expect Trump may try to make a nuclear first strike, but I'm hoping the a… https://t.co/ooVIPs3J20]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@imafaust @funder @deejay90192 Trump obviously has no ethics or morals at all. Ihope that people who do have them w… https://t.co/9hQS9K6sJ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaryCipolla3 @CherokeeNative3 I don't even know if there are detailed records of the total money received from pay… https://t.co/gNbslgc00a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AUkeibro IMO, it's more important the We the People convince them by our actions that we're going to win in the en… https://t.co/yu5LhL6Myj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pikminister @TeaPainUSA Yeah, I'd like to see such a poll ... and Trump has already said, "As long as we have nuke… https://t.co/ViUCuk9e4k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jk_rowling @abutler04 IMO, "lone wolf" is oxymoronic even when applied to an animal. Wolves, like humans, find it… https://t.co/ZTrmHKKRXe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deejay90192 IMO, Trump's operational orders that violate the Constitution are all the :paper trail" we need to fig… https://t.co/ETTdQmp35c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NaturaSacra @fshakir And "the conscience of America" isn't a pious abstraction. It's "We the People" who founded t… https://t.co/EGHiRksV1S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@imillhiser I hope so, but any lawyer can present briefs to any federal judge asking to have EO's declared illegal… https://t.co/hxEi4BCwwV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA @globeandmail Isn't this a good reason to treat "White Nationalists" the same as we treat "ISIS sympath… https://t.co/dCpjL58np2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kurteichenwald True, but CNN kept on covering the story the last I checked. I wonder if they'll eventualy bail as… https://t.co/wFZDOXtmyK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AugustLady241 The Tea Partiers may survive defunding PP, but IMO, if they attack Social Security and Medicare, the… https://t.co/VO1YuWWNqw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA It's the same logic right wingers use to defend corrupt cops who murder people in hopes of "reducing ga… https://t.co/PJ9zdNO7l4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterdaou This is true, and IMO, things are going to get a hell of a lot worse before they get better.… https://t.co/X5iUpFILQO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA Hell, I'll be surprised if he doesn't do it within the next four weeks ... or maybe even days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TenaciousMutt I suspect that both Obama and Clinton are afraid to actively oppose Trump or they would already have… https://t.co/iUTIER3Lj0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AUkeibro True. But all military officers have sworn to uphold the Constitution, &amp; if Trump is violating its provis… https://t.co/4TZeh1bdv3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaryCipolla3 @CherokeeNative3 Actually, the popular belief that SS payments are kept separate from other taxes is… https://t.co/slomWzhIFs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PirateWench1989 @nobanjfk @PortableRockArt IMO, the first step to removing him is to join or support the demonstra… https://t.co/bpe7rV01vV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelNoTrump Millions of people all over the world are now demonstrating against Trump, and IMO, that's a good f… https://t.co/ChXKYdhmBm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ivanroberson @Forbes Yes! The handwriting is fnally beginning to appear on the wall. #ImpeachTrump #TheResistance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AgeDemands IMO, more Americans are realizing this every day. What this country needs most right now is "one less T… https://t.co/FFs25ZZhLf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LisaLimonTx Yes! Anti-Trump demonstrations are taking place all over the world, most with the blessing of the loca… https://t.co/2GCFAlOIt1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelNoTrump Right now, it looks like Trump may not last long enough to sign his commission. #TheResistance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MonicaFalkin @swoozyqyah @realDonaldTrump Yes! Trump is attacking the Constitution itself, not realizing this is r… https://t.co/33P8nQjqJB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rmasher2 And these protesters include politicians and lawyers who realize Trump has attacked the Constitution itse… https://t.co/mCfMiHY7rc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeaPainUSA @FoxNews This is what I'd expect of Fox, but I'm pleasantly surprised that CNN s still covering this story. #TheResistence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rmasher2 IMO, the USA will survive, but the Trump Presidency's chances are getting slimmer every day. He's about t… https://t.co/WY9lYc58uf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisJZullo Maybe so. The first step, of course, will be stamping out Donald Trump and his fascist takeover of the USA. #TheResistance]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>