<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Um, what? Sean Spicer just used an attack against Muslims to justify a ban on Muslims. The world is upside down. https://t.co/YfU8jkpYYs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Projections on the side of the @EPA building in DC right now opposing Scott Pruitt. #PollutingPruitt #RejectPruitt https://t.co/dWUbid6wU9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drvox @voxdotcom Adding "tribal epistemology" to my lexicon, a relevant term for these times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BadHombreNPS Do they dig holes so they can stick their heads in the sand?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#DeVosFacts:
2+2=4
2+2=3
2+2=5

Oh, wait, that was George Orwell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want an example of runaway global warming? Look to Venus; its atmosphere is mostly CO₂ and its average temperature is 462°C. #ClimateFacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ClimateFacts &gt; #AlternativeFacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solar accounted for 43% of electricity generation jobs in 2016. Fossil fuels? 22%. #ClimateFacts… https://t.co/aeJWciI1G7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chants of "Keep it in the Soil, You Can't Drink Oil" outside the White House. #NoKXL #NoDAPL https://t.co/F79kzo6czp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scene right now at the White House. Signs reading "Honors the Treaties" and "Defend the Sacred." #NoKXL #NoDAPL https://t.co/0cqsGrZWWY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protest outside the White House to oppose Trump's executive actions supporting Keystone XL and Dakota Access pipeli… https://t.co/fHSyGg3JFG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The date is wrong on the picture. Just thought you'd want to know. https://t.co/Sor2PHiC08]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #WomensMarch is set to be the largest protest in U.S. history. Humbled to have marched with so many passionate… https://t.co/YLUOwsd9Ql]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inspiring by the events of the #WomensMarch today? Join the #PeoplesClimate March in D.C. on April 29! https://t.co/QfsrXZZz9S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump says BuzzFeed is fake news, so take this quiz instead and compare your perception to reality. https://t.co/Y0m0NMoUXB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the candidates are being so...nice to each other. Is this politics? It's so amiable. #DNCdebate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didn't expect that one. What does "a few things" mean? https://t.co/pYoyHkjWCj https://t.co/ydnrI64FEq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drvox And if the assumption that officials will tackle an issue holds, advocacy and accountability seem unnecessary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drvox This low bar is dangerous. It gives the public a false sense that officials will fight climate change since they "believe" in it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KamalaHarris Thank you for your commitment to the safety of the American people from environmental harms!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This alternating questioning from Republican and Democrat EPW members shows how they're living in two disparate political universes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenDuckworth calling out Pruitt for his "nice-sounding but ultimately vague and hollow mantra." #PollutingPruitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenMarkey: "Will you recuse yourself from lawsuits you brought against EPA as Oklahoma AG if you head EPA?"

No clear answer from Pruitt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pruitt talking about "establishing clarity." Maybe he should focus his efforts on maintaining the clarity of water and air. #PollutingPruitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While #PollutingPruitt refuses to accept the science of climate change, the world around him is warming. https://t.co/lxmAv45XUd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FiveThirtyEight It's compelling that Congress' approval was consistently so low except the years before the Republican takeover in 2010.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[173 environmental and health organizations have signed a letter opposing Scott Pruitt. #PollutingPruitt https://t.co/v736xguUxP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scott Pruitt would undermine the EPA's mission of protecting human health and the environment. #PollutingPruitt https://t.co/JCrWmDhpCT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protecting corporate proprietary information should not be more important than protecting public health. https://t.co/PLUpQpgQ8X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BillNye #MakeConferencesCoolAgain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The entire American public waiting for the GOP's replacement to Obamacare like...

#SaveACA #ACA #ACARepeal https://t.co/soU6yVTY75]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This too, but six times for Trump. https://t.co/ba1WyxFsvk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And this. https://t.co/ksOnjniVTT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's also this. https://t.co/YnTf4HbkDl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael Scott is a benevolent Donald Trump.

Both are self-centered, insensitive, uninformed, and have a desperate need to be liked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Thanks for providing the location. I thought it might be taking place in Moscow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump That's the spirit! Set your expectations low and it'll surely be a success!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2,400 MW = power for 1,250,000 homes
https://t.co/0MUdAyxLRF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EIAgov report: 2016 saw 63% of new elec. generation capacity from #renewables, 24 GW of capacity added overall.… https://t.co/PAYVJfcSKa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unexpected realization of the day: Elaine Chao, Trump's pick to head Dept. of Transportation, is married to turtle man Mitch McConnell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump: "The only people who care about my tax returns are the reporters."

Americans: "WRONG."… https://t.co/XG7sbZPpzO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump: "As far as hacking, I think it was Russia."

Baby steps. #TrumpPressConference]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The president-elect has more pressing issues to address than his ad hoc business deal on the cost of the F-35 program. #TrumpPressConference]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoogleTrends shows searches for "conflict of interest" twice as popular in Nov. 2016 than any time since 2004. https://t.co/MwjLoi0zzd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't wait for Obama to be a private citizen again, what an activist and organizer he'll be. #ObamaFarewell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The real question: Where is Sasha? #ObamaFarewell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The most important office in democracy: citizen." This should implore us all to be more informed and empathetic. #ObamaFarewell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The subtext of Obama's last point on democracy: repeal Citizens United and undo inequitable gerrymandering. #ObamaFarewell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Our democracy is threatened whenever we take it for granted." #ObamaFarewell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Our children won't have the time to debate the existence of climate change." NEITHER DO WE THOUGH #ObamaFarewell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama making vital points about confirmation bias in American society. #ObamaFarewell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The effects of slavery and Jim Crow didn't just vanish in the '60s." #ObamaFarewell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Too many families in our inner cities and rural counties have been left behind." The key word here is "and." #ObamaFarewell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to @tanehisicoates for the beauty and heartbreak that is this story and for eloquently depicting a world I'l… https://t.co/aJ36Nzooh2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plus, there's this. https://t.co/7TYtm9GAT4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kushner expected to be a senior adviser to Trump. Get the man a dictionary so he can look up "nepotism." Better yet, read the whole thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarackObama authors an article on #cleanenergy and #climatechange in @sciencemagazine. https://t.co/0YqEE3BCbT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats should just delay Trump's SCOTUS pick for the next four years. 2021 isn't that far away!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The GOP delayed Merrick Garland's hearing for 10 months but won't delay for Trump's cabinet picks despite incomplete ethics reports?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Earth2Trump Your properties in Miami, Manhattan, and Scotland are at risk from sea level rise. Climate change affects you too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The GOP hates big government but apparently not when it comes to a 2,000+ mile border wall and controlling women's health services access.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's 2017. You have Netlix. Watch the documentary "13th."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man next to me on the metro today was reading from his Fox News app while I read NYT. What a microcosm of the U.S. left-right divide.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CityLab interview with @c40cities' Mark Watts about role of #food and #inequality issues for #climatechange in 2017 https://t.co/01X2sZsEOx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With No Warning, House Republicans Vote to Hobble Independent Ethics Office https://t.co/LkuBz7GTsF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Essentially, the office monitoring unethical behavior in Congress will be controlled Congress itself and will not report to the public.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOP is replacing the Office of Congressional Ethics with a "complaint review" office. An honest name since it will be devoid of any ethics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["American society increasingly mistakes intelligence for human worth." https://t.co/WxUX7OKCRa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep it up, 2017! Some great civil disobedience from #NoDAPL protestors at @usbankstadium to kick off the new year. https://t.co/ffVqOtxnPD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love!" says Donald as he belittles the people who oppose him... https://t.co/zsx1vOg1r5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such devastating beauty. "Elegy for the Arctic" performed next to a melting glacier in Svalbard, Norway. https://t.co/WxlC5Zb09U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never been fearful of nuclear war, but it's 2016 and the president-elect tweets cryptic shit like this so I gu… https://t.co/yD7rGMkr1R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpeakerRyan on whether he denies Trump’s claim of millions of fraudulent votes: “I don’t know; it doesn’t matter to me.”

This is scary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautifully artistic, fascinating representations of the world. https://t.co/8KJvhq95QD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The irony of Trump's call to "drain the swamp" is that rising sea levels are going to fill the swamp.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Equality is about being equal. Equity is about fairness. Our recognition of the difference is vital.

[Image credit… https://t.co/BXvxOQnHts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proud of my alma mater today! Hopkins reaffirms its support for DACA, the privacy and security of its affiliates. https://t.co/Vfbrr9n9BZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wind is now the cheapest power source in America. Costs shown are $/MWh, reflect unsubsidized cost of renewables.… https://t.co/S5dF5TaegT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The clean energy transition isn't even about stopping #climatechange anymore; it's just smart #economics.  https://t.co/FzpeTLVveR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JerryBrownGov at #AGU16 last week. To Rick Perry: "[CA] has more sun than [Texas has] oil, and we're gonna use it." https://t.co/zm8GiZa9BX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who would've guessed? https://t.co/Dg20KHZim5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant story map about income inequality in U.S. major cities. Dense with information and implications. https://t.co/A6gO8dqYLo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These are all the areas in the (contiguous) U.S. where Clinton got more than 50% of the vote, i.e. blue voters are… https://t.co/Qnl670eFIo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Agreed! The level of name-calling would be unpresidented!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[oligarchy (noun): a small group of people having control of a country.

17 Trump nominees have more wealth than 43,000,000 U.S. households.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you, @MichaelEMann, for standing up for climate science and remaining committed to truth despite decades of personal attacks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Account of the threatening and harmful opposition to scientific truth from climate deniers, including politicians. https://t.co/KPiV9uhAut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In an alternate universe, President-elect Bill Gates just nominated Elon Musk to head the Department of Energy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scary political dueling going on here. https://t.co/YqROKCKgKe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CleanEnergy gets a (modest) boost in MI! New bill increases renewable elec. standard, bolsters energy efficiency. https://t.co/OYW0uWwhkj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pewresearch Has similar polling been done before? Would be interested see how older generations have changed their rankings over time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["White neighborhoods stubbornly remain whiter than the larger areas they’re in." From @CityLab:… https://t.co/66Z6MA8AxM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump team member taking #climate denial to a new level. https://t.co/iEQLCtOUpp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inspiring leadership from @JerryBrownGov at #AGU16, reaffirming California's commitment to fighting #climatechange. https://t.co/3DcWHQqanx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ENERGY You've seen the benefits of wind energy in Texas, @GovernorPerry. Will you support it at DOE?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a terrifying possibility https://t.co/4zK50ontWu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JSully27 @TheAtlantic I read the first section on my commute this morning. This man knows how to structure an essay like no one else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost @sierraclub As they should!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A huge step forward for #cleanenergy! https://t.co/ULgzR8vaVa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New resource that examines credibility of news articles about #climate #science. Useful in this new #posttruth era. https://t.co/xc0q94jCmU]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>