<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@brad_barrett @SteveSaretsky @dcochranesbrain @Silver_Watchdog   Meanwhile, rates are going up.  Just got this last… https://t.co/KbOw8ErKww]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndyRay08  leaders are supposed to be accountable TO the public, not FOR them, so if public elects crazy leaders, why punish the elected?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndyRay08   Hahaha, sounds familiar, and then the US got Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@horse_poo @YVRHousing  Um, didn't you hear?  The housing bubble problem has been resolved through lowering of prices.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BallSixOFour @TrackieJimber @bcliberals hopefully the majority can see this for what it is, and SHOWS UP TO VOTE in May.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrackieJimber @bcliberals I guess these maroons don't understand that empty homes = empty restaurants, theatres, shops = empty city]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@horse_poo baby don't hurt me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@M_C_Klein @horse_poo  wat?  Nothing wrong with a father figure.  Maybe they could coin a new phrase, like oh, I don't know...FatherLand?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YVRHousing  I see what's happening here.  When a correction ensues, they spin it as "problem solving", like death is a solution for living.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billchow747 @BetterDwelling  Don't care for sob-story.  Our homes r meant to house people who live and work here, Not meant to shelter $$]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YVRHousing @SteveSaretsky observations in my 'hood; low sales since June, listings slowly expiring, only sfd selling is hi-end, devs gone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@penultsquire @KathyTGlobe @JEVLloyd shhhhhhhh!  Stop giving them ideas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey #vanre, is the Chinese New Year property-buying frenzy over?  Did I miss it? https://t.co/uS2lwOdW0B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BCNewsWire  The irony of China saving us from themselves is almost too much for my brain.  Meanwhile, CC Libs keep trying to sell us out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hmacbe  I can't believe how much I hope that the uptick was the trap.  Please tell me it was]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@penultsquire @StephenPunwasi @rosskay @ewsiddall @TorontoStar 
Do you mean to tell me that a RE board lied??  But why?  O I know! Greed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bcpoli  as far as counting credit as an asset, that's just bad economics. That's the kind of logic that has put us into 167% debt ratios]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bcpoli @bcliberals  I don't believe anything they spew.  The BC Libs have become a spin machine for the RE cartel and 4n invest/launderers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bcpoli   Haha, obvs!  Isn'tt that how it's done?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@INTEGRITYBC  So many flip flops https://t.co/azKJ3Weoig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lainiesoleil77  Let the crushing begin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crimecitySurrey  if parking was free, and parking bylaw officers were eliminated, I wonder if the salary savings would pay for lost revenue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@INTEGRITYBC 
WHAT?!?
Nightmare politics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@penultsquire quite likely.  SFD sales numer was 10.  My point was that the prices are way up again. m/m, q/q and y/y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#vanre who ARE these FOMO MOFOs? https://t.co/MEfW5mPUS0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteveSaretsky  Has the rest of Metro Van seen this same dramatic drop?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@penultsquire @Schtaunkhauser @noshortre  Maybe CC lurks on twitter and reads your esarc in a serious manner, implements them as policy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@penultsquire @Schtaunkhauser @noshortre haha, it's so sad because you're probably right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This looks like a political exercise to give government MLAs a photo opportunity in their community,” said one of… https://t.co/YKlsiRMsRh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinDSamuel @catherinebnn @amberkanwar 
Negative growth.  It's a thing.  For relz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrackieJimber @brad_barrett @TomDavidoff @HousingBC 
MayB 4n buyrs won't trust CC, esp with elexn.  2 mny flipflops, might get caught out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jjhorgan what will you do about the Liberal's reversal on FB tax and new loophole for people with work permits?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brad_barrett @TrackieJimber @TomDavidoff @HousingBC  I'm really asking...is there nothing legally that BC residents can do, besides vote?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@penultsquire @horse_poo @mtnbvan haha! still an actual force of nature, just not law because based on theory of relativity. I believe in it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@penultsquire @horse_poo @mtnbvan 
Well to be fair, gravity really is just a theory.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jhwfung oops, meant $50l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jhwfung quite right, but I don't think it is.  It's backed by a threat of losing your $60k yearly allowance for 3 years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jhwfung does anyone believe that signing a pledge will stop them?  Actual laws with supposed penalties don't seem to even make them blink]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@penultsquire @TrackieJimber @FIVRE604 @mikalfaro @mortimer_1 @MoeVanWasit @Jaytrayne1 
FInally!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrackieJimber @Schtaunkhauser @christyclarkbc  isn't ndp opposition?  U sayin CC is unstoppable?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReverendSM @SteveSaretsky @penultsquire @keithbaldrey @GlobalBC  how mny 4n invstrs will set up BC Ltd Co &amp; "hire" ppl on permits, buy ppty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrackieJimber @Schtaunkhauser @christyclarkbc does CC not have to run these changes past legislature?  Seems like unilateral policy change]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrackieJimber @penultsquire @TomDavidoff @christyclarkbc @steeletalks980 Also, nobody cares what the silly voters are tired of.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrackieJimber @penultsquire @TomDavidoff @christyclarkbc @steeletalks980  agreed, but CC lives in a different world, disconnected]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@penultsquire @TrackieJimber @TomDavidoff @christyclarkbc @steeletalks980  every1 is distracted by Trump, &amp; CC can say she's pro-immigrant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PcnxPeter @RWong1975 @Christina_Mae_1 @christyclarkbc @bcliberals  I really really hope you're right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fixbced @Schtaunkhauser  I might have to open an account there so I can threaten to close it due to their questionable political ties.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrackieJimber  They still need to campaign.  If there's no change, we're f*cked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LangleyAdvance  I've asked this before, but why does our gov't hate us so much?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ted Baxter and his chimp are running the White House.  problem is I can't tell which one is the monkey. https://t.co/TjIbfdVwIe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FreeSpeechcnd @Dontvoteliberal Dear @FreeSpeechcnd, choose a new flag.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theBreakerNews @Schtaunkhauser narcissists absolutely need to be adored.  take that away and they have nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theBreakerNews @Schtaunkhauser the only way to defeat PMSelfie is for the media to IGNORE him and not attend this waste of taxpayers money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FinancialTimes that was no accident or oversight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Schtaunkhauser the irony is that if CC Libs continue as they are, there will be no tax base. BC will be a bankrupt ghost town]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BCNewsWire @bi_politics this is already done at border crossings into Canada.  I think it's voluntary, but if u say no they turn you around]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noshortre @michaelgeller if nobody saw that coming, people really need to wake up!  Trump desperately wants to be the Supreme Ruler.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BetterDwelling  linky for the inept?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noshortre @michaelgeller  How long do u think American ppl will be 100% distracted by this whole #muslimban?  Nobody will b watching Putin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noshortre @michaelgeller  At this level, there are no coincidences.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noshortre @michaelgeller  if you stand back and see who benefits from US unrest and division, maybe looks a lot like Putin gets free reign]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noshortre @michaelgeller  there is a lot of media brainwashing and gaslighting going on, here too, but I have faith that people see it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noshortre @michaelgeller I'm sure they're not, but if they are it reveals deeper things at play here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noshortre @michaelgeller  i think they will overplay their hand.  They wrongly think Americans are too small-minded to think objectively.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noshortre @michaelgeller yeah, Bannon is just a sociopath.  Nobody in their right mind would give him such power]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noshortre @michaelgeller  The people may not be bad, but some of the things they are taught are def not good, according to western standard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noshortre @michaelgeller  no doubt, but I think a lot of people are unaware of Muslim history, and that's dangerous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelgeller @noshortre  it's some intersting history.  Muslims have always persecuted Jews.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelgeller @noshortre haha, Muslims invented the yellow stars.  In the 8th century.  For Jews to wear.  Because they were "unclean".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RiaCKNW980 @christyclarkbc 
The donations aren't issue.  $$ amounts, transparency, 4N $$, access and influence.  Put limits on donations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noshortre @nickmjow @BenRabidoux @AlderLaneeggs 
Anytime a bank wants to give you $$ to get you into a mort, time to take a closer look]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Boolsheet1 @Franktmcveety @jacquie_1959 @OttawaPolitico 
Did he actually say that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Christina_Mae_1  wow, is this the other honest realtor in #vanre?  Taking a page from Steve Saretsky's playbook?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@penultsquire @ChilcoComox  underpaid???  Haha, that's a riot!  They don't even go to work anymore, because they need to fundraise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Eric__Neilson @penultsquire @Schtaunkhauser 
Ya nice.  Maybe there's a big $$ laundering problem over there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nearly 400 B.C. tax centre workers sent relocation notices, inviting them to consider jobs across the country https://t.co/XrMDKaSZGS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Schtaunkhauser @Eric__Neilson 
Was in yesterdays local paper, will find]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Eric__Neilson @Schtaunkhauser 
Meanwhile, in Richmond....
Seriously?  They don't WANT to solve the problem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Eric__Neilson @Schtaunkhauser 
most egregious thing here is that CRA is getting rid of Surrey office  and 400 people are losing their jobs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SaveRHomes @mrdruthers @craigcherlet @SebastianStoker 
Well hopefully it's quick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@craigcherlet @SebastianStoker @mrdruthers It's so much bigger than just our RE markets, those are just a symptom of the real issues]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@craigcherlet @SebastianStoker @mrdruthers Sure, they do those things while they sell off our public infrastructure and allow 4N takeovers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SebastianStoker @craigcherlet @mrdruthers it's sad that the feds won't take any steps to solve these problems on a national level]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SebastianStoker @craigcherlet @mrdruthers  Well you have a great advantage then, through foresight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@craigcherlet @mrdruthers   They will learn a hard lesson in economics but who's fault is that? Why punish everyone to save pain for a few?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@craigcherlet @mrdruthers I couldn't agree more, but the people we keep electing refuse to allow it to happen because they'll lose donations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@craigcherlet @mrdruthers Agreed.
Monday night council meeting will have guests from BC Assess to address $$ inc, said # may not be final]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrdruthers @craigcherlet they probably aren't, but acknowleding it might mean they have to do something or lose their jobs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@craigcherlet you're right of course, but the parking is an issue when it stops people who ARE going out, from going to the beach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@craigcherlet parking costs a deterrent 2. solution?  According 2 city, 300 car parkade for $9m.  I say Free parking &amp; fire some bylaw guys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrdruthers @Russcher @herouxlc @Harold_Steves locusts is a great analogy.  Arrive in the 1000s, deplete everything and move on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrdruthers @Russcher @herouxlc @Harold_Steves  How much black soil will be replaced with worthless backfill and covered with concrete?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@unionwill @StrategicThghts @GlobalBC @keithbaldry  Ummm, are you guys sure you have the right guy?  Maybe you mean @keithbaldrey?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Canadabuster this country is so fucked.  That money should go to the families of his victims.  Prisoners shouldn't b able 2 collect pension]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@berniewins2016 @RCIisLeaking is a little scary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@penultsquire @bobmackin @jonmccomb980  World class soap factory for the chinese laundry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@penultsquire @bobmackin @jonmccomb980  "world class"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@impishchimp BC Liberals really really think we're all stupid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vansanity1 @FIVRE604 starting to wonder if it's ever going to die.  Stupid Libtards, keep the party rolling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suestroud @RCIisLeaking  what a total moron!  Deflecting from the issue with victim-speak.  Grow up and shut up.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>