<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Really? So now half of us are not part of the "overwhelming mandate" and we're losers too. I feel healed already... https://t.co/G03dWsA3NE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Festival of Learning nominations are OPEN! Nominate inspirational learners, tutors, employers, projects #lovetolearn https://t.co/vnHu7l2eRf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great workshop on #citizenjournalist @CroydonLibs today.  Amazing competition opportunity @LondonVoices16 - why not enter?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's all get behind @DavidLammy and the MPs standing up for a future for adult education. https://t.co/zirJHTUPxk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where's our investment in adult learning? @FEWeek https://t.co/x0lP9S2o1O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's never too late - unless all the funding has been cut.... #saveadultlearning https://t.co/BToKyGcO3N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another short-sighted funding decision in a long history of them.... https://t.co/1H5RgvfJBu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see sense prevailing - MPs finally get a chance to do their job which is to protect our interests. All our… https://t.co/noAdxSHPz3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Important battle ahead - EU citizens living here need to be protected! https://t.co/rjAR6qWBSu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great opportunity to learn about journalism and enter high profile competition! https://t.co/d8A1mHvnh5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have your say on immigration plans before decisions are taken! Please complete this survey from 38 degrees - https://t.co/sgrXyrbpvV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great story! https://t.co/Xf52qgBQUm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone interested?.... https://t.co/ntKo89gGO4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for the follow @WMCollege. I tweet about all things adult learning!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like a fascinating exhibition! https://t.co/2lg4VizpjK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just supported Festival of Learning 2017 on @ThunderclapIt // @festival_learn https://t.co/7eXlJHkkUs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good to see lifelong learning reaching a wider audience @TheEconomist @suepemberholex https://t.co/u8ME3LkkwS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Support FE by signing this petition to Robert @halfon4harlowMP. If you value FE, show it here! https://t.co/ekOugl34Ic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More food for thought.. https://t.co/4TW6OZhGgK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious! Glad to know that colleges are "customers" of area review! And I've a feeling that it's a bit late anywa… https://t.co/B2F0PceCvq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Third Sector group in London? Don't miss out on Team London Small Grants https://t.co/myPH1INvY2 to support older volunteers &amp; beneficiaries]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember to get your entry in on time to the #MandHAwards https://t.co/epNsxhYW9I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good resource about standardisation! https://t.co/r2eHgK7cki]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi https://t.co/kFuyjQXzGD and welcome to twitter!  Hope your twitter life will be as fantastic as your massages!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another missed opportunity - sometimes a stick is what is needed to promote vocational routes to learners who may n… https://t.co/yDYmMwqqQK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good to see @theTSNLA still working hard to represent third sector learning providers https://t.co/h06HOS4Jlo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MPs should talk to immigrants desperate to learn English but with no classes or funding to help them https://t.co/tFbJpDXG1t @bbceducation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems so obvious that I can't believe this is a new announcement! https://t.co/xy7B6EYWrG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great summary of what's to come this year for #FE. Always good to start off the new year thinking positive! https://t.co/jbgcrIzpMu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great courses on offer for those wanting to get back into work in Bromley https://t.co/oXZIChX8KB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very useful review of all the @FEontap supplements including opportunities to download - great to have them all tog… https://t.co/eSZXBRziea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice to see adult education honoured - congrats to all! https://t.co/5ERqOwE9FS @suepemberholex @MARKMALCOMSON @citylit @FEWeek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to the 12 adult education/FE figures in honours list - shame there weren't more (as ever..) https://t.co/5ERqOwE9FS @FEWeek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for the follow @network4. I tweet about all things adult learning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And some investment to go with it..... https://t.co/jSkbLs7bNH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting thoughts from @FEWeek to ponder over your mince pies https://t.co/WmfH8Ckz0l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bit of Daily Mail hype, but this is worrying. AEB isn't protected once devolved, so who knows where it could end up… https://t.co/k6NrhQXVUB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovely to get some positive news for once - we can be great at skills with the right support! https://t.co/htdr2Z2iaK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's an important job - but where to start? Adult learning impacts positively on every aspect of life! https://t.co/n4I5kpHlLQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vote here for what adult education should be used for https://t.co/CvQLC76v46]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's celebrate with Europe while we still can! https://t.co/TocIvnqdTL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great cartoon but sad comment on Autumn Statement that recognised infrastructure but not skills and people https://t.co/yko11NhFBD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Skills will be the most important thing post-Brexit https://t.co/C9N9Rs5oVw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FE student? Take good photos? @FEWeek &amp; @NCFE competition to photograph Learning in FE. Great prizes. Deadline 6 Jan https://t.co/KwZiXCS7k1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great summary of what was (and wasn't) in the autumn statement @theTSNLA https://t.co/gErlxfcd0J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always great resources... https://t.co/aTjy2zeJWq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope this is a positive move..... @theTSNLA https://t.co/v7pAAUTDK1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Post-Brexit it's all about the home-grown skills - fingers crossed for some investment in adults https://t.co/rIMXTt6WJ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make Learning a Language Your New Year Resolution! Learn French, Spanish, Italian or German in London. Details at https://t.co/WVJqV3ohPr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting opportunity! https://t.co/E1TP1wTavg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great high quality courses.. https://t.co/n0Vw9Hmge0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out the six reasons why adult education benefits learners from @tesfenews based on @WEAadulted Impact Report https://t.co/Ax6CNhz2T2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read blog from @WEAadulted  Director and @theTSNLA Trustee Joanna Cain https://t.co/8mASmZvRHj on WEA Impact Report https://t.co/dXwz4oksdg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Key transformative effects of adult learning highlighted in @WEAadulted Impact Report at https://t.co/dXwz4o2QOG. Shows how important it is!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for the follow @AWLEducation. I tweet about all things adult learning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uncomfortable reading for any woman who thinks equality has arrived https://t.co/WLYXUt3ZDQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Launch of IPPR Commission on Economic Justice - the case for change. 17 Nov 08:30am in London. Free tickets https://t.co/Z2YiMx7UrP @IPPR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TramsLondon is there any tram into croydon from Woodside?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Super interesting article - for our daily lives as well as planning. Policymaking: should we be ‘messier’?: https://t.co/BE74VFcqw6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Oxford? Concerned about adult education and devolution? Here's an event for you on 17 Nov! @theTSNLA https://t.co/0lWRqaZFjC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good to see @vincecable back talking about FE https://t.co/eZujQrPsYP. Will be nice to get student voice as well as business for a change!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Useful summary of progress - thanks for doing the work for us! https://t.co/OCmzy5mIKG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way forward - FE, adult education and learning through the third sector - it's not all about schools and young… https://t.co/8WuqA7Vqz2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent article @FENews from Dr Ian Hadfield @FEInsights.Think of students as people &amp; this can improve your data! https://t.co/aOafsbOpvB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The pressure mounts @theTSNLA https://t.co/i5Hrzj2oln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Funding savings, but will it make anything better? https://t.co/KgxrLwHgHh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems a bit one-sided - only one set of providers losing out here @theTSNLA @LLClivenews https://t.co/7pQ8gjGIzI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting to see what will happen.... https://t.co/IbWggs7NQV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A good read @theTSNLA https://t.co/lqXrFEN7hc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Launch of 'Towards an ESOL strategy for England' 12.30 today in parliament. @nateclaldn. Read it https://t.co/djEnnmZQGI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Launch of 'Towards an ESOL strategy for England' today in parliament - bigger room as so many people coming! Read it https://t.co/djEnnmIfPa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots going on with work experience week. Check it out at https://t.co/roc719N19m. Apprenticeships today @App4England https://t.co/sj8pxIMwyT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm supporting #WEWeek2016 to raise awareness of the benefits of high quality work experience!  https://t.co/vttMR8vMrW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And that includes adults - we need to stop cutting adult skills programmes and undervaluing its impact! https://t.co/4BzWW5avfT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Announcement on digital skills for excluded adults - great idea - now waiting for more details on how it works % wh… https://t.co/BEaiz834Rl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh dear. Any London reviews behind schedule too. https://t.co/aEDQBcpwmT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Useful summary and links... https://t.co/edMB5rnHjD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We all knew it! Adult learning has loads of benefits in addition to the subject you learn about. @WEAadulted… https://t.co/wWE31Xjwnt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent news for European funded projects @theTSNLA https://t.co/zh4k3Raode]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get involved in the Big @The_Big_Draw. It's on all month! https://t.co/5BebeH9Fcw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't forget to check out events and get involved in The Big Draw in October - always great fun! https://t.co/QTu8Vy1Bjm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrate European Languages Day @EPALE_UK. Great blog with loads of resources on https://t.co/fY6dMDY9yZ. Muy bien!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent article summarising lots of recent changes. Thanks for this Ann - really useful! https://t.co/pHDxtmcKqB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop the cuts and support this campaign - it only takes a minute! https://t.co/6Xz7VC7bo3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you work in workplace basic skills? Get involved in this discussion and have your say! https://t.co/Dz7LIffQmH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to all the winners! https://t.co/0sBj7ugnfj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best of luck - hope it all goes well https://t.co/GJvmeQTGP8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What could you achieve with an extra hour a day? Find out how with a great free book from @MindFitLtd at https://t.co/KnyKWxBCrq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A good motto - and not just for today! Happy Birthday Roald https://t.co/4QEuzeAxeu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to seeing the results of the consultation on Functional Skills https://t.co/wOFGjZH3c8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a difference some literacy support makes. Well done Theresa! https://t.co/f4JNnVu4Gw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great inspirational stories to read... https://t.co/1res6ZBAwr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oops - probably should have checked the evidence first... https://t.co/H48q4jf8qm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hopefully adult education and FE won't be lost in the mix with schools and HE https://t.co/FhKJYAeIfo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In case you want to start your planning early.... https://t.co/SYmq02AIEF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for the follow @EducationTandem. Such beautiful photos and photo/art mash ups - mesmerising!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redawning Where is this number? I am in UK. I have sent lots of emails to Vy &amp; Rick guest@redawning.com. How do you help-phone? email?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redawning No answer on urgent Q. re booking Schonwald #7833 7 Aug cancelled. Please reply to emails-where are you &amp; why don't you respond?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free CPD resources to help with skills &amp; confidence around using earning technologies at https://t.co/WHwD161EYS funded by @E_T_Foundation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to improve OTLA?  Research, resources, models and case studies at https://t.co/ABGZpm75SC from @E_T_Foundation]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>