<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight @SevenSharp we meet the Nelson artist commissioned by one of Hollywood's famous faces to capture her precio… https://t.co/2wng12UctK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back in the saddle filming for @SevenSharp in sunny #Marlborough - tune in when we're back on air Feb 7! https://t.co/TNadHx2aUb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Te_Papa and @WetaWorkshop have been at it again and TONIGHT @SevenSharp gets the first look at their new Bug Lab e… https://t.co/Q6NGUFrvbK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They made it through NZ customs to treat fans at Mt Smart on Saturday night and tonight @coldplay hang out with us… https://t.co/5XoPn1SrdA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What happens when @FlyAirNZ gets @JulianDennison to give @ronanofficial an education in Christmas down under? Find… https://t.co/U0zRz7wIEw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This one's for you @em_cooper23 https://t.co/tucmGsm0aC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From 1926 to 2016, tonight on @SevenSharp we take a sweet trip down memory lane of NZ's oldest ice cream maker https://t.co/hIFQTfoloM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With all these aftershocks and wild weather we figured it was time for some puppy action! Meet these new pin up pup… https://t.co/sIgkQQANy8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right @obriarwells?! https://t.co/rqfZVgGD7N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future of news right here @kristinhallNZ bringing you the latest on the earthquake from the streets of Wellingt… https://t.co/ceMo97DNyD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight we're talking mental health and how one little dog is having a big impact in Whanganui. Meet Bentley tonigh… https://t.co/5X3Smr4IUO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A must watch tonight, incredibly strong women with an incredibly powerful story to tell https://t.co/ogwsjJHiFj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High 5's and chats with one of Henry Hill School's biggest heroes @ValerieAdams84 we're all about the inspiration o… https://t.co/h2CMESeQkH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these faces watching @ValerieAdams84 arrive at Henry Hill School #excitementoverload #somanysmiles… https://t.co/Qg8F3oXr58]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's an exciting day in Napier - Henry Hill School are about to meet one of their biggest sporting heroes.… https://t.co/wJHVsXsCXK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight - turning dreams into reality, we're behind the scenes at the NZ artificial limb service on @SevenSharp https://t.co/uo4Ivcg0PS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Almost lost Cam the @SevenSharp cameraman while out exploring @TaranakiRC Pukeiti Garden. We are stopping to smell… https://t.co/qe7HfCpsVH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's a whoooole lotta red bands .... we're getting a lesson in country life with the #Puketoi young farmers tonig… https://t.co/i3Hbfnc4Hw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THIS!! #excitementoverload https://t.co/tEsqKsMgED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two first loves who met in Hawera have found their way back to each other 55 years on - a bit of a love story tonig… https://t.co/4Cvhzape94]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shereeshar no I didn't! But that sounds delicious!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today camera op Byron and I got to wear our favourite @SevenSharp outfits so far! Giant licorice and great style on… https://t.co/p44Bt2Ze94]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MutchJessica I've literally eaten my weight in licorice ... the dream has rapidly become a nightmare sugar hangover 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do you make the world's biggest licorice all sort?! Find out on @SevenSharp tonight https://t.co/IDFK38JSYq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight on @SevenSharp meet Alan Collins, a bit of a legend who has been capturing Wellington through watercolours… https://t.co/lXBU3cYXG6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pete's @WOWAwardsShow Diva's Dreamscape looking glorious as this month's @FlyAirNZ KiaOra magazine cover #WOW https://t.co/ouK2oxy7YO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicole_bremner @SevenSharp he is such a great guy!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We'll have such a fun insight into the @WOWAwardsShow tonight, that's taking us all the way to a pink garden shed i… https://t.co/C9XBXd6Bns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love @LiamMalone93!! Also loooooove your jacket @brodiekane .... where's it from?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WOWAwardsShow @ToniStreet @AnnaColquhoun1 you guys will love it. Blows my mind how it just keeps getting bigger and better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just checked out the @WOWAwardsShow dress rehearsal .... So many #WOWS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Serious dedication when your @SevenSharp editor edits a story about @WgtnFree Onesies ... Wearing a Onesie https://t.co/hzjBqkImva]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just imagine if it was a Panda Onesie @jehancasinader!! https://t.co/SJOQUAZbBE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wore a Onesie to work today - now wondering if my @SevenSharp boss will let the trend continue?! So comfy! @WgtnFree https://t.co/iqBLzQd77r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They got a shout out from @JohnCena &amp; tonight @SevenSharp has another surprise for the kids at Henry Hill School! https://t.co/Z0nwcoRhFP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight on @SevenSharp we give the Kiwi BBQ a Spanish twist and meet the duo taking on the world with Paella! https://t.co/XxJriZth2t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickiRussell67 hahaha glad to hear it! Now off for the heart transplant .....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate anything scary ... and yet we'll be live on @SevenSharp from a horror filled warehouse supporting @PlunketNZ https://t.co/320yKRsKCc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such amazing community spirit behind this wee daffodil project! https://t.co/Eg1zmZQVmZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ToniStreet not ashamed to say I'm with you all the way @GuyHeveldt! When should we sneak in Walking on Broken Glass?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight on @SevenSharp we meet the small community behind a big hearted project raising $$ for @NZCancerSo https://t.co/l8lt6GiTsh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could not agree more!!! A must watch https://t.co/KrK2Hk1qvu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robertalan1958 mostly from international auction houses! Pretty impressive collection that's for sure!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trash talk starts now @MikeThorpeTVNZ look which southerner we've recruited to back the Canes @em_cooper23 #OurHouse https://t.co/9X7Hvy5toq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jehancasinader @MattyMcLean Oh YES the many roles of Kirk, surely he is. Or perhaps a professional #PokemonGo player?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jehancasinader @MattyMcLean but the biggest question of all .... have HepAlien made the big time?!?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't waaaaait! Maybe we will have to FaceTime during the first Ep?!? @MattyMcLean @BuzzFeed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's Tay Tay golden oldies style, tonight we go behind the scenes at Julia Wallace Retirement Village @SevenSharp https://t.co/JiXX0uHXbL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think getting older means it's time to slow down you should meet Gary and his family, tonight @SevenSharp https://t.co/fVG9JXbHEi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight @WgtnFree give us a taste of the unpredictable life of a paramedic @SevenSharp https://t.co/zobulNWPUU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suzikyla23 @SevenSharp I would've happily driven all the way back to Wellington in it if I could have!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the new owner of this baby has made one special little girl and her great-uncle very happy more tonight @SevenSharp https://t.co/LYs6molAWA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's 30 years since NZ voted for homosexual law reform - tonight on @SevenSharp @Te_Papa helps us explore the pivotal moment in our history]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jehancasinader deciding to dress the same as me - gotta be a sign I'm #Winningatlife https://t.co/TGKYW9N54A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here @DanielFaitaua - this is how this pod business should work https://t.co/s1k4QZR4x1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katieabradford @Morrison_TVNZ @DanielFaitaua @SeanHoganNZ gets buckets of KFC?!?! Still so much I need to re-learn about this newsroom!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katieabradford @Morrison_TVNZ always shares his jet planes. You'll live to regret this @DanielFaitaua]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katieabradford @DanielFaitaua it's dangerous territory. I wasn't sure if he felt the same way about gingernuts as he does about KFC .....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cuteness alert! Meet the pups carrying on police dog Gazza's legacy on @SevenSharp tonight https://t.co/VqOs3EmGiL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tipenesmith Oh no! Just slow on the updating side of things. Such a boomerang child!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onewilliamsj @jamesransley @KimberleeDowns giant snacks no less!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight on @SevenSharp I do a loooooot of pedalling to check out a pretty phenomenal forgotten part of our world https://t.co/lXqPN0AU8n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's office #workworkworkworkwork @ Forgotten World Adventures -… https://t.co/1NmxmlWMew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nope he's not a ghostbuster ..... Jake Burns busts wasps ... Tonight on @SevenSharp https://t.co/P6rV0FRcOp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesransley @onewilliamsj @RuthWW @jehancasinader definitely team feijoa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wednesday night with the @nzballet and the wizard of #oz - two of my absolute favs #winning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kapaiguy no wig needed! boys are more than welcome ... gym tights will always go down a treat though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kapaiguy I shall definitely be returning ..... without a camera next time though!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love busting some moves to a bit of pop? Meet the girls embracing their guilty pleasures tonight on @SevenSharp https://t.co/kIZrwZlLsZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight on @SevenSharp we're catching up with @JulianDennison to talk selfies and the skux life https://t.co/Y3VlEvmzpR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hannahmarkbrown you will not believe how many people have asked me that same question @MattyMcLean]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#PrinceHarry's 'Epic fun' trip to NZ http://t.co/3g4ee4uO1K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With a cheeky grin #PrinceHarry is still backing England to win the RWC - even if they face the ABs in the final @ONENewsNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#PrinceHarry hopes to be able to come back to NZ soon, suggests he'll make the trip back for the Lions Rugby tour @ONENewsNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got a quick iv with #PrinceHarry himself he's so genuinely overwhelmed by NZ's welcome, and has had so much fun here @ONENewsNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flanked by @AllBlacks #PrinceHarry meets a #WheelBlack at AK's spinal rehab centre @ONENewsNZ http://t.co/bS50ommTNn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#PrinceHarry seems pretty stoked to be catching up with @AllBlacks Kevin Mealamu @ONENewsNZ http://t.co/TbQC0bDhd4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rugby great Sir Colin Meads addresses #PrinceHarry at AK's spinal rehab centre @ONENewsNZ http://t.co/DxBE0e2Vzi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#PrinceHarry will meet VIP's - very injured players - supported by the #NZRugbyFoundation @ONENewsNZ http://t.co/hmeyPSbAYW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Karanga welcomes #PrinceHarry to AK's spinal rehab centre @ONENewsNZ http://t.co/KGkFErI5Gb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NZ Rugby Foundation VIP's - very injured players - waiting to meet #PrinceHarry #RoyalTourNZ @ONENewsNZ http://t.co/OHkDT0SJ6T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sir Colin Meads and other rugby stars awaiting #PrinceHarrys arrival at the Spinal Rehabilitation centre @ONENewsNZ http://t.co/J3yRaOklbv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#PrinceHarry completes his Waka journey on the Whanganui river @ONENewsNZ http://t.co/GJJc56p5Pm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#PrinceHarry expected to arrive at Putiki Marae in 5mins. Everyone is ready and standing by @ONENewsNZ http://t.co/UrLodw0hRT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rain not dampening spirits at Whanganui's Putiki Marae - locals all ready to welcome #PrinceHarry @ONENewsNZ http://t.co/W4OAqO0xPn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High fives as #PrinceHarry prepares to leave Linton @ONENewsNZ #RoyalTourNZ http://t.co/SvVK30hL7w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Say cheeeese Linton Camp students pose with #PrinceHarry @ONENewsNZ #RoyalTourNZ http://t.co/4KnaCHKxbU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Total concentration from #PrinceHarry as he performs the NZ Army Haka @ONENewsNZ #RoyalTourNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hail is falling in ChCh, nice of the weather to wait to pack up until #PrinceHarry finished his outdoor activities! #RoyalTourNZ @ONENewsNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spot #PrinceHarry amongst the fans. Bit of a where's wally moment @ONENewsNZ #RoyalTourNZ http://t.co/nbAFqQS5x8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['He's coming he's coming' ChCh fans yelling down the line as #PrinceHarry makes his way along the throngs of fans @ONENewsNZ #RoyalTourNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Impressive Christchurch crowd waiting for #PrinceHarry some have been here for hours @ONENewsNZ http://t.co/t3pbIcrVuG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Why do you think I'm here??' The response from almost every lady when I ask if they've heard #PrinceHarry is looking for looove @ONENewsNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phones and cameras out in force as #PrinceHarry arrives at Quake City museum hundreds gathered here @ONENewsNZ http://t.co/57IBRdA3f2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snug as bugs at the back of a tiny plane as we make our way back to Invercargill @renee_tvnz #HarryWatch #RoyalTourNZ http://t.co/iJ0RtnDIAV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#PrinceHarry is off for some personal time this afternoon. I'm picking Queenstown as the royal choice #HarryWatch @ONENewsNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last minute goodbyes on Stewart Island before #PrinceHarry heads off after charming the locals @ONENewsNZ http://t.co/ZvoARLkyOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids at Halfmoon bay school can't get over all the camera flashes as they pose with a real life prince @ONENewsNZ http://t.co/XXoOtdrklK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['I call the Queen Granny' #PrinceHarry answering questions from children at Halfmoon bay school @ONENewsNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crowns on show at Halfmoon Bay school all for #PrinceHarry @ONENewsNZ http://t.co/qdLaTSn0zN]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>