<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@JJMSports what odds he stops whining and goes out and gets a proper job like the rest of us?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would imagine @suttonunited will be moderately pleased with that draw!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shugiehughie Worth reading @kinneston blog as Nick did have a positive for it. Must admit I trusted the form book instead of the blog!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shugiehughie on the other hand take out its last race and it hadn't been beaten more than 5.25 lengths over jumps. Recency bias?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ACMold Certainly showing more interest than Reading did!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Either #Chelsea or #ManUtd to win #FACup , at least they look interested unlike some of the others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This may be a below strength #LeedsUnited, but if they get any injuries they are stuffed if this is the best the replacements can manage!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MillieBroon Always does! Metophorically 'smacked me in the face' when I first saw him @KelsoRacecourse and always has since!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#KnockaraBeau still trying his best even at 14. Hope a nice little race can be found for him @KelsoRacecourse close out his career]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With all respect to #Skybet, it's the Great Yorkshire Chase #RetainProperRaceNames]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good ride in defeat by Kielan Woods on the gutsy Midnight Jazz.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cracking ride by #FelixDeGiles who would have been round a few X-Country courses on the continent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had real thrill watching from course centre as #ManyClouds zoomed round @KelsoRacecourse last March. RIP and thanks for the memories.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pace a no brainer, Smad Place surely?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BetVictorRacing @DavidPipeRacing @WetherbyRaces @tommyscu Wouldn't mind seeing that one if it goes over fences!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Presenting #AlternativeFacts - Isn't that a tactic that politicians have used since politics came into being?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ursusocculta That's getting into Darwinian Selection territory!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#StillOpenAllHours just doesn't work! Open All Hours was Ronnie Barker and it hasn't worked moving forward without him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't watch much skiing, but well done to @daveryding on a superb 2nd place in the Kitzbuhel World Cup slalom! Hard graft rewarded.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BetVictorRacing @jackkennedy15 is a real right place, right time rider.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theracingforum In the better races concentrate on lightly raced horses. In poor races such as Cl5 hcap chases, miles on clock seem better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theracingforum The problem there is that these days if they've done it before the market is smart and allows for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JJMSports Backed 2 in a race at Fontwell once, first one fell at the 2nd, got up, ran loose and took out the other at the 4th fence!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JJMSports and one falls and brings down the other!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JJMSports Hope so, got Definitly Red in @theracingforum 10TF, need this one to follow up Waiting Patiently!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No Colin the proof of the pudding IS IN THE EATING!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Harry05Derham @HAYDOCKRACES Good, and we appreciate you taking the time to let us know!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Narrowthefield Whatever, he's just bagged 42 grand in a Grade 2. Wish I owned him!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TheNewOne is a great one to bet on, because it looks hard work but he gets it done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done @Braveheart_Alex on Deepsand for @lucindavrussell This lad is a decent young rider.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steeplechasing He tanked away from them down the straight off a pretty decent pace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Impressive by #NeonWolf and I get impression he'll be even better stepped up in distance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Luke Morris didn't do much wrong there but Chevallier is frustrating]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itvracing @ITV4 and race times delayed by 5 minutes I understand, so your first at 1.35.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@auntiejackie_ @flyfromsadness @RevolutionUK @JackChevell and sticky out knees!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McRaces On which basis it would be hard to see them getting permission to build on the whole site. Aim for the stars, reach the moon?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McRaces One option would be developing the old Jubilee course/sprint spur area, largely untouched recently. Are the JC angling for that??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McRaces I believe Ascot would keep more of the the King George feel. Conversely, my wife thinks Sandown is where it's at, loves the place!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McRaces @Sandownpark @talkSPORT2 I think the phrase is "Yes, but he would, wouldn't he?" !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tom_Seagul @Narrowthefield No, Kelso is in Scotland, would have been the scotch pie wagon...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice to meet up with @BetVictorRacing along with @theracingforum at Kelso this afternoon. Believe me Jack, that wasn't cold for Kelso!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Narrowthefield Think he realised he'd lost because he'd picked the wrong gap after the last. Should have gone between the other two.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Soft, Heavy in places at Kelso looks about right to me. Some gooey spots but generally not too bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done @lucindavrussell with One for Arthur! A cracking performance in a really competitive staying chase.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CommentatorMark A tactic to press for redevelopment on the old Jubilee Course land?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BradfieldCC @SandhurstCC @BerksCricket Yes, duly noted and #Mickeytakingmaterial lodged away for future reference!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done @MCYeeehaaa at Sandown yesterday, made some bookies look very uncomfortable about each-way terms. Keep the pressure on!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shugiehughie Yes, it will be snowing the week the SPL starts up again!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catching up with earlier race replays, nice to see #Catchamat and #CathyWalton stick it up the southern hot pot in Newcastle opener!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looked a good ride by #DavidBass on #MaestroRoyal as his mount didn't look totally straight forward, odd head carriage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sound decision to retire #Dynaste Owes nothing to connections and here's to a long and happy retirement for the old boy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shugiehughie Kelso bumpers are always worth a glance I've spotted some good jumpers from those.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TillyrieStables Well done Amy, the penny has finely dropped and he's doing you proud!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shugiehughie You have to identify the genuine jumping types from bumpers. Decent types come through but they need to have scope.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bit disappointing from Reading at Man Utd, gave it away early. I expected a bit better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shugiehughie Be interesting to see what happens after that one, they're an exposed sextet hardly likely to make huge forward leaps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shugiehughie pound drops mean f*** all. Drops to enable entry to a lower grade, now that makes a difference!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shugiehughie It's the system. if you lose it pays to be stuffed out of sight rather than 2nd or 3rd.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any questions about strength of female jockeys knocked on the head by Lizzie Kelly who threw the kitchen sink at that one #Agrapart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shugiehughie @Jamesracing1 Problem being assumption is made that 2nd has run to form. The concept of crap race doesn't register with BHA!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shugiehughie Yes but nice to see Cogry back to form after a dicky spell over fences, he really battled hard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shugiehughie I did wonder if he had gone up too far. The Ayr race was a bit of an 'egg and spoon' race.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done Tour Des Champs, all guts and determination to hold on. 2 wins from first 7 runners for #SamDrinkwater]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shugiehughie Certainly seemed more soft ground horse conditions when walking the course and I note they added 'soft in places' after race 1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IMO Kelso going is on softish side of good to soft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All in a heap in the Lexus, nothing to worry Thistlecrack there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch out for NOBLE INN, down the field Leopardstown 12.50 but never in a position to put in a challenge. Suspect much better in the locker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Decent entry for @KelsoRacecourse tomorrow with double figure fields for all bar one event.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tdthurgood Ryanair for Cue Card maybe?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That Word Search thing on @Channel4! What a racket! £3.60 plus a bit for a raffle ticket...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That may put Native River in as stable second string for the Gold Cup. Some performance!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The runner up at Chepstow, EVENING HUSH, looks more a good ground, sharper course type. Aintree maybe?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice job done by the Drinkwaters with #WorkingTitle in the first at @SedgefieldRace . Nice placement!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[100/1 Gray Wolf River. Not exactly taking any chances there are you bookmakers? Add a nought?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Punting4aLiving Thankfully the horse was OK, but jockey really lost the plot after 2 out. What was the flailing of the whip in aid of?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 plus 2 equals 5 says @realDonaldTrump ! People voted for this man!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaveSoper1959 Quite right! Worst places to pass these days are the doorsteps of public buildings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad to hear of the passing of Ade Keep of @mortimervillage . Knew him for years through cricket and a genuinely nice bloke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shugiehughie Hope not, I've got Big River in a Horses To Follow comp! However I fear automatons that pass for h'cappers might just do that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theracingforum Last year's trophy??? It helps when he keeps winning it!! And Lennox Lewis is improving his presentations!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why doesn't that huntsman at Fakenham do something useful and catch the loose horse?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoopsRacing I think it should be earlier. 10-11am is just too close to racing, particularly in the winter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kenneth_hawkins @steeplechasing @HAYDOCKRACES Which I would have thought worthy of noting in the meeting Stewards Report!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steeplechasing I have asked @HAYDOCKRACES how they arrived at the result]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HAYDOCKRACES Dare I ask how the placings were determined for the 3.15? Shouldn't there have been some sort of Stewards Report on the farce?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steeplechasing and, given that no distances were returned, one wonders if they just asked the jockeys where they finished?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HAYDOCKRACES Stewards Report for 3.15 reads 'Nothing to Report'. Presumably because they couldn't see anything?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steeplechasing presumably it would be a void race.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steeplechasing Anyone playing in-running at Ascot or Haydock today wants carting away by 'the white coats'!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardHoiles There are sometimes I envy you your job and sometimes I don't! It's the latter @Ascot today and very well done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HuntyCaller  Remember from when I was down south, peering through the fog is part of tradition of this @Ascot meeting! Still a favourite!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DELUSIONOFGRANDEUR franked Aux Ptits Soins @KelsoRacecourse form very nicely @CatterickRaces today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PITLOCHRYft @Channel4Racing We did indeed. Scrooge was an absolute cracker of a musical.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would be nice if the Turkish Cross Country team had the odd Turkish runner...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shugiehughie Looks like a a literal view of that given Walking In The Air's mark. Handicap marks based on big margins are often dubious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shugiehughie 'never travelling after mistake at the fifth', reported finishing with a 'wound on his stifle'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great afternoon watching @Channel4Racing now off to @PITLOCHRYft for Scrooge The Musical!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice Time Trial by CLIFFS OF DOVER at Donny!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Narrowthefield Agree. He's run a lot of races and would be going to chasing comparatively late, but still one of the best hurdlers around.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cracking ride by Jack Sherwood on Present Man. Lesson in how to deal with wonky steering!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>