<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Mayor Bowser says DC finances "best in its history...$1.165 billion in liquidity." https://t.co/QTVUBEj8Pu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Mayor Gray has a message for Congressional members "considering meddling in the District's affairs"… https://t.co/LuLE0oOmcw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And a good surplus for rainy days.  https://t.co/1hwwgfENwh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DDOTDC military rd crossing rock creek - guard rail blocking lane. Cones up but no lighting. Hazard you should check out. Saw near accident]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConthesceneWTTG fingers crossed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#bobcatwatch https://t.co/tresEEVdQN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New legislation https://t.co/KjSt1wG0Y8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crackdown on home sharing in DC. @kenyanmcduffie proposing major regulations. https://t.co/bR2KaVBrt5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DC schools that have suspended outdoor recess because of escaped bobcat. https://t.co/JoF2qE11iI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinMcCarthyTV Kev, I loved this movie. Voted for it too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DC Attorney General @AGKarlRacine condemning executive order. https://t.co/ZCJbd64Adb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge denies release of Duane Johnson. Sets next hearing in April.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Johnson's attorney to judge: Anything Mr Johnson said should not be take seriously.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking: Judge finds probable cause in the Tricia McCauley case. Defense attorney claims Duane Johnson may have been mentally ill.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Write-in effort for a DC hero.  @fox5dc  https://t.co/7Jw9Hm4Muu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boston Mayor responds to Trump's sanctuary crackdown. "If necessary we'll use city hall itself to protect anyone who is targeted unjustly."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JBurchDC both]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@jasoninthehouse wants documents "as soon as possible but no later than 2/1/2017 https://t.co/j5BEjcodDS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasoninthehouse is demanding all documents on how funds will be distributed and monitored for fraud.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New: Congressional Committee on Oversight demands documentation from DC on $500K being used to help w/immigrant leg… https://t.co/QyGH7UaHdo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mayor Bowser expected to speak at 6:30. https://t.co/ICuE4e5Sgn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuAnGusto_ Ha! Thank you! Action shot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York's Mayor speaks..and now Mayor Bowser plans to hold a press briefing on the immigration executive order signed by President Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mayor Bowser didn't want to speculate earlier on impact if Trump signed sanctuary city exec order. Now that he has we hope to get her plan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Trump pulls federal funding it will hurt. Could leaders use rainy day fund to make up for cuts? https://t.co/ZQVWJUgHDp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[State's Attorney for Anne Arundel County says he buried his brother in law a week ago after an opioid overdose. https://t.co/3G18LrkoeB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anne Arundel County Executive says the heroin problem is getting worse. The number of deaths from OD has doubled.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proposal to get tough on heroin sellers. 30 years in prison for those who sell to someone who dies from OD.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Governor Hogan begins media briefing on heroin crisis in Maryland. https://t.co/N6SPXIttmz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@VinceGrayWard7 wants a big bonus for officers who stay. https://t.co/4NxPytqNrY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police can't make out the license plate on the car because of lighting. Not even sure what state.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chief: "These suspects attempted to murder a police officer"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["As your Chief of Police I am pleading for help from the community" @fairfaxpolice https://t.co/2nCBmw33tW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fairfax Police: officer attempted a traffic stop and then became a crime victim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fairfax County Police will brief media on this soon. https://t.co/3Eb5dJyIKJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KarenGarner2168 @ldemarcofox5 @fox5dc thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@legldiva @ldemarcofox5 oh - now I see. Yes that's oxon hill - we have a tower there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@legldiva @ldemarcofox5 hi. It's at the top of the studio https://t.co/bxhvwlcXjd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former DC Police Chief Charles Ramsey speaking about yesterday's protests on CNN. " I don't think you'll have that problem today."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mayor says Police Chief will have more on arrest #s at a briefing at 6:30]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New: Mayor Bowser "Some people have come to town who mean to break the law." https://t.co/K3XUhJrNb8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big crowd gathered in front of Freedom plaza. Lots of cheering. https://t.co/NoibM6Lb6X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Will not condone crime and vandalism" https://t.co/MR3eg5qZ15]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And now this - Mayor and Chief to brief media. https://t.co/xKlE3FIVeR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We've asked that the Mayor to brief us on camera. Her spokesperson said that won't happen for at least an hour.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm told the Mayor has asked Director of DC Homeland Security to report to her office to update her in person.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New:Mayor Bowser is monitoring the protests from the Wilson Building. She is in contact with the Police Chief. Staff is working on statement]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protestors scream at motorcade #fox5POTUS https://t.co/xOSvHPpYx6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Where's the tax returns?" https://t.co/X7cn3OxAWu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lionfamily1999 yes. I'm from Florida - lots of Floridians here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiting along the parade route. #fox5POTUS @POTUS https://t.co/H4MgtnRHpb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More officers near treasury dept https://t.co/VF3hGNqJmv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look at all the officers gathered along Penn Avenue https://t.co/ED2cRlw4KG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking: security gate at 14th street is closed. Protestors are blocking https://t.co/mot8FeHJHX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9:25: line to get in secured area. This is 13th street NW https://t.co/RLlVml6fiN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wilson Building: Frederick Douglass "Power concedes nothing without demand. It never did, and never will." https://t.co/2KvCNm90v2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @cstevenson7 @JeffLennox @RobbinSimmons7 thanks for sending us some of your finest  https://t.co/zwQgjRGh37]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunrise from Freedom Plaza #fox5POTUS #Inauguration #inaug2017 https://t.co/TjW0kkFKea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're coming to inauguration make sure you don't bring a bag..no items that can be thrown - even fruit unless it's sliced.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ha! They told me to go to the back of the line. Hey, @tomsherwood - we hope it's nice and warm inside.  https://t.co/8I1LhPWmOy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great shot on the front of the @washingtonpost https://t.co/VGa21eHajP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[National Guard arrives at security checkpoint #fox5POTUS https://t.co/cx6iTjy0Nq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's do this. Heading to @realDonaldTrump inaugural with the team #fox5POTUS @MarinaMarraco @fox5dc https://t.co/vbakgW7hiJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this. https://t.co/ZSUvT69WW1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inauguration Day 2017 Survival Guide: Know where to walk, find restrooms, and more https://t.co/OkhLbPxpHm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please do. I'll be joining the morning team (with LOTS OF COFFEE) https://t.co/4CWjOW5uzz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's do this. Join us early. https://t.co/S41sGv255y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trucks lined up on Constitution Avenue loaded with concrete barrier walls. https://t.co/OrG1gvmXKo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At 5: Seeing those signature #MakeAmericaGreatAgain hats in DC. These supports are from California. https://t.co/pF6zlhOii1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New: When @realDonaldTrump passes the Wilson Building on Friday he'll see this message from @cmdgrosso -"DC Protect… https://t.co/Dg7Xas7dD7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Norton ready to fight https://t.co/woXs3qEg4B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thousands of officers will be sworn in to help with inauguration https://t.co/lhlaRO0ztG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Metro adds service for #WomensMarch https://t.co/SIrFYkViDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Same vendor says Obama merchandise sold "like hot cakes" 4 years ago]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vendor: "Trump is coming. Ain't nobody going to stop him" https://t.co/NJAWykC3Fv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LadyMsJay yeah. Happening right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inaugural parking restrictions have just begun near the mall. We spotted three tow trucks asking people to move. https://t.co/z3po8RGjMM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vplus i'm afraid to know who plays Cersei]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had to see this coming. 
Is D.C. city hall big enough for both of them? https://t.co/uvUZ7RvZ3m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US Mayors gathered in DC. VP-elect Pence greeted with standing ovation @politico https://t.co/sUGMRPQed1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Update: Staff for @trayonwhite and @RobertWhite_DC tell me both won't be attending the inauguration. https://t.co/9rR1UnKxjH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Update:Bus permits at RFK. 
Inauguration day @DDOTDC says approx 435
@TheEventsDC says 1200 permits issued for women's march.
 1200 is max.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheh's release says the unit will "better serve the District's Muslim population amidst a national surge in anti-Muslim attacks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New: @marycheh calls on DC Police to establish a Muslim Liaison Unit. https://t.co/78FfYwUOQo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mayor Bowser is joined by Mayors from Philly, Seattle, and Dayton, OH. at Center for American Progress.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seattle Mayor speaks about undocumented residents in his city. "They are scared out of their wits." https://t.co/aMfcyjSRib]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks, David https://t.co/HKJ3RvGAuQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GPS tracking for officers  https://t.co/G5v8BMpqX9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm told @DDOTDC is in charge of permitting for buses on inauguration. @TheEventsDC is doing it for women's march.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Update: @DDOTDC says 393 RFK bus permits for inauguration. @TheEventsDC says 1200 for women's march.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maustermuhle I eat two a day. I wouldn't call them delicious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chairman Evans says Metro is a safer system then it was a year ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SafeTrack is back.  https://t.co/ehBgbssH7a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man who scaled White House fence sentenced. https://t.co/DY42qU32EO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CMCharlesAllen @CharlesAllenW6 @DC_HSEMA Can you update us on women's march bus permits please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting development. The picture is meh https://t.co/MIREa3SS0u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New #'s from hearing. 393 buses for inauguration. https://t.co/gXzoazS2x3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Committee votes to keep Jack Evans as Metro Board Chairman. Full board needs to approve https://t.co/WmLGEbLyjR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@CharlesAllenW6 says approximately 1200 by Inauguration day. He says permits often coming in fast during the final week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@CharlesAllenW6 says at this time in 2013 (before inauguration) there were approx 900 bus permit requests for RFK parking.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>