<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Nae words to describe how good it is being a Celtic fan right now #historyinthemaking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So refreshing to hear a calm, collected and honest post fight interview from a boxer! #CarlFrampton ðŸ‘ðŸ‘ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cannot wait for the trilogy ðŸ™ŒðŸ™ŒðŸ™ŒðŸ™Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a fight again! 117-14 Santa Cruz. Bring on number 3!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is so fucking close]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a difference from the last fight, that's 3 zip Santa Cruz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is gony be a cracker this fight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really fancy Santa Cruz but I really can't decide what tae lump on ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thought he was a goner there ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a knockout, holy fuck ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it just me that fancies Santa Cruz tonight? ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1st time out in Bathgate in nearly 2 year, definitely a reason for that length a absence ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That Derby own goal ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gazwilliamson they had it in a tiny tent at Mint last year and it wasn't as good. If the line up is shite I'll be selling mines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gazwilliamson they will aye, that'll sell out straight away as well. You'd think Elrow was the only decent night in Glasgow all year ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everycunt pure freaking out about Elrow, it's almost like there's nae other decent nights on every single weekend ðŸ™„ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danielmurray67 if it is it'll be easy enough to flog them to some mug who's only interested in some confetti and blow up toys ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danielmurray67 what a bastard that ðŸ™„ðŸ˜‚. Better no be a shite lineup now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fucking Â£80 for 2 Elrow tickets and it's sold out already ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ed Sheeren's new song and the video for it would bring a tear to yer eye man. Getting old is pure shite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vikkiferrier @ssgarrity the whole a Scotland has ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vikkiferrier @ssgarrity I mean either or, any advice helps cause we're a pair a indecisive bastards ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vikkiferrier @ssgarrity fuck, can ye no go earlier and tell us what it's like? ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vikkiferrier ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚, beats any yer sci-if shite any day ðŸ™ˆ. @ssgarrity should decide based on our opinions and our opinions alone tbh ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vikkiferrier depends what ye like, real life or kid on real life. It was never going to be as good as the first ðŸ™ˆ, no got the shock factor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vikkiferrier @chrislammie aye but the T2 reviews haven't been great either ðŸ™ˆ. In the end I'll be going where I'm telt anyway ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vikkiferrier @chrislammie you're no kidding ðŸ˜‚. It looks weird as fuck aye but it seems like a thriller which is right up our street]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vikkiferrier @chrislammie Sam has convinced me to use our vouchers on that before T2, better no be shite ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cannot believe we've made it ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ. This helps heal the wound of 2013 ðŸ˜‚ @SkySportsNFL #RiseUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gazmitchell92 be some laugh that ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gazmitchell92 fucking buzzing ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚. If the steelers win later you need to take a sicky for the SB, me and Pratt will be rolling about ðŸ™ˆðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YASSSSSSSSSSSSS!!!!!! Super Bowl bound now surely ðŸ™ŒðŸ™ŒðŸ™ŒðŸ™Œ @AtlantaFalcons @SkySportsNFL #GBvsATL #RiseUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gazmitchell92 about 90% away ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚. Stop at the start of this half and I'm starting to celebrate ðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHAT A FUCKING START ðŸ™ŒðŸ™ŒðŸ™ŒðŸ™Œ @AtlantaFalcons #GBvsATL #RiseUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WilliamHill Boswell #LastActionHero]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The nerves man ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ @AtlantaFalcons #GBvsATL #RiseUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing better than having a few beers watching the scores on a Saturday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrislammie your life will be a fucking misery within 6 months. Nightmare journeys to spend the day listening to an even worse accent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy fuck man, what an incredible game that was ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ #DALvsGB #NFLPlayoffs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great fight and great judging]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarynPhillips honestly mate, fuck knows! Good luck scoring that ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter what way it goes, there can be no argument. Draw for me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a fucking fight ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarynPhillips only thing you've no got is happening ðŸ˜‚. Some fight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarynPhillips rounds ye got? This is points bound. I'd have City before man utd the mora ðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarynPhillips biggest giveaway by the bookies this year that ðŸ˜³. I honestly wouldn't touch that game, City at evens is yer bet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarynPhillips fuck sake, some odds that! Wish to fuck I'd seen they odds ðŸ˜‚. No even worth the bet that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarynPhillips aye fucking sure a have ðŸ˜‚. No even looked at the odds for the boxing the night at all. Lump the mora, money to be won]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EastonDaz @GrantEaston1 some talent! Bit like me telling ye about some Kazakh nobody a few years back  ðŸ™„ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarynPhillips I've turned over now, game over. No like ye to lump ðŸ™ˆðŸ˜‚. I don't fancy a knock out but I wouldn't be lumping against it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarynPhillips NFL is too good to miss ðŸ˜‚. I'd be shocked if he never won tbh but I reckon it's points bound]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarynPhillips fuck up ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚. Switching between that and the NFL, that last fight seemed a topper! I'll be watch the DeGale fight though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarynPhillips correct, she's more mental than me though ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something weirdly hilarious about yer wee sister coming in blotto and causing it ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couldn't be happier, roll on the NFC championship game! #RiseUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aw man, this offence ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ #SEAvsATL #RiseUp @SkySportsNFL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a half that was, more of the same please! #SEAvsATL #RiseUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't know whether this is excitement or nerves ðŸ™ˆ #SEAvsATL #RiseUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing would give me greater satisfaction than the Chinese fucking ravaging the premiership ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚. Reap what ye sow ya cunts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not an hour of the day goes by where I'm not wishing I was at @TheBPMFestival . Wit a comedown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some laugh it's gony be no making it to a 48 team World Cup and spending the summer getting blitzed, shouting on San Marino against England]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WilliamHill Hauschka #LastActionHero]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine 'sweating' over the fitness a Joe fucking Garner man. Wit a worry it must be, who's gony get the bookings now?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a day and night! Cannot believe I've lasted this long either ðŸ™ˆ. Has there been a better Hogmonay? Probably not ðŸ€ðŸ’š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm all for more games against them on Hogmonay, what a way to end a year and lead into a new one ðŸ‘Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All kidding aside, that was a fantastic game of football today. Must have been a fantastic watch for a neutral]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danielmurray67 don't get yer hopes up too much]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 coupons up to the tune of Â£350, some day and some night ahead ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adelante34 need to force yourself to drink it or folk think you've been talking shite ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Earlier this year I mentioned I loved Prosecco, ended up with 6 bottles the day ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚. Nothing brings about overkill quite like Christmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PLAYOFFS!!!! Yassssss ðŸ™Œ @AtlantaFalcons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas Eve and a Celtic win, SCOOTER ARE YOU READY! #scottysinclair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[31st in the charts and 31 points behind in May #magicnumber]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WilliamHill Robbie Gould #LastActionHero]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last minute goal to fuck the coupon âœŠðŸ’¦]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This just feels like a 6 months pre season for the Champions League qualifiers now ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WilliamHill Dustin Hopkins #LastActionHero]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing better than a Monday off work and a proper Sunday session ðŸ‘Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Richy_Ahmed tonight! What a way to start the festive season ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worst performance at home this season, win is a win though. Don't think we'll play that poorly again for a while]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[161/1 coupon up ðŸ™ˆ. Been a long time coming this!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter how good Joshua is, the heavyweight division is utter dug shite. Zero interest in it it, a division living on its past]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarynPhillips ye know what I meant but ðŸ˜‚, Hamilton away on Christmas Eve would be as well being a different world from any home game ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarynPhillips told ye about Griffiths scoring tae, fanny ðŸ™ˆ. See ye for the Christmas Eve piss up ðŸ‘Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarynPhillips nae mare Friday games this season, eyes are welling up ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is looking like the easiest title win of my lifetime! Is it cold in our shadow huns?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cannot wait for this tonight! Perfect way to make up for missing out on Manchester ðŸ€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friday night football returns, should be a weekly occurrence!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonder how many folk thought we would only lose 3 games in that group. Next year is the year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well played Celtic ðŸ‘ðŸ‘. Should have won it right enough, missed chances again!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Played well there, need to take our chances at this level though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fancied our chances all week which probably means we'll get a tanking ðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck right off Liverpool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Trundle14 aw aye, him and McGregor were absolutely superb. If ever there's a reason to get mwi at the weekend it's that the day ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Trundle14 from our worst 45 minutes of the season to arguably our best ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are nae words to describe how much I love the Celtic ðŸ’šðŸ’šðŸ’š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quiet weekends without a drink sound smashing at 7 on a Friday morning, 12 hours later no say smashing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Newcastle game ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing fills me with more satisfaction than a fucker of a hun meltdown ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚. Just think how many of these we've got to look forward to ðŸ™Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danielmurray67 out on my arse man, got in at 8 this morning ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>