<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShadowTheFury @Blarbby don't take my lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UltraGayWeeb you're welcome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UltraGayWeeb you don't need it though, you made Frost perfectly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UltraGayWeeb and a furry book]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't hold back peeps https://t.co/5r1vFkC9WJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Silta_Gamer exactly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Silta_Gamer stealing from Nick Wilde and Sans from Undertale I see]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UltraGayWeeb I can't draw though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UltraGayWeeb I want someone like that lol sad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UltraGayWeeb aww that's cute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UltraGayWeeb the beginnings of Iox's e-girl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UltraGayWeeb the irrelevant part hasn't changed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShadowTheFury what's up?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@XDArturoXD @Zaptie tbh it doesn't matter if he shows them or not, he discussed nudes with an underage girl, he should be held accountable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter if you're defending Zaptie or want him gone, we can at least agree that he's a piece of shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@XDArturoXD @Zaptie so all we're 100% certain about is that he's a piece of shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@XDArturoXD @Zaptie and for the record, there still hasn't been any medical records released saying he is, so that defense isn't usable yet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@XDArturoXD @Zaptie he is still held accountable. Lying is one thing, breaking the law is another]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@XDArturoXD @Zaptie he's not mentally ill in that he can't help himself or doesn't know right from wrong. He knows, he just doesn't care]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@XDArturoXD @Zaptie unfortunately, based on what he's done, I'm not convinced he's innocent in this case]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And before the "She sent them to him, he didn't ask" argument starts, he should've ended the conversation and blocked the number. He didn't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@XDArturoXD @Zaptie doesn't matter. He should've ended the conversation and blocked the number.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lying and cheating are both terrible yes, but requesting nudes from underage girls is much more terrible and disgusting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never said this and honestly meant it before, but @Zaptie should delete his YouTube channel. He cannot be allowed to do this again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What have we learned today? There are some awful human beings in this community that should be held accountable for their actions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't know Zaptie was attractive enough to get nudes tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you support, show affection towards, or like a pedophile, please unfollow me right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GodUnfollowedMe good, took too long enough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GodUnfollowedMe are you alright?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GodUnfollowedMe play Minecraft with me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AllStarBacon @GodUnfollowedMe OwO what's this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GodUnfollowedMe @AllStarBacon stop being gay on my timeline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kingdingah get a few of them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BetaEtaDelota it is though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Silta_Gamer idk maybe he just never mentioned them but he knows that you like them, so it's a surprise I guess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Silta_Gamer hasn't he seen your mask?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't give a fuck how many followers you have or how famous your friends are, if you treat my friend like shit, I'm coming for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You DO NOT treat a friend of mine like shit and then expect me to act like nothing's wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excuse me would you like to run that by me real quick?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miraizuu at least I know what you look like now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miraizuu why did it take so long for you to bless my timeline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why don't they just do everyone a favor and stay off twitter. They've hurt too many people and destroyed too many friendships/relationships.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WHuner exactly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realGordonFrost or if you're SkyyeFall you leave for 9 hours then come back like everyone loves you again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh no I've been exposed for being an asshole who's only relevant because I sucked a relevant person's dick, better leave twitter for a day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey if you leave Twitter because people don't like you anymore, at least stay gone for a few days before you come back to dick ride more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want you all to know that if I was given the option to save YouTube or delete it, I'd smash that fucking delete button so fast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delete your account. Better yet, delete YouTube https://t.co/AEbwD2oeM0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[KFC is awful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fixed my bio again lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you see your friends subtweeting about you https://t.co/9QLBDlit0k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WHuner hopefully people will avoid the negative ones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you like and support people who have cheated multiple times and feel no remorse for it, please unfollow me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The real question is, will they stay gone or will they pull a SkyyeFall and come back after a few hours because they need to feed their ego]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Silta_Gamer well I'm happy he's fucked off then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Silta_Gamer ohh, so he probably has a nice inflated ego then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who's Assault anyway?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At this rate, maybe all of the negative people will just leave or be forced out of the community]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess every superhero needs his theme music]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going to hate myself next week for this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not going to sleep lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's up peeps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd nuke the entire world for a Klondike bar, don't tempt me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Omg I forgot it was February]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh would you look at the time, I'm staying up again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doctor: For this treatment to work effectively, you'll need to get on a proper sleep schedule and eat correctly

Me: *has no sleep schedule*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wear red so when you get shot, your blood doesn't ruin your outfit https://t.co/SJY7aR8hD0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kilo2341 just because I don't follow someone doesn't mean anything lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I'm sad Ziggy won't follow me back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell @ShadowTheFury to follow me back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Silta_Gamer @ShadowTheFury let's see how long it takes for me to block him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShadowTheFury @Silta_Gamer never put "my nama jeff" on my timeline again or I'll sell you to the gayest, RPing furry I can possibly find]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will not allow people to continue acting uncivilized and think they're doing nothing wrong. I love this country, but there are problems.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've put off making a video discussing the current situation in the US for a while now, but I think it needs to be made.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can think I'm a fucking moron all you want, but I know more about what's going on in this country than every news outlets combined.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-refuses to educate themselves on subjects 
-cannot have a civilized discussion without making illogical claims 
-will not accept reality]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's how to detect an extremist:
-blames an entire race for problems 
-wishes death on someone 
-supports the destruction of property]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The extremists on both sides need to get the fuck out of this country and never come back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may disagree with someone's beliefs, but I will NOT act like an uncivilized idiot about it. Learn some basic manners.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you feel like you need to destroy property to prove your point, please rethink your entire life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doing so is against the law and you should be taken into custody immediately. That's not protesting, that's fucking rioting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let me make one thing very clear, you do not have the right to destroy private property that does not belong to you due to your beliefs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Silta_Gamer aw we could've played if you did]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does anyone have Dead by Daylight?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FolfHavoc so that's what it is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm assuming death grips is a meme]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is death grips]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck off Werner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That podcast thing was a joke btw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What if you quote it? https://t.co/3Zffza2xLq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShadowTheFury you wouldn't fill that out and give to me?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@XDArturoXD what're you going to do about it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@XDArturoXD I'm letting people fill it out bitch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fill this out for Valentine's Day https://t.co/9Ed6o3XTnT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who wants to start a podcast?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're reading this, I'd murder you for $1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I die, let the world know that I didn't get 8 hours of sleep like some pussy ass bitch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@acidicsulphur and I are the new Minecraft YouTubers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Played Minecraft for 3 hours, now I'm going to take a nap so I can function somewhat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh 
Oh
Ohh 
It's magic]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>