<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Lyall Bay looking breezy for today's  @oceanswimseries. Good luck to all the swimmers @ellashepston @LizShepston]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going through the book now and it's looking fab https://t.co/AVS932stwD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When #Wellington is good it's very very good. https://t.co/Ef3rEcG8S5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ellashepston found Kaito #Wellingtonwildthings https://t.co/Jzwqf6I31c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Squirmingly hilarious. Why haven't naked parties taken off? @ellashepston https://t.co/r2WmwqNXyW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nick from Piha - integrity personified. Surely New Zealander of the Week @crywank]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My feers of being stalked turned out to be rhubarb #fruitondesks https://t.co/fTh4GqTkdW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight's dinner conversation topic "What's your least valuable organ"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to catching up with Jonathan in a few weeks. Welcome to City Care. @WesternLeader @bdcitycare https://t.co/GuuWsRJ730]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'd think after all these years of practice I'd be able to drink wine without choking? Must try harder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovely long walk in the hills above #piha just me alone with my thoughts. I shouldn't be left alone with just my thoughts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Late on the news but congrats to @AlisonBallance for the NY honour. Well done chook.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know you're losing at Pictionary when Polar Bear involves drawing #LeonardoDiCaprio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I said let's go camping and @ellashepston dd the rest https://t.co/QKBQEWk6kb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The one (only) good thing about a swim at #missionbay at 6.30 is the parking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas Day greets me with the news #RickParfitt has died, a good rockin mam gone. Sod off 2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First mince pie of the season https://t.co/DuAxHlYbFI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @airNZ for all the the beautiful service.  See you in 2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So 2016 claims Zsa Zsa Gabor as well. The original and best famous for being famous star ever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelenTheShark In my case the no-idea switch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why's there always one light switch in a hotel room that doesn't seem to do anything?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sure I'm sitting next to Mitchell from @ModernFam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To stay ahead of the game I've broken my New Year's resolutions already. One less thing to worry about.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's happening at @guardian?Two stories today on Teresa May and @thegrandtour both quoting #mailonsunday as their source]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Glenn was the epitome of what a boy's hero should be and I couldn't get enough stories of him and other pioneers of space. RIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lord of the Ring of Fire #AddASongRuinAMovie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Long and Winding Road to Morocco  #AddASongRuinAMovie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty Vacant Woman #AddASongRuinAMovie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grand Budapest Hotel, California  #AddASongRuinAMovie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ready to go for the Auckland Harbour Swim @ellashepston @LizShepston @oceanswimseries https://t.co/pRKIxUcpm9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How sick am I?  It would take three tweets just to list the drugs I'm taking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1Victs Welcome to NZ 😆]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Passionfruit mocktail anyone? Very tasty. @FlyAirNZ https://t.co/nMP9TckXYt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Pilates for Animals - here's Benji demonstrating Upward Facing Dog https://t.co/JceQULxv4Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In The Reheat of the Night #Leftoverfilms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Magnificent Seven Courses #Leftoverfilms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's a Crazy Cat Woman #catthebeatles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I Feline #catthebeatles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got tickets to @Adele for @ellashepston and @LizShepston and cemented my place as third most popular male in our house]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ticketmaster_NZ @Adele Or you are successful then the website says a problem has occurred pelase try again!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When did Southland Sheep Farmer take over from Italian Bistro Tablecloth as men's shirt material of choice?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just met @tamineilson and coolly and  calmly became completely incoherent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LizShepston and men are keener on rat eradication than women but why?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LizShepston finally gets to meet @NZBatman at @ERA2016Conf https://t.co/FYE25IP2oB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Already overwhelmed by the ideas at #era2016conf.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good luck to @ellashepston and @LizShepston in tomorrows @oceanswimseries at Mt Maunganui this Saturday. Do an extra lap for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelenTaylorCG Where are you with all this fascinating stuff and how can I get there next year?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For a poor Jafa visiting  #Wellington that was a big one #earthquake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good old fashioned OMG I'm going to die landing in #Wellington Pilots earned their pay today @FlyAirNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whole family supporting #AllWhites at QBE today https://t.co/iSonjqPfLT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlyAirNZ When a plane's give us the bad news in one go not in 10 minute increments. #nz460]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time travel in action . Left #Auckland in summer and arrived in #Wellington in winter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paterstella No, I can't explain it. Completely baffles and depresses me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can someone explain to me how any women could vote for Trump?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let me be the first to wish you a happy St Martin's Day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very much looking forward to @BlackGraceNZ at the Herald tonight. Slightly fangirling Neil Ieremia who's standing just over there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Refugees aren’t the problem. Europe’s identity crisis is

https://t.co/ayQw2CnuRT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still getting over kokako being #BirdOfTheYear. Well done #teamalbatross for a great campaign. Another year of soaring the lonely skies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damned #auckland traffic. All roads running smoothly so have arrived ridiculously early. I blame @phil_goff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great organization for #aucklandmarathon @HeartNZ #volunteers https://t.co/aumDiDsvVB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lizshepston If you liked I Am Pilgrim check out @ParadoxTheseus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattHeathNZ is bringing the Fact Factor into disrepute. I'm sending my OBE back in protest.  @crywank]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do Sid James and Charles Hawtrey get royalties everytime an airline makes an announcement about Carry On Baggage?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's happened to me - even I'm excited about #GBBOFinal. Mainly to see what lipstick @CJ_Brownie is wearing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlisonBallance I've voted Albatross.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I listened to @AlisonBallance and voted Albatross  Welcome to Bird Of The Year | Bird Of The Year https://t.co/0sU6H7sLN5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Following up with a Parrot Dog Dead Canary. Yes just because of the name @pomeroyspub https://t.co/YzLeLY8lvk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a post-truth election, clicks trump facts https://t.co/E30F3rZYun via @ConversationUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoying a pint of Pomeroy's Pale Ale at, where else, @pomeroyspub https://t.co/k3anJKV5P0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think my wife's having an affair with Terry Hayes the amount of time her and I Am Pilgrim are spending together]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#osgood and #zygon but which is which? #DrWho @HumanAndZygon @Armageddonexpo https://t.co/D31irBKCJE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rey rey @Armageddonexpo https://t.co/6Tp2zeVYUs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great meeting #astronaut Rick Searfoss at @Armageddonexpo. What a cool guy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lauren being tempted by the Dark Side https://t.co/dCCer7WaDe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ready for @Armageddonexpo @ellashepston https://t.co/uqwEpZfXDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And people say maths isn't useful - World's longest pub crawl: Maths team plots route between 25,000 UK boozers https://t.co/c0EC9dXXjq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only 3 days to the most anticipated day of the year @Armageddonexpo !!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JMulliganRNZ plays Siouxsie and the Banshees on @radionz . Brilliant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi @Vesta2e have you branched out into catering? https://t.co/bUs8UjQTkY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FPayne100 How often does a touring team to India win a test after losing the toss. @BLACKCAPS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The weather forecast is broken. It's saying it isn't going to rain in #Auckland today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tamineilson But really looking forward to you playing my home town @ellashepston]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best headline of the day Cod speak with regional accents, scientists believe  https://t.co/GzVriE9Yts via @telegraphnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can a blatant basketball fact be better than the best
goat/armed robbery fact ever? #factfactor @crywank]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The office sign in system says I'm from Gallifrey so it must be true #timelord #drwho https://t.co/IiGI22uZoC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tip of the day - keep your mouth shut while applying antiperspirant. Teeth feel like sandpaper but at least my tongue’s not sweating]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great social housing forum from @NZCID1 . Special Thx to Bernadette Pinnell from @compass_housing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I dunno, you confuse your boss's mochacinno with a macchiato once and your whole career's in ruins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does every country have a batman? @LizShepston @NZBatman https://t.co/lGq29yDQ31]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[50 for captain #kanewilliamson @BLACKCAPS doing it nicely #indvnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm liking this scoreboard. You stay there @Martinguptil8 #indvnz @BLACKCAPS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They're criticizing it cos it's dumb https://t.co/GNEon3gfbK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ellashepston Got to be @SophiaMyles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's it called when the wind chill sucks so much heat from your body your limbs stop working? Ah yes, Wellington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In @malthouse and actually drinking real beer @TuataraBrew IPA. I might move here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just took the test on https://t.co/6QOxuw4xwG and it turns out I'm Ghandi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dangerous driving officer? My hands weren't even on the wheel so technically I wasn't driving.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been described as creepy #drWho shrine but I don't see it like that https://t.co/W4Tnl2uRax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thx for the bunny update. There's a whole bunch of people here who can start breathing again. @crywank @MattHeathNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the whole if the Labour party on this flight @jacindaardern @DavidCunliffeMP Kelvin Davis?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>