<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[When life gives you lemons, don't have a sour face. #smile]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the most sincere forms of respect is actually listening to what another has to say.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chelseahamill Hang in there Chelsea :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So freaking adoreable :) https://t.co/qsjr4Ulahd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FanHamillpage1 @HamillHimself @markskywalker_ Watching ROTJ now. Great minds think alike https://t.co/eTOnhiGzOp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HamillHimself we're you trying to become R2D2 in a rubbish bin https://t.co/aReDatHfUF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chelseahamill I completely agree with everything you wrote, it's great that Mark has such a wonderful loving daughter who looks out for him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HamillHimself This cracks me up, well done â¤ï¸ðŸ¤— https://t.co/B8yFPZVsPu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mark Hamill, Tonight Show, Johnny Carson, 1977 https://t.co/nTNzFDFeFB via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HamillHimself I'm sorry you have yet another loss in your life. Mary will be sadly missed by all. My heart goes out to you and her familyâ¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HamillHimself Have you ever thought of making a Twitter for Millie?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tafish @carrieffisher All I can say is Beautifulâ¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephenAmell  @RobbieAmell I'm sorry to hear about your grandfather. My thoughts are with you and your family]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NathanHamill Loving it, can't wait to see what u come up with next ðŸ’™]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HamillHimself If Luke Skywalker had a mobile phone in space, would he use an I Phone or an Android Smart Phone lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome pics Nathan, keep up the great work. #Lovingit https://t.co/sLnmXVnvC2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HamillHimself Hanging out at work, does anyone know how to  I can butter my toast with this thing ðŸ˜‹ https://t.co/3AFNjJtx2z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HamillHimself Just another day in space https://t.co/QMvhQwliLy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carrief_gifs @tolkienianjedi Time for @realgaryfisher to bust some movesðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsJoelyFisher I did the march in Dunedin New Zealand. I'm proud to do this as Carrie always stuck up for everyone â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WomensMarch Stick up for what you believe in! https://t.co/UN42EZ6wzg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HamillHimself Hope is important it can make the present less difficult to bear. If we believe tomorrow will be better, we can bear hardship]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to Vader himself @jamesearljones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chelseahamill So cute, what did u name him or her]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HamillHimself keep up the #trumpster  tweets, I haven't laughed so much in my life :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HamillHimself Please don't let Millie see this, I'm sure she would get jealous https://t.co/4apTEgQA7V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who thinks Twitter should have more than a Like Button]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The supervisor isn't doing much supervising. Rosie the dog is facing the wrong way ðŸ˜‹ https://t.co/c4v0K24TTv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Workout done ðŸ‘. Laundry done ðŸ‘. Clean the house ðŸ‘. Drink loads of water ðŸ‘. Cook dinner ðŸ‘Ž. I'm buggered lol ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May The Force Be With You during 2017 https://t.co/Gp7XnJBgBS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy New Year to all the amazing peeps out there https://t.co/4TEtFcGStC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a reason for everything, just keep looking forward before the past kicks u in the butt!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy 2017 to all, may it be better than 2016ðŸ‘¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes you need to be insane. Being Normal is overrated ðŸ˜‹]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HamillHimself Just read part of the article you told to EW about Carrie and Debbie #beautifulandkindlovingwords]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished my workout... Now to watch some #StarWarsRebels https://t.co/3DTRFlladu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tafish Condolences from Carrie and Debbie's fans in New ZealandðŸ˜¥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think @HamillHimself would agree with me, that we all can't wait for 2016 to end! Let's hope that 2017 will be better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsJoelyFisher I'm sorry for yet another loss you have to deal with, just know your friends and family are here for you all ðŸ’”ðŸ’š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My heart goes out to @HamillHimself and @MarilouHamill for another sad loss ðŸ’”just know your friends and family are here for you. ðŸ’š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gary_TheDog My heart goes out to you @Gary_TheDog ðŸ˜¥ðŸ’”hang in there and know your friends and fans r with you always. #maytheforcebewithyou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRock RIP @DebbieReynolds1 loving mother of @carrieffisher ðŸ˜¥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RIP @DebbieReynolds1 and @carrieffisher . my heart goes out to @tafish @Gary_TheDog and Star Wars cast @HamillHimself @HarrisonFordLA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please be alright @DebbieReynolds1 we can't lose anyone elseðŸ˜¢ðŸŒ¹ðŸŒ¹ðŸŒ¹]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016 F##k you, I'm over you taking my favorite actors and singers. Get this year over with already :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For @carrieffisher @HamillHimself @HarrisonFordLA @TheWookieeRoars She will always be with the FORCE :( https://t.co/ylEp0wFqhP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsJoelyFisher I'm so sorry for you're loss, my heart goes out to you and the familyðŸ˜¢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gary_TheDog I'm sorry to hear about you're mom :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so sorry to hear about @carrieffisher . My heart goes out to @HamillHimself @HarrisonFordLA @TheWookieeRoars @DebbieReynolds1 and family]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sitting here eating ðŸ“and drinking ðŸ·. Merry Christmas everyoneðŸŽ„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know this Christmas will be tough for all of you @HamillHimself @MarilouHamill and family Merry Christmas. Praying for @carrieffisher ðŸŽ„ðŸ’“ðŸ‘¸ðŸ‘¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GretchenRossi Merry Christmas Gretchen â™¥â™¥â™¥ Have a wonderful New Year :-D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HarrisonFordLA  Please let @carrieffisher know we're all thinking of her and hope she makes a speedy recovery â¤ï¸ðŸ’›ðŸ’šðŸ’™ðŸ’œðŸ’“Thank You :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HamillHimself Please give our love to @carrieffisher as we are all hoping she will be okay ðŸ’“ðŸ’œðŸ’™ðŸ’šðŸ’›â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get well soon @carrieffisher , we're all thinking of youâ¤ï¸ðŸ’›ðŸ’šðŸ’™ðŸ’œðŸ’“]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another Kidz Karts at Forbury Park Race Track. https://t.co/iaxugyr4GM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kidz Karts at Forbury Park Race Track 21 / 12 / 2016 https://t.co/ehw6VFFN2A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Anniversary @HamillHimself and @MarilouHamill ðŸ’–ðŸ’–ðŸ’–]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching LOTR Two Towers with the talented @SeanAstin @elijahwood @IanMcKellen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have a kick ass birthday @C_Butt_Racing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HamillHimself Hi Mark if your not too busy, I was hoping you could wish me Happy Birthday. Thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gr8 job Lazarus, Mark Purdon and everyone at the All stars stables for winning the NZ Trotting CupðŸ’–]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good luck to everyone in the New Zealand Trotting Cup at @AddingtonNZ ðŸŽ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ðŸ‘»ðŸ’€ðŸ‘ºðŸŽƒ happy halloween]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HamillHimself Happy Hamillween Mark and family ðŸ‘»ðŸ‘¹ðŸ˜ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Halloween everyone ðŸ‘»ðŸ‘¹ðŸ˜ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have a wonderful and Happy Birthday @carrieffisher â¤ðŸŽ‰ðŸŽ‚ðŸŽ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@khloekardashian Good luck with the release of your jeans line ðŸ˜â¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yolo... Make the most of it ðŸ¤—]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using ur voice is the only weapon u need in the world #nomoreviolence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to my all time favorite actor @HamillHimself ðŸ’–ðŸ’–ðŸ’–ðŸŽ‚ðŸŽˆðŸŽŠðŸŽ‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@J_R_Schneider @StudioSchneider I'm so sorry to hear about the passing of your mom. Condolences to you and the family ðŸ’–ðŸ’–ðŸ’–]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Karma is the best word ever invented ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Father's Day to all the dad's out there â˜ºðŸ’–]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The loss of harness trainer/driver Peter Scaife another sad day for all in the racing industry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have a wonderful and happy birthday @chelseahamill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had to laugh when I saw this @HamillHimself @carrieffisher https://t.co/jw2Mz8nPiw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dream big or go home, life's too short to think tall lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday @HarrisonFordLA â¤ðŸŽðŸŽ‚ðŸŽ‰ðŸŽ‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now is the time to take a stand against Child Abuse. #fightforkids]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HamillHimself  dont' work too hard, you might lose you're sanity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have a very happy and fun filled Birthday @NathanHamill â¤ðŸŽðŸŽ‚ðŸŽ‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to get rid of someone annoying, just do that thing you do. You know that thing, yeah that thing that annoys everyone :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Father's Day @HamillHimself :) &lt;3 https://t.co/L4Kzo5z35i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HamillHimself If you had the chance to work with @SamuelLJackson in Star Wars, what would you like your character to learn from him?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Mother's Day to all the Mum's out there :) &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't you hate it when one person posts the same thing every day ðŸ˜’ðŸ˜¶]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRock Please tell me your gonna bring the calverey in Fast and Furious 8 ðŸ’–]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to my darling motherðŸ’–]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carrieffisher Gary is getting cutier by the minute ðŸ˜ŠðŸ’–]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday double trouble @MrSilverScott and @MrDrewScott ðŸŽ‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday my pretty @bexmader ðŸŽ‚ðŸŽˆðŸŽŠðŸŽ‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's one smart pup ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/bwu8XEKfAj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have a wonderful and Happy Birthday @dhewlett ðŸŽ‰ðŸŽ‚ðŸŽ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday @ChloeBennet4 may all your dreams come true ðŸŽ‰ðŸŽðŸŽ‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HamillHimself Hi Mark, I was wondering what's the best thing about playing such an iconic character as Luke Skywalker?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamchrisjudge Looking super hot there Chris ðŸ’–]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol cute, but sweet https://t.co/VHF723AAJs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have a kick ass birthday @_KrisJStewart ðŸ’–]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching #OnceUponATime #Elsa  @GeorginaHaig looking for #Anna @elizabethdlail]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>