<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@carlyematthew thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carlyematthew brilliant idea, if I may, I would like to copy the idea? Thank you for sharing your finds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeCCunningham @BelieveInFilm thanks :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BelieveInFilm thank you. I'm a dope.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@filmdevelop @kickstarter I backed that too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elliottucker d'oh! Of course! Thank you. I shall hide now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chichic @OldSchoolLab my pleasure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chichic @OldSchoolLab these are fantastic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chichic @OldSchoolLab I love your shots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry for being a bit stupid, but what does the BIF in #bifscale17 stand for? Thank you. #believeinfilm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It just occurred to me that February starts tomorrow and so does #bifscale17. #believeinfilm #emulsive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wakefanatic @OldSchoolLab may I ask what dilution you used? Did you agitate the soup at all? Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FaultyFlipFlap @JonWilkening @schneidan I use the tetinol kit, it is very good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elliottucker I have a friend in Argentina who follows the nazi story there, and their impact on the government. It is fascinating.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elliottucker All true. It will be intreasting to read.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elliottucker it will be an interesting read all the same, and it's not mein keimf, which I will never read.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elliottucker true. Good point. I wish you luck. I love reading, but, I don't think I could read that particular book.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elliottucker That's an awful lot of hate to read.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elliottucker wow. That will depress you, even more than the news.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elliottucker thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@niallcarsonpa @ADWart @PA Thank you! I can't wait to see it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elliottucker I will just write to all of them and the tds too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@niallcarsonpa @ADWart @PA where are these please? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elliottucker mine will only list meps and councillors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlakPhoto what would it involve? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheVonster thank you for sharing this. It's great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elliottucker Does that Bozo think he playing Sims? Annoying the military is not a good idea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Reuters it is a Ban (however long) on muslims travelling to America. How is that not a #muslimban ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ukigoni Remove Mentions of Jews from the Holocaust??? That is like trying to describe rain without mentioning water (But WAY more serious)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EMULSIVEfilm I am looking forward to seeing the results of this project, it is an interesting one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CtyOfBlackbirds have you seen this? https://t.co/MdItHRmLec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nbrez @UpliftIRL I have signed it. Thanks for sharing it Bressie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@victorbezrukov been there, done that, felt like a prat. :-/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlakPhoto how would you like us to participate? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrHolga that is a fantastic name!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrHolga He has a great name by the way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrHolga there is a detective joke in their somewhere. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TMAX_party I bought some film today, so I am ready to party! #emulsive #believeinfilm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hacerfotos @takingphotos @35PHOTO_main they look like they are about to salsa in the snow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elliottucker Wow, that sounds very cool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZDP189 Happy new year to you and your family. I like your daughters dress and camera. Have fun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RIP John Hurt. I used to see him around town, seemed like a great guy. I loved his work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@filmdevelop knit? Moonwalk? Cartwheel? ....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markmitchellbro @BelieveInFilm yes, all the time. ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have now found the 110 hacks I need. I see a mess in my future :) #emulsive #believeinfilm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@InteriorDIYer She look is very excited about her ribena ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tedforbes wahoo! I am looking forward to it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elliottucker my dev efforts need LOTS of improvement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elliottucker I scan at home. I'll need to figure out how to do that for 110 too. If I had important scans I'd give it to Steve Crozier.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elliottucker cool, you could try red rua, rua red, whatever its called in Tallaght, if you were around that area for whatever reason.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elliottucker what scanner will you buy? Did you see that mammoth scanner that has been released?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elliottucker I have been watching that. I think alt-snowflake was great. Maybe next time you could be a rogue snowflake?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elliottucker by the way, love your new name.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elliottucker I have done colour before with the tetanol kits, it's easier than b&amp;w. You should try it, you will do brilliantly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elliottucker true :) I was going to go in tomorrow anyway, 110 reels are tricky to find.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elliottucker colour. I have 35/120 reels. Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Q: I have 4 rolls of 110 that need dev, do I send them off or try 2 hack a way of dev them myself (I don't have 110 reel)  Thanks #emulsive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnGobanSaor I can spend a long time faffing about with my digital files.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeCCunningham I only forgot about the stop for one roll. Thanks for all. Your help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeCCunningham ok, that's great. Thank you. I put through three rolls afterwards and they seem ok. I won't m forget about the stop again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeCCunningham ah ok. So, should I get rid of that fix and start again? Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnGobanSaor That is all true. I enjoy it though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeCCunningham thank you. That's good to know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnGobanSaor yup. Everything seems to be ok though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoops! I forgot to use a stopbath before I fixed. #believeinfilm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jk_rowling Good Morning. This morning, I can't help but remember Dolores Umbridge in front of a wall of magical decrees.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlakPhoto This picture reminds me something.... https://t.co/NEVfKdtQGl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FilmsnotDead it's a good thing I don't live in London anymore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elliottucker I'm not sure. In Trumplandia, I doubt it. It might help other people though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elliottucker have you registered as Muslim?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@victorbezrukov seriously!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@victorbezrukov it is easier than b&amp;w development.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@papercamera I love Pinhole and would love to attend one of your events. Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@papercamera hi guys, will you be running one in Dublin? Or maybe London? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mushypea007 a friend of our family was part of the first syndicate in Ireland to win the Irish Lotto. They blew it all in no time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mushypea007 Ah well. The doggos will have to wait for a treat. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fotodudenz That's good. It's still a pain though to deal with people like that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mushypea007 oohh, did you win Mush? Are Buddy and Pearl going to have their favourite treats?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elliottucker @TheVonster congratulations guys! Happy anniversary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mushypea007 apparently it is a syndicate that works in a factory.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fotodudenz oh, ok. I hope your day got better after that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jesskellynt I think it's legit, I saw an analysis on YouTube about it. He can be hit or miss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeCCunningham @Grumpyfck in Switzerland if you order tea, they want to know what is wrong with you, so they can give you the right one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeCCunningham @Grumpyfck strawberry tea with honey tastes jelly or jello.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeCCunningham @Grumpyfck Barrys Tea is the one to drink in Ireland.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeCCunningham Irish Breakfast tea, is also just tea, unless in a cafe. I'm not sure of differences between English &amp; Irish breakfast teas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeCCunningham if you are in a cafe and you want a particular tea, you would call it English breakfast tea, as opposed to green tea etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mushypea007 his name is Bernie, that will be enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mushypea007 I like your thinking. Maybe we could adopt him? We could give him a passport.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mushypea007 Maybe? Though Trump doesn't seem to like science, so maybe not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mushypea007 England has Bernies brother. Maybe if there is another brother, we could borrow him?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sergeysus unfortunately, there are some men who seem to believe that because they have a penis, they decide what is going to happen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonWilkening it really is. Nice work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonWilkening I love this one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ukigoni is it just me, or is he genuinely scary? #orangeoverlord #humanityvacum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elliottucker I am. Thank you, I need to do better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@papercamera @fslashD I just spotted this now, I wonder will they sell it afterwards. Also, where can I find their sites? Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcgregor_ewan @piersmorgan fair play Ewan, it's a waste of effort talking to that creature.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlakPhoto Nicely put.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bruko I know, he wants devotion. Intreasting.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>