<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm gonna be that wife that goes to the store for milk and gets 4 dogs, 2 cats, and a hamster.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you want to write a novel but have no inspiration whatsoever ðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noodlerella Phil or Thomas Sanders!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How come youtubers never tour in Florida. WE NEED LOVE TOO YA KNOW.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish I was clever enough to compose a good enough tweet for @tanamongeau to follow me but. I'm actual trash. ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NoahGrossman214 I was so scared to open that omf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheGabbieShow YES MOM PLS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm finally watching La La Land because literally it's all @doddleoddle talks about. Not even 2 minutes in and I get it. I FUCKING GET IT. ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clarkcwells marry me ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MANDELA EFFECT ITS "THE" NOT "A" @shanedawson https://t.co/K5EswG3HL8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@supershayne I can barely get 5 hours of sleep HOW ARE YOU GETTING 15]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvanEdinger I need to see that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YAS NOW @AnnaTaughtYou AND @natalia_taylor_ ARE BOTH FOLLOWING ME. MOMS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smosh I thought ass would be on here. Oops.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WillFerri I swear people get offended so damn easily now ðŸ˜’can't even have an opinion without people getting pissed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys are assholes. Not all of them but a fuck ton of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markiplier god this was perfect timing... needed this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THE ADVENTUROUS ADVENTURES OF ONE DIRECTION IS LEGIT AMAZING. ðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GodHatesAmanda FUCK MATH THO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WillFerri AND I DONT KNOWWWW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessismiles__ glad you guys are okay. Being in that situation is terrifying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessismiles__ Omfg what the fuck happened? ðŸ˜­ I'm so sorry. ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're still waiting for another video from @lily_marston BECAUSE ITS BEEN 6 MONTHS I NEED YOU IN MY LIFE ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ https://t.co/gjiGdb3z72]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can we make this happen @jk_rowling ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ https://t.co/n978CNovi3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really want to hug someone rn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IF YOU DONT WANT TO BE CALLED AN ASSHOLE, DONT BE AN ASSHOLE. ITS THAT SIMPLE FFS. ðŸ™ƒðŸ–•ðŸ¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Petition for @shanedawson to go on tour and his shows would just be him eating because like... Who wouldn't want to go to that shit? ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #pls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IM WATCHING ROCKY HORROR PICTURE SHOW AND IM IN LOVE AND LATE IN THE GAME BUT IDGAF ITS AMAZING]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thefinebros starting my YouTube channel ðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessismiles__ ITS SO PRETTY ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaronxfuller literally same]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I. CANT. LIKE. THIS. GUY. STOP. ME.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markiplier A PET NAMED STEVE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OKAY IM WATCHING SUPERBABIES:BABY GENIUSES 2 AND THIS SHIT IS HILARIOUS OMFG ITS SO BAD BUT SO GOOD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need therapy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love when people just assume the know the whole story of a situation YOU WERE IN. Then they wanna say people are pussies like okay ðŸ‘ŒðŸ¼ðŸ‘ŒðŸ¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessismiles__ HOLY FUCK CONGRATULATIONS MOM ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're talking to a really cute guy anD HE LIVES LIKE 2,000 MILES AWAY LIKE FUCK MY LIFE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["His radioactive dick just saved us!" - @Co_Mill Quote of the year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ATC_BAND  When you live in Florida ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smosh I would say but it's inappropriate ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clarkcwells give me your handwriting pls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvanEdinger PLEASE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHEN THERES A FUCKING KADABRA AND YOU HAVE NO POKEBALLS https://t.co/kgReE5hLN2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now changing my twitter bio to "Life's a party, you're a boy." -@OliviaSui]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnaTaughtYou shit I fucking love you ðŸ¸â˜•ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not everyone you lose is a loss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Garrett_Watts @TheGabbieShow I'm literally eating and watching greys anatomy rn. I'M NOT ALONE IN THIS WORLD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrissyCostanza people are assholes goddamn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrissyCostanza dolphins have been doing decent and now they're just fucking up ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baby Godzilla is the cutest Godzilla ðŸ˜‚â¤ï¸ @Matthiasiam @heyamandafaye https://t.co/toNFgEWtjx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why am I laughing so hard at this- https://t.co/CK59TzQsnO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish I could be vegan but I like cheese too much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHAT IS THIS https://t.co/4eqN0DQByb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeresaYaw Can you be my mom, please? ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@doddleoddle literally me right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YASSSS BITCH @shanedawson https://t.co/xie1qTq5QZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are guys such assholes? ðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tana is literally so sweet omfg https://t.co/CW2g2Rpcla]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really wish I could hug @AnnaTaughtYou and @natalia_taylor_ right now ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnaTaughtYou either anxiety or eating disorders (specifically bulimia)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnaTaughtYou words to live by]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natalia_taylor_ how is there more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natalia_taylor_ HOLY SHIT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is literally a thing @shanedawson https://t.co/B3D2sx1l8y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[? Please inform us @colesprouse https://t.co/zplxoQfGJx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THIS IS GOLD @ChrissyCostanza https://t.co/umYNwNdtNh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShowstopperSam @TheGabbieShow it's so cute and I'm so happy for you and yeah ðŸ˜‚â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShowstopperSam @TheGabbieShow IM SCREAMING OMFG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tanamongeau I will give you all of the nonexistent money I have in order to win I stg. ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OliviaSui literally same]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HIS FUCKING LOW NOTES FUCK ME UP CHIP I STG ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜ https://t.co/2EYT6hsy6s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaronxfuller so proud of you Aaron ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Number one reason why I can't be vegan: I love cheese too much. https://t.co/M543QKEJNn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please kill me this is freaking me out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I stg I'm watching @danisnotonfire and @AmazingPhil baking videos THAT IVE NEVER SEEN AND SOMEHOW I REMEMBER SHIT THATS HAPPENINGI'm psychic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@doddleoddle it's me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's 2AM. I walk past my lamp and the lightbulb blew. IM AFRAID OF THE DARK WHY DOES THIS HAPPEN TO ME?!?!?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ROSESLBBH the end "I like ducks" kills me every time I see this ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natalia_taylor_ what about a picture of me? Bc I'm a pussy. *ba dum tssss* I have jokes. Not good ones, but they're okay I guess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlxJames10 let's see how long this lasts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanedawson new video has me in my feels. I relate to his situation so much it hurts. ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheGabbieShow singing old school Demi in her Snapchat. Holy shit. GIVE ME YOUR FUCKIN VOICE ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another life goal: sing Disney Songs with @brendonurie ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Possibly bleaching my hair tomorrow. Platinum blonde. Oh boy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am I psychic? I start singing a song and it comes on the radio. Then I go to text someone and they text me. WHAT IS THIS FUCKERY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vaporscabello what even happened I'm so confused]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ROSESLBBH her fucking highlight and her voice and ugh. They're so perfect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm afraid to bleach and dye my hair pink fml]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My only tweet that's gotten over 1 â¤ï¸. Thank you @natalia_taylor_  ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚â¤ï¸ https://t.co/UZaZYI8v9A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natalia_taylor_ please ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natalia_taylor_ When's your single coming out tho??? ðŸ˜‚â¤ï¸#wisherisoverparty https://t.co/W2xxrF3nBE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is creativity? I don't think I have any.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I rarely use twitter bc I'm a piece of shit. ðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natalia_taylor_ fucking slay me mom ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone take me to California. Or New York. I want out of Florida. Fuck Florida.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone else with the reindeer filter: looks cute as fuck.
Me w/ it: looks like an actual chipmunk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do you start youtube. How are people creative. Give me yall's creativity because I'm fucking trash. Bye.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WillFerri I'm boring.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High key wanna be @AnnaTaughtYou 's best friend. You're cool as shit ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚â¤ï¸]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>