<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@aa_gilli At the end of the day, it depends how much you want to publish with @WarOnTheRocks. Getting caught double-submitting -&gt; ban for us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PSA: Don't double submit your articles (to us and another outlet). It wastes the time of others]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a very silly tweet. Loving your country like an adult means acknowleding what your country has done - right… https://t.co/TqikqTdIfw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join the WOTR team. Exciting full-time opportunity https://t.co/dcxCZJ9x1U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I like it when people underestimate us..." Indeed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This old video of Christopher Hitchens interviewing a white supremacist is worth re-watching today. https://t.co/TiYIza1Ob0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 opportunities to work for @WarOnTheRocks (that's right, fulltime jobs!) in our latest newsletter (sign up for it!) https://t.co/lWQKOlP8Jl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This closing paragraph in @MichaelNeiberg's latest is a homerun. Or, given the day, touchdown. #history… https://t.co/mvZp3d9uJ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The problem the United States has always had in crafting a Syria strategy is _______ https://t.co/oGg31lPxU9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actual lone wolves issue rare joint statement: "Stop comparing us to white terrorists"
https://t.co/Jiq4uY7dNy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerful short essay by @MichaelNeiberg https://t.co/G9If5XXruv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@briancdarling @PrivateSnuffy @WarOnTheRocks thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worth reading. Since @NKFinney wrote it, that's not surprising. https://t.co/0OCyA4VEsK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That job I announced yesterday is not the only one we are looking to fill.  https://t.co/BaCpQzvaXl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spread the word https://t.co/WO2Lu4sR7A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kelly fought back https://t.co/KCgln8TOC1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["How the little piggies will grunt when they hear how the old boar suffered"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JimmySky There will likely be some work with @charlie_simpson but I am afraid it will not be Bombshell related]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am very excited to share this news and this job opportunity. Please share far and wide. https://t.co/j5YvI11pyi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smsaideman You mean this? https://t.co/1JWvP9xaer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smsaideman Poli Sci and History]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeharSadr So you're annoyed I am trying to rebut a conspiracy theory. Interesting approach.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter: Best academic jobs sites?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There really is no evidence this is the case. Coup came much closer to killing Erdogan than most people seem to und… https://t.co/XwR0wGXbiB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a cool job. Closes 2/7 https://t.co/KlAzvmKfLY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bill_Owen yes I do very much. I was identifying issues that traditionally would have enraged Republicans. See Benghazi. Slow your roll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Almost complete silence from the right. What does the GOP stand for anymore on the international stage? Asking for a friend /2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SEAL killed in poorly planned op, allies are being shit-talked by POTUS, the Russian duma applauded his election. /1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I suspect most locales feel the same way https://t.co/fyerpY8a0Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rcjackson the irony is of course is that Trump habitually lies and makes up his own evidence. So he deserves/earns our trust more?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@couleurkf He already did on the campaign trail. This is our reality]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rcjackson You're accusing me of engaging in dishonest discourse? I am comfortable with Miller/Rucker's sourcing https://t.co/SiymLQn2pp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...If you support this guy, I truly have no idea what to say to you. I am going to work on that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["U.S. officials said he used his calls with Turnbull &amp; Peña Nieto to mention his election win or the size of crowd at his inauguration."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most GOP members of Congress who flipped out at Obama's attitude toward allies are totally silent now. Oh my]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tcwittes @LorenRaeDeJ @benjaminwittes @Susan_Hennessey @shaneharris @RatlSecurity team scotch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@painter_nancy It was something @LorenRaeDeJ said in the episode. No laps were harmed (or involved) in the production of this podcast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LorenRaeDeJ I have no stress inducing tap dancing to give]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurenFishDC well, it sure is something]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Champagne in the shower vs shower beer, only on the latest episode of #BombshellWOTR https://t.co/KJnIbUbJEM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charlie_simpson @LorenRaeDeJ @RadhaKIyengar #fakenews #fakenews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charlie_simpson @LorenRaeDeJ @RadhaKIyengar tell the whole story on the options you proposed #fakenews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just in time to download for the ride home @charlie_simpson @LorenRaeDeJ @RadhaKIyengar https://t.co/qVSY4zkJGo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CorsairQueen you know how to do Wednesdays right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving this essay by @ColinKahl and @HalBrands1 - two fine strategic thinkers who you should be following https://t.co/8lkMASpMjQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sorry it's by @shaneharris AND Gordon Lubold/4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@shaneharris cited @BuzzFeedNews' reporting - another outlet. Other papers (AHEM @nytimes) rarely do this now. Should b standard courtesy/3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd like to praise @shaneharris and @WSJ for doing something that other newspapers (AHEM @nytimes) often do not do.../2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good article by @shaneharris https://t.co/A8N4jsTuiH.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will never just call them Wikileaks anymore. From now on, always "The Kremlin proxy known as Wikileaks" https://t.co/CqqMnzBFZw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black is white. Up is down https://t.co/z7VzntHybm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benjaminwittes does this statute allow for a member of the NSC principals committee that isn't confirmed by Senate? https://t.co/neNgjwdp19]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rickmorgan2 Royal Institute of Technology]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am going to Sweden in June to talk about US foreign policy and ties btwn foreign and domestic politics. Should have some things to say]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@studyofwar thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It really is a massive success story in terms of implementation on every single level," said a batshit crazy senior administration official]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too many anti-Trump Republicans are stuck in schadenfreude over the left's anguish. Time to join hands and fight for our country]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. #mustread by @juliaioffe https://t.co/RNwYdNHOlT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bannon "expected a new &amp; even bigger war as part of the current crisis...did not seem at all fazed by the prospect" https://t.co/9B3mI4hfvM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually lots did but whatever. Expect to see this argument raised in far right media to defend Bannon https://t.co/iYeBLHZ6R2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@PopSci just jumped the shark https://t.co/tkNBzF5vAI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@benjaminwittes: Malevolence Tempered by Incompetence: Trump’s Horrifying Executive Order on Refugees and Visas https://t.co/i3DVjFJsmO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@DavidMaxwell161 compares past National Security Council organizations. Good context for yesterday's Trump NSC doc https://t.co/ySQhMnpTGm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thus, within minutes of his swearing in, Trump began exploiting Mattis just as I feared. My latest. https://t.co/AWXImK8p4z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ilangoldenberg @ZekeJMiller one has to assume there is a reason they changed this. Not just a minor reshuffle to preserve status quo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvansRyan202 @neonleon79 @dhnexon in the room and the nation's senior most military officer might not be]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neonleon79 @dhnexon When the Trump administration is facing a major national security crisis, the Breitbart guy will definitely be]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[principals committee with Steve Bannon, a far right extremist idealogue, &amp; without Joe Dunford, the Chairman of the Joint Chiefs of Staff/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the natsec world, we often say the president gets the National Security Council he wants. This president wants one that has a /1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bannon in. Dunford out https://t.co/79SOGrhQsT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How depressing... https://t.co/3Cxug8voNg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhD_femme @ushasahay yes actually]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lilla: "Today political Islamists, European nationalists, and the American right tell their ideological children essentially the same tale"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two books I have found to be helpful to understand where we are, both by Mark Lilla: The Reckless Mind, and The Shipwrecked Mind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamiemaccoll thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My latest. On Mattis, Trump, and the new executive orders https://t.co/AWXImK8p4z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grief-stricken Navy mourns the departure of beloved Secretary Ray Mabus https://t.co/7Y4OQlQumg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HarlanKefalas that's what the tv ad said]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im in a bar and just saw an ad for Jeff Sessions. Have there ever been ads run for a cabinet appointment until now? Ever?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrmaxrose @nicksknows I think you were supposed to dose our drinks with acid before the final comic's act]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching the GOP try to figure out what to do with the Affordable Care Act is like watching the dog that caught the car]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In our latest podcast @RichardHaass and I talk world order https://t.co/xMzBALIdL5 You should listen!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanaSchwartzzz he would do this but those photos are not exactly the same and it is hard to tell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnsemTartarus Haven't read enough about it yet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't even know where to begin, but probably with that line about a camel passing through the eye of a needle https://t.co/sFwPwHjJZe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OmerOzkizilcik @LizSly @Reuters  So I am comfortable with "descendant"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OmerOzkizilcik @LizSly @Reuters none of this changes the fact that the three AKP founders were former Milli Gorus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OmerOzkizilcik @LizSly @Reuters yes I know. Milli Gorus was the original subject of my never finished doctoral work. You're right but...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LizSly @Reuters AKP descendant of Milli Gorus. Similar to Brotherhood in some ways but never part of it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I cannot emphasize enough the profound psychological dysfunction this reveals https://t.co/W3thogoBt2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After all his time living in Hong Kong, the foreign contacts section of Bilden's SF-86 should be interesting reading]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wide-ranging discussion with @RichardHaass in the latest @WarontheRocks podcast https://t.co/xMzBALIdL5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#bombshellwotr (not pictured: @LorenRaeDeJ but we still love her) https://t.co/Ta4u9C8df8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeithNHumphreys @DrJJoyner i asked because the article explicitly explains how it is different from the norm but thanks for the snark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeithNHumphreys @DrJJoyner Did you read the whole article?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@profmarlowe I do think we need to carefully prioritize the stuff we actually hit the panic button on. This isn't at that level...yet anyway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People now out of govt who I am excited to hear from in all sorts of media. Add to the list! @elyratner @ColinKahl @ExumAM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Trump himself...had personally ordered the fiery response &amp; actually thought his spokesman was not forceful enough" https://t.co/tURYhapTYt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@profmarlowe I guess we will find out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reply to @cgberube Not too late]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>