<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorCollins thank you for standing up today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ananavarro please keep speaking for patriots everywhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TieDyeNation love y'all. Heartbreaking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AaronBlake @Bakari_Sellers really? Our country has come down to this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump not using your presidential account?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SopanDeb thanks Sopan. Surely, we are not all insane I hope]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatyTurNBC have been following your coverage since the beginning. Thank you for the reporting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenFranken yes. Hold the line!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ananavarro absolutely. Kids are off limits. He seems like a good kid too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaxineWaters just saw you with Katy Tur. Keep preaching the truth!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ananavarro I am losing all faith in anyone holding this democracy together]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MalcolmNance but who will step up and prosecute if appropriate?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bakari_Sellers and who will hold him accountable?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid but won't he be able to shut this down? Who will step up?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HallieJackson hold the line.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatyTurNBC counting on you and others to keep reporting. A free press is our last hope. N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#trumpdangertotherepublic speak up Patriots and remain vigilant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AshleyJudd thank you!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RachelPlatten thank you and great song!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#InauguralBall hope they release this on DVD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fight Song..just why? Classless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bakari_Sellers I'm an NC resident. Holy crap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid scary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ananavarro that was awful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid Is this a lecture or an uplifting speech?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid yes. I am speechless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnKerry thank you for all of your service.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump what is that crap behind you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bakari_Sellers some things are way over the line like attacking John Lewis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@repjohnlewis I stand with you sir]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ananavarro can we make him president please??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MalcolmNance we knew this would drop at some point. Matter of time. Good call]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ananavarro we all knew this was coming]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deray it is an insane argument.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid most people have tried to bend over backwards to be decent and make a bigger point. We are in an awful place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid well they claim it was made up. No way to win any points]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@89SteveSmith welcome home man. We have missed you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid @JohnWDean @Newsweek ready for this interview!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ananavarro I just read an article about how it started. Can't remember where at the moment. Collection of groups marching.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT just stop the nonsense please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thedailybeast @JoeMyGod misleading. There was a total ban before DADT. I was there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#inners good show. Stay woke!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CapehartJ still makes me cry. Every one of those. Thanks. Good man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump bless her heart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creating courier jobs! Lol https://t.co/1zgQiKCHBb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@politico @POLITICOMag just stop and give the woman some space. WTF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fahrenthold subscribed today on their special. Can afford that. Looking forward to more of your great reporting!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cher I don't trust them either. I would give directly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SopanDeb I hear Putin constantly. "Those aren't Russian soldiers in Ukraine"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC @Lawrence yes and thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenFranken thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump did your staff write this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisMurphyCT thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Charlie_Edward @Bakari_Sellers no words for this injustice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bakari_Sellers @Charlie_Edward well we will never hear his answer, sadly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZekeJMiller @maggieNYT @realDonaldTrump and well did that really happen? No facts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @maggieNYT and since there are no facts so..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HallieJackson the uniter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ananavarro @c_low_brown @Princeton yes please!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeMyGod this would be my sentiment. And then they could arrest me wish I would deserve.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MalcolmNance I am sitting here with a flag in one hand and a constitution in the other. What else can I do??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glaad @pjwcnc @HuffPostPol horrifying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Evan_McMullin thank you. We need someone to stand up please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maggieNYT yes. Please!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid @dcexaminer scarier every day and he's not even sworn in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid what is this report of Obama saying concede? Not happy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid damn lazy democrats. WTF sing this song every two years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ananavarro @MittRomney well, he did say Mitt would have gotten on his knees.  Disgusting. No respect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ananavarro I am a democrat but respect you so much. Someone needs to stand up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ananavarro give them hell Ana!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid @Obamas_Wing_Man that was the quote I was thinking about. Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MalcolmNance @Uab_BabaKofi I need one of these. Where to buy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ananavarro I'm in NC and this is what I drink. I need that cup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC please tell Trump that Putin is not our friend. I am beyond scared at this point]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid not enough alcohol in the world at this point]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeMyGod thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alivitali hugs to all of you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeMyGod as an NC resident, not happy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SopanDeb I see he's back "on message"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alivitali can they not ever tell the truth?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeerJeet @JoyAnnReid @ddale8 help us all!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ananavarro it's my favorite and now a reason to buy more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CapehartJ   loves seeing you on Hardball. You make me smile when things seem grim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid @lysoh @thedailybeast my brother works in IT and agrees that a private server is probably the way to go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid @aravosis of course they will. It's their plan for the country. Destroy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatyTurNBC Yes!! Hugs to you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SopanDeb maybe Lindsay Graham could explain it to him. What a moron,!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SopanDeb what would I do without you, dude. Just wanted to say thanks for all of your coverage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid I only know this from listening to the evil NPR. Thanks NPR!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid @yashar @RonRadosh what??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cher incredible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeMyGod I now need brain bleach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SopanDeb explains everything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SopanDeb @JasonMillerinDC @AlisynCamerota this was pretty amazing to watch this morning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CapehartJ thank you!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SopanDeb yes!  She alone could have stopped it. Keep digging. Lo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid I don't understand where these women are coming from.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid yep. He is projecting himself on to others. Classic case.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bakari_Sellers @CapehartJ thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CapehartJ I am about to have a panic attack.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>