<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Get @othemix to perform and I'll go https://t.co/Zgg12V6EAG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MY LIFE GOAL IS TO MAKE THE JAY Z BIOPIC SO NO ONE ELSE DO IT I CALL DIBS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[reasons i love The Economist: https://t.co/NLOYoAjHul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hahaian I'll see you in the camps they eventually send us to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Green is for the honey, gold is for the money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1000000% here for #punchanazi2017 https://t.co/ENuoVI7ouA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@angel_ninoo at the shopping stores? What about the justlookingaround stores?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What rhymes with fettuccini]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@holysebs I got breakfast tacos for the low]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salt water will kill leather]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thebindigirl who wears leather boots to the beach?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're not born in the wrong generation you're just a jaded fuck who thinks they're smarter than their peers and likes the Beatles. Go choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My favorite video in the world https://t.co/GhuCD56xO2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who knows a good tattoo artist/place to get tattoos at]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kikidahoe you try that Strawberry yoplait?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[who knew @LILBTHEBASEDGOD would be the one to blow this whole Trump-Russia thing wide open]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BASED GOD KNEW SOMETHING WAS WRONG THE WHOLE TIME WHY HASNT HE SAVED US https://t.co/I68C6dXjjZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world is a parody of itself. https://t.co/MwfRmqyxjh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think about this daily. https://t.co/yFzVMgRSag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need to actually be good at instagram it's embarrassing rn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate white people omg https://t.co/jmKUitsxFX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gambino really did a Gangsta Grillz mixtape and a smooth ass r&amp;b EP and you people act like he ain't the goat. Smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who tf thinks San Antonio is even a good city? Please tell me who loves the irradiated river walk?? https://t.co/QYkUCDQAdP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@freaakaay you mean your whole life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PLUG JUST TOLD ME NAH WOWOWOWOW IM JUMPING OFF A BRDGE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PMannie @alemmarie she stole 100 then stole 70$ worth of clothes b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@y0wassup damn dude I'm sorry this dude totally stole your girl in one tweet https://t.co/UcSfFwnd8L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alemmarie I hate that all your friends are stupid. It's 170]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who's tryna go to Coachella?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[asked me for my inspiration I told them global warming]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I woke up for no reason :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Memories are brain movies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hispanic girls are good for the soul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OH YOU WANT SPACE OKAY BET ILL GIVE YOU SOME SPACE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neverlandken with fireworks in it yeah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FUCK EVERYONE IM GOING TO ROGUE ONE BY MYSELF AND SPENDING MY WHOLE PAYCHECK ON FIREWORKS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If this is love why does it hurt like this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Correction: Yung Tuna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want Taco Bell :-(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neverlandken everyone knows the answer Kirkland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neverlandken it's bad for the baby tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I honestly love Nina Simone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just wish I was good enough for her]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HAHAHAHA YOU THOUGHT YOU WERE SLICK TRYING TO HIDE https://t.co/4tHsk7UnMK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bigbootayhoes OH SHIT OKAY BAD BIH MICHELLE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Legit just need to cuddle with someone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yo I wanna be headass and spoil this girl so bad wtf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lmaoooooo when that feeling of existential dread comes back to you and you fall into a pit of sorrow lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kanye is Secretary of State. https://t.co/hgvF1TaXAc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sorry to everyone for having a mental breakdown but now I've realized J Coles new album is the album of the year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hibachi for lunch is the best thing out of 2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My hobbies include typing out long texts about my emotions and then just deleting them because I'm too chicken shit to send them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@notmarcofuentes it's okay I forgive you man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does anyone want to be my friend?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alemmarie that's a waffle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing is going to make me happy like she did. Now I have nothing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SOMEONE ACTUALLY KILL ME]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IM SO PATHETIC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She won't call but wow if she did]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why am I so alone :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's snowing in Hawaii]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She doesn't care about me and in need to understand that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emotions are stupid and I'm stupid for feeling them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's 6 and I already want to die.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can I mute the words"j cole" on twitter?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How is J Cole gonna talk shit about fake deep rappers? https://t.co/swjUnqiYez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NathanZed not a performance but this freestyle is insane https://t.co/BcfOlRcII5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DEALING WITH DEPRESSION BUT IM THUGGING WITH A PASSION]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm now suddenly an Astros fan https://t.co/MSfpcjXaIr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@holysebs show your spirit!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@othemix @937thebeat @ChickfilA I know trill Sammy coming]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lmao there goes my good day and here comes the fucking sorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nah I can take a wild guess and say it's still gonna be trash J Cole shit https://t.co/1VgTET2tcI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know she won't but I hope she calls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would love to but I feel like if I even tried showing my emotions like that it wouldn't go well https://t.co/B87tiddoXV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My day went from 0 to 100 in 45 seconds https://t.co/gbKqu2ZgVC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlfredoVTEC that's almost a fourth of a gallon of gas tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm gonna lay down in the road and whoever runs me over can get my money from my dead body]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will pay for someone to slit my throat btw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who wants to do me a favor and just hit me over the head with a frying pan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I WAS ASLEEP I WAS FINE AND THWN I HAD TO FUCKING WAKE UP WHY OMG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[did someone say existential crisis in the middle of the night? Way ahead of you 😎😎]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know it's late but can someone come and suffocate me I already have a pillow just come thru and kill me right quick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bigbootayhoes no. So it's more entertaining if you cut their brakes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life without her is like a pencil with no lead, like a canvas with no paint, like https://t.co/g7oByKoqrT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was about to sleep now this got me lit wtf https://t.co/SyjrWn45d6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got a call from my mother and I think she's in the upside down]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not that I hate anyone it's that I hate myself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LOL I THOUGHT I SAD BEFORE BUT BOY O BOY IT JUST GOT REAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah so don't ruin it https://t.co/SEuBq6ShdL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Water drippin ice tea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Whateverr_14 lol spread the love then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually me https://t.co/qTH92twDef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rachel__Evans :-( then what's the point]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is taking a shower drunk safe? Some pls answer need for friend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish she knew.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck around watch diners, drive-ins and dives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who the fuck eats pecan pie?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@queendreeea 😄thanks Andrea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alemmarie thanks almond head]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>