<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Meaning achieved!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today, my desperate quest for meaning in life has brought me to Crystal Palace. #CRYSUN @SunderlandAFC https://t.co/ZaZaf2Lfig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He'll be the judge of that. https://t.co/UerwkOSt1u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's bin day AND #transferdeadlineday. This won't happen again in our lifetime.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#DrainTheSwamp https://t.co/NHSFjpkPMF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danthomascomedy Haha yes. It's not just impressive or anything. Genuinely enjoying it. Seems best not to question it as you're going along.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danthomascomedy Worth it.  Me and Chopping are in the 300s.  It's an astonishing book. Never read anything like it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danthomascomedy That's a belter!  How's #DanReadsInfiniteJest going?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonArnopp @RetroGamer_Mag I thought she was going out with Wayne Of The Exploding Fist?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonArnopp @RetroGamer_Mag I loved Space Harriet.  How's she doing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's why Jill Stein's in the new Adam Sandler movie. https://t.co/BR8FpK7xXb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump45 is the political equivalent of a "100% Unauthorised" boy band calendar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I keep my Linkin Park Crawling CD close and my One Step Closer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeling optimistic #WBASUN https://t.co/oyLvD7pApM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SiHawkins I'm going to West Brom tomorrow. I'll have a word.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danthomascomedy @MrChrisChopping Just finished Neil Patrick Harris' Choose Your Own Autobiography (which is great) for light relief from IJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danthomascomedy @MrChrisChopping Enjoyed it. Got a bit samey in places like all of them. Really liked the epilogue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SunderlandAFC Let's hope they mostly attack down their left]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was worried about Moyes' lineup for tonight's #FACup replay, but relieved to see he's only started with 3 right backs #Sunderland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danthomascomedy @MrChrisChopping We need to start shorthand : IJ p193 U4 c10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danthomascomedy @MrChrisChopping Just got to Madagascar.  Great so far, except the Scottish bit felt like filler. Jump, shoot, jump etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrChrisChopping @danthomascomedy You missed out on what we now just call 'The Scottish Level' so you're doing well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonArnopp I loved the Texas Ticklestick Massacre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robdelaney Glad to see your large son doing so well. https://t.co/i0BvX1ZD6O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophia_salmassi @inkysquiggles eBay, search hamster shirt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danthomascomedy @MrChrisChopping I played 4 games of top level Scrabble and read zero also]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I'd been at the #Trump press conference, when he said 'germaphobe' I'd have bellowed "URINE IS STERILE!" and stormed out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta catch 'em all... HEGEMON #Trump #TrumpCabinet https://t.co/5D4BMK7tKH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is this news? I thought everything in his bathroom was gold #goldenshower #trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danthomascomedy @MrChrisChopping They do say 'Hijack' is one of those books you must read before you die]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bechillcomedian Before Countdown audition had the word 'culminate' in my head all day. 1st round of audition the 9 letters made 'culminate']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrChrisChopping @danthomascomedy I've stopped at 95 as the nearest chapter break to 100, and am awaiting further instruction]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrChrisChopping @danthomascomedy The train game story footnote is even longer. Good though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrChrisChopping @danthomascomedy OK, I read the damn footnote.  Fair enough, it got more relevant as it went on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrChrisChopping @danthomascomedy I read 2 pages of that and skimmed the titles of the rest.  It can't be crucial, surely...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danthomascomedy It'd be quite a thing if he made that up.  It feels older than time itself.  A classic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrChrisChopping @danthomascomedy was in middle of Murakami/Ozawa on music and Neil Patrick Harris autobiog but they've gone by the wayside]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danthomascomedy Like Infinite Jest, Uncharted series is enjoyable but I find the depth of character and plot bewildering, had to make notes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danthomascomedy I did 1, 2, 3 so I enjoyed 1 due to lack of context. Got bored halfway thru 3 from fatigue I think, but rallied for ending]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danthomascomedy @MrChrisChopping Let me know when you finish 3 and we'll have a discussion group]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danthomascomedy @MrChrisChopping You've got more children than me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danthomascomedy @MrChrisChopping Should we all meet up at a certain point then? I'm at page 78. Skipped 5 pages of Himself's filmography]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GingerWildheart Fuck me! I want to hear THAT RIFF from 'Deterioration' live! #mutation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaftLimmy I'm in Cardiff and would definitely come to Bristol for it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danthomascomedy Likewise. 30 odd pages in. It is dense but more readable than I was expecting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisPurchase @matthaig1 Certainly helped me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markolver @phlaimeaux Is it a dugong show?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dafyddg @sophia_salmassi That IS a dynamic list]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dafyddg I used to love Fruit Polos - my secondary school sweet of choice.  Impressed that anyone got anywhere near that hashtag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dafyddg ...because Polo mints are white...?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Bromwich Albino #SwapALetterDepigmentAFootballClub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danthomascomedy Me too, or the bath https://t.co/PYVN3bWjdK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danthomascomedy I think adult undergarments may be needed to finish this book.  Some of the paragraphs are 5 pages long.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danthomascomedy There's a chapter break at page 95 called YEAR OF THE DEPEND ADULT UNDERGARMENT - I'll see you there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elisjames I'm planning on doing Palace vs Sunderland on my own. I'll now be thinking of myself as adorable while I'm there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danthomascomedy I understand.  I missed the whole 92/93 season because of Greg Bear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danthomascomedy I don't, but I like books. Just finished re-reading Murakami's 1Q84 so I reckon I can handle the strain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danthomascomedy Nice. I'll grab a copy in town tomorrow (hadn't even got that far) and we can go from there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danthomascomedy I've been meaning to read that as well.  Fancy doing a mini book club?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisPurchase @washingtonpost @ArkEncounter *googles "girl-Jesus twin incest tandem-crucifixion vids"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dreamt that someone got Eden Maine back together and I was the only original member, but on vocals. Other original members were very angry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bin day is just pain leaving the body]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like I dodged a bullet by not seeing The Matrix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Serena or Venus?  Who is the most tennis-y Williams?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've got a problem with the balls of my feet, so I'm going to the uropodiatrist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In American porn they have a thing called 'ass to mouth' (or ATM for short).  In the UK we call that manoeuvre 'cashpoint'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only straightedge corporation is XeroX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHAT DO WE WANT?
Scientific accuracy!
WHEN DO WE WANT IT?
Linear time is a human construct!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Festive joke participant 1: Someone's taken the German fruit bread!
Festive joke participant 2: You mean... WE'VE BEEN BURGLED!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaftLimmy Don't make me mantinsplain it to you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GaryLineker Got to the semi-final of Countdown and played for my primary school's third team. Sunderland fan so have low expectations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colhowarth I know mate, but if Jamie Carragher can play for Liverpool, there's no reason you can't play for Burnley U23s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone who half-heartedly sleepwalks is a somnambipambulist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...touched for the very first time https://t.co/L6nzQQY89Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClintJEdwards Maybe it was champagne?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My wife went to Slavia.
Yugo?
No, she went on her own.
#CLASSIC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danthomascomedy @HighCastleTV Could be construed as a dig at the Japanese? That show would be better for more 70s sitcom humour actually]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pattonoswalt Weird Science]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exciting! I love a cup draw. I wonder who Sunderland are going to get! https://t.co/YZLI5CYXAB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is #niche #gold https://t.co/lUvM1UpMC0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MartinPilgrim1 It'll be fine. After Z we go into numbers, then punctuation, then emojis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 5 stages of metal grief : Nile, Angra, Blind Guardian, Dissection and Accept]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HILARIOUS new #ComedySheep #Stand-Up TV series starts TONIGHT 10pm on Made in Cardiff TV!! LIVE STREAM: https://t.co/eyxv2f3bBT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're alone, and life is making you lonely
You can always go
Down
Down
Down
Down
Down
Down
Down
Down
Down
Down
Down
Down
Down
Down
Dow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GingerWildheart I'm going to the shop for eggs &amp; bananas, and now that's stuck in my head to the tune of 'Cars &amp; Vaginas', just so you know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vickyhungerford @GingerWildheart @BLOODSTOCKFEST That sounds perfect for a Mutation live show XXXX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Red white and blue Brexit" is on a par with "quiet bat people"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A red white and blue #brexit?" American? French? Dutch? Slovenian? Slovakian? Cuban? Congolese? North Korean? RUSSIAN!?!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonArnopp I'm currently working my way through everything the Duplass Brothers production company have made, and it's all gold]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteveMartinToGo I dunno man, that's a pretty nice straw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My favourite episode of Seinfeld is 'The Alt-Right Soup Guy']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spherulitic "Brain-drain the swamp"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TWAT FACT : Eric Bristow's full name is HystERICal HuBRISTOWeighinonsomethingyouknownothingabout]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone do this! #TweetForShelter https://t.co/QdOEZs83Vb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DEATH FACT : Fidel Castro's full name was High Fidelity Castrol GTX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mocking Trump is like shooting fish in a barrel... if those fish controlled the world's largest military.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's topical anagram pair : We need BALLSIER LIBERALS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy birthday and #InternationalMensDay to the man of all men... @BretMichaelsPUA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@comedylopez It's on XXXBox One and Babestation 4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaftLimmy Cardiff please!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>