<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump's early crisis// management by edict reminiscent of Henry the 8th  https://t.co/X5kqqJ3GHn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House statement on acting attorney general // they say betrayal I say it's protection of the constitution  https://t.co/5nPn3p71MC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[J.K. Rowling slams Mike Pence with 1 biblical tweet // checking social media of green card holders &amp; views on #Trump https://t.co/PLtolgmIeM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maureen Dowd: Who knew it would get so weird so quickly?
via @IrishTimes
https://t.co/MeyCSssYf2 // the scariest man on earth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slapdash Trump order ignores real danger: Max Boot https://t.co/H092cL9tDE via @USATODAY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once again, images show colossal crowds taking to the streets against Trump https://t.co/hJc066EhaE // who did they vote for I wonder ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump executive order: Million sign petition to stop UK visit https://t.co/HPjVQwpCT5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moran opposes Ireland facilitating US refugee ban // gobshite  https://t.co/O3lNYOvY0F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Remove US officials from Irish airports' - Minister // what a stupid pointless &amp; typically token political "idea"  https://t.co/SyPlg9HY6F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fianna Fáil is the most popular party in the country https://t.co/j8nSIEwQ7s // Do F-all for 5 years &amp; bingo -you are electable. Sad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Philippines to suspend drug war to clean up 'corrupt' police //same cops who killed the drug addicts for him ? https://t.co/ryoP33Izfw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/5IMO66UeYz. // America slipping into radicalism and intolerance - bye bye miss American Pie https://t.co/5IMO66UeYz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outrage over Trump's immigrant ban helps ACLU raise more money online in one weekend than in all of 2016 https://t.co/gL3cpTR2uk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Philippines' Duterte orders police to 'cleanse' ranks amidst murder scandal // the hypocrisy is breathtaking  https://t.co/kEFqlahpv1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Trump said about travel ban is false // can America survive this shambolic president ?  https://t.co/8vLk0MQSai]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dual citizenship Britons exempt from Trump travel ban // oh well that's all right then isn't it ?! No it's not… https://t.co/eKU5y0SV9z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sir Mo Farah: Olympic champion criticises Donald Trump's US travel ban https://t.co/quXclUGTbn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House discussing asking foreign visitors for social media info and cell phone contacts // madness in the USA https://t.co/NKcOHSmPzk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calls for Enda Kenny to cancel White House trip over Trump's refugee ban  // yeah lets have more unemployment #duh  https://t.co/2cbCoTSYdd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's the future": Restaurants and cafés are cracking down on smoking outside  (via @thejournal_ie) https://t.co/yI5AHKkw1R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poll: Should MMA be regulated in Ireland? (via @thejournal_ie) // irrelevant because the money is NOT in Ireland  https://t.co/wo4Ck9bi4o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Green card holders from Trump-restricted countries impacted by ban https://t.co/zbnu3PrujT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theresa May fails to condemn Donald Trump on refugees // gone to the #darkside  https://t.co/eUjPokRUOV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FauxMole You are right &amp; there are lots of US grown Ines too. But Syria particularly is a basket case]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theresa May signs €117m fighter jet deal with Turkey  (via @thejournal_ie) // for bombing the #Kurds ? https://t.co/1iPmINzZyl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FauxMole And Trump is saying - I want to know who I'm letting in to my country]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FauxMole That's silly - Merkek let 1000000 refugees in with NO checks on who they were - that's crazy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FauxMole No - but we must do very good checks on them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FauxMole That's what was wrong with invading Iraq too - but letting in battle hardened jihadists because we feel s… https://t.co/n0PvZpIm9Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FauxMole Well random nuts with a chip on their shoulder aren't the same as trained terrorists with a mission from hell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Incompatible like oil and water' Fine Gael rules out Sinn Féin coalition  https://t.co/ldmUVPiYq1 // 2nd time this kite flew recently in FG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FauxMole The prob is that it only takes one nut job to kill hundreds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FauxMole True - so we have enough of our own without importing them - I just think we need to be careful who we le… https://t.co/vvYvk5c0ye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do people object to Lidl and Aldi in their towns? // silly because they are cheaper and better quality  https://t.co/Uaio6be7L3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poll: Should Fine Gael consider going into power with Sinn Féin?// the old guard is still in situ  https://t.co/CQcpNwj6EX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mark Zuckerberg drops controversial lawsuits seeking to buy Hawaiian land (via @thejournal_ie) https://t.co/IqnK6sIHOU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump executive order prompts Google to recall staff // lets face it - refugees have been involved in EU terrorism  https://t.co/fnnkg2KySG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[KGB chief linked to Trump file found dead amid Kremlin cover up claims https://t.co/Vn8S1PvgU0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump says he will make Christian refugees a priority https://t.co/t374lBPlCS via @USATODAY // naked racism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doomsday Clock: Humanity might be edging closer to its end // prophets of doom  https://t.co/U0TLPFpgI9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2,000 years later, scientists finally know what's in these charred Roman scrolls // Bread , Milk and a pot noodle  https://t.co/Ezw3VIXbwr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nikki Haley, Trump's UN envoy: 'Back us or we're taking names' // bully tone won't go down well in Europe  https://t.co/JYMm3o6x1e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richardadalton You could be on to something there 😜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump fan charged with hate crimes over JFK Muslim attack https://t.co/OqUrQNfPws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enda believes undocumented Irish with 'minor indiscretions' will not be turfed out by Trump // what's minor ?  https://t.co/NhXGk2orYe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More crap from the bully https://t.co/j6QKx2RI3m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FauxMole @Independent_ie Who knows - it's baloney because lots of tickets miraculously turn up on the legit scalpi… https://t.co/HLKTWvx5mn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia decriminalises some forms of domestic violence https://t.co/Mb49464keb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most annoying type of airline passenger is ... https://t.co/3NbbfLoBNc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning issued ahead of Ed Sheeran ticket sales // this is a smokescreen to deflect from the legit sites scalping  https://t.co/nJCFD3MOJt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drunk driver with 485 convictions who killed teen while speeding jailed for 18 months // dysfunctional system https://t.co/joygz6XSpX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kenny in firing line over 'nonsensical and concerning' Sinn Féin comments // chief whip did this too - it's a plan https://t.co/R5grquPsDD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Occupants ordered to leave 'unauthorised hotel' with 17 people sleeping in one room, 36 in basement   https://t.co/J3Qn8MPJf1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Donald Trump changed the presidency in 7 days // a bit like the Berlin bunker but at the start not the end  https://t.co/ez97lNqTxs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump floats 20% tax on Mexican imports to pay for wall, but considering other options // on the fly  https://t.co/lDQ8IQmYWU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Building iPhones in U.S. is non-starter, says ex-Foxconn exec https://t.co/dONVxSNEL6 via @USATODAY // Trump will destroy America]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump: Import tax to pay for Mexico wall // there's no doing business with this mad dog  https://t.co/bDOrwwTR2l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VICTORIA WHITE: Trump, a climate change enemy Disney couldn’t have dreamed up https://t.co/cbwISDJURX // short term Armageddon more pressing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US to upgrade Philippine military bases as Duterte reverses stance // another nutter in charge of the asylum  https://t.co/SYGZNTE59M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Opposites attract': Theresa May signals strong relationship with Trump // #May is going to sell out principles  https://t.co/j9kjzg6SKB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jeremy Corbyn faces ANOTHER round of resignations over Brexit
// i get a bad feeling about the world #trump #corbyn  https://t.co/veydzWfyoG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-British soldier says he was ‘kind of a torturer’ in Northern Ireland
via @IrishTimes
https://t.co/OCA2rfMmOw // where does it all end]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump slams Mexico as leader cancels trip // a bully in the playground  https://t.co/Rp0bXYUyXo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shia LaBeouf arrested outside NYC museum https://t.co/vDhgJddCBE via @USATODAY // more trouble for Shia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richardadalton Lol - sounds like it's not very hard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ireland drops another place in global corruption ranking (via @thejournal_ie) // corruption eating up our democracy https://t.co/zY9zR2WeqX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBC News: Lindsey Graham to Trump: Stop Claiming Millions of 'Illegals' Voted https://t.co/LOQ3lvBeAw // unfounded racist crap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia: We want to normalize relations with US, Europe // Hitler did too until he invaded Poland  https://t.co/mZ5GMiW0nj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dow makes history: cracks 20,000 barrier!  https://t.co/Kp5xocvf8p via @USATODAY // #trump &amp; his billionaire friends happy - joe soap poor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump calls for 'major investigation' into voter fraud // an independent one I hope  https://t.co/ZMBni4FJAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will Donald Trump mean the end of global trade? // higher prices in the USA  https://t.co/ARNU0yBV9k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Badlands on Twitter: US park climate change tweets deleted // when the truth is not allowed by the leaders  https://t.co/2mw2XaHnX7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paris Jackson: 'My father was murdered' https://t.co/dZcbM3kXQz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man held over 'threats' in Gina Miller Brexit case // good to see this being dealt with by police  https://t.co/fJACS6mAuP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oscars accidentally names Adams instead of Negga via @RTENewsNow // #alternativefacts  https://t.co/oICZaCaOwR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBC News: Analysis: Why Trump May Regret 'Alternative Facts' Fight https://t.co/6etph59134 // the Trump who cried Wolf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump believes millions voted illegally, WH says -- but provides no proof // next it will be Roswell https://t.co/uyMGrvEyWZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's voter fraud claim 'based on evidence' // more alternative facts ? https://t.co/mxcjG9ksp2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FBI Director James Comey says president asked him to stay and he agreed https://t.co/qrHfysuQVZ via @USATODAY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senator says driverless cars could save rural pubs https://t.co/m1U5ntsNgE via @rte]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outrage as south Dublin apartment residents hit for €30m over planning failures // the planning enforcers must pay  https://t.co/yYnj5VU4kd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nigeria suicide bomber 'was carrying baby' via @RTENewsNow https://t.co/McYotWa8vG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Irish bloggers will now have to declare when they're promoting a product in their posts (via @thejournal_ie)  https://t.co/1MIyPCEpsH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[60% of Irish people borrow to pay their household bills (via @thejournal_ie) https://t.co/Qjz3YdTlLp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An awful lot of Irish people are feeling less positive about the world following Trump's inauguration // change  https://t.co/AKi8zpcL8l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apartment owners could face 'up to €30 million' bill to bring complex up to regulations // failure of government !!! https://t.co/DWbr8oiSzx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MICHAEL CLIFFORD: How eager is the commissioner to hear from whistleblowers? https://t.co/18k7bWlDg1  // something rotten]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ewan McGregor snubs Piers Morgan over host's remarks on women's marches | Irish Examiner // #obnoxious #Piers  https://t.co/KgJDIZerHa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outrage as south Dublin apartment residents hit for €30m over planning failures // #beacon #sandyford https://t.co/yYnj5VU4kd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK Supreme Court says legislation to trigger Brexit must be brought before parliament https://t.co/jXuV7sDHGs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backlash after Ryanair mocks Aer Lingus link to illegal immigrants // it IS a criminal offence so why the hysteria ? https://t.co/TpBQWBowpb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inside the Obamas' new $6.4m home...just a few doors down from Ivanka Trump - Independent.ie // a bit twee ? https://t.co/aBpmYpcQJe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear team Trump, 'alternative facts' are lies - https://t.co/48grz0OWQF https://t.co/DVenrdfGsB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 things you should know about Michelle O'Neill, the new Sinn Féin leader at Stormont | Irish Examiner https://t.co/G3g2Fe68YF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US investigating Flynn calls with Russian diplomat https://t.co/ljL7GRILEu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poll: Should people go on strike over abortion in Ireland? https://t.co/hmeYeS1Wyc // ridiculous concept !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exiled Gambian leader 'stole millions' from country in his final weeks of power // bring him back in handcuffs  https://t.co/tF0aLDJKRe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Anglo Irish Bank director jailed for two-and-a-half years for fraud https://t.co/n5fhH9DDOD // Anglo victims didn't get off easy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iceland in mourning after missing young woman's body found on beach  (via @thejournal_ie) https://t.co/aTgUjpxqvG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mater Hospital warns of very long waiting times and high numbers at emergency department  (via @thejournal_ie)  https://t.co/DPS1ZPB47a]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>