<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Colinja21771976 @elliemail as soon as the AFP let Abbott sleep in their bed they were compromised]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnfieldHQ @JamesPearceEcho @LivEchonews thought he had already left, been very quiet for a while]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Thefinnigans amazing when words come back to bite people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Phil_Mattingly @jeffjarvis must too close to home for DT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@byTonyWilson he might be chickenshit but he is our chickenshit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia always a step behind UK, how long till we hear about this https://t.co/QKpDWZ45cq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MinhKular @virgotweet if you think these ones are bad, you should have seen the ones that didn't make the cut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cricket_fan_cz @christnagavier @elliemail sorry but with the greatest of respect you sir are a wanker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarWhyte and so they bloody well should]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emilyjanefox @VFHIVE how much is that in US$]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@firstdogonmoon china has to be favourite So will it be US/Russia v China with Australia advising the troops]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charlesfirth to take place where?  On foreign soil or at home #interestingtimesahead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@workmanalice when will pollies learn to stop repeating themselves. The comedians love this stuff, I'm sure it will be a "news" item tonight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another brilliant text by Ms Caro. Please take time out your busy lives and read this. Thanks Jane https://t.co/2KeK09XKCH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timdunlop @SkyNewsAust @PaulineHansonOz Tim, how much money have you just saved the Taxpayers of this Country]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katobell @beneltham I want to know who it was that ate Gary s sausage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkDiStef no muslims thank you very mucho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redmedic56 @ged0407 @RedAlert1963 He jetted Suarez back from Uruguay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@npomalley @trintran @NYDailyNews where's Rup Murdoch at present]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeCarlton01 @JohnBarilaroMP @pmens72 @GladysB do the Nats have that much power?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Asher_Wolf you seem to attract the nicest people Asher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oneplanetmikey can't see Pauline liking this poster, will be change to one more suitable to her]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oneplanetmikey @aulich7 @workmanalice yes He is working two at once]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bprophetable @deemadigan was that on Spikes headstone? #brilliant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deemadigan @bprophetable always liked the one that said "I told you I was sick"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MyFirstCousin @jboyded I'm sure her boyfriend will only to willing to sign up to attack China when we follow US blindly into another war]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@giddyupbill @samdastyari @AmbientUXr wouldn't Mexico then buy product from another supplier (Country) and so send a US company to the wall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KimLeutwyler check out local artist/hip hop singer https://t.co/9t5shuvkPB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid he wants that "popular" vote figure any way he can get it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LelHulagirl63 @TimWattsMP @KKeneally @tanya_plibersek @Perorationer @theage Transparent in that we can see straight through them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wendy_harmer change the locks while they're out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cpyne @workmanalice @Defence_CASG @DeptDefence Why hello sailor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AP that is not "Breaking" news]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Susan11790 @ktumulty maybe that's what Trump would like, gives him a chance to press those buttons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tess_tess2 @ktumulty @jim_hollifield I believe Nauru is controlled by Australia $$$ paying big time for refugee concentration camp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChangeMillieu it's seems to be all about fast tracking these days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bugwannostra @SenatorCash unemployment stats up yet $b given to employment/training agencies for what result]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorKarl @ag47phoenix that will make Rupert Murdoch a happy man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChangeMillieu Engineers these days are taught using blocks. In the past Meccano sets were the rule]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davrosz @independentaus he doesn't hail from Cardiff by any chance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pyne is back #theproject]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HuffPostUK @toninicho Do you have a breakdown for the amount of money spent by each country in the search]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JB_AU @toninicho @MarkDiStef only because she believes that is where the votes are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Asher_Wolf @YaThinkN @HuffPostAU $1m doing what? He's in bed by 9pm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvolvingMeme @GeorgiaWesten @7NewsSydney just follow the Ministers around for 6 months &amp;report everything they do, who they meet where when]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are Mr Pyne and Mr Morrison still in hiding]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TweetAuspol cmon media please follow up on this #FederalICACnow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@susanamet @rranwa @smh the Senate committee should start by probing themselves. Although some may enjoy it too much]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SWSyd @PCKJ3627 @BarnsGreg I thought he was a Telly Tubby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bugwannostra ?? A living away from home allowance is paid daily, doesn't one need to prove an accommodation expense has been paid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YaThinkN where are Morrison and Pyne they both have been quiet for awhile]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bugwannostra to claim an expense doesn't one have to spend the money 1st. If so how can someone claim more than one earns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@virgotweet was this finalised?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mickeyg4 @ChangeMillieu @MarkDiStef $1.6m and how many jobs did her agencies actually fill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Qldaah the sad fact is She wears a see through top but nobody looks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bugwannostra @TurnbullMalcolm could make things tough in the HOR for him but stiff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bugwannostra @TurnbullMalcolm He should make her resign/sack Then recontest the safe seat they will the margin reduced but shouldn't lose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@demon_dave @bugwannostra @Forthleft2 @ladywhitepeace1 @SkyNewsAust @SenatorWong so be it, let the fun  begin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Thetribalmind @Colvinius #bringbacksubs not while Abe is here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Slate I thought they were doing an Abba impersonation https://t.co/46c5mSBgEx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidbewart @9NewsSyd @TurnbullMalcolm is MT showing Abe where the WW2 Japanese submarines came up to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For a thorough investigation of Trump check out @Khanoisseur brilliantly researched https://t.co/pzpOLxLuLB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phbarratt just another excuse for a pissup at someone else's expense, always ends up with the taxpayers of Australia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump how many screenshots have been taken of this tweet, could be a record.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chuckwoolery @lapuntadelfin so many experts, so many opinions, how do we the public find "The Truth" who do we believe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Amanda_Moseley_ @WeathermanABC I heard that it's bc rural readings were taken by volunteers/farmers therefore a reasonable time was needed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KetanJ0 @IndigenousX I believe the Syrian toddlers name was Aylan not Alan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TonyHWindsor could they be afraid of getting some MP's caught in the ICAC net, even so still need to push hard for it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bugwannostra @TurnbullMalcolm safe as,  needs a swing 22% to lose the seat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Sydney residents should boycott Waringah area until voters get rid of Abbott. Blockade at the Spit bridge" I've be… https://t.co/rS3aaMpI5J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BertUlsterman @JohnWren1950 @Bishop64 @Umbreago75 @KellyODwyer pollies wouldn't read it anyway They don't read proposed bills/laws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Left_of_Labor @sharpfang cmon @billshortenmp you should have enough to push for #FederalICAC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaneCaro sorry Jane I didn't realise you had seen this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this yours @AndrewLamingMP what a nice man you are. cc @JaneCaro https://t.co/nk0jeqs5wD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YaThinkN should be "our" license as we are paying for the planes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobCoco it takes 3 of them to say sweet f#@k all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSmarmyBum @JenLucPiquant proof once more that politicians do not read the legislation they vote on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lenoretaylor @guardian that's great Are there any Pro bono Lawyers out there willing to take these cases on Or maybe a Class Action]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Katieisfree @EddyJokovich @vogrady2132 there was no mention of Arfur being part of "independent investigation"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BettyBowers @toninicho does that include entertainers who supported Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nadiasdaly @abcnews there are investigations and there are "investigations" wink wink say no more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Henry_Belot @AndrewBGreene these things take time meanwhile there's rotting to be done]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erinrileyau @AndrewBGreene @sussanley @AusGovFinance I believe that she had a ComCar waiting in every US city she visited, I could be wrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nrllosers @SkyNewsAust @AustralianLabor @SenatorWong @sussanley it is already]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PCKJ3627 @brucerossbrc @abcnews that must have Arfur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@geeksrulz @smh he lived in Bella Vista which means beautiful view (of the poor people in Seven Hills)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sciam @TurnbullMalcolm can you pass this on to Arfur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrumens @beneltham @JmarrMarr Arfur only looks into brown paper bags]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brucerossbrc @abcnews I'm impressed that Ley hung around long enough for about 10 questions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephanieando @hamishNews @sussanley investigation #bullshit and reinstate bloody Arfur #notgoodenough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JustJen64  just poor and absolute arrogance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YaThinkN @gongvoter I'm not donating just to get someone elected I want for my hard earned $$]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brucehawker2010 where is Turnbull he should be fronting up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AshGhebranious Presser at 10:00am then turn up ready to start at 10:00am no reason for being late #arrogance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AshGhebranious I don't know, I'm a trifle cynical]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AshGhebranious and sorry I'm late]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AshGhebranious 3 questions and "have to go" sorry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnWren1950 are there any apartments for sale in the building]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeCarlton01 @billshortenmp it seems Lab is afraid some of its own may get snagged in the #FederalICAC net,if it happens then so be it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Undercoverinfo1 @DeepPolitics you don't think Russia will try 2 take back some of the old states esp w US (Trump) onside #interestingtimes]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>