<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Too much, too fast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Adventureden Friday can hardly wait for his next day at the Den. He hangs about dreaming of his favourite place! https://t.co/1qDYeivENn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Met Opera’s ‘Rusalka’ Is a Dark, Sexy Hit https://t.co/f2FfGrzMeZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a great article on @kingsgatemall in the Vancouver Courier!! Home away from home.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kitsilano We are back into the snow here in #Vancouver https://t.co/I68QqOw3YX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Erin_R05 I am so glad to have that sorted in my mind. She was an amazing basset, the oldest I have ever heard of and magnificent!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Erin_R05 I think this is Tippy. Want to make sure I am right. https://t.co/omFEBFmrjS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@streetcrow What great profile pics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fab #shippingcontainer housing on Alexander Street #Vancouver Love those lines! https://t.co/XFkLtaUcEG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@HrishiHirway: In 2017, being a reporter is the most punk as fuck job there is."@tlupick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing like a basset hound #basset to keep you honest and with noble intentions #dogfriday https://t.co/5IQJwWrBkd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#car2go three car 2 go's all lined up ready to go in #Vancouver this morning https://t.co/z2VZwJ6S2S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My old shipping container home in the DTES, Vancouver. My heart took me there today. #heart https://t.co/Acf4NIEMlU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JustinTrudeau I am so glad you are our Prime Minister. This image of you is such a positive statement for Canada. https://t.co/XORnBJpe8S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@globeandmail Brave story revealing struggle with mental illness of a member of the KC Irving family. A blockbuster for #BellLet'sTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxNews There is NO Wall between Guatemala and Mexico. NO Wall on the southern border of Mexico.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I dreamed I was a lazy boy on an old LazyBoy but it was like sleeping on a diving board." #dogfriday #basset https://t.co/HmV6RXDKUG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inside Glanrhyd, the first solar 'eco hamlet' in Wales https://t.co/Jsldak0TgA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["How long do I have to hang here before we can go for that walk?" #bassetlife #dogfriday https://t.co/r8z65N0EGC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#BellLetsTalk Put some colour and/or marks on a page every day. Keep on Paddling. https://t.co/oIHMONypjL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Press Should Skip the White House Briefings https://t.co/f5dgGDohjO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘We the People’ Demand Mr. Trump Release His Tax Returns https://t.co/XxsWT47q53]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did I really hear @oreillyfactor Bill Oreilly on Fox tonight say that $90million had been paid to make the @womensmarch happen?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton I do hope you will run for Mayor of New York!! You looked vibrant and determined yesterday. https://t.co/WvCf5duRbK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really think Friday is part seal. #bassetlife https://t.co/g19oUi6SpI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Horrible protectionist speech. Close those borders eh? So tired of #MAGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Erin_R05 love the profile photo; I don't know who is sick but sure hope it all gets better!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FLOTUS Happy Birthday Michelle Obama! Strong, steady and smart; funny and celebratory all at once. https://t.co/aGBt6pJqLA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sadie_basset Hope it's a good day for you today! https://t.co/M6GFTv59Md]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheMinimalists finally got to see the documentary on Netflix. Had to pause it, and there was scene of chair table and lamp. Beautiful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michikokakutani Thanks for the article in the NYT on President Obama re the books he reads to keep perspective. And for the best tweets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama’s Secret to Surviving the White House Years: Books https://t.co/vhbfOpx4Es]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yet another way to look at the world. So many perspectives. #bassetlife #dogfriday https://t.co/zkpS2vzIY3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alfonslopeztena and why did some of them applaud?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump, Trapped in His Lies, Keeps Lying. Sad! https://t.co/gJN7Pson2C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump #merylstreep was saying that you are a model for others, that what you do and say makes it ok for them to do the same]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton Hope you read the nyt this morning!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rumors of Hillary Clinton’s Comeback https://t.co/bPGKPSHF1m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DeweyBasset He looks like the sweetest dog, with such a wise face. Just amazing that he should have such a long life!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DeweyBasset Here's a hug from Friday in Vancouver. Special thoughts for Dewey. https://t.co/2UbDM942ff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My best ever apartment on Alexander St in Vancouver #shippingcontainer #housing. #Vancouver https://t.co/5fTB2jhGqT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cynthia headed out for her polar bear swim in Vancouver today. She did a real Arctic plunge last year! #NewYearsDay https://t.co/Jncoe9CONe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hample_ted That tweet last February made a big difference for me. Stranger to stranger, thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Erin_R05 All the best for the new year ahead. Not long for you until midnight!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@winstonbassett All the best for the year ahead. Since you've gone to bed early you will be really ready for tomorrow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MuskokaRosebud All the best for the brand new year that will bring lots of greets and treats.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sadie_basset All the best for the beautiful new year ahead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yessirree! Bring it on! Happy New Year from Friday in Vancouver #bassetlife https://t.co/TFuadxYyED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Muskoka411 hasn't happened yet has it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#dogfriday on Friday dreaming dreams for the new year #bassetlife https://t.co/5lNabhy0Yj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasue_two Happy New Year to you Susan; you are one of the few people I actually know who likes Twitter! I enjoy your posts as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friday resting in his tent after a busy day #bassetlife https://t.co/I8HER3ACJT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@millie_clooney only in my dreams, one of the good places. Love your friend Friday. https://t.co/yGhFR4iMlZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeAlisa Merry Christmas Joe from Vancouver, Canada. Love your thoughts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Erin_R05 All best wishes of the season. Thanks for being such a good friend. Love  Friday in Vancouver, Canada. https://t.co/20Oje5zJdd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MuskokaRosebud All best of days with lots of Christmas treats. Love Friday, of your harem. https://t.co/yVMmmJVjL6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LittleKingLouie I see Louis has his own place, posing nicely in front of historic buildings! Good boy. Love Friday https://t.co/KVyz0azNYd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RubyMonster Wishing you a peaceful Christmas; a lovely photo of Ruby on the profile; love from Friday in Vancouver https://t.co/QuQDAcFYH7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republicans Are in Denial on Health Care https://t.co/yjWFlqAfb7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sadie_basset Wishing you all a peaceful Christmas. Love from Friday in Vancouver, British Columbia, Canada. https://t.co/syEchByroV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MuskokaRosebud oh ho ho you've got snow! In Vancouver too. This could be a Muskoka tree...don't you see? https://t.co/iZiNC8TC81]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friday in front of the fire, stockings hung with care, a grand tree with lights, even a present! #Bassethound #xmas https://t.co/qslIkTVikq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Truth is a lost game in Turkey. Don’t let the same thing happen to you | Ece Temelkuran https://t.co/afBpFBI2Xg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tlupick Please take a break and look after yourself. #concerned #noticing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gusterbear that puppy does a lot of snuggling and sleeping, a model of smooth and peaceful. Friday is good too. https://t.co/30wR2I16nx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Perfect Weapon: How Russian Cyberpower Invaded the U.S. https://t.co/gYoSd4ombg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteveBarakatt Best of luck in Seoul. It will be magical. Hope to see you live some day. "Flying" made such a difference for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is very hard for a dog to hide a treasure in an apartment. Friday has been trying so hard. #bassetlife https://t.co/Dz3xYjbRHT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Is America Without Influence? Trump Will Find Out. https://t.co/MG2f4yxtAc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Erin_R05 such a beautiful photo of Tippy. I also can't believe more than a month has gone by since she left.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friday, my turn. I hear that you rarely went near this couch before I arrived and added some padding! #bassetlife https://t.co/UPt9Fc0EpA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice snowman in @Kitsilano today. https://t.co/18vTISXJuq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Muskoka411 #vancouver snowman. More snow tonight. Down to "a frigid minus 5". No kidding, it's cold here. https://t.co/TnSk8ZbzIE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PortVancouver How I loved living in my shipping container apartment looking out at  Gantry cranes in all weather. https://t.co/brB7wfrAWB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's where I'm sleeping Friday!! Time for you to move. Did you hear me?! You are not acknowledging. #bassetlife https://t.co/sL5WTaKDDe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rlhminnie Love your Christmas tableau.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder if Friday will get his wings? #bassetlife https://t.co/8Jnb32ddcO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Harvey looked extremely short beside you in the documentary. I felt sad for him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump What specifically are you referring to?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Why wouldn't he invest in Japan, his home country, using the same philosophy you are espousing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MuskokaRosebud yes, the one and only Honey Harbour, Georgian Bay, Cairngorm Island. Cabin is gone now but window remains.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking camp again, the window from the cabin I built on the island at Honey Harbour still alive in Kitsilano. https://t.co/BlgfwptiLv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sadie_basset Thinking of you. https://t.co/E3K1fqTFVh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Is Handing a Strong Economy to His Successor https://t.co/7JjbCXfwHL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have come to stay with my daughter and #dogfriday for awhile. Love her bright kitchen. https://t.co/KFLGhbKn8R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sadie_basset Sending good thoughts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump’s ‘Monster’s Ball’ https://t.co/hogmrs94AZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Obama Years - Los Angeles Review of Books: The Obama Years https://t.co/wz7eyv3B1y via @lareviewofbooks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sadie_basset "Pick one card out of the dizzying array and go for it." I did the laundry and lost only one sock.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sadie_basset small things we can do for each other; the basset connection is Twitter at its best https://t.co/Vvi9XlxtWf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sadie_basset so sorry for your troubles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Muskoka411 I'm here in Vancouver. Love the Muskoka news and photos. https://t.co/VxJcMrFobA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MuskokaRosebud Love your wall! And your Christmas accommodations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gusterbear Ah, the basset ability to nap so sweetly. With tucked in paws.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CharlesMBlow @nytimes terrific article by Charles Blow; necessary as most (gotta be where it's at) run to the other side of the ship.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, Trump, We Can’t Just Get Along https://t.co/7rRQ8xlUTb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama presenting Medals of Freedom to so many wonderful men and women including Cdns Frank Gehry and Lorne Michaels was a North Star moment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alfonslopeztena Thank you. A great post from the LA Times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sadie_basset Thanks so much for all your encouragement. Noticed and appreciated!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Friday! #dogfriday at work again for @gadventures. His acting classes were definitely worthwhile. #bassetlife https://t.co/UA9vwM7XRh]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>