<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lionfire STRAP YOURSELVES IN KIDS WE'RE GOING FOR A RIDE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eRonin but at the same time I'm really competitive so maybe I could do it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eRonin in all honesty I know I couldn't do it I don't even really like peanut butter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eRonin that'd be the plan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHO WANTS TO SEE ME, A DEAD SET LEGEND, EAT A JAR OF PEANUT BUTTER SOMETIME? https://t.co/98tdIETIJZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lisyk @Pierreth is that a challenge?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HaxJoel she's vocal goals. Her technique is on point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lisyk whole jar?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Punkasaurian only God can judge me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HaxJoel still into you by paramore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tpeter267 ahhhhhh the throwes of retail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@megsandbacon @peterwells @youwontknow no no it's directed at the fact that he obviously LIKE likes you. Ew human emotions. Esp love ones.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@el_jordinho I wanted a food name. Oatmeal &gt; oats &gt; boats &gt; boatmeal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Helalost I'm too tired to do the right thing atm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Helalost he has been very naughty today and we've kinda let him. We'll do better tomorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@filmgirl152 been there done that, no progress makes me feel like shit and if there's nothing forcing me onwards I'll just cut my losses]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just wanna smell boatmeal but he keeps biting my face come on man help me out here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VanillaLantern not up to date and very forgetful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SoftKittyWarm @noblemonkey aurora Borealis? At this time of year? In this part of the country? Localised entirely in your kitchen?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VanillaLantern yes but I can't remember what it's called 🙃🙃🙃🙃🙃]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SimplyPressMe all my shit dies cause I'm neglectful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IcyMindRacer nah you're good fam I just didn't want people to think that aye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bekarydin more like he's looking forward to working with me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eRonin I don't have a wiiu :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jayt0401 they say dogs do tricks but I'm the one that tricked him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomHarmathy no I find it hard to spend money on things like that even though I like them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pinkgirl4000 it's overrated]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IcyMindRacer wasn't drinking to drown sorrows. Catching up with a friend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rupertofly if it means something to you go for it. Make sure you get a good artist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SimplyPressMe I like hiking and gardening, though I don't garden much now. I used to do Muay Thai and wanna start again. Also cycling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomHarmathy that sounds sick definitely do that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@csimps0n yes pls I have a nice bike go bike ride with me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulverhoeven @bajopants thank you for loving my dog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jacksingleton15 I don't play heaps of those maybe ftl that's kinda like survival]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomHarmathy that sucks. Everyone has their own motivation and that's valid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MostStrange crying. I won't - we're gonna egg each other on until there's nothing left]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noblemonkey oath. Go ham.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomHarmathy that sucks. Netball is great. And has a totally different, important vibe to basketball.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulverhoeven @bajopants I think if I continue I'm borderline sexting on a public platform with a nonparticipant party included]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomHarmathy oh that's awesome. Pick that up again. Dancing is lit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sylvia_a_morris will look when I'm on a computer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dave_A_Beattie I feed off other people, so the performance aspect sends me into delirium where I no longer worry/care about anything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomHarmathy swimming can be good. Team sports are great for socialisation. I like basketball and netball.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrimFacade I have that now. Three beers no dinner just snacks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hausghost it's always changing but maybe this https://t.co/0ZdfttQzoq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SimplyPressMe gawd thanks for pointing that out 🙄 jk yeah was alright fam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomHarmathy what do you enjoy? Or want to get out of it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaveK_Says eh. It's only okay. Separate and together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rupertofly chewing on a chopstick https://t.co/0srV4ap0gt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More of you need to talk to me faster I'm not prepared to go deal with my life and actual needs yet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrimFacade I also feel like it's maybe a trip towards an uncomfortable belly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jayt0401 dog want stick. Human take stick. Human hold stick ransom and make demands. Profit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HuhConfused I didn't expect this to be actually really nice but it is I feel nice thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulverhoeven @bajopants do the do. That's a euphemism for sex.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@littlefaline never be creative just lie down and prepare for gentle death]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natemossamo RIP get off my internet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JLaG013 @HuhConfused never tells me off in dota just here to have fun what a legend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stacker_39 who wood like that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natemossamo you are a light in my life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just used a chopstick boatmeal wanted to chew to entice him into urinating. Ahhh dog mum life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rupertofly you and what army]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulverhoeven @bajopants mine or his?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tenzenmen no one wants me as their drummer. I'm not in the scene, can't find a band, have trouble connecting with people to get in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulverhoeven @bajopants just kidding I've gone home go let my dog eat my face]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulverhoeven @bajopants but I'm GOOD AT IT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VanillaLantern tabs are fun. Guitar is fun. Remember to have fun. Music should be fun. If not why not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VanillaLantern playing guitar is really fun. If you can play one song on chords chances are you can play like 50]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoodOldFinn thank good old finn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HuhConfused now compliment me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@solwat I will never be a good enough musician to do my songs justice anyway so whatever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jayt0401 then they murdered us RIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tenzenmen thanks. It felt very pathetic. And continues to. I don't have the strength to feel pathetic anymore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@solwat fair. It's hard. And easy to be discouraged]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@solwat not even a weekend warrior. Pathetic human with an album out who pretends they maybe mattered once]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoodOldFinn thanks. No I'm not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HitByATractor real as being hit by a tractor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@solwat but your twitter profile says you play guitar in a band]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol guys I say I play music but I don't really anymore because I was never going to succeed in it and I'm too driven to fail willingly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_muul opportunity to reveal things about oneself that you otherwise wouldn't. To dance. To sing. To feel locked into something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HuhConfused seriously nice &amp; chill dude with a cutie pie face who rocks at music. What more do you want?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phluid61 I don't think I should play music anymore really]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colinnixon idc didn't cost me anything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colinnixon no idea there were no t&amp;c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_muul I still follow Ellie. I wanted to be a musician for a long time. They were kinda role models. And paramore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dave_A_Beattie both have value. Fps for pc tps for console]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colinnixon prefer fresh but mostly cause there's less people and sand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@orrinxu pengest munch fam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomHarmathy enjoy yourself. You get to learn such a variety of things, take advantage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_muul pop musicians that I loved in formative years. Avril lavigne, the veronicas, Ellie goulding]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Helalost oath]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomHarmathy top notch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bentatoes I'm reading through the lotr series atm. Almost done]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colinnixon mmm somewhere with water to swim and few people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesQumsieh thank!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SimplyPressMe I still have a job this year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheTynManFromOz HBD! Sing up a storm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dave_A_Beattie what's tps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tpeter267 he can be a bit lazy hey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@42agentcrm cya there cuz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pinkgirl4000 I don't think I have one specifically]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>