<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["Mr. Trump understands that attacking the media is the reddest of meat for his base" 
https://t.co/Up8HRydNtl
Expect more of same.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High standards indeed. Thank you Malcolm. Wishing you all the best in  what's next for you. https://t.co/HaSapzvpId]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inevitable media mistakes corrected in good faith are absolutely NOT #fakenews. We need to keep making this clear. https://t.co/T5hwrLJTnQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What’s public interest in future of Canadian media? We need this conversation about The Shattered Mirror.https://t.co/JfwO98XyHc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@njaved The world feels even heavier today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Washington Post chief @PostBaron: “We will expose falsehoods coming out of the White House” https://t.co/Et2vz1O9Yh via @el_pais]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What’s the public interest in the future of Canadian media? We need to have this public debate. https://t.co/JfwO98XyHc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kellymcb @Sulliview Yes, and today we have all finally admitted it. Loving all the fine tributes from great female journalists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fostersarah Thanks Sarah. The magic of @rlautens (and a good hair day).
Hope you are well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anndouglas Yep. I have struggled. Family, friends and colleagues have struggled. That's okay. That's real. Truth matters. 
#BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robedits Wishing you all the best in your something new.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CapitolClio @Sulliview Me too. It is delightful and captures perfectly my thoughts and feelings about Mary Tyler Moore show. Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeatherMallick @CBCOmbudsman We all need that spunk now more than ever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@judithtimson 
Yes, when i was falling in love with the news biz. Part of why i loved her and her show so much i think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBCOmbudsman Me too. Somewhere on my bookshelf I have book that provides a synopsis of every single episode of the Mary Tyler Moore Show.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mary Tyler Moore made being a single career woman an attractive option for me and other confused teen girls in 70s. https://t.co/LFS9Arpyrd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thekeenanwire Thanks for posting this!. RIP to one of my favourites.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Journalists are vulnerable to the whims of society and government officials" The limits of First Amendment. https://t.co/cPgJO5bqS2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ladurantaye Can I triple fave this one?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A call for global collaborative journalism to investigate Donald Trump - from journalists who broke Panama Papers.  https://t.co/itVn37JLtz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does a news organization optimized for trust look like? https://t.co/Uz53WwKcin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasmeetSidhu @TorontoStar @dmrider @the_scolby This is great. We should copy it for all new interns.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@egreenspon @politico Yes, in Trump America media must be more responsible, ethical than ever to win credibility battle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can Dads Parent While Mom Is Marching? Do You Really Have to Ask? https://t.co/D5QTShNWfI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glad to see NYT admit this story was misguided. https://t.co/FfgxOFpITu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Important work. https://t.co/QgNC6QM8bz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ddale8 "alternative facts" 
Wow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yavuzbaydar4 @ddale8 @jayrosen_nyu Frightening as you well know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@linwood_barclay Did not know whether to laugh or cry at your characterization of the man as an obnoxious gasbag.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Must read by @linwood_barclay https://t.co/VLwOCtviZg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@imediaethics @jdvorkin I don't know but would like to find out too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sydneysmithnyc @TheVarsity @The_Cornell_Sun Thanks much for this information.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CANmediacouncil @TheVarsity And perhaps consider joining media council too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C’mon: You @bruce_arthur are a real journalist and it is always great to see your work on Page 1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jdvorkin It was a great suggestion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can engineering principles be applied to writing? https://t.co/tEhleJBUg6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alex_mckeen It is a big step for any news organization to appoint a public editor. I wish you all the best with this. #TheVarsity #UofT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Varsity editor-in-chief @alex_mckeen on why U. of T.'s The Varsity appointed public editor https://t.co/TcDtaCE7OO 
Congrats to all here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bravo to U. of T. The Varsity for appointing public editor - is this a first for campus media? https://t.co/sABLaj2pSC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A hellscape of lies and distorted reality awaits journalists covering President Trump https://t.co/cI2ZKwqydy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jdvorkin @Sulliview, Yes, big congrats Margaret.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Newsroom recognition for relentless @ddale8 so well deserved.Congratulations Daniel. Keep on with your truth-seekin… https://t.co/mW1fVSItZs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump only looks like a master media manipulator because he’s allowed to | @MarinaHyde https://t.co/RxlohdRU9N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, @Ombudsman, Glad you made this important point https://t.co/3K5VFfIJHE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report outlines challenges and recommendations for ethical journalism in 2017 and beyond  https://t.co/zZCKIobzLB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How BuzzFeed crossed the line in publishing salacious ‘dossier’ on Trump https://t.co/JeKL6WmtgE
@Sulliview nails this one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why publishing the Trump dossier set a risky precedent: https://t.co/2tgUOz32jN
Smart, thoughtful piece]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fkelly25 @njaved @TorontoStar Oh my, I covered his first mayoral win back when I ran "one-man" Milton bureau for The Spec.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About that vulgar word printed in the Toronto Star this week. Readers shocked, surprised amused. https://t.co/r2M7yoyoPi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Foundations and the foundation of a new way of funding journalism https://t.co/2ZxwxftlCH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kathyenglish Likely safe to say we have Toronto Star Typo of the Year for 2017.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unfortunate production mistake certainly hits a chord with Star readers. All involved regret this error. https://t.co/Qxl9y7Q11B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laforet @TorontoStar Oh, no! Thanks for pointing this out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lessons From the Media’s Failures in Its Year With Trump https://t.co/0kY8CscFZQ
By @NickKristof]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That time I got confused about the capital of New Brunswick. The year in corrections was no laughing matter: https://t.co/7LMA2jnTN8 via]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nspector4 @globeandmail @statnews Answer to that more complex than this platform allows. I don't say there is no media bias though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fake news invades science and science journalism as well as politics https://t.co/KaZc8jiXoB via @statnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@judithtimson @TorontoStar @jayrosen_nyu Yes, excellent analysis, as always. Much to think about.Looking forward to his part 2.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@judithtimson @TorontoStar Mazel tov to you @judithtimson Your commitments for 2017 make good sense to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You be the Editor: Would you publish these words and images? https://t.co/r0OGsYBVWH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Correction: Previous tweet about power of journalism should have been attributed to @niemanfdn not @NiemanReports.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The power of media is the power of reflecting human experience." @NiemanReports  https://t.co/uLgPOpmKnv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nspector4  I always look at your concerns- could not determine answer to that ? and then lost track of it. Will try again. @murdochdavis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My annual quiz for Star readers: You be the Editor: Would you publish these words and images? https://t.co/r0OGsYBVWH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lessons From 2016 for the News Media, as the Ground Shifts https://t.co/q3xWerObqB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poynter's  best of media corrections, 2016 edition. https://t.co/hZNwHo4YDT
No Toronto Star corrections on this year's naughty list.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JQStar @SmithRaps That last song choice- superb. Thanks for making my day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaneEliz @AmPress This is terrific information about great reporters who do great reporting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thekeenanwire Great example of accountability and transparency by a journalist of integrity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jdvorkin @andrewphil @TorontoStar That was Toronto Star view from the outset.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RosalindR @TorontoStar UGH! Can't imagine why anyone would think that was an appropriate ad to be served up on Toronto Star.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9 Important Rulings, Guidance &amp; News from Press Councils &amp; Press Organizations in 2016 - iMediaEthics https://t.co/YEsMWOkzhE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovely piece that matters to all of us who've been saved by great copy editors who sweat the small (and other) stuf… https://t.co/eZRiYwAXqK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConversationUK @libertarianspir Some solid ideas for vigorous media self regulation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nspector4 @milnews_ca @Mark3Ds @TheLocalFrance Not able to look right now - what is error?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Poynter @craignewmark Wow! Spectacular news for journalism ethics and never more necessary for future of journalism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lizrenzetti @globemediagroup @theglobeandmail Great piece. I always loved walking into that building and riding escalator]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theo Moudakis: Trump and Time https://t.co/CtD2Hbvwog via @torontostar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not fake news. https://t.co/OHI30BcxmA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@saila: Of course! “Post-truth” is  disinformation for the social media age https://t.co/NNdxkTk5vu /thx @h0d3r”
Smart, smart piece]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unbelievable news? Read it again and you might think it's true https://t.co/JzZn2RR3Xd
A psychologist's take on fake news.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCAcademy Much good guidance here about journalists' difficult task of talking to bereaved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wendygillis What a fiasco. Beyond even the usual disregard of open court principle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who else has the exam dream? @UA_magazine archives: Exams that haunt us still. https://t.co/Up64c0NLlj https://t.co/A6IYA1FaLu”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Perkel @smeurice @CdnPress Malcolm McNeil always so helpful when we bring reader concerns about @CdnPress content in @TorontoStar. Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NYT public editor @spaydl: When the Language of Politics Becomes a Minefield https://t.co/PnH4yfY0Hb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Must add for my Christmas book list. https://t.co/Ef07Wp6fs9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurenPelley @EdTubb Thanks. Ed's leadership on this issue was commendable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Alt-right’? No, call it racism.The Star and the so-called alt-right https://t.co/spnxvCyJhl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robertbenzie @JustinTrudeau @TorontoStar After 75 minutes listening to our PM never happier to be a Canadian.#progressive #proud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mathewi @FortuneMagazine @CraigSilverman @BuzzFeedBen Congratulations Craig! Well deserved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really? Facts no longer exist? That cannot be fact. https://t.co/vuB7cpQ6Ch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jembradshaw You did a great job reporting on media biz- one of my most reads. Media's loss is banking's gain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DiversityMusing @TorontoStar @CityNews Yes. Writing about it this week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can journalists have "sense of humility about their work, even as they burn with purpose?'@sulliview inspires again. https://t.co/3cTRJCPO3g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why commenters comment: "To correct an error" cited as top reason. https://t.co/GTs4Lf4fcW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rachel_Pulfer Thanks for all the important great work you do with #JHR.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#gilmoregirlsayearinthelife #GilmoreGirlsRevival Gotta love @Carole_King showing up in #StarsHollow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening for truth and reconciliation: The first  step toward improved media coverage of Indigenous people. https://t.co/KiuHt8J3oJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to become a better writer? Follow these 7 steps, and look for new tools every day https://t.co/Xi2e1zK7BY]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>