<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished watching #VictoriaPBS..  another great epi!  Loved the wedding!   Can't wait for next week! (Glad Lord Melbourne is gone!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darlingcarlile You're not the only one.. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I were her, I'd ask to be put in a medically induced coma for the next four years. https://t.co/qcg8TrZw20]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChicagoSWE I hope we see him again at some point.. :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@literallydawsey I know getting married is allowed, LOL  but I was just wondering if it affected any name change... :)   guess not then?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could she though?  Even with them being at the same house?  Or does it not make a difference cus she's on Ambo, and… https://t.co/ej0TEnFXQc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Because the florescent green colour wasn't disgusting enough, let's add some brown to it'🤢 https://t.co/ahnD71X2E6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yup,  still miss Louie. #ChicagoFire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DawseyAlways @monicxraymund  Where's this from?  who said this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaniaCae1 @katriendanvers @ChicagoSWE @xoxoCF_MonR  THANKS!  :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LizRaftery_TVG uugh..  ok thanks anyways!  :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm gonna need for someone to put that new clip up on YT for me please if they can!? Ok thanks!  😃]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarrabr_4 no I mean the Puffin app doesn't load on my phone at all when I've tried it other times..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarrabr_4 It doesn't load on my phone properly..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't view the new CF sneak peak!!  😭]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LizRaftery_TVG any chance there's an unblocked version of this I can view from Canada?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you wanted me to TUNE IN to your show she is not the way to do it. If you intended for me to TURN OFF the TV, th… https://t.co/6TTMeqHR3z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're too busy freaking out about the RL craziness going on in the U.S. 😧 https://t.co/Okcy1AecR1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really think this show should be required viewing for HS students in history class..  #XCompany]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poor Alfred must be so tortured with all these  heartbreaking stories in his head now...#XCompany]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['If we fight, then there's hope for everybody.' -Harry  Jesus this is so relevant to what's going on in the world today.  #XCompany]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only if we get an #Alfora spin off as well!! #XCompany https://t.co/3KyHbnOCJp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hughes_nl YES! Completely agree!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Canadian_Gal_eh I didn't spill any details!   Just giving a polite 'heads up' for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok I just saw an early broadcast of #XCompany..   I'M NEVER TAKING A TRAIN AGAIN!!   The last 10 minutes tho!! :( 😨]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm really starting to hate trains.  #XCompany]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even though it's only been a week, any chance we can get the #PresidentTrump show cancelled? Cus it's weird and scary, and I don't like it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tv_eh Yup,  but it'll be a stellar episode that's for sure.. (and I already have my thoughts on who it may be)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aw crap, who dies? https://t.co/qLhTjS30WF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AKA: 19 Movies that won't be screened at the White House. https://t.co/gPxaBumen9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't Beyoncé announce her pregnancy with an ultrasound photo like other celebs?   No, she has to have a set designed and props.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty sure the latest episode of #VictoriaPBS had the most obscene moments I've ever witnessed on Public Television.😉]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kwanfan1212 @michaelwbrandt  I can't use either of those in Canada sadly..:(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sharkygirl74 2/2 but then I saw the last 2 pics of her and Stella, and now I'm wondering...?🤔]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/2 Ok so I read that Fire PR, and the first thing I thought about Brett was that her 'personal changes' meant that she got a tattoo? con't]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only thing I can hope is that the ratings for it are in the 🚽 https://t.co/I79TwH8q0Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If she didn't marry him after this..  I would have. 😘 https://t.co/bQTwsuE6Py]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I drive by this place at least every other day...  😨 https://t.co/hHXmVcyRSk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anti-LGBT Trump Executive Order Leaked To Media – Prepare To Be Outraged https://t.co/CaUyDuymIg via @Bipartisan Report]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WTH?  If you think a 5-YEAR OLD poses a threat to your life, you're seriously fucked in the head. https://t.co/kgd7duDIZE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh my god I LOVED THAT SHOW!  💣👧 https://t.co/DD6sIr7qLJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And this is only Week One people..  😕 https://t.co/qi7pi9J8Cp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#1 Aurora Luft  - #XCompany   #2  Gabby Dawson - #ChicagoFire  .. I may think of some more later.. but def those tw… https://t.co/VZB0imgsE1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought he wanted to 'tear it up' and/or 'renegotiate' NATO? https://t.co/Xh8B6mrfJm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[40 Canadian Towns You Haven't Heard of But Should Visit ASAP https://t.co/5HzSeTvJ3H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoops.. https://t.co/fUBhAS9p4C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bmaggiemay He said this today?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bmaggiemay When did he say this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lets face it, noone's surprised by this at all.. https://t.co/gJs0nX5ojF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So of course Trump will take this to mean that he's the best President ever in the history of the United States... https://t.co/cwgqSyfMq6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahem... back then Gabby Dawson.. now Gabby Casey.. 😉 https://t.co/PBr1RmlNs5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAG awards are Sunday &amp; I wonder if the President will have a Twitter rant since he wasn't nominated for his performance in the Election?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching @XCompany always makes me miss my Opa. :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I suppose it's too late to ask for a two hour series finale episode to wrap things up?  @XCompany]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crap that preview... Aurora and Faber on a train again.. this is gonna suck isn't it? #XCompany]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why say it's a mistake?!  IT'S NOT A MISTAKE! YOU'RE PROTECTING HIM!! #XCompany]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#XCompany aw crap she's going back on a train?  That can't be good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SHIT!  #XCompany]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Canadian_Gal_eh @MarkEllis_TV and Tom.. and Rene.. 😭]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YO @CBC! Any chance we can beg you for a 2 hour movie to wrap things up properly?We aren't even close to the end of the war yet! #XCompany]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the HELL are you up to Faber? #XCompany]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yea, he was well.. right before he tried to blow up my Camp and Krystina shot him..#XCompany]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everytime someone writes a damn letter on this show they get interrupted and it never gets finished! #XCompany  #Tom 😢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christ, this episode is intense! #XCompany]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why the hell weren't they worried 6 months ago?  He was addicted to the media/TV then too.. https://t.co/4zHHGFQGyO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tivasdavid pretty sure about a month has passed in between last nite's show and the week before..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DawseyAlways @Nikita_Citizen Why is it preempted next week, do we know?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously tho..  can someone check in on Betty White please?   They were good friends.. #MaryTylerMoore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jillybobww And a puppy for everyone inside..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, Stella's got that psycho ex,  and Anna's probably gonna die so...  Tough choice..😕 https://t.co/JnSOrWIvnu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChicagoFireSWE yeah i know...  Why you smiling? 😒]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do I have a feeling we'll be hearing the media say that a lot? https://t.co/gqqBzLB0XE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile, in Canada.. https://t.co/OEbZVFBYhq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear America, Whatever the steps are to impeach a sitting U.S. President, Please, for the love of god, get started on them. Now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a deal they have with @NBCThisisUs  #TuesdaysTears https://t.co/g8JrQJSgsD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHAT? https://t.co/HcDdSxg0Vi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the FUCK is going on here?  'We can disagree with the facts?'  WHAT? https://t.co/uRN2JjUHBE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CrazyforSVUPD @TaniaCae1 they aren't splitting them up again...  that's why it took them so long to get them married to start with.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AAFEgleek I haven't heard anything yet, but if I remember from last yr, they didn't get renewed until close to the end of the season..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear USA, Remember in 1933 when we elected a megalomaniac &amp; the  rest of the world freaked out? FYI it didn't end well. Sincerely, Germany]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChicagoSWE @Gaellicious @Nikita_Citizen &amp; the Twins were asked twitter if they are off CF for good, and the reply was to 'keep watching']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChicagoSWE @Gaellicious @Nikita_Citizen Someone asked Derek in the Jan 18 Q&amp;A if we'll see Louie again and he said yes..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NW #VictoriaPBS... Please tell me Prince Albert shows up tonight?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yup, now more confused then ever about Louie. 😒]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nikita_Citizen @CurlyBuckeye @Gaellicious @ChicagoSWE so that means they'll be back then? Or not?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CurlyBuckeye @Gaellicious @Nikita_Citizen @ChicagoSWE maybe something happens in the fam that changes? Someone gets sick or a job loss?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CurlyBuckeye @Gaellicious @Nikita_Citizen @ChicagoSWE well didn't the dad say they had a lot of family to help w/Louie?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CurlyBuckeye @Gaellicious @Nikita_Citizen @ChicagoSWE yes exactly!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChicagoCFPD I think it's either this week or next week.. it's soon tho..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CurlyBuckeye @Gaellicious @Nikita_Citizen @ChicagoSWE yes this is the one I remember..I took this to mean they'd be back?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gaellicious @Nikita_Citizen @ChicagoSWE what did she say specifically?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nikita_Citizen @ChicagoSWE so why would they and Derek say that then if it wasn't true?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChicagoSWE @Nikita_Citizen besides I can't forget that one tweets from the twins account  saying we'd see the twins again..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChicagoSWE @Nikita_Citizen doubt he's going to give away that much info for the rest of the season.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChicagoSWE @hai02lin exactly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChicagoSWE @hai02lin they aren't getting divorced.. given how long it's taken them to get married. Writers have said this was going to last]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CrazyforSVUPD me too.. I love her as a EMT..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hai02lin I don't think she can be a ff again if she's married to Matt.. she'd have to leave 51.. and the show is set at 51.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No words, no words at all. https://t.co/I0AGkb2OaW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only in office 24 hrs &amp; Secret Service has to knock down a lie told by new W.H. Press Secretary.The next 4 yrs are… https://t.co/m4tynVZ29j]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>