<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@sovereignpath In the interests of diplomacy it would be very unwise to stand up to fascists. But being snivelling cowards suits many people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pmbillenglish please condemn Trump, this is the point where you get to chose which side of history are on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TroyHammo pls tell me these stories one day. My friend had someone in a meeting say "we don't need algorithms, we have machine learning!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomasbeagle ouch, overspray got me too. I hope you're okay!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off to Kiwiburn to hang out with insanely creative weirdos. Cya!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevin_zakka @Reza_Zadeh sum of activation flow across a batch? No idea how one could utilise it though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keunwoochoi @alexjc I work with vfx ppl, they tell me that vfx easily spend several days rendering a final frame, but have massive farms.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A subclause of the Paradox of Tolerance also specifically recommends punching Nazis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ebolajulius2 that's why it's great that Trump is putting Goldman Sachs in charge?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still think that drunk user testing is the best thing ever. If I swear at your app while trying to do basic shit then you lose.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OH: "why not panda balls?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["the Trump administration was considering cutting advanced scientific computing research to 2008 levels" lol 'murica https://t.co/rO3mcwtNKt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Must suck to be first author on a paper with famous people, everyone says the paper is theirs and ignores your existence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesmacfie sweet need to resurrect my personal site and start writing about art projects again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesmacfie @Netlify will it render Jekyll or other static site generators from a git repo?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kyhwana indeed. And even though it's pleasant as far as such things go, I need solitude to fully engage &amp; concentrate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Managed to solve a stupid algebra problem while working at home that I struggled to solve in an office environment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dennybritz In addition, lets not get started about the number of detached Caffe forks people have created.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomasbeagle You prob wouldn't, but don't spray pledge on your wooden floor. (voice of exp before almost sliding through a glass door!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keunwoochoi cool thanks! I've mainly worked with computer vision but keen to learn more about audio processing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keunwoochoi Looks really cool though! :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keunwoochoi Excuse my ignorance on implementing Keras layers, but what is the trainable component in the trainable=True version?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NikeNewZealand I don't want my shoes to kill people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dancres yeah that kind of operational testing is great, so long as actual customers have low probability of being affected.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fchollet many open data sources for weather, predicting daily weather temperatures would be interesting non-finance domain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dancres I've seen people use prod as the dev and test environment. never again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesmacfie @mikeforbes I also see them when I'm not logged in and follow a URL to a specific protected resource.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@inconvergent fwiw, I write most of my code in vim, but import/reload functions into my notebook. So I use it more as a graphical terminal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@inconvergent Tried to find a particular example on github, but I'm on my phone and GH doesn't seem render notebooks on mobile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@inconvergent but it's more about the story of how someone got to a solution, that can include failures. By context I meant the human ctxt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@inconvergent I think if you had an editor which showed images or graphs from raw data that'd help. I hear xcode can do markdown images...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@inconvergent yeah, I'm not unfamiliar with comments... but it's clear we have different use cases.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@inconvergent For kaggle competition entries I much prefer to read a notebook than context-less code or non specific blog posts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@inconvergent @DanCouper I love vim, but when I'm doing research, exploring an imgproc API, prototyping a CV alg: visual feedback is great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@inconvergent @DanCouper it's actually great for research where you have to explore and visualise data. It's a record of work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@inconvergent a row of bots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I spent a lot of time on aliexpress this weekend, yet I only spent $20.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ferrouswheel or parabolic, abs, and others with a peak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any know a good recent overview of using periodic activation functions (e.g. Sin) in deep learning?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phil Chou on how compression is once again important with a new problem to solve in volumetric video https://t.co/uvSwNi4JeT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jcrichman @savagejen @tholmz @Debonair_David by using "8 month abortion" you signal yourself as someone who has no fucking clue about this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AuntieImperial @adamjohnsonNYC @yoshiefuruhashi only in the US. Not in civilised countries where blood donations are actually donations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Steam_Support It's on my wish list because I want to know when it changes from "Coming Soon" to a thing I can buy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Steam_Support Hi, can you please stop notifying me about when Steam Link is on sale since I can't actually buy it in New Zealand?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@goodfellow_ian I'd be curious how many conferences ppl go to per year. I live in NZ, so I tend to do only one (usually in US) a year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GristC @GossiTheDog I went, but DNS was broken already.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SiDawson I had already tweaked my settings as much as possible to minimise the unrelated tweets. Seems to have stopped happening now tho!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulg I have an entire folder of posts I don't publish :-( But I guess that's what they call journalling &amp; it still helps clarify thought.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@quasimondo while it was a different application, I used weighted average to window center pixels to get nicer gradients]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rickasaurus @nuttycom I'd never heard of the guy until now. like Trump controversies it gets him recognition even if it's bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ratkins I bought one of each, but still have to make full use of their capability! (made a signal generator with one)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ratkins have you played with 3.5 or 3.6?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Postfix description in tqdm just merged! Makes it great for training ML models &amp; was a feature request I made https://t.co/lPBhxCKsD2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpireSec yeah, tho ddos are just among the most visible actions one can take with a Botnet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump release your birth certificate!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RelearnML why does it give a different answer? that makes no sense. :-\]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So works when static, the symbols exist, the dynamic library comes after the static libs on the linker cmd line, but no dice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to convert one library to be dynamic but it's symbols, depended on by the static libs, are no longer resolved when I do so]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm struggling to get symbols resolved while linking an executable that involves a combo of static libraries, object files and dynamic libs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone have a good resource on deep diving into gcc linker behaviour on Linux?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rich0H this is what I imagine you doing km up in the sky https://t.co/6cyx80EdeP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't understand my twitter feed anymore. Random accounts I don't follow showing up in it (not promoted, no interaction by ppl I follow)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samim I use evernote for bookmarking and capturing content. Full search and automatic context creation between notes helps keep them alive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidPylyp tho @Matterport is much more than 360 video, creates a model you can explore!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamRackis @ag_dubs fwiw, I'm finding it neat for computer vision and machine learning algorithms. More fun than C++.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pinboard Also the plot was kind of haphazard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pinboard I realised this when I was 10 and wasn't making as much progress on the complete Encyclopedia Britannica as I wanted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fjoppe @rickasaurus from experimental perspective, changing params in complex systems &amp; observing result is one approach to understanding]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fjoppe @rickasaurus as a former scientist (both compsci and bio), I find equal use in debugging and reasoning about code.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rickasaurus @pigworker haha, I was being entirely facitious and am sympathetic with OP. Something something halting problem. ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pigworker @rickasaurus I am very angry at interpreters that run my code to find out what it does.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dysinger I'm more concerned about Perl being a runner up. Why won't it die??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cuervo3 @maxseddon where "world peace" equals letting Putin invade whoever he wants.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OH: "@realDonaldTrump is the sort of guy you'd be embarrassed to invite to a BBQ because he's such a knob."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Submitted my first rust/cargo issue https://t.co/3jp1Rsb85s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back hacking on linux and 1 minute in and I'm already fighting against stupid defaults for samba access causing mp3 playback to rebuffer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WLTaskForce Congratulations you have turned into the security apparatus you once fought against.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevesi thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevesi are there examples of malicious agents attacking the supply chain? Sounds like you've investigated tho, any book you recc?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevesi harder to attribute liability when it's a heterogeneous group of a million insecure IoT devices.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevesi cars risk death, businesses have liability there, nobody cares about the IoT botnets responsible for ddos.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevesi admittedly that was a couple of years ago, maybe it's impossible to get a dumb TV now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevesi last time I tried to buy a TV there were only SmartTVs at my price point. $2k more and I could get a kick ass TV without gimmicks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevesi meanwhile, consumers will pay a premium for the disconnected secure version. Not data monitoring so includea the "privacy" feature]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevesi all other computer security problems become trivial.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevesi I look forward to them solving the computer security problem, because if they can solve it for discontinued IoT products...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rickasaurus what would you have to sacrifice? (apart from a little bit of speed)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just reported Trump's nuclear arms tweet to twitter as a threat of violence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edersantana The reverse of 2) because I can read the abstract in the pdf. I almost never want only the arxiv page.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The identity of "Master" is revealed https://t.co/GJ5zWsDHtr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoanieLemercier There is no such thing as an original idea. Stop focussing on what others do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samim I feel certain things are much easier to teach with the context of a couple years of life experience outside school.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samim I think a lot of the answers on your original post assume school kids to be a lot more mature than they are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dan_ps @find_evil @jaspergregory in the cyberpunk dystopia you have to pay extra for disconnected appliances that are secure with privacy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zargony that's @plinz :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tired of fighting against people justifying untested and terrible software. Don't normalise it, otherwise entropic decay and complexity wins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@living_syn @FiloSottile Yeah, I was excited, but as an alpha it seems pretty limited right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[105(!) year old cyclist sets hour-ride record for age class: https://t.co/F8Jhnr3rSL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samim If they'd linked calculus to neural networks and optimization I would have paid a lot more attention!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heytrav haha, that'll be it. Too clever but in the uncanny valley of clever.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>