<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Will IMF’s response to UN report on women’s economic empowerment change its policies? https://t.co/LNmpSzUOuQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Young Girls Don’t Think They Are Smart Enough https://t.co/C5bGujvBha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The blueprint calls for eliminating...Violence Against Women Grants" https://t.co/UI2T6lvqYl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the US distributes $1.3 billion in aid for women around the world https://t.co/6GPU8fsKBk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women Are Not All Born Equal—And It Matters https://t.co/yNlpQbp6UR via @cgdev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“The Tipping Point: Can the World End Female Genital Mutilation/Cutting?” by @AmbCathyRussell https://t.co/vNkdOuSaV5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Currently reading https://t.co/00CAgTWx66]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Joyce Banda Talks About Sensitizing African Leaders to Maternal Health Challenges - https://t.co/eIAOrkYsC6 via @NewSecurityBeat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ivanka Trump turns to Goldman Sachs partner for advice https://t.co/SyhP8KZFqb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feed the Future: 2016 Year in Review https://t.co/bt38KQhUX6 via @StateDept]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Charities alarmed as aid spending shifts from poor countries to refugees. https://t.co/aeOplN6nuB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9 Things People Get Wrong About Planned Parenthood https://t.co/BCTxT4vcsU via @thecut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attitudes Toward Female Genital Mutilation Changing in Ethiopia https://t.co/k15ZDXAU1l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Lessons from the Obama Administration: Why Gender Equality Should Continue to Be Part of U.S.” by @AmbCathyRussell https://t.co/uB68t2dqsf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's 2017, the TIME to Empower World's Girls https://t.co/KGpEGoCRGi via @HuffPostImpact]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The invisible workload that drags women down https://t.co/NIYFhrtUNq via @MONEY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women’s Rights Are a National Security Issue https://t.co/ggXdqDkueg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global Family Planning Funding—What Should Funders Be Thinking About Now? https://t.co/bPsP9ss7sP via @cgdev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next UN chief names three women to senior posts https://t.co/nz8oqvGNOO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cellphones have lifted hundreds of thousands of Kenyans out of poverty https://t.co/Dphk7D5Ob8 via @voxdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worried about how we continue to make progress for global gender equality? New idea from @charlesjkenny https://t.co/muG5YzgCeb via @cgdev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Agenda for Harmful Cultural Practices and Girls' Empowerment https://t.co/H7ig4Ys0lc via @cgdev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Malawi’s first female president writes on how to raise girls’ aspirations in Africa https://t.co/c40zrnKTcz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 things the Trump team needs to know about foreign aid https://t.co/vnqwJCaAtL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Currently reading https://t.co/AX2CMIFnf0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unlocking Opportunities for Women with Smart Design https://t.co/swaj0QhlyP via @cgdev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The global AIDS response is "Stuck in Neutral" https://t.co/s6MkieyOEd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. Efforts To Support Women's Economic Empowerment in APEC https://t.co/Ks9dbqDkpb (from @StateDept)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BSR: Advancing Women’s Economic Empowerment through the Financial Services Sector https://t.co/erXard9jzt @bsrnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Global South Takes the Lead on “Gender Sensitive” Trade Policy https://t.co/3xnW6qOjun via @cgdev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Reasons Everyone Should Celebrate Women's Entrepreneurship Day https://t.co/KnYFDmulbe via @HuffPostWomen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When it comes to gender-equality aid, the US lags behind its peers https://t.co/Al5MLtUJrf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Revisiting What Works: Women, Economic Empowerment and Smart Design https://t.co/rJpqCK6bwc via @cgdev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Smart Investment: $1 Billion for Promoting Women’s and Girls’ Economic Empowerment https://t.co/98LOppo3JC via @cgdev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can we make the world's cities safer for women and girls? https://t.co/OBUOuLJRbr via @ConversationUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the US distributes $1.3 billion in aid for women around the world https://t.co/FDpE9yOyMp #womenslives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Economics has a serious gender problem – it needs more women https://t.co/QaGkIow0Jg via @ConversationUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UN News - UN statistics forum addresses efforts to support Global Goal on gender equality https://t.co/pfoMJ30L1g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Tackle FGM and Early Marriage—and Still Respect Culture: President Joyce Banda and Kakenya Ntaiya https://t.co/SdFn0dnmWh via @cgdev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attn: Presidential Transition Teams – 3 Big Ideas and 3 Smart Reforms for US Development Policy https://t.co/GAEXwCiXFj via @cgdev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girl Summit DC: Keeping Promises through Policy Research https://t.co/eKRkS5J502 via @cgdev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Measuring the Quality of Girls' Education Across the Developing World https://t.co/1Z5szFZwrh via @cgdev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opportunities for Pro-Poor Growth in South Asia https://t.co/D7DKGnBADy via @cgdev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unleashing the Power of Women and Clean Cooking https://t.co/ByI9WEACJw via @HuffPostGreen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UN Women launches flagship programme initiative, Making Every Woman and Girl Count https://t.co/p2GJ4p16Ek via @UN_Women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To Boost Growth: Employ More Women https://t.co/MejCmyZIyY via @wordpressdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FAO and India SEWA join efforts to empower rural women and youth https://t.co/BmU7XbNTrU via @BigNewsNetwork]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many countries allow child marriage https://t.co/yLnmjqzjF2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Melinda Gates on sexism, contraceptives and global development https://t.co/JbqE8lSMnW via @macleansmag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Promoting Women’s Economic Empowerment: What the Next US Administration Should Do https://t.co/m1rfIT8HWo via @cgdev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Egypt's parliament is to vote on tougher penalties for FGM https://t.co/d8uwC3jxOC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gender equity (girls' education, contraception access, economic empowerment) are needed to change this: 

https://t.co/SVOY4e2nn9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can helping women achieve financial freedom help the environment, too?: https://t.co/ANUIWAXHRn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Brazil's government rolling back women's rights? @AJEnglish  https://t.co/BIbOW5EEhF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sierra Leone urged to ban FGM after death of teenage girl. https://t.co/K4BihmfpTn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UN High-Level Panel on Women’s Economic Empowerment meets in South Africa https://t.co/8i9OnX3sbE via @sharethis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding data points to shed light on girls left behind https://t.co/WIrH0tk524]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Are Gender Barriers Made Of? https://t.co/xoZcbrvvKE via @freakonomics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Currently reading https://t.co/ToYz9tnDor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Burkina Faso, an anti-FGM/C law may have prevented over 200,00 girls from being cut. https://t.co/waRuKB82UN via @cgdev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Government of India and World Bank Sign Agreement to Diversify and Enhance Household Income in Bihar via @WorldBank]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Majority of men and women oppose FGM in countries where practice persists – UNICEF figures  https://t.co/HW1hktzbbR via @unicef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lagarde @CGDev Christine Lagarde: Girls' education/gender equality = high priority areas to ensure economic growth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cambodia's garment workers vulnerable to unsafe abortions https://t.co/E6AGxoKQEP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tanzania launches crackdown on child marriage with 30-year jail terms https://t.co/kD2yaRKrzq via @Reuters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Empowerment' is warping women's view of real power https://t.co/HbfeIuPGFa via @TIMEIdeas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gender budget's real impact unclear
 https://t.co/jVE4z0N1jI via @dailystarnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Legal restrictions on women's access to ID limits economic empowerment. Women without ID have more difficulty getting a loan. #genderdata]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CGDev @Data2X Romesh Silva: Registration data sources don't routinely disaggregate by sex. #GenderData]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Head of UN Women vows to tackle laws blocking women's economic progress https://t.co/D06Lqg1Rp9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women and All Their Fake Free Time https://t.co/hpbkgh77fD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our Duty to Protect https://t.co/HskDOcyMw7 via @allafrica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Capital Women: 9 Gender Lens Investors to Know About - Inside Philanthropy - Inside Philanthropy https://t.co/sucAfmOiy2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The missing development trillions: how you would fund the SDGs https://t.co/TlfuxAbJ70]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[• Chart: Which countries ban FGM by law? | Statista https://t.co/K4juKH2DTs via @StatistaCharts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 framing questions for women's economic empowerment https://t.co/eCWQqxHOS1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geraldine Fraser Moleketi launches women empowerment fund https://t.co/ecfws90TXF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do investors care about gender equality at the companies they invest in? https://t.co/94Zl9M7f50]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BSR: Accelerating Private-Sector Action on Women’s Empowerment https://t.co/cUeVRPqIP6 @bsrnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Data Holds Power." A Big Plan from Melinda Gates to Help Close the Gender Gap https://t.co/Jag5ThKIHZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We don't know how many women own land. Why?. https://t.co/5eB3E7Wc0g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women Deliver: Four Ways to Challenge Ourselves https://t.co/CJzwEJVda8 via @cgdev #WD2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Queen Maxima: Financial inclusion is a 'core enabler' #WD2016 https://t.co/Hbv0ZXyk4d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Is there a sexist data crisis? https://t.co/mFbUhckpkn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Susanna Puerto Gonzalez: 'Being young and female is a double strike for anyone trying to access formal employment.' #WD2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HM Queen Maxima: 'A financial service catered to men will not work for women.' #WD2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Muhammad Yunus on financial services and mobile technology: 'If you combine both, you can transform everything.' @Yunus_Centre #WD2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing the Gender Data Gap https://t.co/yoOgUfz0ec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emilia Reyes: 'Infrastructure has everything to do with the quality of life for women and girls.' #WD2016 @equidadmx @CGDev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ngozi: We have 'more than made the case over the years' for gender equality -- now we need to show how to get there. @CGDev @WD2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Via @NPR: Dude, Where Are The Women? #AllMalePanels In Global Development  https://t.co/eBBvb4Vx94]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Without Data Equality There is No Gender Equality: Watch the new video by @Data2X! #genderdata #WD2016 https://t.co/0D4btfjE7U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The changing face of women’s political participation in the Middle East https://t.co/IlluhUqslL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to debate on gender quotas at #PowerShiftForum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s Tough to Stop Sex, Study of U.S. AIDS Effort Shows https://t.co/0yTrkgM7ia via @business]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Capital Credits for Empowering Women and Girls https://t.co/KKgAeT0Ht3 via @HuffPostWomen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liberian legislators drop provision that would have banned FGM https://t.co/UZHUHoqZ0J via @WomenintheWorld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liberia needs to muster the courage to ban FGM | Mary Wandia https://t.co/Sx9fYKFOXK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tanzanian Women Face High Rates of Abortion-Related Deaths https://t.co/7TdXFq88RO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Look into the US Global Strategy to Empower Adolescent Girls https://t.co/HYqAADOtlK via @cgdev]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>