<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Just found out @clubpenguin is shutting down. V emotional rn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stepdad, looking out window: one of my bloody tomatoes has fallen off... f*ck this wind #tomatoproblems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mb_inthehutt Revised date 16 September]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoelRowan I'll rent it. Can pay $450 a week in rent. Willing to pay bond and 4 weeks rent in advance. Quiet young professionals as tenants]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mum: Wednesday is raining!
Dad: F*CK OFF! I have a course to go on.
Us: A golf course...?
Him: EXACTLY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Humanity is an ever balanced scale of kindness and disgrace https://t.co/oi0X12NBCK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't decide if $42 on lipstick is a good idea or not. On the one hand it's a lot of money, on the other it's pretty #help #poorlifechoices]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Currently hearing bass and cheers from town centre. Even Featherston, population 2253, has a more raging social scene than my own life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@liamkernaghan @laurenjwallis I ate two whole packets of shrewsberrys last weekend at @rainermac and @_abbey_'s house.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dude in dominos goes: little hoodlums that's nuts. 
Me: classic Upper Hutt!
Him: is that normal?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Omg some little kids just had a brawl outside UH dominos. Wild.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just overheard head conductor: "I love my job, I love my job, I love..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also hot af thanks to no air con.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Generator on train is broken. Have to get off at UH cos it's "dangerous" to go thru tunnel without lights #traintweets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rainermac I just thought about "poop soup" and now I can't stop laughing cc @_abbey_]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_abbey_ I BLOODY CALLED IT. I TOLD RAINER THERE WAS NO WAY A WEDDING DRESS WAS FITTING IN THAT BOX.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mb_inthehutt don't use "work" and "cake" in the same sentence if I don't get any]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mb_inthehutt why are we having cake?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When all of your work is in that stage where you just have to wait for things to happen and you're just SO DAMN BORED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Current mood: https://t.co/P2L9YJvc3b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LOOKING FOR 2BED FLAT IN WGTN: willing to Rumplestiltskon this shit and offer up my first born child in payment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshuasmith1234 please never bet on me ðŸ™]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rainermac and I are going to start using the work gym. Any work friends feel free to join our shambles of a workout crew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GR_PowerGordon sounds like a decent song. Unfortunately 7yo's version consists of "ONE WAY, JESUS" followed by unintelligible shrieking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GR_PowerGordon questionable label for the shrieking 7yo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In an unprecedented turn of events, the 7yo is now loudly singing "One Way, Jesus" in the other room]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Semi regular reminder from me to you: be kind to people, see good in the world, and know that I love you
 #positivityforthesakeofpositivity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me to 7yo: U can't use the tablet, you'll have to wait for it to charge
7yo shrieking like a demon: I CAN'T WAIT
Me: *grabs bible*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dog whines
Mum: Yes we will in a minute
Dog whines again
Mum: yes I know, I'm just watching the weather]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dad covers the dogs ears to ask Mum if they should go walkies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still haven't found a house but I bought new lipstick today so I've got one thing going for me #ultramatte]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My step mum on strawberries: mmm natures candy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emotionally wrecked by #TheWestWing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rainermac @NZPhotomac @WgtnPhoenixFC @ALeague thank you for this stunning photography]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mb_inthehutt nope? Have applied for heaps of places but no luck getting any]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flat hunting got me ready to live in my car in the car park at work. Except I backed my car into a lamppost today so yeah...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_abbey_ I'm gonna get tee shirts printed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 more flat viewings today. At this point I'd be happy to be offered the single room Anne Frank and her family lived in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've done some stupid shit in my time but seriously I think I'm just taking the piss now https://t.co/HePC2r1odV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went to an open flat today. Decided not to go for it before I got in the house. I think the exact moment was on step no.78 #halfwayup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rainermac the being sick is making me more stressed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rainermac creep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so tired and stressed someone pls shower me with materialistic gifts and hugs and attention to make me feel better x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great lunch at KFC with @rainermac #workingfornz #kfc cc @GR_PowerGordon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mb_inthehutt I count 6 uses of the word organisational. C- for originality and variation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Concept: me but without this awful swollen sore throat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laurenjwallis @_abbey_ 5) failed at throwing me a towel 6) He made fun of my intern cc @joshuasmith1234]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm tired and getting sick and over it someone pls buy me some ColourPop Ultra Matte Lipsticks to make me feel better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mb_inthehutt @cjsbishop what's byo?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama is the Dad we all need https://t.co/A1sux2WaLY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_abbey_ Classic Rainer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rainermac @edufk @DearMama_  I'm not crying you're crying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TheWestWing Season 7 Episode 8 omg I adore this show]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cjsbishop thank god there was never a job interview before you hired me. CC @mb_inthehutt @JoelRowan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm that scene in #Miranda where she sings The Greatest Love Of All at a job interview]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friendship is storing shitty vodka cruisers for the next visit. Thanks @rainermac @_abbey_ https://t.co/PXeulVSvO3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can confirm this was both drab and miserable https://t.co/hv7BrS3Jzw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mb_inthehutt @JoelRowan terrible influences on the sweet, innocent office child]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rainermac @jgmccl it's just something about their paws - it creeps me out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rainermac @jgmccl most accurate description of me I've ever heard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flat hunting is so bloody stressful. Gonna move into the basement at work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's as easy as riding a bike my ass. Just rode a bike for the first time in 5 years and crashed into a fence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mb_inthehutt do I count with Mississippis?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tried to fake tan two hours ago. Literally nothing has happened. My pasty AF skin has no chance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Babysitting. Kids in the other room. Haven't heard either one speak for 25 minutes. V suspicious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rainermac you definitely imagined it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mb_inthehutt crush the patriarchy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mb_inthehutt it's the pale skin isn't it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mb_inthehutt the comparison has been made...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is Monty. He likes vodka and isn't very good at tug-of-war. https://t.co/CgnJW5nQiX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is Bo who frequents the cat tunnel. The other cat in the clip of called Possum. https://t.co/MIwWlP5xHY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Family friends have a cat tunnel from their house to a play pen outside. A freaking cat tunnel!! #cattunnel https://t.co/z9XtUoIzio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dad putting together his new chair
Dad: Uh Oh
Me: ?
Dad: we're missing something
Me:?
Dad: someone qualified to put this together]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mufasa's death is the single most traumatic thing to happen to me. #lionking #tv2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've eaten so much today I think I might be sick. 
Mum: do you want some food
Me: yes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_abbey_ you guys are the dream children (in law)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cjsbishop fitting re recent discussions on The War On Christmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There was more than one lobster present at the birth of Jesus?" #iconic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time for the compulsory Christmas Eve viewing of Love Actually]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_abbey_ @rainermac I thought we were friends and then I learn this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She left me standing holding the milkshake while she went and looked in a shop with a 'no food' policy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mum: do u want a sip of my milkshake?
Me: mmmm not really
Mum: no try it *shoves milkshake at me*
I take it and she immediately walks away]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man, Sister Act II is a great movie #sistermaryclarence #tv2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're the only one on your floor at work and you don't have a key to your office #crosswordtime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshuasmith1234 Thanks &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Upset about all of these MPs resigning/ not contesting. I've been learning all their names using flashcards for no reason #wastehertime2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baked over 100 Christmas Cookies today. If I see one more smushed star shape I think I will spontaneously combust.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_abbey_ this is the funniest thing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iadambutchart @NewshubPolitics @NewshubNZ Still don't see where you're going with this argument]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does that even mean? https://t.co/fnWi56nApf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying to tab through a spreadsheet and wondered why the page wasn't moving; turns out I was aggressively turning caps lock off and on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshuasmith1234 @mb_inthehutt @JoelRowan @cjsbishop NO ONE BREATHE ON ME]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rainermac as far as I'm aware, that's not the case]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things you don't expect to hear at home: 
Mum to Step-Dad: You're just a whore, honey.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things you don't expect to hear at Subway: "Oh god stop licking the wall"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rainermac ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ this is next level https://t.co/CTjMLileTH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rainermac pls &amp; ty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rainermac yes :( hanging out without me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rainermac We did. It was great. She's my new best friend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Babies are great for office morale. Not so much for productivity]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>