<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[European leaders open way to Australian style detention centres in Libya https://t.co/GhFvcDJCTl https://t.co/r0BBxabky5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EU strategy stems migrant flow from Niger, but at what cost?: https://t.co/vxAhokIhDG (@irinnews)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somalia famine fears prompt UN call for 'immediate and massive' reaction https://t.co/FPQbMzvBWO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UNHCR call to EU ahead of summit: Libya is not a safe country or a place to process asylum seekers  
https://t.co/bpuFXKUT2k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automatic open door for Eritreans is shut 
Switzerland makes life harder for Eritrean refugees
https://t.co/9l7lEIv5eH @swissinfo_en]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Africa's finances on the brink as Zuma contemplates replacement of Fin Minister to grab Treasury https://t.co/TS6jmXWoRw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of mining.  Must be bringing in lots of money. When will it lead to a real increase in living standards? https://t.co/fJf6r174Nz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the ANC took control of the South African unions https://t.co/lTpoPLBRP4 https://t.co/n3WExrwfG1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EU navies entering Libyan waters to attack people-smugglers a step closer https://t.co/u25eJCAMJK https://t.co/heycP1NPE8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In case you missed it: Ethiopian general who fought fascism: Jagama Kelo
https://t.co/O0p4qcJWkb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jews in Texas handed Muslim worshippers the keys to their synagogue after town's mosque destroyed in a fire. https://t.co/WCjs4e3R9s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fight for Britain's place in Europe is just beginning https://t.co/GOVzqyUcGm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - DR Congo opposition leader Etienne Tshisekedi dies aged 84 https://t.co/3QZAOtkNlp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freed Nigerian ex-governor Ibori 'to go home within days' https://t.co/36RYzkrIGK via @BBCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Libya may allow EU ships to pursue people-smugglers in its waters https://t.co/eZe8DQmhyx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eight-year-old American girl 'killed in Yemen raid approved by Trump' https://t.co/UzcUzBw8yc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beware of "Marshall Plans" 
https://t.co/sHF6yOBQA3 https://t.co/szehXtnQOq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Zimbabwe's #ThisFlag pastor Evan Mawarire detained on return to country
https://t.co/pQCsD3AmcJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Secret Moscow papers of the South African Communist Party https://t.co/OZojiMHRqf https://t.co/GViN00F0UM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Egypt, Ethiopia and Sudan meet at AU summit over Nile
 https://t.co/elXkj2CN6f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EXCLUSIVE: EU migrant policy in Africa built on incorrect Niger data https://t.co/lc1XYQOGs9 https://t.co/yPdw14LxWA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The district commissioner notebooks of Malawi are some of the records saved by the Endangered Archives Programme https://t.co/cENWuH3h2J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[African leaders plan mass withdrawal from international criminal court https://t.co/dikwCLWlCa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[News you don't want to hear.  Well, I don't! https://t.co/fBd0LCvMWO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Morocco rejoins African Union after more than 30 years https://t.co/rJqtSxOOSL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somalia: The drought that began in 2015 now across the whole country. The North is in 'extreme' condition
https://t.co/FhXN1b7Yfu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zimbabwe mine threatened with 'seizure' - for the third time!
https://t.co/dNPwLIximR via @BBCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Malaria drugs fail for first time on patients in UK.  Is the parasite becoming more dangerous?  https://t.co/45i2WVBEpH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US acting attorney general defies Trump immigrant ban. Believing it is illegal  https://t.co/22uMLXFkf0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Demonstration against Trump state visit to Britain this evening outside Downing Street https://t.co/yMbZEucPut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Egypt and Ethiopia leaders to meet at African Union - can they end Nile conflict? Sisis says "life and death"
https://t.co/l62DvSRuqp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Africa: Date of ANC conference: 16 - 20 December 2017 https://t.co/U5M8xKcYl0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump and Theresa May: One million Brits say she got this relationship wrong https://t.co/h6gAYON4t6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Petition opposing Trump state visit to U.K. while ban on travel to US in place passes 1 million mark! 1284 signing every minute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[British petition opposing Trump state visit to U.K. while ban on travel to US in place passes 900,000 mark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Petition to bar Trump from a state visit to Britain passes the 800,000 mark
https://t.co/ziugqW1djf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now over 600,000 and rising! https://t.co/eUu5JMx8Ij]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[500,000 UK residents sign petition: Prevent Donald Trump from making a State Visit to the United Kingdom https://t.co/87pI0SpHen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - West Africa - from dictators' club to upholder of democracy https://t.co/mExArbO1WK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theresa May does 'not agree' with US ban on refugees https://t.co/FHEKa5Ry4G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grim outlook for Africans refugees as Trump bans Somalis, Sudanese and Libyans from USA
https://t.co/zNbPjr52GG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In case you missed it: Eritrea: fury and protests as National Service conscripts pay withheld
https://t.co/K2TLUIjYoK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Africa: Money lust ‘threatens to split the ANC’ https://t.co/enxpJcDXX3 via @BDliveSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh no!  Trump has accepted an invitation of a state visit to Britain. The poor Queen will have to be his hostess!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did Sudan use chemical weapons in Darfur? "victims suffered injuries that can only be explained by chemical agents" 
https://t.co/NF1yz0fRLo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South African Platinum mining firm tells massacre families: we can't afford to house you https://t.co/Sc6YVxPHlJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inside Ethiopia’s “retraining” programme for thousands of detained protesters 
https://t.co/TOUF26JceT via @socializeWP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In case you missed it:J oe Slovo, the SACP and the Angola massacre of May 1977
https://t.co/dulsMvoScY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a moment to celebrate! https://t.co/lO2FUJx8rW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Europe’s crackdown on African immigration is hitting vulnerable refugees https://t.co/b1SQ9QhjE3 https://t.co/ic3zpNRgl6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Europe’s crackdown on African immigration is hitting vulnerable refugees | Martin Plaut https://t.co/zbXKdBWC5p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clashes between Mozambican army and Renamo forced 11,000 to flee to Mwanza district, Malawi, since December
https://t.co/PHA4NYzVvJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mozambique floods: Since the beginning of 207 14 people have died and 79,000 have been affected
https://t.co/PHA4NYzVvJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[European Commission seeks to stop migration flows from  Libya
https://t.co/ydNdjj7mYj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Africa: the Guptas' London PR firm is well-known for mastery of 'all sorts of dark arts'.
 https://t.co/31bvPerocw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An insightful review of “Understanding Eritrea” in Times Higher Education https://t.co/Hne8f7t7tb https://t.co/vaqQ6JSzKr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grim outlook for Africans seeking refuge as Trump looks to ban Somalis, Sudanese https://t.co/rd7Hqnxfup via @TC_Africa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to Vanessa Berhe and Idil Osman for the Understanding Eritrea launch at SOAS - passionate debate! https://t.co/1WG3L1vzdZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Launching "Understanding Eritrea" at the Royal African Society - strong, engaged discussion! https://t.co/WG0Dngeqaj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Egypt considers return to Nile Basin Initiative after absences of 7 years
https://t.co/KkWj2dNYqp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[London court to rule on Shell’s Nigerian oil spill today https://t.co/1xtEPuf4L6 https://t.co/KsWKz57ynJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Africa's Most Repressive State? Politics, Rights and Leadership in Eritrea
https://t.co/rXhyGrJckI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Madonna applies to adopt 2 more children from Malawi
https://t.co/A3vjFt1tlq via @MailOnline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Africans view South Africa: xenophobic, patronising and selfish. A pity. Both sides have a lot to offer https://t.co/L31HhbTwzH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gambia: UN Security Council to be briefed on holding Jammeh to account when archive may be destroyed
https://t.co/CK3pugWfXf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rhodes Must Fall activist wins Rhodes scholarship: branded hypocrite  https://t.co/oI214s5WRi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uganda's sprawling haven for 270,000 of South Sudan's refugees https://t.co/DxYXH4QydH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ANC's Black Ops, paid Twitter, fake news – a real threat to South African democracy | Daily Maverick https://t.co/Z2qd9F9es6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's threat to Voice of America https://t.co/B3SeMRaZml]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ma'am?  Was not this the person implicated in the death of Stompie Moeketsi? https://t.co/wrYkDKGgrz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A reward for investigating Clintons emails in the dying days of the election? https://t.co/mUCwYvFekw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israel: sick asylum seeker left on streets of Tel Aviv as ministries dispute responsibility https://t.co/12ogNk3z9l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inside the ANC’s “black ops” election campaign - how the "War Room" secretly “disempowered" opposition parties 
https://t.co/CZvcXGNjlT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What southern Africa can learn from west Africa about dealing with despots https://t.co/QtfnlxyHJQ via @TC_Africa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tories write off stoke-on-trent central by-election, to give UKIP a clear run party sources say https://t.co/TWd5LgqBoI # via @HuffPostUKPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - The Gambia 'missing millions' after Jammeh flies into exile https://t.co/hGqDQ2FVQB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Angolan banks appealing to the government to help put together a bailout package as oil slumps. https://t.co/wQX9Z11Dn6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[British government softens Eritrea guidance softened to reduce asylum seeker numbers https://t.co/tcS6rkdUmf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will the poor people of Equatorial Guinea have two dictators instead of being run by a kleptocratic family? https://t.co/vqeztx9t0P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sudan: SPLM-N denies refusing to allow USAID to transport medical to civilians in Blue Nile and South Kordofan 
https://t.co/R7Cw77TwMC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ECOWAS agreement that convinced Jammeh to leave: his rights as a Gambian citizen guaranteed https://t.co/UCALkNFwHL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[James Onanefe Ibori, governor of Delta state among the African elite that bought into London https://t.co/4mK4NVfkaq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Mugabe survives while Gambia now looks to freedom and a better future https://t.co/zMkaFyBKCN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Comparing Donald Trump and Barack Obama's inaugural crowd sizes @CNNPolitics https://t.co/b5d5Rr4rb5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump Is Completely Obsessed With Revenge https://t.co/idEA1Xzke7 via @motherjones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why the South African government is still protecting apartheid racketeers
https://t.co/cZ2ujS6wJV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Qatar, Ethiopia played role in lifting US sanctions on Sudan https://t.co/ng7z8MlxUU via @MiddleEastMnt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gambia: 7000 ECOWAS troops give Jammeh  until midday Friday to hand over power and leave country  https://t.co/hq8zv5qb8x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Gambia crisis: Senegal troops enter to back new president https://t.co/xrZ4fmTOMk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South African police raid home of acting national police commissioner‚ Lt-Gen Kgomotso Phahlane
https://t.co/BDCVkzvo1I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kenya: Tullow Discovers New Oil Fields in Turkana https://t.co/ehOQ90QjzY via @allafrica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UN to vote on Gambia intervention today. https://t.co/XtNnA27BtY via @BBCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Gambia crisis: Barrow inauguration in Senegal as Jammeh stays put https://t.co/O1ZtFjTmDC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did Sudan use chemical weapons in Darfur last year? https://t.co/hNbFPGIxxk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mauritanian President flew to Senegal to meet with President Macky Sall after last-ditch talks in Gambia 
https://t.co/XdJVPMZDAI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senegal troops move to Gambia border as Jammeh crisis grows https://t.co/bIQQIuHRqq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sudan: Notorious Janjaweed militia integrated into army, just as Obama lifts sanctions on Khartoum
https://t.co/p3oixYVsCF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to understand the global rise of populism, Trump, le Pen and others? This is an excellent guide 
https://t.co/5Zi8ibMwhM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvilGeniusPub No alternative plan. And no - CARE is not the only int. aid agency barred.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eritrea: "many major aid organisations such as CARE International are not allowed" to aid 2m hungry 
https://t.co/aq7PlP04U5]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>