<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoying this a lot. https://t.co/nZVZnx2jDP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katieabradford @gtiso Investment in software is philanthropy? Helping out those poor software developers?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katieabradford any word and how much and where the philanthropic money went?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hmmm, remind you of anyone? https://t.co/YpPZRV28Ml]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is really worth a listen. With Donna Miles @UnPressed Murdoch Stephens @DoingOurBitNZ &amp; @theabbasnazari, with… https://t.co/8r58LkQRLV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarristerNZ I remember him well Felix.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JimLewischch @AndrewLittleMP @nzlabour How did I not know about this when I get so many emails from Labour?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irihapeta No I mean we can only dream of it not being celebrated here. I loathe GF night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irihapeta We can only dream.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@torpidkiwi that is nuts!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edmuzik @publicaddress @tmurphyNZ @JimLewischch @nzlabour @AndrewLittleMP Official capacity 350 standing only. 200 if the leaners in there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edmuzik @publicaddress We actually only had 200 for the F Nun gig. Felt like a lot more. Unless people snuck in of course.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pjkmorris I'm staying well away from that - my fragile ego would not take it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteveBraunias @pjkmorris They won't!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hissingswan @pjkmorris Being on Twitter and talking about anything at the moment feels weird.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pjkmorris How have you noticed though? I wouldn't notice if anyone unfollowed me. Or do you have that app that tells you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Argh! https://t.co/do9xM6c9gw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bbcclass @BBCOne Any chance we'll be seeing this in New Zealand? @Patrick_Ness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helen_lehndorf Hell yes! Trying to keep my kids informed  about the world without also scaring them to death.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MoataTamaira I'm watching on demand and I have ads! Well promos anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went to watch the Sherlock I recorded last night only to find my 7 year old had recorded 21 hours of rugby Sevens. #partrecorded #diskfull]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lightyouonfire But not one you should be in any way concerned about! Trump for a profile pic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lightyouonfire No it was just an abusive one not a questioning one. Serves me right. Off to wash my hands.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lightyouonfire Argh I went to click on a tweet to see what lowlife was saying nasty things to you &amp; I accidentally liked it! I don't like!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@isaac_davison @secondzeit Not good enough!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SophieFern Well that's a pity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I slept in. Has the PM said anything yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pmbillenglish Please let your next tweet be soon &amp; be a link to your statement on the US #MuslimBan. We need you to respond on our behalf.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In fact this is like something out of the Hunger Games. #PresidentSnow #rpt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is like some awful parody of an infomercial. The horror. https://t.co/QqupGzgTKN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarristerNZ @GemWilder Have they appointed a new ambassador yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BillEnglishMP Where is your tweet? https://t.co/uO6xkqc9kl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pmbillenglish Where is your statement regarding Trump's outrageous ban on Muslim refugees and immigrants? What will you do to help them?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AJFitzwater Where can I find it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AJFitzwater oh for a minute I read that as "Little talk" and I was wondering who you were following!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pjkmorris I guess mine's more a 'how can the system allow this and not that' rhetorical-type question, which can't be answered in a tweet!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurieFleming @testpatern Well that is just fucked up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaireMabey I could basically just read full time. Pesky jobs and families!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can Trump do all this in one week when Obama couldn't do anything about gun control in 8 years?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaireMabey Yes! It's great. You can spy on what your friends are reading, and have conversations etc. Also logging read and TBR is helpful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaireMabey No I haven't to either of them. SO MANY BOOKS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaireMabey Are you on Goodreads?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaireMabey Also, I've really been enjoying peronsal essays &amp; memoir lately - breaking out of my diet of mostly fiction. Any recommends?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaireMabey I feel like this is my year to find some quiet space in my newly organised home office &amp; maybe even learn how to write again,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaireMabey Mind you, who knows when I'll get to read them. Currently reading Dying by Corey Taylor and a million children's awards books!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClaireMabey Good idea. I'm getting the Oliver and the de Botton. I have the Gleick (not read yet).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@banquotrilogy @netflix Yes except that it is not bingeable - releasing one episode a week. Have you checked out Frequency? That's all there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This list has made me want to BUY ALL THE BOOKS. https://t.co/phzQLS9l0d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shessassy Me too. Enjoyed it. Cool that the actor who played Archie is Samoan from NZ!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok and wow the first ep is called 'The River's Edge'. Broadcasting its influences! #Riverdale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just started watching Riverdale on @Netflix - based on Archie comics but with a Twin Peaks makeover.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@loumagooo F*** that! Embrace the clutter!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LOTEIGHT Be offended. That is offensive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rachaelking70 @BMHayward The veganness is ironic because that site used to be a butcher!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BMHayward Also that block is nice - they have rebuilt sympathetically. The one across the road on the other hand... 😳]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BMHayward That's in my hood and I haven't been there yet (waiting for school drop offs begin again!). It always looks busy. &amp; it's vegan?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is amazing. https://t.co/Zw67PFfjaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdrienneRewi @MonzaGT School holidays &amp; kids home in evening further shackle!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdrienneRewi @MonzaGT Having said that I was tricked into it today and sweltered on the back of a horse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdrienneRewi @MonzaGT I stay indoors / I always get less fit in summer!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdrienneRewi I feel cheated. Forecast said 23 so I went out in it. Melted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And yes @goodreads says 1978 but it was 1977. @PenguinBooks_NZ @MrJonathanKing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just taking a moment to celebrate this book being in print for 40 years. https://t.co/TLexRbO1ZP @PenguinBooks_NZ @MrJonathanKing #TePuea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElizabethxKerr Thanks - looks like I'm going in August! Has been a dream of mine for 25 years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lightyouonfire Also, after the school holidays I look 90. But thanks! X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lightyouonfire Or maybe expectations of what 47 looks like can change? 😄]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lightyouonfire There you go! Nothing to do with age then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lightyouonfire Just do some squats and you'll be right! I have much better leg muscles now than I had at 20!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lightyouonfire You say that like 47 is old (says she who turns 47 this year)!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@harvestbird Was it your recommendation on here that sparked my interest? @amy_may]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just met a nice writer from Orkney who confirmed I should buy this book I've been interested in. @amy_may https://t.co/71Rxi0ces0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ALJwrites The fee is no different from an agent's fee. They have to keep the site running somehow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[American friends reporting the Melania Trump grimace video being removed from their FB pages!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RDUBreakfast @FergusVUP Oh darn missed it. Online later?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swimmingwbooks Says on front of bottle it's from Nelson.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swimmingwbooks I'll look closer next time! I was just groaning about the obvious bid for the paleo crowd's $$.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Knhannah were you working for him just before he died?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swimmingwbooks The water or the photo? New World.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally! I can drink water again. https://t.co/J5KRbRDquu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaneyArthur What's the new job???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaneyArthur 41% on the first day!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Knhannah I also got this one from my Dad but 13 years ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Knhannah This one? https://t.co/yAlihmQ1KI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Are you the boy who has to say poo bum fart?" @JohnJCampbell to Gareth Morgan, just now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Sapling - Because Books Grow Humans on https://t.co/ynzuWBfsnJ https://t.co/DUDIuTHbm4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got A+ &amp; overdue non-fic to catch up on in between kids' book award reading. @ashleigh_young @clementine_ford… https://t.co/zqemWmgSef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaneyArthur I craved a lot of soy milk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaneyArthur See you're on your way to having my 36 year! Congrats. And commiserations on the sickness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edmuzik All the women look the same with different hair colour - must be his idea of what a 'feminist' looks like.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WomensMarchOnWashington #christchurch https://t.co/EoUEke1Z7D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WomensMarch #chch https://t.co/U9BxvXTPHg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaqTweedie I remember! Washing a car, if I'm correct. It was glorious. @dylanhorrocks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Becs It's fab!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Becs There is a 'want to read' shelf but you can create your own shelves, so can make a 'recommended' list.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnthonyByrt I haven't seen the doco but find the whole concept annoying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@testpatern @Ghetsuhm See you there! I hope there will be more!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who in #Chch is going on the march tomorrow?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's a lot of manspreading going on... https://t.co/41Se9kUjv6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Helen__Heath Thanks Helen! I canvassed widely and in the end, these made the most sense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wellreadkitty @librarykris Which book Kelly?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>