<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#Travel How free Ryanair flights are the future https://t.co/qkT44ekUHi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Brexit Dublin: Exhausted Teresa May was with us in body - but not in mind. https://t.co/jC01WMaVin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FACup 5th round draw LIVE NOW #BBC1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump made election promises,including the now infamous Travel Ban. He was elected on the back of these promises. I… https://t.co/4aufhpakzw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Arsenal Wenger likes the better view from the Stand. https://t.co/zSwaxFqh8e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maggie May (from It Had To Be You) https://t.co/pmRzDN41tv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Dublin Teresa May is in town #Brexit https://t.co/NOQAmZErzc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Arsenal to benefit from a 'Pool win...Liverpool v Chelsea - Klopp issues rallying cry ahead of Chelsea showdown https://t.co/2wJWcxoBY4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wormdogg @JiveArsenal Leeds Utd are not in the draw.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every time I'm in London there's some rail dispute....Tube Ticket office staff will not join in next week's walkouts https://t.co/cLC0jqJTtv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jay1law_ Yeah,well I would'nt fancy Millwall away. #TheDen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Brexit Enda Kenny meets Theresa May in Dublin today https://t.co/I7QCcKL5sK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jay1law_ #FACup Draw during "The One Show" which starts at 07:00pm #BBC1 Draw about 07:20....don't care who we get. #Arsenal will win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#MuslimBan The ban does not apply to UK Nationals,so Mo Farah relieved to be exempt from Donald Trump's travel ban. https://t.co/eahas5PBSY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DunLaoireDLR Cabinteely Renters in 'hell' house plead for more time https://t.co/UciKV6mi2O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Arsenal ready to spend £85 million and ruin Manchester United's summer plans  https://t.co/chjlGAvJh1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federer beats great rival Nadal to win historic 18th Grand Slam https://t.co/24rdIIcqCa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jay1law_ Yes....pity about Frampton though😫]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamrockRover @Arsenal @Jay1law_  Just thinking.....Arsene Wenger might be sitting in the Stand beside us #UTA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamrockRover @TheTollington @Arsenal Yes indeed,I was just about to tweet the same thing.The other young fella @Jay1law_ is coming as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cold, wind and rain on the way as Met Eireann predicts mixed bag https://t.co/CLjiO5ELtO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NewsPapers Some of the todays Irish Front Pages. https://t.co/dVm2GMgQur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Arsenal Arsène Wenger hit with immediate four-game touchline ban by FA https://t.co/vSf9ZRcoYN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Travel Tube workers to stage two strikes next month after talks break down https://t.co/EfyYAmRLg8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Travel BA cabin crew set to strike over six days amid 'poverty pay' row https://t.co/myQ9FzFA5p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Arsenal James Lawton puts forward this analysis of Arsene Wenger whom he says is a prisoner of his own dreams.https://t.co/dvJbAa4kV7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fozziedublin @thejournal_ie @rtenews Yes,I agree with you.#CoverUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drunk driver with 485 convictions and who killed teen while speeding,jailed for a mere 18 months. SACK THE JUDGE.  https://t.co/wlbyHf06Jk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Southampton vs #Arsenal: FA Cup preview https://t.co/vMNxBpkPNF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rafa Nadal sets up Australian Open final with old foe Roger Federer after classic https://t.co/JpddLSCz7Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamrockRover Ha..for a moment there Mick,I thought you were talking about the East or West Stand.  Anyway,it was on the East Pier,I was.😀]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Judge in this case should be charged with perverting the course of justice.483 convictions &amp; gets just 18 months https://t.co/vAlrpKmSHk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a great stroll by the pier,I'm awake now. There was no need for Sun Factor 50 today. https://t.co/K4qfXXivZG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man United manager Jose Mourinho awaiting Arsène Wenger punishment for pushing fourth official https://t.co/jyVlABlb1j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arsenal boss Arsene Wenger accepts FA charge. https://t.co/blx9edjZwl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you have Discovery channels on Sky.... They're set to disappear next week. https://t.co/ajeX4muVh8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To cheer you up .  Four-year-old girl wins hearts across the world with her rendition of 'You've Got A Friend In Me' https://t.co/tbMMNOg4n5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jay1law_ Yeah,I had been thinking that today was Tuesday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jay1law_ I thought it was to day,but he's not due before the FA until Thursday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Premier League fixtures on TV in March announced by Sky and BT Sport https://t.co/U37WHlmACZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Arsenal Theo Walcott Reveals: Arsene Wenger went full Al Pacino in bid to kickstart Arsenal season  https://t.co/Eid4pMZgxV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Arsenal Wenger requests personal hearing in bid to minimise FA charge https://t.co/WTc6HXLoaZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jay1law_ Yeah,they might come down heavy on him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jay1law_ Oh yeah..good thinking about Elneny.. ..I don't see any news yet,of Arsene Wenger getting a ban.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jay1law_ Fired a blank.....Anyway why do you hope for that result tonight?.......I have'nt seen the teams.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now you don't need an internet connection to send Whatsapp messages https://t.co/RHbQpCLY3h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pjanic, Saul and five signings #Arsenal could make to revive their title hopes https://t.co/T06OK8dpcQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Arsenal's Granit Xhaka faces police abuse probe over claim he called BA worker 'f****** white b****' https://t.co/CZMEQo4jvg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freezing fog sees hundreds of flights cancelled at London airports early today. https://t.co/SknJm3iKCY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jay1law_ Haha....poor old Maureen for the chop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Arsenal 'Why are you doing that?' - Henry blasts Xhaka for red-card lunge https://t.co/lraVtgwEdK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jay1law_ I googled his name..there are a good few of them.I read the long article again and still not sure who Tony Evans is @standardsport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jay1law_ Yep,I've sorted all that out. Ryanair to Gatwick,Travelodge Nth London, &amp; ClockEnd ticket for the match #UTA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One guy wants Wenger to get 10-game ban if FA are serious about protecting refs'. https://t.co/BqnyR37LfX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jay1law_ Yeah,it's looking bad for Wenger, especially since he's had previous barnies with refs/linesmen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two Aer Lingus staff among three arrested at Dublin Airport over people smuggling. https://t.co/UbaveZzwN9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FA might try to throw the book at Arsene Wenger, Liverpool hopes over: Four talking points from weekend PL action https://t.co/FfzNZaQjvE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Allo, Allo actor Gorden Kaye dies in care home aged 75 https://t.co/144XWcPgrj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This simple trick could improve a cheap bottle of wine https://t.co/kpBFj2Hqwn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Arsenal 2 : Burnley 1 Wenger sent off as Sanchez seals epic late win https://t.co/UuxedWtxGj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Arsenal team v Burnley https://t.co/Hh1gEdV9Ex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Punish thugs that cut dog’s ears off and posed for photos! https://t.co/29nJofs945]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shock Liverpool loss hands title boost to Chelsea,and #Arsenal https://t.co/KGT8vhLZuH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Petition | Punish thugs that cut dog’s ears off and posed for photos! https://t.co/29nJofs945]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The White House....Donald J.Trump's new address for a while, is reportedly smaller than one of his own houses. https://t.co/rqaCu2ZpgH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HooliganAlert Conservative MP warns over potential abuse of Wembley if Tottenham and Chelsea move in https://t.co/aU5sXGK3A3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump's inauguration timetable https://t.co/8Ih6VZwHMm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Arsenal are top of London revenue table,but struggle to keep up with Man Utd https://t.co/t0A1bGvjFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wrap up well! Freezing weather ahead with temperatures set to fall as low -4°C this weekend. https://t.co/DVayJVRUWY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manchester United complete record signing - a counter terrorism manager https://t.co/Hjrs9ELlYS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#London Man killed after being hit by train at King's Cross https://t.co/s4alN5gphD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some nice houses,where these football players live! - https://t.co/RDCjQX7xNw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Travel Earthquake shakes central Italy, sending tremors through Rome https://t.co/bqnXUzb42R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lethal powder drug U-4 on Ireland's streets for first time 'could be mistaken for cocaine' https://t.co/WEyhmCfyNn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jay1law_ Yeah,that's the downside of the place,so might put it on the long finger for a while.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jay1law_ Yeah,we can both go on the #Arsenal plane to Dubai,but have to checkout the "Pub" situation first. (very… https://t.co/S1ztcdqMVv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jay1law_ I've a relative out there,so might make a visit.It's great that I could fly direct from Dublin. World's tallest building etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jay1law_ Just saw this. Yes Jay,I hope to take the #Arsenal Plane on a trip to Dubai.....not sure when though. https://t.co/dO5Ymvgk0p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #Arsenal Plane.....Hope to get a seat on it,in the near future https://t.co/jBB297MCLk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jay1law_  Good memories from those Henry years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jay1law_ Arsene Wenger was manager even back then,with Pat Rice beside him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Referee Mike Dean sent down to the Championship after heavy criticism over controversial decisions https://t.co/3JJyw1u2IT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jay1law_ That's good going.Do ye remember who Arsenal were playing that day &amp; what season?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jay1law_ Haha...I think Mick is under curfew from his Mrs.to get home early.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WorldCupQualifier Wales fans 'outraged' by ticket allocation for Ireland clash https://t.co/dHB2kF6Nnm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Dublin An artist's impression of how the Luas Cross City will look when work is completed later this year https://t.co/sQDMRuQYKE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jay1law_ Yeah we can but hope. Anyway I''l be up in Finsbury Park for the Hull game...so one game at a time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jay1law_ I think it was from a contact in the Tolly that I met at an earlier match. We can ask around,when we're over for the Hull game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jay1law_ Yeah,me too. How about Spurs away...29/30th April.I was at WHL a few years ago when #Arsenal won 5-2.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arsenal vs Burnley: Premier League preview https://t.co/6TLyTPp5W5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jay1law_ Well after the Hull game,I want to take in 2 or 3 more before the end of season. New manager in next season according to reports]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jay1law_ People are been fooled into paying crazy prices.Btw I was looking at the fixtures,and I think I might go to the Leicester game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U2..I would'nt go to the back garden to see them but,Touts make a killing as U2 tickets are now  in excess of €2k https://t.co/oh6uXl7IEt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#BBC Farting about with Match of the Day #MOTD...missed it..'cause it was on #BBC2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Swansea v #Arsenal The Arsenal lineout. https://t.co/byQkpOOH0t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamrockRover @Jay1law_ @TheTollington Dead right Mick.They'll be ready for us,and willing to serve up many,many pints and plates of grub.😀]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FootballFocus... A tribute to Graham Taylor and all the latest football news....now  #BBC1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamrockRover @Jay1law_ Great stuff Mick....now all we need is for the Tolly @TheTollington to open early on day of match ( k/o 12:30) #UTA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Dublin locals object to Costa del Sol-style development https://t.co/hf5hR9nnIL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Swimmers warned of E Coli outbreak at popular Dublin bathing area https://t.co/XAbKVBjgNb]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>