<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[dedication to @ twitter user tobjizzle https://t.co/HYSLXJKeZ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laraxroig my life in a nutshell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tobjizzle why must you hate me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tobjizzle I'm having the worst day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Manny_Official how is this early you need your sleep schedule fixed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piercethewik whoever eats a large pizza the fastest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Callux maths clearly wasn't your strongest subject]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i want to be in a gc so i can procrastinate even more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[me: y'all are too damn sensitive
also me: cries if someone is mean to me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tobjizzle @MoniqueScarlet @Manny_Official told U, he loves seeing me suffer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MoniqueScarlet @Tobjizzle @Manny_Official probably does but he just hates me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tobjizzle @Manny_Official do I need this disrespect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What are your views on pineapples on Pizza? — disgusting should not be a thing  https://t.co/Mq95t8ZYkb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i just burped really loudly and scared my cat rt your goals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tobjizzle coconut oil works well too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Callux on the internet, your memories exist forever. but so do your mistakes...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Manny_Official do you ever sleep or at least rest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Callux well surely they had a reason to not let you it's probably against the school policy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miniminter random question but can we expect some nice collabs anytime soon *cough* joe sugg perhaps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CeIizzle happy birthday babe I hope you have a good one 🎉✨💜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[u know your sleep schedule is fucked when you get happy over getting 5 hours sleep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it's 3am and i have a 9am start why do i wish death upon myself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Noah fence but my fans are very fucking real you absolute loser https://t.co/HKxRBDozPf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miniminter everyone's gotta start somewhere you know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[countdown till i meet my favourite youtuber 😇✨👇]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i haven't showered since last month 😩💯]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@caitlinperryx I'm down to collab if food is involved]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[booking a train to Manchester real quick https://t.co/NQZt3FmL3n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamWoodx good shout will definitely plan out my night differently next time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamWoodx basically yes and also surprisingly chicken nuggets, ice cream and Mexican don't mix together well I felt a tad sick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamWoodx it was great but also gross yet somehow satisfying but not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ffsmaan isn't the challenge just one large]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ffsmaan next time I order dominos I'll time how long it takes me to eat it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[last Friday was wild i had McDonald's, a Kaspa's sundae and Chiquito's in the space of like 4 hours i felt like a mess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bethanysnxw Bethany.... you have seen me eat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[someone do the dominos pizza challenge with me but only if you're prepared to LOSE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vvanessatorres if this ain't me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thoughts on Muslims? — don't think i should really have a generalised opin... https://t.co/BbFNddSXRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really want to talk to you but I don't know how t... — send me a meme if i laugh i'll reply https://t.co/9S06czv632]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my favourite song is the what are you doing in my swamp remix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[more tutorials like this please :-) https://t.co/bNtkkbtKkv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tobjizzle ever heard of this sick app called 'Weather'?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tobjizzle cars* don't wash cats pls you'd die]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tobjizzle it's god tryna tell you you suck at washing cats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ffsmaan @luxlikeamna @Iordpearce the fact you actually saved that ffs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ffsmaan @luxlikeamna @Iordpearce STOP USING MY OWN MEMES AGAINST ME]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ffsmaan @luxlikeamna @Iordpearce who asked you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@luxlikeamna @Iordpearce he hates me he would never follow smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keeleysw_f I'd call dominos and u could probably get a refund &amp; keep the food if ur dramatic enough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Manny_Official love how you get deep over cereal but then don't care about anything else]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@luxlikeamna @Iordpearce user tobjizzle follow user veronicatls too pls x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[imma act shocked https://t.co/NOjAZ3cdIX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Iordpearce @Caspar_Lee copyright him smfh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[texted the gc saying tobi dmed me and gee believed me, as if he would ever pls he hates me smfh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Caspar_Lee how have you not followed @Iordpearce she's literally in your header come on now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gabbysdmn_ @Tobjizzle this is SO good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tobjizzle night mode made me feel uncomfortable it's just NOT right sorry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Caspar_Lee you're rich get yourself some food]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Caspar_Lee 'af' who are you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miniminter got any more of those tweet sprees of yours in store?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JMXFifa £300 for two days for the first one and we got ourselves a deal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JMXFifa for the two or one?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JMXFifa £500 an hour x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JMXFifa take your pick https://t.co/rsWxaqIh9h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miniminter i want to win a collab]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miniminter would get those views right up for u too x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this was meant to say simon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sink is fit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tobjizzle @miniminter more content like this pls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tobjizzle collab with simon and manny more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tobjizzle how about this fun challenge where you read all my tweets and reply xxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Manny_Official why did you change your icon i found the other one reflected who you truly are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[imagine your fave appreciating you, can't relate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joeweIIers @MoniqueScarlet us tbh https://t.co/vEotw0Lh99]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wtf is this https://t.co/006i2RMcQR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stayaIjve u loved it rly my humour is my best quality x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[knew my random knowledge of countries would one day be beneficial even if it's for a geography quiz online]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MyNamesChai where's that letter of defeat then? 😜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IuxIike @MyNamesChai not everyone needs company stop russian to conclusions (ha ha)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IuxIike you got poland that's all that matters x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MyNamesChai I left Europe until the end and did Africa first bevause my geography teacher always nagged me about African countries 😭]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MyNamesChai I got so stressed I forgot Italy Jesus christ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MyNamesChai weekly geography quizzes at school for 5 years clearly paid off ngl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miniminter V always fucking you over innit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[me: ok now im gonna concentrate and do work 
me 30 seconds later: laughs to myself at a meme i saw the other day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CAN'T YOU SEE I'M ON THE PHONE — JHFGJKFJF stop https://t.co/MQOkSeKe5p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joeweIIers joe and Elliot the ghostbusters™]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ffsmaan had a crush on that fish ngl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dylansus can't believe stiles is moulting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KSIOlajidebt can't believe you're a chef now, is youtube not working out?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bethanysnxw generally is in general and genuinely is really they're two different words 😭]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bethanysnxw STOP GETTING GENUINELY AND GENERALLY MIXED UP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Callux vidcon is tired of your shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vikkstar123 why do u always tweet people at like 6am it's like we're in different timezones but irl your sleeping schedule is just fucked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miniminter what are you planning to film next?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tobjizzle do simon next i love seeing him in pain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this show fucked me up https://t.co/jvEg4F86H1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[can Basshunter hurry up and announce tour dates pls im stressing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MoniqueScarlet @Manny_Official my teachers did at school]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Manny_Official how do you think i felt when i moved to the uk and everyone kept calling dinner tea oh god the confusion]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>