<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kawanatanga1 @MPD_NZ @NZNationalParty but where would they meet? oh: #videoconf #broadband]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaxRobitzsch @jdeheij @richardhills777 @Brycepearce @ruatara @lennartnout @TransportBlog worked at Waitakere Central, sah #realswales]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jdeheij @richardhills777 @MaxRobitzsch @Brycepearce @ruatara @lennartnout @TransportBlog check all that wasteful greenery]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robellcampbin only the staff kitchens thereof #heathens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MPD_NZ @Kawanatanga1 fine if you qualify for that avenue - way unfair differential in NZ already]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kawanatanga1 @MPD_NZ @NZNationalParty need to make services accountable to recipients]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kawanatanga1 @MPD_NZ @NZNationalParty problem is already geographically distributed :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very simple step: make universal design compulsory for every state-funded home. Then private ones. UK does that - why not NZ? #nzpol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kawanatanga1 @MPD_NZ people have tried]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MPD_NZ @Kawanatanga1 @NZNationalParty going on forever. bad karma for many many decision-makers who ignore such needs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kawanatanga1 @MPD_NZ the whole industry is broken]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["She'll help us down the stairs, no questions" #rpt #chump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MPD_NZ @NewshubNZ lack of structural advocacy, empowerment, basic service, human respect #nzpol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaxRobitzsch @richardhills777 @Brycepearce @ruatara @lennartnout @TransportBlog but of course the Germans have a word for that :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaxRobitzsch @richardhills777 @Brycepearce @ruatara @lennartnout @TransportBlog is the genius still on staff?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaxRobitzsch @richardhills777 @Brycepearce @ruatara @lennartnout @TransportBlog whay was it changed?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaxRobitzsch @richardhills777 @Brycepearce @ruatara @lennartnout @TransportBlog plenty of space for one's Morrie to pass that buggy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ageing population means more disabled people. All housing must work for everyone's needs. Fix it #nzpol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Govt agencies act after publicity, admit lack of housing for disabled people, do nothing about that https://t.co/trkOVuABC7 #nzpol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richardhills777 @Brycepearce @ruatara @lennartnout @TransportBlog how is that not a roundabout?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bridget_Burdett @richardhills777 @Brycepearce @ruatara @lennartnout @TransportBlog at least yours has useful trees]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@5WinstonSmith5 @reckonsemoji looks like the issue is my sight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reckonsemoji @5WinstonSmith5 ah, that faint smudge. #asyouwere #thehorror]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@5WinstonSmith5 @reckonsemoji did they not require promoter statements? assumed it must be ages ago. prefer banana theory]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@5WinstonSmith5 @reckonsemoji may have been the famous east auckland banana crisis where Otahuhu was a smuggling corridor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@5WinstonSmith5 @reckonsemoji metaphorical, innit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reckonsemoji @5WinstonSmith5 maybe during his epic battle with a local scrap metal dealer?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@5WinstonSmith5 @reckonsemoji no promoter statement. hall monitor sounds about right? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lindaclark1 or he saw it coming ..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HamishMack @reckonsemoji true, the unmet desire for recognition would have been there all along]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vincristine how would we know, really]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@guywilliamsguy @Pno_nwa 'shit or get off the pot' as my grandpa would have said]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reckonsemoji he actually stood for election? must be pre-laziness, maybe a decade ago]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edmuzik great crown lynn vase. nothing about where he's speaking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edmuzik @nzdrug is the door locked? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wekatweets @mwehipeihana most of us have no idea which organisations do what]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelFieldNZ his team did a great job of spreading their message at the Mt Albert event on Sunday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wekatweets @mwehipeihana unsurprised - our governing systems do not include all values]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JCE_PC nothing good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NapierinFrame fashion victims start young]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jgmccl @kumararepublic genuinely strong people do not need to pretend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LI_politico southern repugs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worldwide taonga threatened by dairying https://t.co/28cNVltbkK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@real_Deity great paint-stripper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NikkyD77 plus they will love you for it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenRoss_AKL @MariaSherwood2 no new policy also offered no easy targets for the usual suspects]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@plinythemidlkid @SarahLibrarina as it should be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reckonsemoji cool. have they visited us before?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reckonsemoji do they follow cricket back home?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@plinythemidlkid nup. got nothing reassuring to say, sorry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahLibrarina @plinythemidlkid @yonatanzunger @Medium check this https://t.co/Qy8VPLXj8b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kumararepublic @yonatanzunger pushback from some Repubs will be interesting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kumararepublic @yonatanzunger probing, calibrating, sussing out GOP house members ..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pv_reynolds @lancewiggs more about maintaining relationships than shipments]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pv_reynolds contains preening blonde, fulfilling editorial requirements]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbrislen they want to hire Andrea to run their PR, apparently]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lancewiggs yep, must help trade enormously]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1FightingIrish @kumararepublic @ScottBaio @AJemaineClement a plastic teaspoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tat_Loo @williamjordann @Gallup impeachments or assassinations do not consult polls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Steve Bannon is the Dick Cheney of the Trump administration https://t.co/TTyAee7Nh4 @carrasquillo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tat_Loo @williamjordann @Gallup who said they would? he will be gone by then anyway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Covlin @LI_politico onto it for such a nipper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbrislen @kumararepublic if anyone can do it ..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[State governments resisting federal fascism #chump https://t.co/0x00GYBhrB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More falling glass. Recent #eqnz didn't harm Welli office buildings much, eh https://t.co/C4oUi1VQHy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@writeonleah @NZNationalParty @pmbillenglish let's acknowledge the evidence and stop treating Bill as the boss. What does Joyce say?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AucklandIsland @real_Deity read with the rest, indeed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dovil Tat is 'CV' on te standard, so you know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shhh. Nobody tell Spicer about onions #chump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@webweaverToo thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@webweaverToo sounds awesome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LI_politico @Dovil @David_Cormack plus they lack diversity expertise cos Welli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@webweaverToo (not watching) where is match up to?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deborahjonesnz I've seen people saying it's obeying or defying judge's order]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interpret this response by Homeland Security to today's legal injunction https://t.co/RUcFUW6mx5 #chump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbrislen how I love the prospect of all those upraised fingers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tweetandtwig @BMHayward always is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s cronies are actually scared, and therefore defeatable https://t.co/IbHVaqvCub @NaomiAKlein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Madicattt and I want my tribe to take more responsibility]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Madicattt thank you. great points]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mizjwilliams @GregPresland @KeirLeslie @reedfleming @bootstheory quite. learn to have your spats behind closed doors, amateurs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephenStra not 'pungently', whatever that means]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kumararepublic @DavidYankovich internal satisfies fewer donors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Madicattt garner is bullshit, yes. Can we please get a capital P for Pãkehã like we do for Samoan or Korean or Somali?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GregPresland @reedfleming @thestandard yep, just keep it away from tomorrow's event - and preferably DMs not public Twitter #unity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxyLustyGrover @ChrisKeall never heard of another]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisKeall seems unlikely to cause any confusion #economic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reedfleming @GregPresland @thestandard bad faith argument, dude. no evidence they have ever done that, where's this coming from?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FranOSullivan @nzheraldbiz picturing same transparency as MBIE about grants, nothing more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FranOSullivan @nzheraldbiz eg: Thiel offers significant valuable influence in relevant networks. $$ not the primary thing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FranOSullivan @nzheraldbiz minimal if it was clear what the benefit to NZ was, surely]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Taroaroa @jgmccl nothing deliberate. reckon Bob Marley gig might fit the tone :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FranOSullivan @nzheraldbiz doubt it - and the lack of transparency is my issue, unlike some other folk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FranOSullivan @nzheraldbiz why not publish decisions if they're exceptions form normal rules?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arnie03 @FranOSullivan @nzheraldbiz someone like Thiel will never fit that criteria so I do get the need for exceptions. want transparency]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FranOSullivan @nzheraldbiz adds to pattern on here recently from others of conflating the two. wonder how many residents do become citizens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Taroaroa @jgmccl somehow I always feel more solitary than social on the day, it seems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jgmccl always been a reflective day for me. don't want to jeopardise that for no benefit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeeFaerie @NikkyD77 I prefer this position on it: https://t.co/wCQFXPGYfs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Misleading story https://t.co/eHQP8vjLQn - Investor Plus is a *residency* visa, not citizenship https://t.co/ZG3r6Ut0Ur @FranOSullivan]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>