<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[It's hard to believe that it's only Thursday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeIsaac How do you find out about people unfollowing you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@asadotzler Really appreciate the help!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@asadotzler Weird, I did the "refresh" and now it works like normal. No idea what the problem was.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@asadotzler I have not tweaked about:config recently. Any easy way to do a "factory reset" on those or see what I've changed?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@asadotzler Actually, they seem to not be loading at all. (Firefox on the left, Chrome on the right) https://t.co/pi3mS42AoQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@asadotzler Only add-on enabled is Recap. https://t.co/t5WsCseU1i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@asadotzler Example tweet: https://t.co/tryiNX11j6 https://t.co/u1s5typqEV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@binarybits @asadotzler Whereas in Chrome it shows up on top of the existing page.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@binarybits @asadotzler And clicking on a tweet embedded in another tweet causes a new page to open.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@asadotzler https://t.co/1ua401lRUi. Twitter cards seem to load slowly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@binarybits @pjdoland @brian_carnell It's not like I totally boycott leading products but I like to increase diversity at the margin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brian_carnell I try to avoid using popular products, and Chrome's market share is getting really high.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just started using Firefox for the first time in years. For some reason Twitter web client experience is much worse on Firefox.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jon_naz @mattyglesias More precisely, it would stop nutritionists from taking kickbacks from french fry makers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's argument *for* reversing the fiduciary rule is that it's like putting more unhealthy food on menus. https://t.co/DO3ROc4bji]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearSplenda OK, I think we're on the same page then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearSplenda Yes, I understand the concept. But under this logic people should be deleting Lyft too right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearSplenda How does paying drivers less encourage them to break the strike? That makes no sense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearSplenda You can say that they should have cancelled JFK pickups altogether, but Lyft didn't do that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearSplenda I don't understand what you mean by "using it." Disabling surge pricing likely meant fewer pickups.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@madjayhawk Random acts of violence are bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattSepara What makes you think he knew it was coming?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WillOremus I agree with you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoa how did no one tell me that there's a podcast that regularly features the @reihan experience? https://t.co/xR8vci3Lfg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ComradeVeidt @ddayen Is he talking about me or the protestors? It's not clear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Errorreporrt Scalia's Brand X dissent was great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shuls13 @voxdotcom @awprokop @DLind Guys, it's time for some game theory.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liberals are learning from the Tea Party. https://t.co/QCMaDiufKQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Scott_Radcliffe Yes, we will have to see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Scott_Radcliffe Sasse has said a lot of stuff. Has he cast any anti-Trump votes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@moral_hazard @mattyglesias I think both parties will wind up more polarized than they were in 2009.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dchetson @mattyglesias And partisan polarization makes it less likely Congress can stop Trump from starting a war.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CalebWatney I think it's a rounding error, but at the margin it probably makes governance worse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Scott_Radcliffe And Democrats are under pressure to obstruct everything Trump does, "overreach" or not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Scott_Radcliffe But Republicans are sticking by their guy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Scott_Radcliffe If *Republicans* start pushing back against executive overreach, that would be a positive sign.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Scott_Radcliffe No, that is not the argument.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattyglesias I thought that before the election, but I underestimated how much Trump would galvanize liberals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is causing the left to organize like the Tea Party, making the democracy-is-doomed case ever more convincing. https://t.co/haNdiEwwLV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mims @JasonKuznicki I assume he means it gives the Trump administration a ton of power.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This was hard to read. https://t.co/1oSsuaSeUK https://t.co/2zlBdqCTcP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Republican party has changed a lot in the last 16 years. https://t.co/Rmmf5HDNJi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattSepara You should just pin this tweet for the next 4 years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think it would be bad for the US military to invade Mexico. https://t.co/DDExm6BMex https://t.co/IKV0QDefVJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@apblake @ErrataRob Right, I don't understand why the protestors would think that was better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ErrataRob That is nutty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did Lyft change its policy about JFK pickups during this weekend's protests?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bergmayer Seems like that could work both ways. Maybe an agency is stuck with its first interpretation until Congress acts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bergmayer Immigration law seems equally bizarre if the Gutierrez-Brizuela case is any indication.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bergmayer It seems more problematic to allow agencies to reverse themselves or the courts based on policy concerns.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bergmayer It's one thing to say courts should follow an agency's lead the first time an issue comes up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bergmayer One thing that concerns me here is the low threshold for agencies to change their minds and/or over-rule courts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bergmayer But it seems to me that letting the FCC decide has created a lot of mischief.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bergmayer My view on this is heavily colored by Brand X for obvious reasons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So far I'm finding Judge Gorsuch's case for Chevron skepticism pretty persuasive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alittlelilypad @germanrlopez That is my view for sure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jacobgrier yes, that seems to be the majority position.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a bitter feud over coffee flavors going on at the Vox Media DC office right now. French vanilla partisans are on the defensive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lee_Ars The high priority button is an anti-signal. I've never received a high-priority email that was actually high priority.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be fair, Douglass did do an amazing job. https://t.co/zJMo2G58ZR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CommonplaceBiz But opposition to Chevron deference could also cause him to be an unpredictable swing vote.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CommonplaceBiz I have no idea. Maybe he'll be the lone dissenter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Though admittedly this is the outcome Justice Scalia wanted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going to laugh if Justice Gorsuch eliminates Chevron deference and then the courts rule that broadband is a Title II service.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The tech sector is mobilizing against Trump's immigration order. The Chamber of Commerce? Not so much. https://t.co/1fB4KZl8Ys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People and dinosaurs are shown to scale." https://t.co/zreUXAwMD4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRogue_Elf @voxdotcom I am confused. My article doesn't mention Buzzfeed and I'm not sure what you're talking about.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the other hand, "I don't impose my own values, I just follow the law as written" is the way to get confirmed by a polarized Senate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obviously judges should follow the law when it's clear. But the law is full of phrases that are ambiguous or ask judges for value judgments.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge Gorsuch's 2016 CWRU lecture seems substantively vacuous but politically astute. https://t.co/xE4chWrNbE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@catlin201 It is a good reason to write a snarky tweet though!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@catlin201 There are many highly qualified lawyers who aren't appellate judges with JDs from Harvard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh good a Harvard guy. That's what the Supreme Court needs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@madjayhawk how's that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gojomo yes. I mean it is jarring to be compared to turkey at all in this context.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Chamber of Commerce doesn't seem concerned about Trump's immigration order. https://t.co/byyuITZ6Sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vikrum5000 @hyperplanes Wow. I assume they didn't actually draft a lot of 60-year-olds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarketUrbanism right it's a stupid study.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prediction: trump names Kanye to Supreme Court to neutralize a potential 2020 rival.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarketUrbanism Other "IP-intensive" industries: wood products, footware manufacturing, dairy products, beverages.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarketUrbanism "KB Home" is a trademark, for example.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most of the "IP-intensive" industries are ones that rely on trademarks, like grocery stores and residential construction.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I debunked the claim that 40 million jobs are "IP intensive" in 2012. https://t.co/kzsqw4Ki1f It won't die. https://t.co/8GEpBZeI0n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See? Trump is totally normal. https://t.co/tijbAhYES5 https://t.co/BH5aESLLKH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the key paragraph of Dell's statement. He favors "immigration reform" but doesn't specifically say he oppos… https://t.co/mWNcnItGpI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I asked Dell about their position on Trump's immigration order. Here's their response. https://t.co/gSz77tDQ74]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jobead The Obama version was the same way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattbraga Where does the link go?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hyperplanes Like a botched FEMA operation that gets thousands killed, for example.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hyperplanes I'm imagining something worse than ordinary corruption or incompetence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hyperplanes Though in that case maybe the public rallies around the president. Ugh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hyperplanes Or we could have like a war with China whose awfulness would be impossible to deny.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hyperplanes I think there could be a "heck of a job" / "mission accomplished" type moment that galvanizes public opinion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's becoming clear that Republican lawmakers won't defect from Trump until he commits a massive blunder that hurts a lot of white people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rachelbotsman Hi, are you free for an interview? If so please email tim@vox.com. Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahjeong Does that make someone more or less in a bubble than not knowing someone with a pickup truck?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It really seems like we're living through the later seasons of a poorly-written political drama. These characters a… https://t.co/EkJ9CPOGVv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cqwww There's lots I can learn about the topic before the actual order comes out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who should I be talking to about Trump's rumored H1-B moves and its effects on business and particularly Silicon Valley?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>