<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@joepike @GordonAikman he has been an inspiration to us all with the way he led his life. Thoughts with you and the family.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RuthDavidsonMSP @joepike really sorry to hear that, he was a fine man with a good soul. An example to us all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's been a while.... https://t.co/ti2lHEXZWt via @wave gardened #Ratho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@0604Arb1320 @JohnnyDundee @joe90kane i thought it was another picture release of pitch invaders from @policescotland ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when you see tweets from people saying  Rebecca Long-Bailey was impressive on #bbcqt https://t.co/8SWAd7DsEQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#englishdream Labour dont even try with Scotland anymore. games a bogey. #bbcqt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[another #brexit nutter confirms why they voted to leave. #bbcqt https://t.co/gQV8CUec86]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[christ on a bike. #straightbananas #bbcqt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jpt1965 @CollectCelticFC meh as Meatloaf sang " 2 out of 3 ain't bad!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mstewart_23 no doubt some ex Rangers player would have picked him  to appease the hordes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Nicholas Soames MP 'woofs' at Tasmina Ahmed-Sheikh MP https://t.co/eeWpmpq3en]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCGaryR can just imagine you warming up the voice box the now getting ready to say fratricidal for the first time on the radio. 😄]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrMalky @tartanthing ya bunch of #fratricidal maniacs that you are! #indyref2 #youyesyet ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ruth Davidson #fratricide #jumpedtheshark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love the smell of #fratricide in the morning. #indyref2 #youyesyet ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the dead of the night - https://t.co/DwIeDqy6TS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCNewsnight @feministfox as in @bbcquestiontime "roughly equal"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GAPonsonby @Jenemm3 she is obsessed with army and militaria. just look at her photo ops and content of speeches.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Record_Sport @Daily_Record a swoop under the radar for a highly rated wonderkid wanted by a number of top Premier League clubs?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MSmithsonPB Not even pretending to hide your Libdem roots now Mike.  poor show.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edinburghsport Fantastic news.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WinstonIngram @tedermeatballs @scotsunsport @Arsenal @RangersFC @ChelseaFC almost as if He is doing cold calling sales for them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#SilentWitness becoming unwatchable. terrible series in general.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What will @RuthDavidsonMSP opinion on #brexit be today? #flipflopper https://t.co/cbJDT66p9I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UKGovScotland overtime bill getting bigger than the leccy bill at the Colonnial HQ #gettingawaywithit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@al_duncan @SteveArchibald8 thats an assault, never mind a penalty!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MeanwhileScotia @Alasdair91 we always knew that he was a ...... https://t.co/FXV8TQproC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time catches up with us all - https://t.co/NiNNQL0B5s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Willie Rennie says he loves himself. Confirming to all why we do the coffee bean shake whenever we see him on tv. #scotdp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[lol, Willie Rennie threatwning another election. #bless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doesnt #TheresaMay look tired?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still going well for you @murdo_fraser ? https://t.co/o8FAmjg0FI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[smug Tory line that the #theresamay trip had been such a success now falling apart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tambritton what channel is that on?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tynie_1874 @fezz1874 @Wan27 @John_Fettes is he any better than Jamie "tom daley" Walker?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealMacKaySTV thats bordering on Teal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sparkle__Monkey seen a few dodgy reviews, definately worth going?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Call the experts - https://t.co/GKteNmsk0o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I #ScrumTogether with @DoveMen to win #SCOvIRE RBS 6 Nations tickets. Pick your match by 8pm &amp; you could too https://t.co/nPxZhimmRP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamieRoss7 can you make sure Dan Snow gets this memo?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so that right wing, Tory voting, leave voter "comedian" has so far also told us he is working class and normal. Who knew? #bbcqt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[loving the love from our friends and equal partners in this family of nations. #bbcqt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[aye No voters, hope you are enjoying #bbcqt tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rafadont dont forget the army, Ruth never forgets the army.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[why does #bbcqt bring on these "comedians"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama loved UK. he told us at #indyref we should vote No. #bbcqt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dimbleby really cant help himself interrupting every Snp representative on the panel. #bbcqt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tim Stanley telling us what May will tell Trump in private. #ayeright #newsnight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScotlandStewart @ScottishFA @EuroQualifiers do we get to know how much for or if BBC or STV even made bid?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fezz1874 @Tynie_1874 @Wan27 @John_Fettes 2-0 and you furked it up. Ding ding. Here we go, 2 in a row. #ggtth https://t.co/XKA1VpOiob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@John_Fettes @Tynie_1874 @fezz1874 @Wan27 @adriandevlin Sit back and reflect on how the game should be played with… https://t.co/O8pUuegI1y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexmassie after the retraction is yours now an alternative commentary?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ladbrokes must be a highly rated wonderkid with a string of top European clubs after him?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[interesting that the only critics of @AngusRobertson at #pmqs are from Yoons. Clear he is more effective and respected than Corbyn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UKGovScotland @scotgov your Scottish Secretary confirmed its not his job to defend Scotland.  #gettingawaywithit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While the truth gets its boots on - https://t.co/XhO9lsTc3a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexmassie but Malta can veto something they dont want the EU to do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarrylBroadfoot @kmckenna63 dinny tell Darryl the price of the tickets, might get ideas for the game against Canada at Easter Road.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this series of #silentwitness is really poor.  past its sell by date.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chicgibson apparently you get 30% of any McGinn transfer.  Drinks on you end of season!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey check this out https://t.co/U2YjH1ZlW1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chicgibson How much for Mallan? .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Vow was a lie https://t.co/2Oxmh2eh3T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pwmcomms how many years without a win in any round of the Scottish cup is that for them now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FraserNelson is Scotland an equal partner in this United Kingdom or a region like Kent?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boris Johnson  can decide on Scotlands future in Europe whilst Scottish government can't. #devolutionisanillusion #indyref2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Devolution is an Illusion.  #supremecourt #indyref2 #youyesyet ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleyfeinberg @ScotsFootyCards when he came to Scotland, we had a plan... https://t.co/GGVcP0SHp8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@akmaciver although I thought UK gov "clean Brexit" seemed to gain some traction last week?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScotsFootyCards had the battenburg leisure shirt and white shell suit with me to Magaluf that year. Got Locked  in pub as English rioted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Edinburgh trams ‘continuing to perform ahead of expectations’ https://t.co/hPNYHBg8nN  Contradicts Scottish Tories lies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrsanderzisin dont understand this, @afneil stated this was wrong yesterday?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kenny_Millar here we go, two in a row......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FamousFive1875 that's what we are all hoping!  Bring on cup loser Andy Halliday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[why do @BBCSportsound persist on commentating from a quiet studio on Rangers matches? should simply ignore till clubs petulance is over.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[major point not really addressed is that Status Quo argued for before,no longer the same.Loyalty to British state c… https://t.co/Hey3H1Lvcx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To win #indyref2 we must understand and learn more about the other side. interesting thoughts from @blairmcdougall… https://t.co/WNFzKYbR6H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this.  epitomises #indyref in 10 minutes of video. #imperialmasters https://t.co/gFcWMVXQeU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@offtheballbbc the brave Motherwell players doing all they can for the club. https://t.co/yF925sxhRT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@STVEdinburgh Ratho Station, not Ratho, different village.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WinstonIngram German press wil be saying that Leipzig swooped for a highly rated ,sought after wonderkid, beating a string of top clubs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christ on a bike. Britnat lovenest on #bbcqt we need tomget the hell out of this.  play this on repeat during #indyref2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carmichael the Liar laughing with the britnat chums about Scotland having another #indyref. horrendous individual. #bbcqt #indyref2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UKGovScotland history will not look kindly on Mundell and Scottish office. #lastdaysoftheraj #gettingawaywithit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new lie - https://t.co/fHsLWxxwOZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you really have raised the bar with this #brexit supporting doughnut. #scotnight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScotlandSky @SkySports but, but, I thought Andy Halliday won the cup???? #ggtth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating court proceedings on a punters claim for £500k vs @Coral reported on  @jamesdoleman timeline just now.  #bettingexperts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The competition - https://t.co/6aLj82UoKP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JimFairlie @MillerMattu do the dutch, germans,italians etc think they are not Independant. argue your case once we get to that stage,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JimFairlie @MillerMattu get our indy then argue the case about EU continued meembership. jim, your stance will only hinder what we all want]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WingsScotland cracking mention for you on the Hootsmans own documentary. they must be pure raging! #thepaperthistle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[oh my. just diid a big GIRFUY with @WingsScotland site views being cited against falling Hootsman circulation. #thepaperthistle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesdoleman bloody hell, so if you have an Irish name you are anti Rangers, is that what was just said?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RossMcCaff Ian Murray. without office, now an ostracised lame duck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexmassie c'mon Alex, #indyref2 time to talk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jelle_simons @PiratesForIndy not all UK. scotland is with Europe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@faisalislam any mention of Scotgov proposal?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C'mon the @dallascowboys #FinishThisFight and set us up to be those Dirty Birds @AtlantaFalcons in the Division championship]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tynie_1874 @jamesbseaton1 @fezz1874 @Wan27 @John_Fettes its a glorified bus shelter full of tramps.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>