<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Received the books yesterday, so excited to add to Library collection #tlchat #educationmatters https://t.co/Ur9DLE9uPb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Students quickly introduced to wide range of reading material. Will do Musical Chairs with books for Yr 3, 4 &amp; 5 (11 classes total) Cool!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Each chair had a book related to Reading Challenge we danced to Bollywood music, when music stopped one minute of viewing book.  #tlchat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[25 Ideas to Motivate Young Readers https://t.co/0z9oTnNiV2 via @education_world I did musical chairs today to intro new reading challenge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @clpe1 this is outstanding! #schoolibrary #tlchat https://t.co/3aNXS2XSkR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Refugee Experience Booklist CLPE https://t.co/xy0To9f4Ot Thank you   valuable school library book recommendations #schoollibraries #reading]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonderful to receive This is Banjo Paterson today, a must for the school library https://t.co/iDC8byaUqt @TaniaMcCartney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So good to have copies of new History Mysteries series by Mark Greenwood ready for Term 1 https:// https://t.co/gaVHd69irP @PenguinKidsAus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perfect achievable advice for teacher librarians, thank you @schoolscatinfo &amp; @aasl  #futurelib leading the way. https://t.co/r7J65YR88j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @MikeReading a great overview, appreciate the sharing #edtech https://t.co/R6cuzoDgop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for Biographies for children - I have a few books to share via https://t.co/vgF6slfOaj #education @Pinterest https://t.co/pWP7vVgjJx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thinking about the Internet: how to introduce a series of search skill lessons to upper primary https://t.co/QSKNFXYe8R
#edtech #education]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sounds like the place to be! https://t.co/zJpRpaxiJ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know Book Week @TheCBCA @CBCANSW was some time ago but Yr 2 created dioramas for shortlist and they were amazing!… https://t.co/lBy3en56K5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fab list! Loved reading 'No Way Yirrikipayi' to Yr K, children joined in, so much fun. https://t.co/DQwviofMxg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2017 Poster https://t.co/dnpjWaq4Hn via  Just added the poster to the School Library Homepage - superb! Thank you @bookgivingday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Library book returned a century late in San Francisco https://t.co/cSyB2yfxo5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I relax I browse my Book Interest Pins https://t.co/BhRHoNp13n @Pinterest #libraries #ChildrensBooks #booklover]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My result - Mrs Tiggy-Winkle the hedgehog! Care a lot about working hard at everything you do but always find time… https://t.co/t3PIJfaik8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such fun - Which Beatrix Potter character are you? quiz @guardian https://t.co/ZLNE4OrRS9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GabrielleWang Dear Gabrielle, a poster to promote/acknowledge Chinese NY would be ideal for library display I will keep following for tips]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New - Peter Pan display at my school library #libraries https://t.co/ic0A77ChZE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Visit to my school library today, books look neat waiting for the students to borrow. Updating suggested reading &amp; new reading challenge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delightful &amp; good advice! Do you have a poster @GabrielleWang for school library use? https://t.co/9uI6lqwQew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow! Just joined ACER library - looking forward to exploring &amp; keeping up to date thanks @acereduau #libraries https://t.co/bHtapqfzWm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top Picks for Connecting the Classroom and Real World https://t.co/sBrLrWZCmL via @CommonSenseEd #edtech]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @Lynch39083 this is really helpful! https://t.co/vPH0c0jOMO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Relationship between literary elements and verbal/visual details in picture books https://t.co/xZMTaWV8fU https://t.co/IMvtyaIiZD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TOUCH this image: Visual/verbal ideas from 'The Red Bridge' by Kylie Dunstan https://t.co/HwwMj6Vf36]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read, Think, Create! Step Inside - Visible Thinking Routine with picture books https://t.co/F0OgSCOxGs https://t.co/hQuPYbMwMu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you, love this! https://t.co/HiPCmq9408]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the year ahead holds for readers https://t.co/ScLsCGiDjD via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[20 ways to use a tablet in the classroom https://t.co/qomiueG3Vp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to be happy: a guide for teachers (and everyone else) https://t.co/empsItOWS7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @AskATechTeacher for insight &amp; useful tips #edtech https://t.co/liZONWauZr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choice Boards Literature - a superb resource to add to our school library 'Reading Challenge https://t.co/Rx0qlSnwIb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Things Every Teacher Should Know Before Starting Their First Day In The Classroom https://t.co/12kr8xTErj via @shaunkillian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ready for a wonderful learning journey for the school year ahead. https://t.co/epkyXDbHEy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thankyou @leecrockett   Good reading for school preparation 2017! https://t.co/M7Bka0Fj8K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @HarperCollinsAU just put  both books mentioned in your Tweet on my 'to read' list https://t.co/EZktil5adM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jasper Jones - Official Trailer https://t.co/ZxjkSTvy2y look forward to the release in 2 March]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glad I revisited this - planning for the year ahead 
Top 10 Evidence Based Teaching Strategies https://t.co/OjA8PzDSaB via @shaunkillian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It has been a while since I visited Diigo @diigo - very impressed to see Outliner https://t.co/HStDACFq9F  plans for me to brush-up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonderful visit to @ReadingsBooks in St Kilda, have been using the site https://t.co/7g7MsROFdy for reviews and reading stimulation Superb!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this video from @CommonCraft, it explains Digital Literacy - https://t.co/IyPyEK5SDR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this video from @CommonCraft, it explains Web Search Strategies - https://t.co/DHBWHbzUaz Great for younger students search lesson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Best Beak in Boonaroo Bay by Narrlle Oliver was handed to Yr 5 this week as the best literature for bird adapta… https://t.co/yUdw1q4NSt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great ideas, links well with behaviour management &amp; positive classroom environment. Thanks! https://t.co/VXIAlMgoBP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Stella Prize books have kept me in touch with current Australian literature, the reading journeys has been superb @TheStellaPrize]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a great idea! https://t.co/tJq0rZZFo1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A superb book to read &amp; explore creativity, growth mindset and lead into STEM activities.  https://t.co/oZAl0gE29B https://t.co/tjlMQnnI9x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Revisited some old Tweets &amp; very glad to go back to this article, helpful in plans for information literacy lessons… https://t.co/fegqBJ3mmN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A must for my School Library so glad @ScholasticAUS sent me a copy of Crinkling News @crinklingnewsau  https://t.co/mrXCqwpy3y cool website!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @statelibrarynsw interesting &amp; userfriendly unit for Library sessions. Will compliment Yr 4 Geography https://t.co/w2QHX39dSM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Received Black Rock White City by A. S. Patrić today, looking forward to the reading journey ahead.@_milesfranklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Step Inside The Character with Year 1 and @TheCBCA shortlist. https://t.co/aZs9iPLZgb @cbcansw https://t.co/dRiSqYMkzo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian Curriculum Digital Technologies https://t.co/ozsJUpdDn2 looking forward to exploring #edtech]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @anthsperanza for directing me to Hello Ruby https://t.co/UgVFtkeNBx a must for the School Library and gr… https://t.co/Qe1bmjzyLA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mind the (Digital Technologies) gap https://t.co/OQcfqBWTvN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @BCNAPinkLady for an informative &amp; inspiring day! I understand more now - big picture &amp; personal travels. Many take aways...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to use search like a pro: 10 tips and tricks for Google and beyond https://t.co/L60UAuBu8V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Google Like A Pro! Top 10 Google Search Tips &amp; Tricks https://t.co/3a1MHZlZIR via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tgaletti thanks Tanja, that makes sense. I will follow a similar plan. So many great Alison Lester books to use. All the best, Josephine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tgaletti was the class familiar with inquiry process I am planning on looking at story elements for AL but keen on inquiry process approach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tgaletti Hello Tanja, I have been looking at your inquiry into Alison Lester with Yr 1, very interested in finding out more, looks great!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That is some Library! https://t.co/NKDhiutj6x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New display at my School Library https://t.co/MSRYyJSsTP … Thank you @_IanFalconer @SimonSchuster @SimonSchusterAU https://t.co/CiegWv1G3k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The URL Game a great way to teach students online search skills. https://t.co/pvQldLl1w5  #edtech #edtechchat https://t.co/O5ZM9Jefba]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OLIVIA new display at my School Library. https://t.co/UOhSFYsMiA via @pinterest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fab! This will become part of my online search lesson series - relevant &amp; easy to remember. Thanks https://t.co/q2gHquLlbd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walker Books - A Child of Books https://t.co/XwE8ELWlQI via @pinterest Book received today and added to Books about Books &amp; Libraries]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exploring Colour Symbol Image Thinking Routine through Picture Books. Year 3 responses to CSI shortlist @TheCBCA https://t.co/wQr0qIdFTd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Memories of my casual teaching bag early 1990's the book is still in high use and so relevant the shock so important https://t.co/BaQv5hpwnP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to Jeannie Baker made me slow down and reflect I became deeply aware of her creativity and the importance of her books @Sydney_Uni]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superb time spent last night: University of Sydney Artist in Residence Jeannie Baker in conversation with Professor Robyn Ewing @Sydney_Uni]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Held 'The Great Book Swap' for teachers this arvo as part of staff meeting. Four Swap sessions planned for next week K-6  @IndigenousLF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Tidy' was a very special book to read to children (as are all Emily Gravett's  books) wish I was there! https://t.co/nAJmYkFIOf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, this was fun to read, I like getting rid of stuff... https://t.co/vK8lE2w4bb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This really did shock Yr 5 https://t.co/PkCR3dfsUP they were born the year YouTube 2005 or Twitter 2006 was launched.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting comments Yr 5 what their parents use WWW for &amp; because they missed out when they were young - making up for it now big time!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Year 5 found https://t.co/sNm6CdOv6p amazing, they were born in 2005/6! A Infographic of the Internet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great site that you can see students think is cool is ‘In one second on the Internet there are..’ https://t.co/UjcntKM5LJ @airguitarbandit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great discussion on difference between the Internet and WWW with Yr 5. Light bulb moment when students considered what came first.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History of computers: used this over past years as intro to search skills lessons, still a hit with Yr 5 https://t.co/BXh4uv2EkR @ABCSplash]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/PkCR3dfsUP 
Another great info graphic on the History of the Web]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The History of the Internet | @scoopit https://t.co/EzjFen5e7a
This is terrific, but I need more up to date - anyone able to help?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The evolution of the web | @scoopit https://t.co/sHymcE7OCi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Visual History of Internet Firsts [Infographic] | @scoopit https://t.co/ZDKQsXfmUo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Miles Franklin Literary Award: A.S. Patrić wins for debut novel Black Rock White City https://t.co/nzR0f48yAs via @abcnews not read yet...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good advice for expert TL's too, focus and refocus to make a difference. https://t.co/JJBC6Ujxxj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is timely as I am about to start search skills with Yr 5 - great focus, thanks. https://t.co/dxuNtWTIxR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pin on Pinterest... https://t.co/3JCSjBldi9 hmm new project in waiting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonder what I would do without books? Hold memories close of childhood visits to the local library - must have sparked something in me...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Book Week lives on..Yr 3 Colour Symbol Image, Yr 4 Step Inside the character. Finalised Yr 5 promo posters @TheCBCA #BookWeek2016  @CBCANSW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Book Week will be with me for a while started this week Yr K character bunting, Yr 1 crayon resist character designs, Yr 2 book dioramas...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wish I was in WA to go to this...https://t.co/iLO4TxXlUx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Books standing proud on displsy at a  new women's / children's shop. Books make me feel good. https://t.co/nrx9tp2jZq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you, another good thing about today! Yes Librarians do have super powers... https://t.co/jxy7YlzsXy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shared The Croc &amp; the Platypus read by @andrewjhansen on @StoryBoxLibrary Book Week K-2 Assembly. Perfect  Australia! Story Country @TheCBCA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superb visit from Emma Quay for K-2, she shared drawings from her childhood and read to the children her delightful stories.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>