<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@CHRTB_ Thanks! I've sent them a message. If I hear anything back I'll let you know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CHRTB_ I will. Jockey Club of Canada? To be honest, I think she should not only be nominated but that she would win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CHRTB_ pix:1VictorytoVictory2King&amp;HisCourt3Caren4AmisGizmo 5MidnightMiley6AreyouKiddingme7LexieLou8GlenvilleGardens9PassionforAction10Casse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CHRTB_ - Why isn't Lexie Lou up for Champion Older Female in Canada? What am I missing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heyitsashlyg @santaanitapark - WPS on the 9 in the 9th.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CHRTB_ Ami's Gizmo, Glenville Gardens, Sir Dudley Digges all have a solid 2016 resume. Great year for Canadian horseracing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CHRTB_ @ONTRacing - these horses are not all in one category...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@racetrackandy @DRFInsidePost - Good, it was totally useless. Woodbine operates with very low profit margins, they have to stay lean to earn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonmorosi @MLB @MLBNetwork Current #Indians players, including Edwin making &gt; $10M per season: 2. Current #BlueJays, including Morales: 7.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@racetrackandy @DRFInsidePost - IMO Ellis likely knows the horse will still test positive &amp; his back story is bull and this is just optics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@racetrackandy @DRFInsidePost "...Masochistic was tested on Monday and that results will not be available until Friday." Why test so late?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HayesTSN Ken Pagan: Toronto's Steve Bartman. What the hell was he thinking wasting that beer? And, what's life like living in the gutter?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimeformUSfigs Craig, am I missing something? She'll be bred as a 2 year old and foal as a 3 year old...is she even fully grown?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think @MikeRichards01 &amp; @DavidBastl triumphant return should include the 2017 premiere of "As the Leafs Turn"...a… https://t.co/bzjjQYe4Ft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonahkeri Does Mark Shapiro look more like a retired Skeletor living in Miami or the wrestler Sid Vicious off the juice?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonmorosi @MLBNetwork Famous words: "I'm not going to sit here &amp; try &amp; bargain for a couple of dollars."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OverDrive1050 @Wrangler @HayesTSN @odognine2 Hey @jamiemclennan29 you're looking slick with the no-belt tuck! Well played...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gregorMLB any chance the Jays go after Cutch? They need a bat in the lineup and desperately need a quality outfielder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ken_Rosenthal would the #Jays try to land McCutchen? Trade package potentially starts with Greene &amp; Alford? Stroman?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just thinking aloud...but how is it possible geldings are sold at a breeding stock sale? @BeemieAwards @raypaulick @chare889 @BloodHorse ???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShiDavidi Smoak will be the everyday 1st baseman?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@racetrackandy what about attendance? Watching all the way from Toronto it looked empty especially compared to last year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OverDrive1050 Ken Pagan wins 2016 City of Toronto Mayor's Community Safety Award #FutureHeadlines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffPassan Nice to meet them. Question is, have you introduced them to Mom and Dad yet? #LoveAtFirstSight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @Wilnerness590 if Estrada isn't getting it done how quickly does Gibby yank him?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamToddyTickles @benminer @BlueJays @MikeRichards01 @HayesTSN Here's @Indians @BauerOutage Twitter page after an I… https://t.co/3V2cwyHP2a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BauerOutage LOL. Gotta be honest, you're a funny guy. I'll never cheer for you at a ballpark but I respect the tro… https://t.co/IFkUNNIskL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BauerOutage @SheilaHash @iamToddyTickles played, yes. 2 BBs in 2/3 IP...played poorly. Taking you out saved the Indians! #thankthedrone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BauerOutage  -----&gt; "Laughs At His Own Jokes Guy"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamToddyTickles Nobody relies on their TEAM more than @BauerOutage! 2016 Postseason: 5.1 IP 1.50 WHIP 5.06 ERA 2 HRs. #bigmouthlittlegame]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamToddyTickles not only does @BauerOutage need his teammates to win games for him, he needs fans like @KeithRBelcher to troll for him too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @BauerOutage great outing last night! You really put in a solid 2/3 IP to earn the W! Saw this &amp; thought of you: https://t.co/7GVXWss9Jv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey #Indians @BauerOutage I feel 100% exactly the same way right now. Well done Pinky! #GoJaysGo  #Jays https://t.co/Uucnz1LG4x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Drew31Rico @BauerOutage funny when someone says "you should try being a big leaguer someday" and is still learning the process 4 years in..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Drew31Rico you are never going to win a baseball game with stitches in your finger either. Well done @BauerOutage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BauerOutage 19 innings, what a game! Carapazza's top-notch ump show almost stole the limelight! Be honest tho, you loved 2015 vs the Jays!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BauerOutage - LOL. It looks like a lot of fun. Did you learn to have this much fun from JJ Putz and Miguel Montero in Arizona?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @BauerOutage I have a couple of questions. What's it like to have a career 4.42 ERA? Also, how does it feel giving up 20+ homers a year?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You ever seen anyone more disappointed than this guy? @HayesTSN @odognine2 @jamiemclennan29 https://t.co/UFrYGCPJmK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HayesTSN - Will I be accepted or beaten up if I dress up as Ken Pagan for Halloween?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check this guy's basement already. @HayesTSN @odognine2 @jamiemclennan29 https://t.co/dNDnOXiFk8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffPassan - any substance to idea Anthopoulos passed on Twins job to clear path for Tony Lacava? Cherington hire seems pro-active by Jays]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @keithlaw - Jays feeling heat for decision to move Sanchez to pen because of IP limit. Marlins have limit for Fernandez and that's ok?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @jonahkeri can you explain why it's okay for the Marlins to put an IP limit on Fernandez but not the Jays for Sanchez? Both in WC spot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @JimBowden_ESPN if you think the Jays putting an IP limit on Sanchez is "terrible" then how come it's okay for the Marlins &amp; Fernandez?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hey @jonahkeri apparently it may be the other way around per @ShiDavidi - thoughts?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeRichardsTSN @ING @TSN1050Radio @TSN_Sports - Joey Crawford would be proud.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SmithRaps pretty decent of the Raps to give Kyrie and the Cavs a break there...worst timeout ever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HayesTSN @odognine2 @jamiemclennan29 - every time I hear RAD interviewed I immediately think he's been Tunsiling in the clubhouse...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SmithRaps - Joseph needs to come off of the floor. He's all over the place on the defensive end]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hoping the @Raptors roll to a victory tonight. Who's ready? @SmithRaps @MikeRichardsTSN @HayesTSN @odognine2 https://t.co/sqN7rsFPMJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@liamdbenson - fields of 7 and 5 respectively are the smallest of any prep races.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@liamdbenson - Size of the crowds isn't the concern, it's the size of the field for Lani. Coming off races with much more room to navigate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeRichardsTSN @TSN1050Radio @TSN_Sports @torontomike @GinoRedaTSN @CTVCanadaAM @CP24Breakfast Question is where's the party bus?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeRichardsTSN @TSN_Sports @newstalk1010 @CTVCanadaAM This bus should be rolled out by @TTChelps on Friday afternoons for my commute home]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeRichardsTSN @TSN1050Radio @TSN_Sports it makes no difference if he knew or not. Can't be willfully blind &amp; then cry about it after.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CHRTB_ @TripleDeadHeat @HplayersAssnNA now THIS is what I'm talking about...4 days and counting! https://t.co/lSPtFidjKM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeafsLunch1050 @HayesTSN @odognine2 the NHL isn't going to reward a basement team like the Leafs with the Winter Classic #onlywinners]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @DanonymousMan is right then I'm totally off on Race 1 at Santa Anita. Wouldn't be the 1st time though. 13-7-10.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somebody please tell me who exactly is being attacked? #OregonUnderAttack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonmorosi Lee needs to be "perfect" for Lee to pitch in 2016.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeRichardsTSN @HayesTSN never seen so many players on both sides with arms in the air chasing calls. Canada playing to the Fins game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SmithRaps Raptors are getting the "Raptors" treatment from the Refs. Good thing is so are the Bulls. #consistent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SmithRaps Lowry needs to lose the All-Star attitude. It only gets worse as the season goes on &amp; he keeps jawing at the refs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BloodHorse: Records, Handle Growth for Woodbine in 2015 https://t.co/BDTfySH1OI @racetrackandy pay for the Tapeta &amp; lower the '16 takeouts?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Message to Dwayne Casey #freeJamesJohnson @Raptors @LeoRautins @Matt__Devlin @SmithRaps @raptorsrepublic @RaptorsHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeoRautins then the Raps would only have 2 quarters to catch up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally, @Raptors take Ross out of the game. Results in immediate improvement, down by just 2. #TRossgotstogo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heyitsashlyg you are awesome! Go Raps!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonahkeri @ElliottPrice690 same with @davidbastl who has been awesome with @MikeRichardsTSN , All about shareholders, not the listeners]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fadoobobcat @richarddeitsch @jonmorosi best radio I've heard in a long time #killingthedrivehome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richarddeitsch @FAN590 @FadooBobcat the best and maybe most telling thing about Bob, following 0 people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HayesTSN my 3 year old won't wear his costume, I'm gonna tell folks he's the Leafs and they need to lower their expectations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to @casseracingnc on a huge Breeders Cup win with Tepin!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How awesome is that for @MelnykEugene. #BreedersCup 
https://t.co/2CA4VBJiep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SimonTVG @heyitsashlyg not for sprints. And, only 10 runners in Race 3 with the two outside certainly the top class of the field.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@racetrackandy @Equinometry I only had a $5 WPS but I hit it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sticking with Mark Casse, @casseracingnc in the @BreedersCup Juvenile Fillies Turf betting Catch a Glimpse to Win. Going 4,9/10 Exacta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Betting a Mark Casse, @casseracingnc 1-2 in the @BreedersCup Juvenile Turf today. Airoforce and @ConquestStables Conquest Daddyo boxed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jensblog @BreedersCup @racetrackandy @TripleDeadHeat @CHRTB_ you're saying that @WoodbineRacing must fleece local players? This is BS!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TripleDeadHeat @CHRTB_ @jensblog @WoodbineBratt @racetrackandy When the sport dies in Ontario, we'll know why! 

https://t.co/DERRgsnaMt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichEng4ProPick Players are fed up with @WoodbineRacing, this is what we live with all year for local pools tool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeRichardsTSN AA: 'Can't believe they hired Shapiro...I'm gonna trade all the guys I drafted &amp; get the F out!' https://t.co/EhrhW18jpt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexmarvez @buffalobills how about releasing Fred Jackson? McCoy looks just as bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimcramer how low will $EMR go? Whens good to get in? 1 of the best dividend plays out there amid major restructuring right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichEng4ProPick #DavidPrice #Royals Bautista just answered your question with that missile #batflip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimeformUSfigs why doesn't Breeders Cup officials have an eye on all days, including Sunday, leading up to the 30th?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@racetrackandy @raypaulick @TbredOwnersofCA @NickCoukos  what's your issue exactly?! What are you getting at?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darrenrovell @WilliamHillUS same bet in Ontario pays only $2000. @playolg has worst payouts anywhere in North America]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeRichardsTSN @belfourhappyhr your cologne is bothering the other guys on the bench. I agree, you smell like you play...like shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greyhoundchan all @RichEng4ProPick does is make money lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darrenrovell show us at 09:00 PST. @williamhillus still has plenty of time to place own large wagers on, say, under bets and mitigate risk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope @Marlins_Man has his passport ready, Toronto is going to get crazy this week #BlueJays]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richarddeitsch @jimrome Rodriguez is the definition of likes to fight guy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simmonssteve @Real_ESPNLeBrun reminds me of a certain Quebec city's fans booing the US National Anthem against Boston]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WoodbineRacing @WoodbineResults #BetWoodbine not so much for the last week or so. Somebody's asleep at the wheel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did the chicken cross the road? Because the #Ravens offensive line couldn't stop it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richarddeitsch Up here in #the6 the #jays are THE story. Keep em flying under the radar, they'll take the AL East &amp; go from there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richarddeitsch @ESPN top MLB story is Cubs clinching playoff spot since 08. #jays clinch same night since...93 &amp; not a whisper.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonHeymanCBS sorry, did you see Dickey's performance tonight? Have you seen him pitch since the All Star game?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>