<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Yay! (Except that part about in America we now need a WAIVER for a BABY to get LIFESAVING heart surgery). We're bet… https://t.co/XuS8OHVYPE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[taxpayer $ spent for no national security  purpose: Former Norway PM held at Dulles airport over 2014 visit to Iran https://t.co/02vK8R3apW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerful from @senatorhassan - Why I Won’t Vote for Betsy DeVos https://t.co/LMky67wgwY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alt-facts as tool of gov leaders = threat to Republic. Kellyanne cites ‘Bowling Green massacre’ that never happened
https://t.co/f7EVdKiIkp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mitchellreports actually since WWI. Australia always stands by America in sacrifice. Perhaps @realDonaldTrump cannot understand sacrifice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recruiting tools ISIS has been waiting for are in the WH: 
Trump Pushes Dark View of Islam to Center of U.S. Policy https://t.co/cV8mu1Xdoh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shouldn't be funny since it is the logical precedent set by GOP...  https://t.co/DseQM4Exy3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bush and BHO's ethics lawyers: Sally Yates and the US constitution: two fatalities of the Monday Night Massacre https://t.co/l2YDZwDWbU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And this is why Yates did what she did. Hero. First of many who will fall on  principle but live with dignity. https://t.co/5sQFDe50cM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This man is sitting on the National Security Council. We will either prevent or look back in national shame at what… https://t.co/kREYbg4x1L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fact: anti-Muslim bigotry will boost extremists, hurt counterterrorism. Danger is clear in this Via @NPR: https://t.co/o0cKxyiInR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does Session think of Trump firing a Yates - a career prosecutor beyond reproach - for being careful about the… https://t.co/MX9gy4UIqT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And a threat to the Constitution that every US official swears to protect form all enemies foreign &amp; DOMESTIC. https://t.co/rG7kUoOOM6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChuckGrassley celebrated Yates as aware "her client is... not the President… not the Congress, it’s the people of the United States." &amp;now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Build an Autocracy https://t.co/gSTOzQtAb2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@igorvolsky + DOS dissent cable reach = all need to fight for their oath to protect the Constitution from all enemies foreign and domestic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RosieGray anyone doubting the need for a special prosecutor for anything relating to Russian hacking or any cases involving Trump people?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please call your GOP Senators, too. They represent you! https://t.co/3Qt0lkLtj7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ignoring oath all took to consitution: White House to Dissenting U.S. Diplomats: ‘Get With the Program’ or Leave -  https://t.co/7nuE9B7AbK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PressSec oath 2 Constitution, not president/party/policy: "the Dissent Channel will not be subjected to reprisal" https://t.co/gDD4frrn2F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-foreign policy officials urge agencies to push reversal of Trump refugee order https://t.co/HddfsfmWSL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fact: No Americans ever killed in terrorist attack in U.S. by national of banned countries! DJT trying 2 change that https://t.co/I9PSEO2TId]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump thinks the "secretaries" he has been nominating are administrative assistants. https://t.co/OZgnjeQsnx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[USG having trouble defining "permanent," and lots of other basic stuff in this #TrumpsterFire https://t.co/k61mY9371Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump literally told them for over a year that he would do this #MuslimBan. They got in line. #GOP folded rather th… https://t.co/VWBTlVhOQV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congressmen try to enforce a federal court order at a D.C. airport https://t.co/ZLAGCsvBOM via @HuffPostPol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much winning! https://t.co/bjAmGItrhI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Illegality is a necessary precondition for authoritarian rule... Game of chicken. Will We the People blink first? https://t.co/JLycOlsY87]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is how authoritarians break nations of laws -- getting away with illegal stuff bit by bit. Resistance must be… https://t.co/Q6sS0gbKhW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump’s Muslim Ban Is Cowardly and Dangerous https://t.co/qrOAztzb9W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not comforting. Competence comes with time. https://t.co/sPUIGCgkDr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DHSgov come on. This EO is illegal. Don't implement and have your staff violating law. Demand legal opinion, wait… https://t.co/IFNI2jcy1X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ilangoldenberg @LorenRaeDeJ given no legal review and risk their staff would violate law to implement illegal EO, DHS can just wait.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump signed illegal immigration / refugee EO without lawyers review or coordination with DHS, State, DoD. Reality,… https://t.co/rB0OPwzgM9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear World: Yes, we are still America. Trump will not stop us from being great. Stick with us through the hard time… https://t.co/l1SXLRGvcm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@delfuego If you stay till 3PM, Trump may invite you to movie he'll be screening (really). Maybe Schindler's List?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. Citizens being discriminated against - prevented from bringing their child based on national origin. Courts ne… https://t.co/Owq2JaKJ66]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Veterans of Iraq and Afghanistan all depended on interpreters, often helped them get out against formidable USG obs… https://t.co/WEjeVhgFDv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dude, where's the secret plan? What have you been doing? So far, you have only helped the terrorists. https://t.co/CWh8hPY29i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is exactly why it is ILLEGAL in U.S. to discriminate for immigration based on national origin. https://t.co/JM4rKtLCYv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These are people who literally risked everything in the trenches with our military. https://t.co/B4ZdKXWt2J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If nothing to hide, Trump should logically want independent commission &amp; special prosecutor looking at election hack
https://t.co/DAiUowvzNB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow @Stl_Manifest to see what happens when America turns it's back on humanity as with #RefugeeBan. #NeverForget https://t.co/lNnhGWU3mF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It has been 100% clear 100% of the time that @realDonaldTrump is not a Christian. He doesn't even play one on TV ve… https://t.co/iLYH7BSRRx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I am ashamed that he is our President." Rep Moulton who fought extremists alongside many Muslim brothers-in-arms:  https://t.co/BjpOQwc2xL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[to read about how they did this, see https://t.co/FZ0fdQKQ9o

ISIS wanted West to fear refugees and Muslims. https://t.co/0TBv68QHLH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many, many times in American history this has not been true. Yet many Americans have always fought to make it true.… https://t.co/ZpELnCa33w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["essential for us all to reject the false choice between security and humanity that President Trump is offering." https://t.co/wwIC5liHEJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Is Already Damaging the Ability of the State Department to Function https://t.co/1LPzb2ae3W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thinking of you and all the victims and the survivors today. #NeverForget #neveragain https://t.co/4QOEDgRl2l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Far-right parties unite across borders to create, ironically, a "Nationalist International" https://t.co/y70CdTK9RM via @TheWorldPost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s Ruinous Stance on Mexico Threatens America https://t.co/sHlG91zO8e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fox: Some have suggested sanctions are going to be on the table right away
@KellyannePolls: "All of that is under consideration."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This seems illegal, is sickeningly immoral. Progressive? Opposing regime change doesn't = loving on war criminals a… https://t.co/vEJJCeLxrV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did he continue "from which we can f things up for several generations to come?" https://t.co/1821yCXWMJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cinco de mayo is going to get pricey: This is how you tax average folks and hide it. https://t.co/Hrbadvr7yE via @markets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That would require staying open, liberal and democratic, not becoming closed (walls), coercive (extort allies) and… https://t.co/KPDQGhovaE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The State Department's entire senior management team just resigned https://t.co/24jZYkU4Vq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Definitely the worst 100 hours or so of all time. https://t.co/ocviBjhkV3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Republican Retreat Itinerary” by @WhipHoyer https://t.co/poNPPd3Ka2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting into just plain foolishness. https://t.co/tRPp4iEuRF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Shadow Knows - https://t.co/3eOQVWsgkN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MariManoog @A_Sloat @ForeignPolicy Thanks! Glad to be in the shadows...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch now! Undermined and Under Siege – Center for American Progress Action Fund https://t.co/FO4n9oRac4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope Modi mentions to Trump how elections and will of the people are supreme in a democracy... https://t.co/kSaa9yip9P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#refugeeswelcome An embarassment and tragedy. Banning refugees fleeing war and terror is when America stops being l… https://t.co/BLyq6G5Fao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@intelwire @KenSofer How many Americans can fit into GITMO?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gizmodo @peterthiel No - you helped create this. You do not get to escape our Island of the Misfit WH for beautiful, nuclear free NZ.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before or after he takes the oil? https://t.co/ywM3TQj0YT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BillKristol @shawnbrimley @realDonaldTrump States rights! The cognitive dissonance for Republicans will eventually cause mental breakdowns.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BRRubin @chrislhayes exactly - we are going to see voter suppression on steroids]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SaraLang
Your colleagues are here for you in this hour of need.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oversubscribed, but join us online or on CSPAN2 at 0930 w @AdamSchiffCA, @Julie_C_Smith, Jeremy Bash &amp; Rand Beers
https://t.co/FO4n9oRac4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rob_bennett @jaketapper Go Jake; BUT Terrifying that reporters conveying facts is now something unusual to celebrate. #alternativefacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't need to debate proof of the LIE about illegal votes. Trump may believe the lie, or not. Diversion @CNNPolitics https://t.co/t7vQKGztKt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorDurbin calls Trump's unequivocal support for Russia "confounding"... To say the least.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sessions does not plan to recuse himself from Russia investigations, never read reports on Russian interference in election. @SenatorDurbin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorDurbin - if things were reversed, we would hear howls of "treason" and "impeachment" from GOP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorDurbin. Don't naively trade away sanctions on Russia https://t.co/xhwqdoeAW4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorDurbin "election day 2016 is a day that will live in cyber infamy" https://t.co/xhwqdoeAW4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes. Don't hire. Instead use contractors for 300% more and keep them going forever. Hiring freeze is a scam. https://t.co/c6PRL5IIvp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I tweeted about this. @ExumAM nails it: No Way to Honor Sacrifice https://t.co/RGGnVafYS8 via @defenseone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember "Trump’s anti-Muslim proposals are likely to inspire and radicalize more violent jihadis" https://t.co/kTbsIKfVHi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy to join @ForeignPolicy for the New Shadow Government https://t.co/Zkl85vKAKK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#MAGA = Trump’s Cabinet So Far Is More White and Male Than Any First Cabinet Since Reagan’s https://t.co/Q7m9xPBfkk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch this video and you’ll see nothing Trump says about immigration is true. https://t.co/rFlNEUEo9z via @WIRED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New WH Initiative: Along with a Credit Rating, every American will get a personal Approval Rating from Kellyanne. https://t.co/fLZkrksCV6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This petition could end up with more people than inauguration: Immediately release Donald Trump's full tax returns
https://t.co/jP7l7jM1PB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science, facts, and reality have a well known liberal bias. https://t.co/I07oiKIKSx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@djrothkopf this was actually quite sinister. 1) distract from millions marching against Trump policies; 2) part of getting us used to lies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Start of the #WeThePeopleParty. https://t.co/9N1hF96rJd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lot of Trump supporters are angry in victory. worried about legitimacy? #womensmarch folks not angry, just energi… https://t.co/V17sGplYlJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes: this is how you start to inoculate against the virus of state lies. Plan is that we'll all tolerate them. I th… https://t.co/RBsG4N7Lnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ha! Perfect. Calling things the opposite of what they are is already the new administration's SOP. https://t.co/tf7du6goWD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adamnlawyer @Profepps 
Don't know. But he went on Saturday &amp; it's an area accessible to visitors. Trump likes to bring groupies 4 effect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's got a real thing about size. Remember "they're not small, are they? . . . I have the most beautiful hands" https://t.co/hIcE0PYYXB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crowd size - what's scary: 
1. It's what our President cares about 
2. He lies about live video feeds
Believe your lyin' eyes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No clue how many CIA employees were there, but may no one ever again demean the stars of fallen patriots on that wa… https://t.co/2PEkyrxemZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anchorage! https://t.co/6l963jOucc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whether it is the 8, or 7, or 98 richest having as much as half of humanity, we have a major problem. https://t.co/YVDMA95HL9]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>