<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[um so every fallout game would be better if i could just go around patting all the animals all the time instead of fighting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i'm a woman wearing clothes.
is this good enough?
#DressLikeAWoman 

(s/o to my last performance of henry IV for th… https://t.co/5tdTsmCXco]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnJohnsonson the fact of the matter is that the nz one is wrong too. he called nz and no-one answered.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elesedowden i met a builder who was working on my fence when i was in my undies one time. i think you're fine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[gotta say, at this point i'm kinda too scared to go to sleep because every time i nap i wake up and trump's done something moronic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[k scratch my other ideas this is one i am definitely behind https://t.co/45EwXqmhMj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[anyway, in other news, @PorkPieMovie is real fun and you should see it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I DIDN'T GET CUT OUT OF PORK PIE I DIDN'T GET CUT OUT OF PORK PIE I DIDN'T GET CUT OUT OF PORK PIE I DIDN'T GET CUT OUT OF PORK PIE I DIDN'T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[dad's fine, by the way, it's just supposed to take a couple of weeks to clear up. he's blind in that eye anyway so he doesn't really care]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[dad's burst a blood vessel in his eye, which aside from freaking me out yesterday, means he looks kinda like he's half possessed by a demon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[bbc please make sue perkins the new doctor i know i don't really care about the show anymore but please validate my terrible crush]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NicSampson and giving lactose intolerant people milk w lactose in, eh? true comedy circa most lazy coffee shop employees]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fancylettuce all of them i take it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fancylettuce I've had the unfortunate experience of meeting him at a debate and.. he's essentially the same in real life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fancylettuce darn, I was really hoping for the Great Lesbian Takeover of 2018, but now it's the Great Kale Takeover? Far less fun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really love the 'New Zealand gothic' feel of these, tbh. 
https://t.co/oMjqxmrHZu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[that bear is bigger than my apartment https://t.co/ZS7zH863FH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it was 33 degrees here today
in unrelated news, anyone have any fans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Alice_Harbourne I've found that burying myself in movie-watching and screaming constantly seems to help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would like to congratulate NZ Post for giving absolutely no damns and just chucking my 'signature only' parcel in the letterbox. :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan fuck off pears]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hidden Figures is excellent. I've seen six movies this year so far and it was the best. (My dad cried the entire way through.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @pmbillenglish do you really wanna  be known by history as a fencesitter? Condemn Trump. Show marginalised people that you actually care]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IBS/IBD are debilitating intestinal issues. Please sign this petition. People deserve to be treated with dignity.

 https://t.co/TPxFXE3iPC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[as someone who has a disease akin to crohn's, please. this would be a lifesaver for so many people. https://t.co/YgB5sI8Ay5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the fallout mod community is a delightful place https://t.co/SakNwcoUsi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pmbillenglish if words are not enough let me explain it in a film since that's what you respond to. https://t.co/FeCcL30SYw #doublethequota]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pmbillenglish your lack of comment on the current US situation concerns me. You must stand with other leaders &amp; denounce this hatred.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vinjii I liked it.. I just didn't love it. It definitely deserves oscars but I think there were other amazing films as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[unpopular opinion

la la land didn't deserve to be nommed for so many oscars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So... Goodbye Pork Pie certainly has... aged.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottEweinberg Afterlife is the one where they try to cut costs by being inside for two hours. I think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so. eyes wide shut is a very long film.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sweden that store from is a block from my apartment. many bad candy decisions have happened there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fancylettuce so is 'resident evil' a person who is vaguely boring and very bad at scaring you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sweden Nope, we definitely have pick-n-mix in New Zealand! It's practically a staple food. (jelly penguins are my… https://t.co/OqcOKDE5xR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 week till i discover if i made it into the final cut of @PorkPieMovie :D :D :D 
(in all honesty, i'm super siked for the film otherwise)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Iesbiansus CHARLES. (I mean he didn't die, but the poor man deserves a break)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like women. I like heels. Fortunately, I also like people having the right to choose what they want to do with th… https://t.co/M0Cvx0aMjC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pacific Rim is such a quality film though. I once watched it on a plane and it made me forget that I hate flying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[letterboxd is a fun film listing site https://t.co/eEKA0GpL1s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@snltrivia Wiig, Hader, Strong, Pedrad, and Armisen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HEY SO I JUST FOUND OUT THAT THE MEDIAN OF THE NZ STUDENT LOANS IS 14k. Mine is already 19k and I've probably got one more year. help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thatlauragirl30 @CIPYDPodcast nice! i know the mum of mine was a jack russell, have no idea about the other side of things though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CIPYDPodcast what breed/breeds is Leland? We have a pup who looks almost exactly the same. https://t.co/FPs0SwmB32]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BindzBrain he's just upset that nothing he ever does could rate so highly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OrientalBayNZ here's a picture I took a few weeks back of (presumably) vaguely similar weather conditions to today. https://t.co/8gBMj8cZuS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do these people... not realise... that we have natural disasters too? like.. earthquakes? and giant ass storms? https://t.co/maOwcjuVSX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, Hunt for the Wilderpeople was EXCELLENT. Excellent. If you haven't see it, go out and see it. #OscarNoms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How on earth did La La Land get so many #OscarNoms ? It was a fine film, but definitely not a good film.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[guess who got food poisoning from that one takeaway place and is never going to eat there again?
(me)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThomasJaames you too! I love your banner. It's really nicely made.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In other news, there is a serious possibility i might never fly again. https://t.co/BasXQZvVql]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm scared of flying and i'm watching a tv show about flying.
it's not going well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottEweinberg can confirm

my (blurry) pup from a few years ago https://t.co/ITdm3oPi2N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itlikesthegirls there were not nearly enough ladies in it tbh - tho nina dobrev was cute as a nerd tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Return of Xander Cage could be described as 'Suicide Squad but less subtle'. It's a big dumb fun movie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...........i'm literally only going to see xander cage because of the ladies in it.
...........oops.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the main reasons that I don't go to Dakota in Wellington is because I heard 'She Thinks My Tractor's Sexy' played unironically there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['political correctness', or as i call it, 'not being an ass to people'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[festival #asmr totally not rhythm and vines lmao why would it be https://t.co/YKqkSyebDP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[every time there's an earthquake now I hope and pray it's not in Wellington. and thankfully that one wasn't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottEweinberg Walk Out Boys - they see half of a movie and make up the rest.. Also Cheap Tuesday, which is quality banter about bad films]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottygb Black Mirror - also, there's an awesome Kiwi show called Brokenwood Mysteries which is top quality if you like mystery shows.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i've had that damn 'city of stars' song from la la land stuck in my head since tuesday and lemme say that 4 note motif is getting REALLY OLD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vaughndavis well I know what i'm doing for the rest of the afternoon then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AliceBrine Yeah definitely! It's not the journos' fault. I just wish the paper itself would suck less, yknow?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AliceBrine every day the nz herald gets worse and worse at their job...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, that's less than ideal, isn't it. https://t.co/MtQxROnBQl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vaughndavis why... does that horse have a human head
....are they trying to make it romantic because i foresee a lot of issues with that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WeatherWatchNZ it's pretty darn windy in Gisborne too - house is shaking... is there any chance that it could get worse overnight?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduced my parents to @Brooklyn99FOX and I'm so happy because they really liked it!! love it when my parents really like things I like!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[can confirm, I wasn't this morning and have blocked all of those accounts, but now I have been. double check, peopl… https://t.co/sH0lKrMmBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fauxparse He also punches Harley Quinn in the face for no reason.
Gotta say, sounds like the hero we all know and love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottEweinberg The Road as a sort of fun preview for the post-Trump world?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeterPetrusma generally shit horror films are the way to go. they have a habit of spawning in the netflix library]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottEweinberg True. Totally legal watching from my totally legal film collection it is then!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottEweinberg And Netflix NZ/AUS! We (might) have some of the films that y'all have.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hey guys this is our normal for the next four years. i'm feeling peachy about it, y'all https://t.co/8vyROyblyH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As we head into a rainy weekend I'd just like to congratulate my brain for being a TOTAL DICK.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@m_m_myers tfw no one is buying ur shit farmville rip off so you have to try to pander to one specific demographic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[anyone know of any good pandemic/apocalypse movies that are in the style of Contagion? - eg rely on science, don't resort to woo bullshit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spat106 and quantity of acts too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NeenersEstrella it's SO quality. I'm really hoping they do as well with the next season!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lin_Manuel you better have made it to wellington mate! it's where all (most) of our film/television greats come from.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanielJLayton same tbh. it was a weird kind of let down. I was surprised it won so many awards.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elesedowden totally agree. it was a weird kind of let down, actually, considering how many awards it won]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This President is going to be terrible, but perhaps, this news is even worse. I cannot stand anti-vaxxers. https://t.co/4cNHBHiaYI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[a friend is asking what i charge for me to do a shoot for her.

considering i've never actually done for profit before, i've no idea?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheHazelHayes it's annoying when films don't tho, because it's like... the bare minimum of female interaction? that's so easy to achieve!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dovil we might all die in four days. that's exciting news]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just found out what our big play is for this year. Considering it is 80% about eroticism/sex, I am both excited and terrified.
(the irony)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidfarrier that is a stuff poll and people who generally comment/interact on that website are often less than nice. That being said.. ugh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NCEA is a weird system, and it has literally no bearing on your life out of high school. Congrats if you did well, but if not, don't worry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NCEA students! If things aren't looking so great in your results today, don't worry. I failed 1/2 of my exams and my life's not going bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can confirm. If you've done well, congratulations! If things weren't as good as you expected, don't worry. NCEA is… https://t.co/VBYiEzLVuK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[La La Land was a bit disappointing actually. Great music, great dancing, but boyyyyyy it was slow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[in today's example of fandom wank, some angry sherlock fans have made a petition for the bbc because their otp didn't become canon. jfc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i'm not jealous of my friend's successes i'm not jealous of my friend's successes i'm-

(continues to be jealous of said friend's successes)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yassss congrats guys!!! &lt;3 https://t.co/K1lj1yIdUJ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>