<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[“But QUEBEC! See, we need racial discrimination of Muslims in order to stop… uh… white racists killing Muslims…?” - The White House today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is 100% false. Shooter was a far right white male. https://t.co/KlZUzgmb69]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada lets in thousands of Syrian refugees and despite all the fear mongering who commits an act of terror? A white male citizen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I blame Trump and his legitimization of far right hatred for this tragedy. How awful. https://t.co/uErdxwXW9l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In better news, 2017 has given us this perfect song: https://t.co/CfesECzUZu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay fuck this shit I’m going to go on a brewery crawl. I hope to see some better news in a few hours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m not gloating. I love my country, but it still breaks my heart to see American go down this path.

I’m just providing some contrast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/H0PT7kUJf6

And yet there has been no significant Islamic terrorism in Canada.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, here it is in English.

Anyway, I love my country.

&lt;3 https://t.co/fAsptbPhFr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada is subtweeting America, but we’re doing it in French and Trump probably won’t understand.

I love it. https://t.co/QRYY0ND2Tb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over 39,000 Syrian refugees have arrived in Canada in the last 15 months.

We’re not some terror-ridden dystopia. We’re fine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America, what fucking good is your constitution if this is allowed to happen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada’s neighbour to the south now seems to share none of our values. The relationship between our nations feels like a facade.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is just week ONE.

Can we really have another 207 weeks of this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I look forward to a hopefully sternly worded statement from @JustinTrudeau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada should not stand for this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[…because I’m hearing this ban also applies to Canadian residents and citizens who come from the seven countries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada’s Immigration Minister is a former refugee from Somalia. He’ll get diplomatic status, but what if he didn’t hold that position?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 episodes in to Lemony Snicket - a lot to like about it but one bad narrative choice fundamentally cripples the show.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kbiegel I say this because, if I remember correctly, it was a tweet of yours years ago that alerted me to the band at all. I love them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kbiegel May I also suggest you listen to the excellent new Japandroids.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus fucking Christ America this shit isn't even happening slowly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ugh. Peter Thiel now lives in NZ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LOVE the Star Wars VIII title. THE LAST JEDI.

Can't wait.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donwinslow almost a thousand deaths in British Columbia in 2016.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I fucking love the Storm Crow. https://t.co/L7Dek39bIF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy fuck did I need these marches.

I feel hope.

People are fucking amazing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kristapley @jack This happened to me too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sorry for your loss, America.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be attending the @womensmarch tomorrow here in Vancouver. I hope it's a big fucking crowd.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only way I'll ever see any of this fucking inauguration is if something humiliating happens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drove past the newly unveiled Trump Tower sign near my home on the way to work this morning. 

Felt ill when I saw it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope a fellow Vancouverite vandalises those big silver letters in the coming days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I find it sickening that the new Trump Tower Vancouver unveiled it’s big gaudy sign today of all days.

I bet Donald fucking requested that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America, I hope you’ve enjoyed your brief time as a respectable country. It’s been nice looking up to you for once.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s January 19th and I feel like I’ve just listened to the album of the year.

@Japandroids - Near To The Wild Heart Of Life.

Fuck yeah.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no bad Oasis album.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricVespe filmed in Vancouver!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy fuck America your elected officials are straight up evil.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So odd that Trainspotting is using the Mighty Ducks sequel naming template.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't link to threads often but as a film industry worker this made me clap. https://t.co/HyO0VS3zzT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love conservative insults. A major Hollywood star is receiving a lifetime achievement award and they're a "snowflake"?

What?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarterNixon I’m so sick of outrage over nothing-issues when there’s so much crazy shit going on. Disappointing liberals are the worst.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come on, people. WikiLeaks has always been a hypocritical garbage organization.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not to be a told-you-so hipster about it but I've always thought Assange was a piece of shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aaron_Morgan happy birthday man!! Looking forward to hanging soon enough! Much love to you and @Kaela_Morgan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 2017 we get new Twin Peaks.

That’s a thing that’s actually happening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read this. https://t.co/sjMtZLpBLL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I adore Nine Inch Nails, but this new EP just kind of washes over me without making a big impact.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was when the film stopped glossing over what's rotten and complicated in Hollywood that I finally cared. Ended up enraptured.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really wasn't all that into La La Land early on, but man did it win me over. Mostly. Some muddled messaging but a great film.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s NEW CAST IRON SKILLET time. A 13 inch beauty. About to give it a damn good seasoning. Spectacular steak and pizza, you’re in my future.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israel’s PM effectively “declares war” on NZ, and the New Zealand subreddit is full of Israelis expressing embarrassment and frustration.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I haven’t seen nearly enough movies this year but I do know that Swiss Army Man, Arrival and Sing Street are masterpieces.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like, I know it’s just Netanyahu being over the top and belligerent. It’s just rhetoric. But seriously, what the fuck?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like we’re not discussing enough that Israel kind-of-sort-of declared war on New Zealand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DustinKH @Susan_Hennessey We really ought to get it shut down at some point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kumailn Not even cg! A physical silicon sculpt.

CG used just to make the transition.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aaron_Morgan @kumailn Well given that I found this in the following old email from you: https://t.co/AZ1TvoQZ77]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aaron_Morgan @kumailn Remember this? https://t.co/ZowwXOquOX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm thankful Leia will be given a proper Carrie Fisher sendoff in Episode VIII rather than that cg monstrosity in Rogue One.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carrie Fisher was the best and this is just horrible. I thought she'd pull through somehow. 

Fuck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like none of us ever really appreciated George Michael enough.

He was fantastic, and pop culture is lesser without him.

RIP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrJonathanKing it's so great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NordlingCS And yet I love how much Prometheus is in there.

Hopefully its an elegant marriage of the two.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScottObiSwan incredible but utterly not good enough. The ultimate uncanny valley.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leia was/is always awesome, but let’s hear it for how genuinely wonderful, honest and hilarious Carrie Fisher is as a person.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God fucking damnit. I hope Carrie Fisher is okay. We need her biting honesty more than ever right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fox really just need to release the Covenant trailer at this point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is exactly the Nine Inch Nails we need right now. This sounds like what the world has felt like since November. https://t.co/SViPpBhUuC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricVespe i always wish Sunshine had gone even further, really explored this idea of the sun as a God who wants us dead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People actually want a Darth Vader standalone SW film? 

Why?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarterNixon imagine Rogue One but with an interesting &amp; unpredictable answer to the question "how did the rebels steal those plans anyway?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keithcalder especially if he lives a super comfortable lifestyle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@williambgoss it's a good show!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@publicaddress I'm in Vancouver. It's huge, distressing news here. Last Thursday we had 9 deaths in Vancouver alone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottEweinberg you don't think it's important to figure out why this man changed his tune? Lessons from that could be applied elsewhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone raved about how good the Passengers script was for years and now apparently the film is maybe kind of terrible?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEW 2017 GORDON COLE EATING A DONUT THIS IS NOT A DRILL https://t.co/WXVw4GxC9q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottEweinberg She’s so fucking great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarterNixon also Leia being all "I'm on a diplomatic mission" at the start of IV makes no sense now. Vader saw her ship in that battle!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aaron_Morgan @rianjohnson Maybe he should just double down. “That’s no asteroid field… that’s a DEATH STAR FIELD!!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyway, bring on @rianjohnson’s Episode VIII and its (hopefully) new, bold frontiers with great characters next year. Can’t wait.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember when one of the main complaints anyone ever had about ROTJ was the Death Star coming back? Since then we’ve had it in 3 more movies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’d have gladly watched a film populated with a dozen Skywalkers before seeing yet another Death Star movie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There was so much talk of “First Star Wars without Skywalkers! Without Jedi!” and then they go and make it another fucking Death Star movie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, and this will be the last Rogue One thought of the day, but seriously:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Force Awakens is an immensely better film that Rogue One purely for its characters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People calling Rogue One "standalone" like it even remotely holds together as its own thing. It's a supplemental, surgically attached to IV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@williambgoss but so many great puns too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aaron_Morgan ha, I had that exact thought during the film.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t do CG human characters in a live action movie.

Just don’t.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's an endless galaxy full of storytelling opportunities and this is what we get?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rogue One is a feature length cold open.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baffled by the love I'm seeing for Rogue One. It has its moments, I'll give it that, but overall it fell flat for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rogue One is not good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricVespe just found out I'll be seeing it Thursday. I don't really have much excitement for it, which may end with me loving it. We'll see]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bought something heavy on Craigslist. Went to pick it up. Parked illegally for 5 minutes with hazard lights on. Got a parking ticket. Fuck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aaron_Morgan I remember this feeling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keithcalder Fair enough. Did you check out Moana?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>