<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@passcod @Wanderlustin I AM STILL YOUNGER THAN YOUR AGES COMBINED! (but only just)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@holocronweaver Oh god, that's awesome. tfatffft.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not going to name my fft library "Quick and Easy FFT".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@holocronweaver last time i used DDG, the results were useless. It's improved heaps since then :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[accidentally set duck duck go as my default search engine. Oh wow, it's actually good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@parsley72 Ahaha, that's exactly right! But someone else might be :shrug:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JodiTheTigger This change over guide is better: https://t.co/6VxfDAfuEM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dammit, bohoomil has dissappeared, along with his
infinality fonts :-( https://t.co/8YXgEZR9dc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IMAKELSEY @Wanderlustin muahahaha.  Procrastination project locked in. Eta... later.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IMAKELSEY @Wanderlustin kerning be damned.  Use one of those auto convert font websites 😊]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wanderlustin hmm.  I wonder how hard it will be to turn into a font.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dotstdy don't be so fast to cast the first stone. NZ has being doing some shameful ass kissing as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[P.s. Fuck you Australian government for supporting Trump's ban on Muslims.  You're a bunch of wankers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IMAKELSEY exactly what it sounds like. I find it really nice. Cinnamon is a nice complement to the mint.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I might have a tea problem. https://t.co/zeIBZdbx1x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is how your personal data is been used. To affect how you vote. https://t.co/HxKPRmbxg9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_june Yup, different people have different sized personal spaces. Too close for some is normal for others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucyamorris stress induced perhaps?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Squibbons well, that's a pretty badass list to me :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Squibbons which games have you worked on again?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucyamorris no hits, but message been passed on. Any luck from the rental agent?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Squibbons I bow to senpai, who out-dorked me. :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Squibbons toot, toot! ... no, wait, what guage are you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New backup system: dmcrypt + luks + btrfs + btrbk -&gt; incremental encrypted backups.

Now I don't care if someone steals a backup HDD.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucyamorris ok, posted to my FB. Good luck in your search.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucyamorris anything? or a house specifically? move in date?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucyamorris I assume it's you and your partner, non smoking, no pets yea?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucyamorris DM me your budget and preferred location and I can ask on FB if you like?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucyamorris Sorry no. I only know (weakly) of two people living in Wellington. Being in Ak I'm a bit powerless to directly help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucyamorris anything I can do to help?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wanderlustin YOUR NOT HIPSTER ENOUGH!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wanderlustin If you were hipster you would have said "your stupid" instead. Cos ... ironic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Donzanoid Why is the door on the ceiling?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiaSae It's like the code you spent months writing worked on first run.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sehurlburt playing with fpga?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wanderlustin just put in some 3rd person and then you have 100% coverage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pervognsen hmm. I'll need to pull up my old notes if I'm to answer your question then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pervognsen range coder overflow is harder to deal with than arth overflow i think. Haven't done compression for a year so I'm a bit hazy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Icetigris but, while always a threat, fascism hasn't infected local or national government to my knowledge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Icetigris but nothing the magnitude as the systemic racism of Australia or USA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Icetigris I'm not Jewish so even though I can't see any antisemitism doesn't mean it doesn't exist. We just have good old racism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Icetigris hi from New Zealand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickSarten welcome to the new rental reality. You'll need to blind bid the rent to get the place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelmoussa @SaraMG hire a plumber to fix it in 5 min or else your fired. You tell them duct tape don't work. They don't care.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SaraMG it's not the engineers it's the management. No money to be made in making it secure. Only in shipping product.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@udonengineering @sehurlburt first step is people need to stop equating code with themselves. So attacking code isn't a personal attack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmyHarman1 I don't really like fishing, yet I've worked in the marine industry for over 10 years. Go figure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmyHarman1 just tell them the depth is all wrong due to thermoclines.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jonathan_Blow which memory orders will you support for atomics?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucyamorris kiwis arnt stupid. Housing will determine how the next election will go. Parents don't like their kids staying till their 40s.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@petrajane yes. Staying hydrated and putting on muscle mass are admirable goals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucyamorris they should do considering that teachers, police, firefighters,  nurses, all have the same problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucyamorris good thing you're shining a light on it then 😊]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucyamorris you have just witnessed NZ turn from an egalitarian society to a class society based on property ownership. Congrats.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucyamorris also note that this has only happened in the past 12 years. Before then you would have had no problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sehurlburt @ocornut Same on my android. Can't read article.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewmeows omg, where do these people come from?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucyamorris had 4 members of the opposing team rage quit 1/2 way though a cp game last night.   It's a cancer in OW.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucyamorris I can't do dps with ana.  My team keeps getting in the way and getting healed instead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gafferongames @jonshiring Modern FPSs build up on the strong base of TCP and use HTTP + json for a standards based networking model.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adastley mprotect is very os specific. And my code would be cleaner without it. Maybe something for sewing v2.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adastley I was thinking of changing my api to have a stack malloc callback, so the user can worry about mprotect instead of me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adastley Have a define specifying alignment for the stack. I set to 4096 bytes for memory protection prerequisite. Can differ between OSs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickSarten Pull down resistor + parasitic capacitance is filtering the square waves so they aren't registered?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stefanzellmann @doppioslash Maybe give https://t.co/9sXTtBJP32 a shot instead?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Squibbons New Zealand does have it's good days...
https://t.co/WN2a3jDUHy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instead of:
Error: selinux is disabled
I get:
chcon: can't apply partial context to unlabeled file

Ugh, death by 1000 cuts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@passcod @Wanderlustin Bad Sex in Fiction nominees?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Squibbons if your the smartest one in the room, you're in the wrong room. ☺]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesWidman @sehurlburt ha. I did the same thing. But I stopped once I started writing C instead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FioraAeterna @sehurlburt I wish I could turn off assignment in Conditional warnings for those only.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@parsley72 use them to make punch or ice tea, then you can get the good stuff earlier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FioraAeterna @sehurlburt even worse if the jokes are read.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@passcod Cool. I'm going to luks + dmcrypt + btrfs + btrbk. Gonna implement this holiday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@passcod Why not LUKs + dm-crypt?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wanderlustin Isn't this what Inception was all about?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[product idea: retractable fake nails.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Liannethy Overwatch 2cup goatse lemon party!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Liannethy _Everyone_ on overwatch is gay ... mic drop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helenhousandi put a drop cloth down before taking down drywall, makes cleaning up much easier :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sehurlburt @fatlimey dammit. Now I need to change the name of my fft library as well ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sehurlburt im working at it, writing a good readme is worth the time :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sehurlburt Dammit, I was just about to release my fft library, and that one beats it hands down in speed :-(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@passcod I got rewarded for finishing my long division before everyone else, by getting another 2 pages of long division :-/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@olson_dan @bkaradzic My beef is I cannot use offsetof with static_assert, to compile time check structs :-(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonOlick @sehurlburt If it had the company logo, maybe it could be claimed as a marketing expense?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FFS people make sure your have smoke alarms and the batteries are fresh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hardest thing for Software, Firmware, Hardware and Mechanical Engineers to coordinate is that the left plug, is labelled "left".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FioraAeterna @rygorous @arktemplar Hey, I nearly bought an A3000, doesn't that count?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@skullface Don't forget transfer of assets on death. That's an important one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richardhills777 @TransportBlog @nzherald They should turn Britomart into a 2nd casino, no-one uses those pesky trains anyway!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was going to ask someone a question, but instead I googled it and found out the answer for myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wanderlustin heh. He should of replied "oh hey, me too."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm still annoyed that even though I have implemented a BSP, I still don't understand how they work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sehurlburt I've always been interested in co-ops and wage ratios, but as I'm not a businessman, I don't know if they're viable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucyamorris I'm old, I recognised the 6502 before I looked at the caption.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiaSae that's awesome. I'm going to be walking down that path soon myself. Nice to know how it goes wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@passcod but that was just my experience. Just offering different view to problem. Good luck fixing yours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@passcod I had a "gold" kernel. But its gold because I only tested it after moving my laptop a certain way reconnecting the WiFi unknownly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IMAKELSEY as long as you don't start doing triathlons you'll be fine.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>