<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@StuartLCondie Echoes of Nixon's Saturday Night Massacre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sean Spicer Retweets the Onion Saying He Gives ‘Misinformation’: ‘Nailed It’ https://t.co/84Kklu3Lg2 via @selectall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Rule: Stop Apologizing | Real Time with Bill Maher (HBO) https://t.co/0IlsuTKDpf via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sheesh, now just waiting for Trump to send police to look for Joan Wilder's sister from Romancing the Stone https://t.co/3yKS6ZwXA5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Foxtel is showing The Terminal right now. Was that in the schedule? I'd like to think it wasn't]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@davidfrum on Trump's counterproductive immigration policies--and how liberalism enabled them: https://t.co/p8qAkPgr8p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Cunt move" has gotta be the most #strayan way to describe this madness https://t.co/JmEjbPeUZ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Airlines respond to immigration executive order https://t.co/V8Gus6HC4m via @Verge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump has suspended due process for Muslims. This is a constitutional crisis. https://t.co/qSRPpRw70l via @slate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump the Bully https://t.co/BfXE8aBMAj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haven't heard someone be called a "fuck-knuckle" in ages eh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charstarlene worth it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bold stand by the Times wouldn't be complete without a big, self-loving think piece about its bold stand https://t.co/4yGsB8seFo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Mexico's President Laid the Foundation for a Wall https://t.co/t8Y3t0y3SV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blokes are really rocking the Dad Wear today #heyimstillcool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mary Tyler Moore’s Greatest Performance https://t.co/NFzSJ1wAlI via @thedailybeast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The funniest episode of the Mary Tyler Moore Show is a brilliant rumination on death: https://t.co/qYzBbHEvX3 via @BrowBeat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch Anne Hathaway play monster see, monster do in the trailer for Colossal: https://t.co/sBxwOOKuWn via @BrowBeat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ellenback A day without a Big Lebowski reference is a day wasted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to @ausoftheyear, Professor Alan Mackay-Sim #ausoftheyear https://t.co/fkhilPOhIZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Know who else is 40? Urkel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CrazyinRussia Is that snow or bullshit?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After all these years it's still trippy how many people remain stumped by Subway #whatsortasandwichesdoyouhaveluv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Reportedly Brought His Own Staff to Cheer During C.I.A. Speech https://t.co/deLdjJRgCp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump, "Alternative Facts" and the Women's March: A Closer Look https://t.co/xSlKCHYmgL via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump turns his back on the world https://t.co/HGXGidTupI via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Struggling Media Company Almost Desperate Enough To Hire Someone Qualified For Job https://t.co/tkheuIcBPm via @theonion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hipster + Millennial = twice as many ways to fuck up a sandwich #redfernwank #gimmemy15bucksback]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who the hell still drinks Fanta?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But are there any sex acts the tabs don't think are sordid? https://t.co/1z3jSsrU6Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bit of speaker echo goin on with Obama here. He should finish with a little Phi; Collins DO YOUUU REMEMBAH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Age of Anger by Pankaj Mishra — in the danger zone https://t.co/BMZ4yhcbTb via @FT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Alec Baldwin holding a pot or schooner? Either way he holds it like a Marvel villain holds a smoking test tube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice work: Donald Trump’s Soft Spot for Russia Could Be His Political Undoing https://t.co/8eMypjizWt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NY resolution to answer every question with "dunno, maybe five bucks will refresh my memory" going surprisingly well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StuartLCondie Russians got the right idea too https://t.co/45Nibo7Y5g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StuartLCondie gotta get hold of some bowling shirts. So liberating]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I'm fat AND middle-aged, the #Sopranos' wardrobe makes a lot of sense https://t.co/Ex3cpk8Nnd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blahblahellis Can you still buy those frozen cordial kangaroo-shaped deals? That would make my summer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ethics fuss pitted the GOP’s shameless against Trump’s: https://t.co/N69FL0wLIz via @slate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HAPPINESS: Having only two puffs of Ventolin left but remembering there's a new box in the bathroom cupboard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus WHY AM I JUST FINDING OUT ABOUT @SimpsonsNRL??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[judging by the stories, people only get hangovers on New Years Day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davemeddows Sounds swanky. BYO coffee mug?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every Trump presser report needs to use "word salad" at least once: https://t.co/YShV0csN3G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To: 2017
From: Earth
Due to present circumstances, we would like you to start here a few days earlier than previously agreed.
Regards, Earth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016's seriously running out of Celebrity Death Wall RIP #DebbieReynolds https://t.co/Ke7XFiQL6Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Requiem for an ’80s Kid: We’ve Lost Our Prince and Now Our Princess  https://t.co/CgNKBG5acQ via @thedailybeast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world's scruffy lookin nerf herders to #CarrieFisher right now https://t.co/fAvHZG7PZl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carrie Fisher Died Having Figured Out How to Truly Be Carrie Fisher https://t.co/ZrbDQtiDEF via @vulture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Carrie Fisher gave 30 Rock one of its greatest episodes: https://t.co/yQ2HNluUtA via @BrowBeat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once again, 2016 shot first. May the force be with you, princess. #CarrieFisher https://t.co/mrwSPBMwTh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/2 he did it and laughed. I got a selfie with him. He didn't like making Last Tango in Paris. The end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dreamt I met Marlon Brando among tomato vines. Before I could ask him to put a piece of orange in his mouth a la The Godfather, 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama Clears 2,000 Square Miles Of U.S. Airspace For New Free-Range Drone Preserve https://t.co/3OYgjbkjow via @theonion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikesheffler yeah I was typing on the bus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is 'Arrival' the best 'first contact' movie ever made? https://t.co/3EKZgxuRXN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama was so channelling Ray Patterson during his last press conference #obama  #trump #simpsons https://t.co/VDi8ub5IVS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehighsign Obama: Ray Peterson redux https://t.co/AOP70gPbj5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anonymity has poisoned online life. https://t.co/I8IQZX4QgU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retrospective - Battle Without Honor Or Humanity (Kill Bill Theme) https://t.co/3Eumk51smJ via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael Flynn Called Hillary Unfit, but Spilled Classified Info Himself https://t.co/Oymqisiygb via @thedailybeast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China starting WWIII, Trump murdering us all, mega heat wave ... busy day on https://t.co/c6Nc3KpDpX ...https://t.co/XCenXTab4V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Year Everyone Realized Digital Media Is Doomed  https://t.co/kjLzAXgDfH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OK if 2016 were a T-shirt it would have this on it #yeezuschrist https://t.co/XJ7znjq5IW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another cold, soggy, late delivery courtesy of @menulog. Account deleted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_SarahMcPhee I can hear em from my place]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden Donates Collection Of Classic Skin Mags To Those In Need During Holidays https://t.co/G7dlDKUTSU via @theonion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Negan is killing The Walking Dead: https://t.co/OioV4ik45g via @BrowBeat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So do I block the pornbots or buy em a drink?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump - the orange Wayne Brady @sanderlands https://t.co/tTlVjqtiIR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not grabbing nearly enough p*****s after being told that shit's apparently OK #Regretsof2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only illegally voted twice for Hillary #Regretsof2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Paedophile store terrorised by angry man demanding pizza]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Harambe shrine lacked pizazz #Regretsof2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ate pork, just not the pulled stuff #Regretsof2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didn't change my name to Coachy McCoachface #Regretsof2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bethanyshondark So Baby McBabyface it is?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are people losing their shit over Time's Man of the Year when all it does is surprise people who don't know @Time still exists]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just call it Time’s Hitler of the Year Issue so we can skip this recurring conversation https://t.co/RUlYZUhr5A via @slate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump Has Proven Liberals Right About the Tea Party https://t.co/mgVy0Xmtyi via @intelligencer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just waiting for Trump to appoint his horse to something #youknowit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Victory of  ‘No’  https://t.co/B4IXmFDCc0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BillBailey Fantastic show at Stdney mate. Feel free to chill here until the whole angry apricot thing blows over]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If asked, I'd make every life soundtrack the Beetlejuice soundtrack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RPG Tales from the Loop lets you channel Stranger Things and ET https://t.co/LzF8bRNvXG via @Verge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Hot weather expected in summer https://t.co/7UF3mXGdYM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s Lies Destroy Logic As Well As Truth  https://t.co/J8AhEjgMWK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Changing my name of Johnny Foreigner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StuartLCondie Compu-Global-Hyper-Mega-Net, junior vice-president Homer Simpson speaking ...

It's Patty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching Brandis givin his statement be like #senate #brandis https://t.co/rTKLMQBXSc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian propaganda effort helped spread ‘fake news’ during election, experts say https://t.co/2QqPempRIU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The voters who rejected decades of American foreign-policy consensus might be on to something. https://t.co/o5gCo8EPap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICC: Mr Du Plessis do you swear to tell the whole truth so help you Gold?
Faf: *chewing noise* YETH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump's media summit was a 'f---ing firing squad' https://t.co/NDqUjAciVm via @nypost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Hail Trump!': Video of white nationalists cheering the president-elect  https://t.co/PKY5eMdLrm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shirtless Trump Saves Drowning Kitten https://t.co/aiaxx7qebH via @MTVNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[blockin the hell outta them porn bots]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Helpful List of Fake-News Sites to Watch Out for on Facebook https://t.co/1gHW5mCdeL via @selectall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I was moving into the @WhiteHouse I'd have the removal trucks backing up to the Beetlejuice theme]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>