<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Exactly. There is no such thing as "globalism." There is the victory and global spread of America's exceptional ide… https://t.co/oESKeug8kp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Each day I scroll, click and read most interesting stuff I can find, to read lots of sources. Turns out I've just been reading @TheAtlantic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHAT ARE YOU TALKING ABOUT https://t.co/frpwu6pRM5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to @briancdarling for the review of my book, and to @tomricks1 for running the review on your blog.  https://t.co/gtxs8wlHAS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rebecca_Cusey Those are the best words.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, the mysterious Publius Decius Mus is now the new Ben Rhodes. https://t.co/DMIfWCfBPA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Gorsuch is probably the best thing Trump will do as president. 
Another way of putting it: it's all downhill from… https://t.co/uqYPwTN0Dq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trilogy with story fidelity of 2000 @scifichannel miniseries + production design of its sequel + epic scale of '84… https://t.co/GDXPrGF2Hg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The right way to make a "Dune" franchise is to make the original novel into a trilogy and ignore the sequels. https://t.co/sFBuJBbX7q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To anyone familiar with history of anti-Catholic and anti-Semitic sentiment in US, current #SCOTUS composition is stunning sign of progress]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is a wonderful thing that there is no religious test for public office, and that opportunity has expanded for religious minorities]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catholics and Jews were once second-class citizens. Today there are 5 Catholics and 3 Jews on #SCOTUS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fun fact: if confirmed, #Gorsuch will be the first Protestant to pass Senate confirmation to #SCOTUS in 27 years (since Souter in 1990).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything is seemingly spinning out of control. https://t.co/mhPrnLb1sc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perfect example of rhetorical overreach that makes us disbelieve every politician and cheapens talk. https://t.co/lYLcluc2LS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Gorsuch is plainly outside the mainstream of today's SCOTUS.
He's an Episcopalian.
This cannot stand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump did a good thing today. Good for him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConnieDeckard No, it wasn't. Sorry if it came off that way. Just sharing my concern that between the two, Trump worries me more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@domineeringDom What's more potentially damaging, a media w/o credibility, or a Trump in the Oval Office?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I understand conservatives' distrust of media. But if you are more upset about media than about Trump, I think you are misreading the moment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a David Lynch movie. @jessepstein https://t.co/U5axH9xbr6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikesTweety 1. I didn't realize you were on twitter. 2. Your image is nerdier than anything I've ever posted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@EliotACohen: "This is one of those clarifying moments in American history." https://t.co/CjO37HvQ9F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The overlap between @starwars fans and @LaLaLand fans was apparently too small for this Tweet to find an audience. https://t.co/4xZn1IhoHP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aelkus Academic realism long ago became a synonym for functional pacifism, American retrenchment, and apologies for any other power.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lprekon I take that as a compliment. Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So... we could build ten of them! https://t.co/JF5n08135m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Mideast. https://t.co/B81mRHlL9G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Genuine non-snarky question: where are you seeing the best principled conservative non-hysterical opposition to Trump articulated?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's something I wrote about Syrian refugees a while back. Still timely:
https://t.co/2tqgTWr0zT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During the campaign, we routinely heard that it was just rhetoric and that Trump would moderate once in power. https://t.co/8jiKH0U0ln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RadioFreeTom I'm hoping for an effective conservative opposition.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eric_d_magnuson @FWNeave Here was one attempt: https://t.co/ygwdCjBJ0E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this the first time the US has acknowledged ground troops in Yemen in combat role? https://t.co/h60ULvuZWy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a first. Anyone else think I've been insufficiently critical of Trump? https://t.co/AhMY4TPfBN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FWNeave I criticized Obama's foreign policy. I have much deeper criticisms of Trump: https://t.co/bV9neHtzZS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Archaeopelf as I said, I'm not a fan. It is over broad, poorly defined, probably just a prelude to permanent ban.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bannon gets a seat on NSC, treated as a principal. Precedent-shattering, very bad move.
 https://t.co/DpxHwsovgh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So neither Trump's order nor the criticisms of it seem to hit the mark.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...as if we have obligation to let in any/everyone at all times. Real tradeoffs at stake, valid reasons to regulate flow of people...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not a fan of Trump's executive order on immigration--but I'm also wary of viewing immigration / refugee policy solely as moral issue...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The moment you realize Ralphie from "A Christmas Story" played an elf in "Elf" -- pure casting genius. @OfficialPeterB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattleeanderson The question here is about the obligation of the state, not the church. Can the state discriminate in favor of Christians?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beyond immediate effect of refugee ban is subtle impact these kinds of moves have on our political culture… https://t.co/T90pgi5tfq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FederalistParty https://t.co/1JyvQEP6vo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We should embody justice, not just fight for it. https://t.co/xzRLeksqM5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like the admin is determined to ignore Afg. even when it comes to implementing bad policy. Which is something, I guess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not a complaint: but why did Trumps exec order not include Afg. and Pakistan?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And we are likely to see a replay in Afghanistan in next 3-5 years. Want to prevent atrocity in Afg.? Stay and win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't recall hearing the outrage when Obama withdrew from Iraq without winning, but that's what created the refugee crisis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elections have consequences. Don't like the refugee crisis? Elect someone who cares. Last time we did that was 2004.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't elect these kinds of presidents and then expect the world to continue as before. Or demand that the US pay all the clean up costs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The refugee crisis is the cost of America's withdrawal from leadership under Obama, which Trump has promised to continue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can help refugees by helping stabilize their homes. But that might be "nation building" which is always evil, I guess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm baffled over the moral outrage over refugees given Americans' total disinterest in Afghanistan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's what I wrote in my book about #NATO. 
Short version: NATO is important and good. Stay in.… https://t.co/HEuLc1T1vo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's what I wrote in my book about border security. 
https://t.co/R77MfoaLQl https://t.co/KkO2CT2gCi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is media unfair and biased? Yes, definitely. But maybe there are more important things to worry about.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blaming media for being unfair to Trump is like telling Leia she was uncouth for pointing out Tarkin's foul stench as he blew up her planet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I disagree with a lot of what Hauerwas writes, but I think he is right on the mark here.
 https://t.co/34Dch1WbQY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trumps 20% tax on Mexico trade will make stuff more expensive, us more poor, and, probably, create zero new jobs.… https://t.co/3bo3wEeA2T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The National Park Service was already my favorite bureaucracy before this week.
@NatlParkService]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus truly is a man of God. But, technically, he never left. https://t.co/BAAP2z3t8d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Damien Chazelle's next film, "Cantina: A Star Wars Love Story," see the hilarity and passion of Figrin D'an and Modal Nodes. @starwars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RWurzburg Yes (referenced in my last book). Looking more for theory of nationhood and why it supposedly matters so much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm writing a book about the flaws of progressivism and nationalism. What's the best manifesto of US nationalism I need to read?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am reminded that one of Obamas first acts was to sign an executive order ordering the closure of Guantanamo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheOneSoleShoe try asking people about Afghanistan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Trump's 'National Day Of Patriotic Devotion' Is Creepy" https://t.co/J0zfGh5VOJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the case for Federalism. https://t.co/yff2MMlFuf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rebecca_Cusey @latimesent I just like the one where Andrew Garfield plays the soulful religious guy and gets persecuted for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This thread is what Twitter is for. https://t.co/wrft04VeuS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another excellent piece by @MJGerson. https://t.co/OTepwl6QZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a fan of limited govt, but also of effective govt. Hiring freeze is a bad idea. There are better ways to limit reach of the state.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best accomplishment of the day: convincing my wife to follow @JusticeWillett on Twitter, Twitter Laureat of Texas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent piece by @HalBrands1 https://t.co/SM9ifFqBTy via @warontherocks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prediction: @StarWars Episode IX will have "hope" or "light" in the title, like "Hope Reborn" or "The Light Dawns"
#TheLastJedi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My first time reading CS Lewis' Horse and His Boy in decades. The Trinitarian theology in this passage is beautiful… https://t.co/m72mI3fa7V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Possibly the greatest tweet of all time. Well done @varadmehta. 
The whole tweetstorm is something fantastic. https://t.co/DVk2Nf523x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheOneSoleShoe that's my plan too. Hopefully will turn into a book no one will read not just tweets no one will read.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Media gets facts right, thinks job is done.
But Americans' distrust of media is about bias in narrative, story selection, framing, not facts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instead, you chose to use your visit to CIA to complain about the media's coverage of the crowd size at your inauguration.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are 10,000 US troops there. The Afghan government is on the brink. The Taliban are resurgent. AQ is reconstituting. What will you do?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You won the presidency. You are the commander in chief. You never once mentioned Afghanistan on the campaign trail.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Detailing your plan to win the war in Afghanistan, or the one in Iraq, would have been an appropriate subject for your visit to @CIA today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr. President, what is your plan to win the war in Afghanistan? @POTUS @realDonaldTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump complains that we don't win anything anymore and he wants to win again. So I have just one question:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, he went there to reiterate that we should have annexed Iraq's oil fields, of course.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So did Trump really go to CIA just to ramble about the daily news and complain about journalists and Congress?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[..I doubt it because intel officers are such an eclectic bunch there is no "CIA" vote, no demographic that captures them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He says he won the CIA vote. I doubt it, but for different reasons than you might think.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: Against my better judgment, I'm going to watch Trump's speech at @CIA, my former employer. Next few Tweets might not be sane.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Media: you brought this on yourselves.
Trump and Spicer: this makes you look small and petty.
Me: won't be watching… https://t.co/0RJpoV2aop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For some reason I watched the 2008 Clone Wars film, the only point of which is to prove Phantom Menace is not the worst Star Wars movie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pbethancourt This is excellent news: at least seven more people might read my academic articles than read my tweets. At *least.*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's an interview with Obama's chief foreign policy advisor in which no one ever says "Afghanistan." https://t.co/oi5tp13jE7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvansRyan202 Would Flynn evaluate presidential candidates by the same standard?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I correctly predicted Trump would use Obama's non enforcement of laws as precedent to ignore Obamacare. In a piece that was never published.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JFK: "We will pay any price, bear any burden...support any friend...to assure the survival and success of liberty."

DJT: "America First."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am a patriot--served in uniform, war vet. Love my country. Nationalism is malarkey: mysticism and self righteousness on national scale.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>