<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@AllyStewart__ happy birthday mate, have a good one!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coughed up a grogger that flew out onto ma chest today. Was beautiful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy bday sunshine @EmmaMelville]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ROUNDTHEBEND__ @baileywb99 these are the sounds you were making to yourself in the stock room at work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rossfunston happy birthday Funston, mate!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Av been going tae ma bed at 7 in the morning. Fuck knows how I'll be waking up at that time tomorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy NYE folks. Shoutout to @eden. Gravity https://t.co/RhnbevQzVJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life feels so unbalanced right now. It's weird]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last 2 minutes. Watch. Thank me later. https://t.co/scqP7VnCQt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[at that point in the year when ma maw could buy me a packet ae crisps and ad still get hit with the "aye that's part ae yer Christmas" shite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@georgehaguee you know me so well ðŸ’˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best xmas ever ðŸ˜ https://t.co/a1y7auHtKX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConnorBaker5 mate, al do it. Come into the stock room and...aw wait a got sent home, soz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am not fit for working]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_PaigeCargill_ @georgehaguee @jamdogd that's not my ass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamdogd @georgehaguee mate you're arse is ringing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need a dominos in ma life asap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mums back home from her operation thankfully so I'm a slave for the foreseeable and she's low-key loving the fuck out of it ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[fuck meeeee I'm bored]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Banned from Xbox live for a week because I telt folk to kill themselves. Buzz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dylan_Quigley_ Sky Broadband is a UK internet service mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The centre is the biggest pile of aids to ever come into existence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackFergie1888 and now I'm late for fucking work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've had the worst day ever today and to top things off, I've just slipped on dog shite while walking to work and now I'm covered in it. Fml]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I went on my old iPod today for the first time in about a year and maaaan, there are sooo many memories on that thing. It's mental]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A always go to tweet something then realise ma mates will rip shite out me for the rest ae ma days then don't even bother]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't wait to see Eden live.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dylan_Quigley_ a know ðŸ˜‚ a had no idea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd do anything to stay off work and eat pizza]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being cold and tired is theeee worst combo ever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the temptation to buy a pizza has started]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The things I'd give to be in Amsterdam for the next week ðŸ˜¢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should be legal to dropkick cunts in the centre if they're walking slow as fuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally moving into a new room after 17 years ðŸ˜¢ I'M EMOTIONAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Literally bursting blood vessels in ma heed because ae FIFA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best club in Scotland.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This morning I got out of bed, to then lie back down in the shower and proceed to sleep again. I hate my life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would let someone slam dunk ma heed aff a curb if it meant a could stay off school tomorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[look at this sex. Yes I'm a gimp https://t.co/WXOWivxWa8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'd think James Arthur had a new song out or suhin ae]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cracked a straight up semi when ma maw said a could spend 300 quid in PC world for nout]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone else calling a 5-1 shagging ????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nout a wanted more than to batter fuck out them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't hack Friday nights like this ðŸ’¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to ur boy @jamdogd watched this probs like 300 times and laughed. Lylylylylyly https://t.co/06ufIxNhIA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@henryfong @MiloAndOtis WHAT'S HAPPENING RN LIKE WAT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What even https://t.co/HigstcbkLE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@motiofficial @georgehaguee RIP Moti's account lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish I knew what I wanted to do with my life so much ðŸ˜Ÿ it's so frustrating]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steveaoki tweets this on the day that another DJ passes away from a car accident...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rikos_67 @dylboles check you in the background with yer fam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A don't think my life has ever been this boring up until now ðŸ™‡ðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I needed a long lie soooooo much]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's just no a normal day on Twitter if there isn't at least one tweet fae some cunt complaining about shite slow replies are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check the angle a got on @Leighgriff09 free kick https://t.co/cfRJyNb57c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Soundcloud ads give me the fuckin boke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dominika505x good to hear hitler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dominika505x how to happy birthday in poland 101]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[tired isn't the word ðŸ’¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Liam_Cook4 @georgehaguee when she sends nudes https://t.co/GdacZCnD1y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_PaigeCargill_ @derek_white00 no when D hadds is about @Dylan_Quigley_]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[couldn't peel tatties properly so a started launchin insults at a tattie, a fucking tattie...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dicks out for harambe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should I stay or should I go always plays in my work and it reminds me of Stranger Things every time. That series is soooo good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surprisingly missin ma mum and wee Tyson kicking about the house]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saving money is an absolute mission when aw a do is spend it on pure SHITE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Addicted to McDonald's smoothies ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BreaK_71 @OverclockersUK alright, was just double checking. Cheers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BreaK_71 is there a code I use when buying from @OverclockersUK mate? I want to buy a new mouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why's Tokyo drift outside ma house at 3 in the mornin ??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[lol happy bday to a bro ðŸ’— https://t.co/E57Roqvj7V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a fucking G  https://t.co/E2yRhTNvsE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My reaction to @Alesso coming on was priceless https://t.co/J0rxgzZzJq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd love to be anywhere that's not Scotland right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NAH A JIST SMASHED A MIRROR AND AM STRAIGHT UP SCARED ASF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A miss shouting "bye bye driver" at T and some cunt half a field away would always shout it back at me ðŸ’”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get the razor blades out cause am bored as fuck and due to tan ma wrists]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fucking shitemare  https://t.co/RPH3suOUkY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jordanmcaleese5 neither do a mate, it's sound ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@baileywb99 @Bryan_Cairns11 "cunt looks like he's been put in a microwave and shrunk" ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trek into T was the hardest thing av ever done in ma puff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rest in piece. Bye see you later BG's xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even I was shocked at this shit. Ridiculous https://t.co/jLxd5aQ7LN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like the half ae Scotland is gone to T this year ðŸ˜‚ can't wait]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Must be the only cunt alive who doesn't even know what love island is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YES FRANKIA BRING ME THE MONEEEEYYYYY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Music is life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Italy win, a don't owe this melt a penny. Moan eh Italy https://t.co/J19x8v6xJ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No way are WALES going into the semi finals, the scenes man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mon eh Wales]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG what a goal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turns out I was wearing my boxers back to front all day ðŸ™‹ðŸ¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally got a job ðŸ˜…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to the confident, knows he's good looking cunt, Calvin Haddow ðŸŽ‰ have a good day mate @Dylan_Quigley_ https://t.co/U5yVHTBmJ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joe harts a hero]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing worse than someone who loves drama and arguing ðŸ’¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 days until TITP and I don't have even half the things I need https://t.co/Lpz8PTAUYx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Andywarrenblack quality Andrew lad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kyle macuga is the funniest human alive when he's steamin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sell yer car Scotland]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>