<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Wanted to give a huge thanks to Splott superstar @louclarkie for designing posters for meeting next week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Plaid_Cymru any snappy lines for your candidates swearing from the gallery? Or the abuse I have had from twitter tolls for raising this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever thought it should b easier to punish fly tippers. Welsh Government  r consulting on doing this take part 9 Feb 7pm Moorland Com Centre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@louclarkie no that's great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@louclarkie fancy helping with posters? Task is easy, make consultation look exciting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcvjones @CardiffPlaid he is conducting what the kids are now calling #PostTruth politics or talking nonsense in old money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcvjones @CardiffPlaid it's an admittedly humorous diversion from me catching Neil out. https://t.co/6whmW0zCCS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welsh Gov consulting on making it easier to prosecute fly tippers. Want to take part? Come along to Moorland Community Centre, 9th Feb, 7pm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can cope personal stuff it just makes you look a bit daft. But you voted to remove green space protections. It sh… https://t.co/7zqk4juOsG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are calling to remove protections. Putting power in the hands of developers. I presume me saying this is why th… https://t.co/UgXRNWWO1Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Small thing but important, your motion removed all statutory protection for green space. Making it easier for devel… https://t.co/X8YeaJ50PY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to Talk day Thursday. So many of us have been affected by mental problems of our own or people we love, it is… https://t.co/TJW9BuqSBb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am trying to remember the phrase my mum always used about people who get personal.  Something about them talking… https://t.co/wZYXdhndhr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@girliegirlie17 @RevPhillipJ @neiljmcevoy it shouldn't be personal. Is saying the same thing in Splott and Fairwater to much to ask?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have the hand movements but sadly musically I am hopeless https://t.co/Rkblw1uDjf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@girliegirlie17 @neiljmcevoy @RevPhillipJ is Phil Labour member?Is It not ok he holds his AM to account?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes. That's what's embarrassing. You have been caught. Stop digging and try being consistent https://t.co/nnpawn7hmF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Part of speech from full Council. Still can't inderatand why @neiljmcevoy denied ownership of own leaflet. Watch an… https://t.co/eHBtXBUayi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@RevPhillipJ @neiljmcevoy this bit https://t.co/XagM2eUpXP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neiljmcevoy @CardiffPlaid it's your leaflet Neil you just got found out. Further denials are embarrassing. Own your own campaign]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neiljmcevoy @CardiffPlaid it's got your number on it pal. You just got caught saying diff things in diff parts of Cardiff. #alternativefact]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CardiffPlaid @neiljmcevoy when Neil said that the leaflet about Plaid plans for 5000 homes wasn't his. That wasn't true was it? #typical]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neiljmcevoy @CardiffPlaid yes right Neil "it's not my leaflet Mcevoy" it was wasn't it? #alternativefacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very quiet since you said that leaflet calling for 6000 homes inSE Cardiff wasn't yours. Is that because I pointed… https://t.co/185NWXOpOz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HBIndependents thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rainy morning in Splott but great fun on our monthly litter pick #keepsplotttidy https://t.co/UeGIVfXSNt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Out and about on a rainy Saturday morning with Splott, Tremorfa and Pengam Green Labour team @huwthomas_Wales… https://t.co/2TfnuWQSy8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Knocking doors in Tremorfa with the Labour team, it's a little rainy but as always our neighbours are friendly and… https://t.co/XxH953Gz9k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@louclarkie @cardiffcouncil @huwthomas_Wales is that paper? DM me full location so I can report? #keepsplotttidy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eastmoors youth cen is getting a refurb and the kids have been involved in designing it. Work to start on 6th of Feb. Can't wait to see it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JoGalazka you are the inspirer https://t.co/7W8mqYpGTE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent. Time to show young carers we value them and give them this much needed support. https://t.co/KCzXv6n3TA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One last question about Splott Road resurfacing and I am now finally home from tonight's meeting @cardiffcouncil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Late night for me and @huwthomas_Wales at @cardiffcouncil but always a privilege to represent our area]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CardiffPlaid here is another leaflet same organisation. This one has a phone number. Guess who's?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the sort of abuse I have had all night for daring to speak up for Cardiff South East against what is a ridi… https://t.co/dboC3SlYhg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, you aren't getting away with this. Check out the Facebook page. U just thought South East Cardiff wouldn't see.… https://t.co/zhETBTK9VY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CardiffPlaid have you read the leaflet you put out?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is #YoungCarersAwarenessDay I am campaigning for @cardiffcouncil to introduce free bus travel for young carers @CarersTrust]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Atticus_75 @inksplott all buses will have access to the road.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Debate Cardiff council tonight. I will be opposing @CardiffPlaid plans to build 5000 homes in South East Cardiff in… https://t.co/0VhmDyEJmf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sian_regan Moorland Community Centre?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done guys. With you in spirit if away for the weekend in person https://t.co/H7tdoNgWbZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry you had to be moved. Now time to stop it happening again. We need @swpcardiff  help for that. I am on it. https://t.co/xWKrN80xGo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@inksplott @cardiffcouncil @Chrisnz125 more parking enforcement needed. I have seen a couple of locals who reg dbl park, very selfish act.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welsh Tories label ALL public sector workers as middle class. In the latest bizarre tirade against workers rights]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@inksplott works on Splott Road will be carried out in a way that busses will have continued access.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamieMatthews84 @cardiffcouncil cheers. I will take up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Global_Love @cardiffcouncil @Grettaelaine @huwthomas_Wales thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where's the instantaneous labelling of strangers demonstrates a huge willingness to listen. https://t.co/dVpCnlKO2s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why can't I fight the Tories by talking about local issues? https://t.co/JcFEWS83RW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great #labourdoorstep team campaigning in Splott this morning. Love to chat with residents about local issues https://t.co/E7UAz9N8Z3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#LALALAND was brilliant. Me and Berry even had a little dance on the way back to the car]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's Friday afternoon which means another house call to a resident. Important Cllrs are able to do this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gw7hoc she did surgeries. Apparently this is team? Where is their Cllr? https://t.co/QeYLK14vjS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neiljmcevoy @JamieMatthews84 @Grettaelaine @LeanneWood @Plaid_Cymru when was she last in Splott?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neiljmcevoy @WalesOnline @JamieMatthews84 @Grettaelaine @LeanneWood @Plaid_Cymru I'll try again. When is Her next surgery?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SiobhanCorria Plaid put out calendar in Splott today. No information on how to contact their Splott Cllr and Dep leader in Cardiff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neiljmcevoy @WalesOnline @JamieMatthews84 @Grettaelaine @LeanneWood @Plaid_Cymru when's her next surgery?  Jamie fancy going?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neiljmcevoy @JamieMatthews84 @Grettaelaine @LeanneWood @Plaid_Cymru as do I. Your dep leader and Splott Cllr lives in Saundersfoot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neiljmcevoy she is your Sep leader inCardiff. When was she last in Splott?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neiljmcevoy @JamieMatthews84 @Grettaelaine @LeanneWood @Plaid_Cymru when's her next Splott surgery? When was she last in Splott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home after a good meeting with @thebunsrfc, they want to speak to @PEBradbury. Its dry January so a cup of tea is in order]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoodwayCardiff no but it was a better perspective for the photo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outside the Moorland Community Centre ready for Labour Councillors surgery. Pop along if I can help with anything https://t.co/lSjqoPoUbZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New £4 million school to be built but not the same distance from everyone. https://t.co/DAZmlGBjFB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gw7hoc @GHawke123 that's correct it will be near the Maltings. Lewis Road.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would be great to hear from Yshol Glan Morfa parents about the new school.  In particular what we can do to encoura… https://t.co/VNWsto3Bpp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More good news 4 Splott, Tremorfa and Pengam Green. The planning application 4 the areas 1st new school in more than a generation submitted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Following significant lobbying by myself and @huwthomas_Wales we have a prov date for the resurfacing of Splott Rd, the 28th of Jan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SDoughtyMP @jgfoxy @thebunsrfc @SplottBoy @swpcardiff @cardiffcouncil @huwthomas_Wales meeting with Club next week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovely news that soft play started at the @oasiscardiff today. Pleased to have been able to help secure equipment #splott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning picking up local issues and asking ppl to vote for the Moorland Community in #Tremorfa https://t.co/lnkyWeu0Y8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@louclarkie @inksplott @huwthomas_Wales @tidySTARtweets @cardiffcouncil hopefully people will check again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@louclarkie @inksplott @huwthomas_Wales @tidySTARtweets that is not good @cardiffcouncil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@louclarkie @inksplott @huwthomas_Wales @tidySTARtweets oh dear. Hope they didn't say to many others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't forget it's Friday bin collections in Splott this week due to the bank holiday https://t.co/DUuKj5yibw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please help and vote https://t.co/7QB3w2NLi7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/4XCWAOueR1 training staff to be more mental health aware. @cardiffcouncil we should be doing this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mzdrennan @cardiffcouncil I don't issue any publications but agree the council should miss no opportunity to promote the free collections]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@cardiffcouncil issued 86 Fixed Penalty Notices between April and Nov in Splott ward for waste etc and launched 23 prosecutions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great sign put up by resident in Clydesmuir Road  #Tremorfa. I agree with them. #lovewhereyoulive https://t.co/tcFNwOrVfI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Christmas from an unseasonably warm Habershon Street #Splott https://t.co/uYHy7amaY6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delivering th #Splott Labour Christmas calendar with @huwthomas_Wales. We reported one or two things to… https://t.co/dOLMxUAgkA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beicio @huwthomas_Wales @LidlUK big oversight. Surely can be sorted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is when your bins will be collected in Cardiff over Christmas https://t.co/4Gc6QFDj9o thanks @ruthmosalski]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@louclarkie @PIXIES apparently he has barely said a word all tour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @PIXIES were pretty good tonight #debaser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahgoughy @BroadcastCJS  I was emailed on the 15th of June by one of the parents about both incidents. Will ask if I can share]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahgoughy @BroadcastCJS @cardiffcouncil incidents happened on 3 and 14 of June]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahgoughy @BroadcastCJS @cardiffcouncil bridge closed in late July after both incidents happened.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@inksplott @STARcomms1st hurray. Well deserved]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 years ago today we got married #celebrating https://t.co/0QEQDTixJX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mzdrennan I am trying to keep it healthy, so just bacon and brown sauce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bacon bap from Carlise Bakery #Splott? Well it is #SmallBusinessSaturday #shoplocal https://t.co/Hyeq6nIM1J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoodwayCardiff @cardiffwest well done. We are all accountable to party members]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just been to speak to the lovely residents on Moorland Road about network rail and parking. They are very reasonable people @networkrail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cardiffbites  we have come to a reasonable agreement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RubiconDance @cardiffcouncil @CardiffKWT @AdamsdownLab @HitachiEurope can you help? The behaviour of a few is impacting on whole community]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RubiconDance @cardiffcouncil @CardiffKWT @AdamsdownLab wonder if @HitachiEurope could say what store it was sold in #catchandfine]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>