<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[A daily reminder if you're walking anywhere to PLEASE PLEASE look both ways before crossing the street. It can mean life or death.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WeAccept all who wish to come to America, who flee persecution, and all who choose love over hate. https://t.co/gGsBlOhvYG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Much of America is still very reactionary and anti-intellectual. So we still have a lot of work to do to educate our peers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can equality be elitist when America's elite have been and still are very much WHITE and MALE?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THIS. THIS. SO MUCH THIS. https://t.co/nvbtgxjfEG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very alarming. Another sign of authoritarianism when there is disregard for checks and balances. https://t.co/vhLWRd13nF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, Kellyanne. You used three words. "Bowling Green massacre." And we'll continue to call out all of your lies and… https://t.co/QLcyMmJwH4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also lol at the MEP behind @SebDance who goes "Fuck it I'm not listening to a translation of this crap." https://t.co/BtvLP6v3CR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liberty AND justice for all. #TrumpBan #MuslimBan #NoBanNoWall https://t.co/ghuNWL4bj5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clearly the Trump team didn't do their homework...again. https://t.co/7zv66wvnvi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best thing I've ever seen in European politics. https://t.co/lmWhV5y292]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VP Well if you say so, let's have an election for the #SCOTUS seat. I vote for Merrick Garland. #MerrickGarland2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Third #MorningFact: Betsy DeVos said that a school should have guns because of grizzly bears. Trump wants her to be in charge of education.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#AlternativeFact: The #BowlingGreen massacre was a real tragedy that we mourn this week. Also, unicorns are real.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Second #MorningFact: The U.S. contributes to 22% of the @UN budget. The WH drafted an EO to cut this. (@PolitiFact: https://t.co/jrDQIw9000)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Myth: #Immigrants don't pay taxes. Fact: Almost all immigrants in the U.S. pay income taxes. (@ACLU: https://t.co/wwxVEqFm3X)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SHIT. FASCIST ALERT. FASCIST ALERT. https://t.co/W04eD0nzDa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The truth hurts, America. The truth fucking hurts, doesn't it? https://t.co/iNofea7e85]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crowd gathers outside the #SupremeCourt in Washington DC. No sign of any stop to the protests against the… https://t.co/CYJVxmc09J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Morning fact of the day: In 2016 the US admitted more refugees from the DR Congo than from Syria. About 4,000 more. https://t.co/1dAcm42kIL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The Secretary of State requests to permit the citizen named herein to pass without delay or hindrance." -Every US… https://t.co/GpCaYQqKhp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ffs, Mr. Trump, is this one of the enemies you're referring to? #NoBanNoWall https://t.co/PLDaKnmGdS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The shadow government of Steve Bannon and his puppet strings over the White House must be stopped.… https://t.co/1K6u4eognE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing like waking up to a good Sunday morning with some FACTS. We should make facts the new breakfast cereal.… https://t.co/pcXkdd0uuh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@calopph I agree that sexual assault is horrible, but what does that have to do w/ refugees/immigrants/Muslims? These ppl aren't criminals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One small victory against fascism. But let's not stop now. The fight is far from over. #MuslimBan #NoBanNoWall https://t.co/ACBZZtIuy7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No hate, no fear, EVERYONE is welcome here. #MuslimBan #NoBanNoWall #DullesAirport https://t.co/mmcFxZSaiL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ItWasSoAwesomeWhen refugees could find a new home in the United States, back when they weren't treated like terrorists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While government is kind of in chaos right now, let's remember not to panic. Not everyone has left...yet. https://t.co/g6dCYJJoe2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you for your service. Seriously. Thank you. https://t.co/okIa2Lx1C3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only "America First" policy I will live by is that I will always be loyal to America first before Trump. #DissentIsPatriotic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This message still stands. Remember to breathe, drink water, and take good care of yourself. https://t.co/8ISftSWjjB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarackObama Citizen Obama! Welcome back. 😊 It's good to have you with us. Rest well, you deserve it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Resistance is strong, even in the nation's capital. https://t.co/j12inrYEAr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And right on cue at 12:00, it has started raining. How appropriate for our new President.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@POTUS It's gonna be weird seeing all of these Tweets under President Trump's name. But for one last time...THANK YOU, BARACK OBAMA!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One last look at the https://t.co/9oJIw7pZ7w homepage with #PresidentObama. https://t.co/UttplGqsPs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first President I voted for and the first President I worked for. You may be leaving the White House but you wi… https://t.co/bg90gVsSvH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Try this, because you might learn something about our outgoing #POTUS. I certainly did.

https://t.co/KyNEwBO4Z0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An interesting read on one of our several outgoing U.S. Ambassadors. https://t.co/FFWsKxHJLY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dare I say it, Trump's least insane Cabinet pick? https://t.co/8nkfY3co4l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay, granted Donald Trump didn't hang this portrait himself. But still, he would hang a flattering picture of himself. Because egotism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is totally what dictators would do - hang younger, more attractive portraits of themselves to celebrate their… https://t.co/NPNRGdORdj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because this is totally how intelligence briefings are supposed to work. *sarcasm sarcasm* https://t.co/6rsC8npqOf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Truly, the winds of change are blowing. A storm is coming through the world this January. https://t.co/lEDkUg0BDi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you to the @BreakingNews team for keeping me informed and in the loop. You were absolutely a great resource - one of my favorite apps.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When in doubt, blow it up and start again. Welcome #2017. 🎉 #HappyNewYear https://t.co/YEYfRBQHua]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Why is Kerry speaking about this now?" you ask? Well, if you were basically warning that Armageddon is coming, what is there to lose?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JohnKerry in one of his final speeches sounds pretty angry and dire. Like "Look, you fuckers, at the mess you've made."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real talk with @JohnKerry: "The two-state solution is in serious jeopardy."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh dear. If this is some alternate reality that I'm not supposed to be in, can I please go home now? https://t.co/ybMejNAjjC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NationalChristmasTree #MerryChristmas #HappyHolidays https://t.co/SGBJZXLS0l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no winner in nuclear war. No one outlasts anyone. https://t.co/fb74VbLWjN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like this witch hunt is only getting started... https://t.co/V01EfmECdY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well in fairness, I'd be very unhappy too if I realized I was a pompous, misogynistic jerk that no one liked... https://t.co/NwjPSMoje4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am genuinely concerned that Donald Trump might be the first President in over 70 years to deploy a nuclear weapon… https://t.co/sEketwXNad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fact: Hillary Clinton won the popular vote. Do not forget that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much violence today. Russian amb to Turkey dead, Islamic Center in Zurich shot, and now some dead in Berlin. 2016 can't get any worse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chris Suprun, faithless GOP elector, speaking in Washington DC! #FlipTheVote https://t.co/CSZuppmCpl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inspired to hear from @DanielleMuscato in Washington DC today. #FlipTheVote https://t.co/oJ6IV2pZWY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*sigh* https://t.co/DrmwTCjGSY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd definitely vote for this Mike Pence. https://t.co/XciVx0M0Vq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/y8eCDPWhdP "I'm like a really smart person" is the sort of thing a high school student desperate to be popular would say.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By "intelligence" briefings, it's not a briefing about your smartness, Mr. Trump. It's NATIONAL SECURITY we're discussing. For fuck's sake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In an alternate universe where @HillaryClinton was elected, people are wondering about how we are doing in our own universe with PE Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But most importantly, #RexTillerson has ZERO experience in government or diplomacy. ZERO experience, yet he will be our #SecretaryofState.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#RexTillerson, Trump's SecState pick, opposes sanctions on Russia and supports free trade.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to let it sink in. It's U.S. Secretary of State Rex Tillerson in 2017. https://t.co/s9d0hokNJC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry, can you like....not do that? Please? This isn't cool. #ClimateChangeIsReal https://t.co/YdIuIHpwtX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you were stuck on a deserted island with @realDonaldTrump, what would you do? #Thoughtsatwork]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THANK THE LORD IT ISN'T GIULIANI. Let's get a decent, diplomatic, not-so-evil #SecretaryofState. Please? https://t.co/VuV6BRRLgN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This contest for #SecretaryofState truly is a choosing of the lesser of two (or in this case, twenty) evils.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only 6 weeks until political doomsday. #Inauguration2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's been a tough first week. But there's nowhere to go but up. @… https://t.co/dlRqPdGsWO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember to breathe today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Do not go gentle into that good night. Rage, rage against the dying of the light."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow is the day. Either the Ascension...or Armageddon. #Election2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True then, true now. #motivation https://t.co/6eBpsXiw6D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @StateDept's #ForeignService #Internship Program (USFSIP) is now accepting applications until Sept. 30!… https://t.co/x09ksK7dY5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not Sarah Palin, but I think I can see Russia from here... @… https://t.co/PF2ZuBuNXd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Evening glass of wine at the top of #tbilisi @ Tbilisi Hilltop https://t.co/BqAtPVGf7W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To my surprise, I have passed the #ForeignService Officer Test! Another small step towards becoming a diplomat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Graduated from @AntiochCollege, class of 2016. I will not forget my time here. Now it is on to even greater things. https://t.co/60cSkTpgeU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow. @ Antioch College https://t.co/n2JsB8ykB1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[54 pages. 10 months of work. My #SeniorThesis is done. @ Antioch… https://t.co/FoQHEjh6up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I dare you to check this out. And then think about what you asked and why you asked it. #TheFutureisOurs https://t.co/m4lYPAsUIE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The best way to find yourself is to lose yourself in the service of others." #ForeignService http://t.co/2HWmQNFPqU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the Milan #Expo2015 today! http://t.co/jFPHKidyBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Euros are colorful. Not like our US dollars - too much green.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi, Pluto!! #PlutoFlyby https://t.co/rWCKUHJ8zT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sad day yesterday in the #UNSC. #Veto power is an abusive privilege. https://t.co/Ig9GekR9gL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing weekend at @AntiochCollege for the first Commencement since 2008. Things will not be the same from here on out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dreams can become stories. #USFSIP #StateDept #ForeignService http://t.co/hx1n7MPP0W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great send-off to a great spring term with @anlackovich's Displaced Peoples class: the 29th session of HRC. #HRC29 https://t.co/QNfss1BQlc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ICC has called on South Africa to #ArrestBashir at the African Union summit for #Darfur crimes! @anlackovich https://t.co/PcljypI0WJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had the honor of working with @DiplomacyCenter at @StateDept last fall. I'm thrilled about the progress it's made. http://t.co/vVuYIN7fuo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's victory for the #Democrats at tonight's congressional baseball game. #GoodGame http://t.co/yix1vDif43]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A chilling picture of the consequences of the #Syria crisis. @anlackovich  https://t.co/JE13yOuqjI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy #NationalBestFriendsDay, @Sara_Goldstein. I could not have made it without you, partner. I miss you so much. &lt;3 http://t.co/GNQuXaZzLE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our funding solutions may not have been too far-fetched after all! @anlackovich  https://t.co/FWDVVciatC]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>