<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Win one of two FREE pairs of Yeezy Boost 350 V2 by following @KicksDealsCa. Canada only. Follow them and enter here: https://t.co/zmdyEq3bmu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to @KicksDeals on their 5 year anniversary! They're giving away Yeezys, Jordans and more to celebrate: https://t.co/kyCiHokvwR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatttLodato switch time zones bud. Your like 4 hours behind the rest of us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@staceycoourt watch season 4. Its the shitty season before they hired back the guy who created it after they fired him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatttLodato remember your tissues for FIFA. You'll need em]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatttLodato top way to tell a girl she's uglier than all her friends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@meganmurphy02 serves you right for trying to make a rezzy at jack astors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@meganmurphy02 if it did I was probably too blackout to remember it. I also have the voice of an angel so that might be it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[iPhone just wanted to autocorrect photoshoots to photo hoot. Wtf is a photo hoot. A photoshoot for owls?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life's all fun and gains until you can't move your neck anymore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is no one going to make a joke that the first Japanese goal was scored by Honda. ANYONE?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Working the elections you realize just how terrible people are at following directions. If you can't find the door you shouldn't get to vote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My life goal is to be a big enough deal that Microsoft word will auto correct my name]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AllanSchwenger Feel ya bro. Feel like I'm in the third season of dexter #skinned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatttLodato is it a toronto custom to shoot ones self in the foot?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatttLodato if you've seen season 4 just stop and save yourself the agony.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@staceycoourt if I didn't know Allan was home all day there would be some many jokes coming your way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never trust atoms, they make up everything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatttLodato so your majoring in getting jobs? How about you keep one. #figureitout]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@staceycoourt what contract says you can't have a waterbed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are waterbeds not a thing anymore?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DerekLasovich dude I'm pretty much living my life one Hannibal episode to the next. The rest is a blur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of my dreams is to be pulled off the street to play ball with a crew of Asians]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Ah, yes, divorce, from the Latin word meaning to rip out a man's genitals through his wallet." -- Robin Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too hung for this lab mannnnnn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AllanSchwenger @viclogan this is quality at its finest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatttLodato why did you retweet "all hussle no luck". You haven't left the couch in 2 weeks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's cooler than being cool? CANADA! You are fucking ice cold]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TeamCanada looks like the team you made in NHL 2003 when you traded all the good players to one team]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kadri's playing like a 4th line player out there. More like a player whose on his 4th line of coke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noelfg apparently the bill for the child is. Zing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[13 dollar cover at Gracie's. I could feed my future pregnancy scare with that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noelfg I don't think even Sean Paul has accomplished that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["How do you not have skid marks on your underwear the way your talking out of your ass" - me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I should be a background actor. I've been pretending to do shit my whole life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found a song called back door Santa.  On a completely non-related note I just came up with an awesome new porn movie name]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also I am done exams. There's a snowstorm tomorrow. Well tonight there's going to be a BRAINSTORM for igloo activities tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I get to shave my beard tomorrow I'm so happy" "Ya it's like trimming the baby fat" after exam quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DerekLasovich so it looks like the alcohol couldn't decide if that was a quote or not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Hey Matt. Why you wearing jeans? Are you going to a wedding?" @MatttLodato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bitches love the pea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm surprised kessel didn't break the net with that shot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@meganmurphy02 would the dicks all be in a plastic bag or paper bag? Would friday have to suck the bag of dicks or the dicks themselves?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All engineers should be given a blowup doll at frosh but its only holes are in its ears so that they can complain to it about their workload]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatttLodato you and me buddy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's the best part about giving an engineer a blowjob? He will always be able to tell you how big the load will be #mechanicshumor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. What the fuck happened last night]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@themorgshow see ya there bud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emilymross23 there's no way you haven't done any lsd in the past 36 hours]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently neil armstrong used to tell unfunny jokes about the moon and follow them up with "ah I guess you had to be there."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mac can suck my cack. Ooh kill em #GryphonPride #homecoming]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noelfg shut the fuck up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home fucking Coming! Let's fire it up #gryphons #earlymorningbooze]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@meganmurphy02 its probably the such your more worried about]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@meganmurphy02 what's all the commotion about over there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If people were onions there would be no war, only onions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money can't buy happiness, but I'd rather cry in a mercedes benz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mechanics TA has been in canada for 15 days and barely speaks english. I know math is a universal language but this is ridiculous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Man when I was in your room earlier. The ceiling was pretty fucking nuts"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shout out to sidewalks for keeping me off the streets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I had an accent there would be no stopping me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I lost 110 bucks at the casino last night. Call me rain man #anditsgone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Steeezy_Steeve  3 months in advance. It's an Olympic event]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 teams. 4 people per team. 7 beers a person. 4 grams a team. 1 XL pizza a team. #victory]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Falcone94 @stracogna17 come make a detour by blackout city boys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drake stayed at the Muskoka resort I work at last night]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found out my dad appraised drakes owl chain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the blowjob bandit strikes again #cleves]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stracogna17 I thought you were allergic to dogs not being a pussy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stracogna17 but the strawberry has such a better operating system]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 day benders ain't shit in Muskoka. Ready for first week back at Guelph already]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emilymross23 I'm here where are you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emilymross23 I'm on route to the kee right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need a beer cause I don't know what to do with my hands]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stracogna17 @emilymross23 how about Muskoka with @MattTatarsky?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noelfg @JCarbs9 wants his Adidas sweater back from cuzzy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatttLodato last night in Rome 2night Im peacing back to toronto for tomorrow the off to Muskoka for the rest of the summer #worldtraveler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatttLodato "@MattTatarsky: @MatttLodato you would die in Spain. The girls asses here jeez. I could rest a beer on that shit" I'm a prophet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching girls get kicked out of the Vatican for showing their knees #sluts #GodsHouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stracogna17 we fled to Europe to avoid you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Future college students: make a budget of the bare minimum you can live on. Then cut that in half. Soon you'll wish you had that much money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DerekLasovich @meganmurphy02 I mainly thought it was a movie based around the lesbian scene of Natalie portman and mila kunis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AllanSchwenger best version of wagon wheel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gonna need a compass to find Kim kardashians kid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatttLodato I'm in Barcelona til Sunday. Sucks that I am missing you bro. You might not come back to Guelph after you see this shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatttLodato you would die in Spain. The girls asses here jeez. I could rest a beer on that shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys trying too hard to get the k in this hostel #languagebarrier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatttLodato I swear to God I'm looking at the Asian you right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being shitfaced in another country is the same...EXCEPT ITS WAY BETTER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Amsterdam. Pray for my soul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Father's Day is the day dads get to relax and chill. Like they did everyday before they were dads]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't have your dad on Facebook then don't post pics of him on Father's Day wishing him a happy Father's Day. He won't see it...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top floor living #germany http://t.co/Hsy8afnxz7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They call me nemo. Because I touched the butt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@meganmurphy02 pretty sure thats not what that means]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sucks that I can't be ripped for this flight. But them again time travel would be too much for me #timedifference]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting that blood alcohol level up for this flight. Babies won't be the biggest problem on this flight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never got the idea of asking someone else's girlfriend/boyfriend to prom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clear alcohols are for rich women on diets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whenever I see DD I always think BOOBS before designated driver]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>