<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@halo_mess feel like I missed a lot today but it might have been a good thing ðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miejorgensen @rianne666 totally. She should think before she speaks x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miejorgensen @rianne666 yeah she literally says his name for attention again x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miejorgensen @rianne666 ugh that's horrible but not surprising from her. She seriously would do anything for attention x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rianne666 @miejorgensen oh no. What drama did I miss now? ðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@larrymybabiesx totally think he wouldn't be liking so many if it wasn't a good sign for season 4 ðŸ˜Š x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@larrymybabiesx love it. He is literally their biggest fan ðŸ˜ŠðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes so much. Can we please get the season 4 trailer already ðŸ’šðŸ˜‚ x https://t.co/V7Jzw2DaFN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rianne666 @Shannonbradfie3 don't get what the big deal is. So what if he did follow her anyway ðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nvanmeter the whole thing is ridiculous. Drama over nothing as usual ðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@larrymybabiesx @Jabberwocky_7 totally why is there drama over nothing ðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Blowjobshire same. You think by now it would be different x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Blowjobshire yeah. Ridiculous how they can't even stand next to someone without people saying they are dating x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheBoyStyles @racontreur yeah or heaven forbid they actually stand next to each other ðŸ˜ŠðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessxHazza yes that can be a problem for us too ðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessxHazza same. He is so lucky to have that fashion sense ðŸ˜ŠðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessxHazza totally. Well he looks so in everything ðŸ˜ŠðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessxHazza love that his hair longer. And the red coat looks so good on him ðŸ˜ðŸ’š x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_SouffleGirl_ yeah not everything has to be said on here ðŸ˜Š x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_SouffleGirl_ totally you know he said it to Nick in private anyway. That's more important ðŸ’šðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessxHazza probably . Guess he's just keeping more of a low profile on his work now x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessxHazza true thats totally his style ðŸ˜ŠðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessxHazza same. Seems like he is more quiet than usual since he arrived ðŸ‘€ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessxHazza yeah so happy they have MIA time but miss him so much ðŸ’šðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@My_Joy_89 @Blowjobshire agree. They totally deserve it x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Blowjobshire @My_Joy_89 let's hope. Louis looks really happy now ðŸ˜ŠðŸ’™  x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@My_Joy_89 @Blowjobshire true ðŸ˜‚. But especially since he hasn't really been seen since the airport ðŸ‘€ðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Blowjobshire totally. And another coincidence H has been MIA ðŸ˜ŠðŸ’™ðŸ’š x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@My_Joy_89 @LarryEvakAsFk yeah. At least H has a restraining order against her ðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@My_Joy_89 @LarryEvakAsFk totally. Nothing is surprising about that x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LarryEvakAsFk @My_Joy_89 totally. Let's hope he won't stop for her anymore x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@halo_mess @Blowjobshire totally rubbish as usual. Everyone knows to ignore it anyway x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nickcarter hi Nick. How about a tweet? Haven't seen you since the cruise ðŸ˜˜ðŸ’š x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@larrymybabiesx he knows exactly what he's doing ðŸ’™ðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@larrymybabiesx he is so gorgeous. Love the jacket and rose t-shirt ðŸ˜ðŸ’šðŸ’™ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Happily_7 totally. You are happy for him to have the break but miss him so much ðŸ’šðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NattyHemmlinson @Blowjobshire yeah exactly. He will survive the early start somehow ðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NattyHemmlinson @Blowjobshire yeah. Though can totally understand him to be fair ðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@larrymybabiesx @LarryEvakAsFk totally. Just them cuddling all day ðŸ’š x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@larrymybabiesx @LarryEvakAsFk same. That scene is still my favourite ðŸ˜ðŸ’š x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@I_heart_sunsets @BlondeAmbition8 @nickcarter exactly. That is so true ðŸ˜Š x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlondeAmbition8 @I_heart_sunsets @nickcarter as Karla said said you never know when they are lurking ðŸ˜˜ðŸ˜Š x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@I_heart_sunsets @BlondeAmbition8 @nickcarter same. Well we can't give up ðŸ˜ŠðŸ’š x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@I_heart_sunsets @BlondeAmbition8 @nickcarter so true. Well I'm sure I have to get one soon ðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlondeAmbition8 @I_heart_sunsets that's awesome. I'm waiting for my first tweet this year ðŸ’šðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlondeAmbition8 @nickcarter @I_heart_sunsets aww your lucky ðŸ˜Š. Seems impossible to get a tweet from him lately ðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nickcarter hi Nick. Been ages since I got a tweet. How about a hello? ðŸ˜˜ðŸ’• x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nvanmeter yeah who cares what he might say in an interview. They are always scripted anyway x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nvanmeter totally I find it better to ignore the rest of the drama. No point in getting worked up over nothing ðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LouGirl_4 Hopefully . Like even at a party or something. Would take anything ðŸ˜ŠðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LouGirl_4 miss seeing them too. Can they all just hang out together ðŸ’™ðŸ’š x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItIsWhatItIsHL @nvanmeter no. They are the worst ever at being subtle ðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@My_Joy_89 @JessxHazza exactly. Anyway best not to give her more attention x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@My_Joy_89 @JessxHazza oh that would explain a lot. You think she would be embarrassed  but that's how desperate they are x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessxHazza I know. Totally unfair how the same stalkers get pictures all the time x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lwtjunkie @Blowjobshire totally.  He still says us to after his apparent break up ðŸ˜ŠðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Blowjobshire maybe he knows we have realised he's not 5 foot 9 ðŸ˜ŠðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LouGirl_4 so gorgeous . He must love killing us ðŸ˜ðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Blowjobshire @nvanmeter We totally need it. Maybe filming is starting soon x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Blowjobshire @nvanmeter same. Secretly hope we get one of Tarjei hanging out with him too ðŸ˜ŠðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@henriksmoe can Tarjei join them too. That would make it more awesome ðŸ˜ŠðŸ’š x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@larrymybabiesx totally. Maybe it means he'll have to talk about something he doesn't want to on Jimmy Fallon. We'll see like you said ðŸ‘€ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@larrymybabiesx so gorgeous. Hope he's not trying to warn us about something ðŸ’™ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LouGirl_4 so awesome he's doing some US promo too ðŸ˜ŠðŸ’™ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LarryEvakAsFk @larrymybabiesx yeah his smile is the best ðŸ˜ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LarryEvakAsFk @larrymybabiesx true we have to hear something soon ðŸ’š x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@larrymybabiesx @LarryEvakAsFk that's ok too ðŸ˜‚. Just wish we could get some news about the trailer already ðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LarryEvakAsFk @larrymybabiesx totally. And fanfics ðŸ˜ŠðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@larrymybabiesx @LarryEvakAsFk I guess. I've been watching season 1 to help ðŸ˜Š x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LarryEvakAsFk @larrymybabiesx yeah withdrawals are pretty bad right now ðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LarryEvakAsFk @larrymybabiesx so cute. Miss them so much ðŸ’šðŸ’™ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiaBarber @misfitstylinson yeah they know that we knew ðŸ˜ŠðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiaBarber @misfitstylinson totally. As Louis said he knows we know ðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiaBarber @misfitstylinson yes I have to agree. The black and white is so H ðŸ‘€ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LouGirl_4 he looks so good in it. Hope we get better pictures ðŸ˜ðŸ’š x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucyevakcom even though the ending of that episode was bad most of the scenes were amazing ðŸ˜ðŸ’š x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Blowjobshire yeah and Louis shaving his beard. Guess that's just another coincidence ðŸ‘€ðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Heather_1705 @asilia1981 exactly you feel most sorry for him in this situation ðŸ’™ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emma_25_ totally. Have to love all these hints he gives us ðŸ˜ŠðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Heather_1705 @asilia1981 yeah. It's sad how they use the baby for attention x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Blowjobshire @AllTheLove_C_ exactly. They make it so obvious ðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Blowjobshire @LilClumsyBird totally. Won't be surprised if we wake up to certain pictures ðŸ‘€ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LouGirl_4 they seem to have such a cute friendship ðŸ˜Š x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nvanmeter @SimplyCharlie_ I know they seem to have grown up so fast it's crazy x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@asilia1981 totally. It's so good to see him smiling again ðŸ˜ðŸ’™ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@My_Joy_89 @larrymybabiesx @butterfly73 it's ok. All good fun ðŸ˜ŠðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@My_Joy_89 @larrymybabiesx @butterfly73 came back to 13 mentions ðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@butterfly73 @larrymybabiesx @My_Joy_89 @Blowjobshire agree with that. He is a good combination of the two ðŸ˜ðŸ’š x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@My_Joy_89 @butterfly73 @larrymybabiesx @Blowjobshire totally. Guess they can all pull off any style ðŸ˜ŠðŸ’š x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@butterfly73 @My_Joy_89 @larrymybabiesx @Blowjobshire I said this ages ago. Tarjei reminded me of Harry ðŸ’šðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LarryEvakAsFk didn't know that.  if they really did break up it could be a dig then x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LarryEvakAsFk exactly he could just say it was anything ðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LarryEvakAsFk same don't feel like he would tell us so easy ðŸ‘€ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Blowjobshire of all things I wasn't expecting it to be that   ðŸ˜ŠðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessxHazza exactly he will surprise us. Just keep a eye on him ðŸ‘€ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessxHazza I doubt he will but at the same time that totally something he would do to us   ðŸ’šðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@larrymybabiesx yeah no way she doesn't know ðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@larrymybabiesx totally. I'm sure she has everything ready for season 4 too and is just teasing us ðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@larrymybabiesx that's amazing they had Isak's season planned so early ðŸ’š x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@larrymybabiesx So unfair. of course they want to keep us waiting ðŸ˜‚ x]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>