<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Stressing the fuck out over my college interview in the morning, can't sleep ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@frankcarter23 @therattlesnakes killed it as always, Paris has a different vibe than UK but it makes me more excited to see them in Cardiff!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mostly watch Come Dine With Me for the narrator]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you've been listening to a song for a good 10 years, but the lyrics only just hit you..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*insert copious amounts of swearwords that resembles how much I hate everyone and everything here*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would love to go for a run tomorrow but my knee is still staying no. I need to find some new ways to clear my head.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so ready to come back home to Bristol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hopefully will be doing something super drastic to my hair in the next few days ðŸ˜ŠðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been seeing all sorts of my favourite bands being announced at festivals all over the world, giving me hope for the uk!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["vegan sex is the best sex"... I'm sorry what?!?!?! How can your diet affect your sex life?!?!??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MollyTurville we'll eat enough on their behalf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MollyTurville I definitely could go for a cheeky nandos with the lads]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@therattlesnakes @BiffyClyro @frankcarter23 haha no she's definitely not :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surprising my mum with a trip to Paris to see @BiffyClyro and @frankcarter23 @therattlesnakes ðŸ—¼ I love Christmas ðŸŽ„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silently waiting for @donaldglover to do a tour and have a UK leg of said tour ðŸ™„ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The mental health system is appalling. Got pressured to go to my gp, I did, I have now been waiting two weeks for a referral. Waste of time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of my housemates is French, and honestly her accent makes me swoon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nah actually convinced my work is haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snacking on hazelnuts and raisins.. Who am I ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lordofdacats ye no I know, but it's still weird, right? ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weird thought for the day.. Isn't it weird we all swing our arms when we walk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back and neck in pain from small and ill fitted bras, knee in agony from dislocating in June so sleeping with lots of pillows and heatpacksðŸ˜”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Counting down the days 'til pay day.. I hate 5 week months with a passion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm checking out the first 5 minutes of @RockyHorrorFOX now! #Trixie #RockyHorror
https://t.co/II3g1VKZEN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I forgot how much I hate the radio but then again I'm way too tired to think about what I want to listen to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your girlfriend isn't a goth just because her "whole wardrobe is black" and she's "arty and spiritual" and wears a choker..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I saw Barenaked Ladies perform The Big Bang Theory theme song (which they wrote) tonight in work.. I love my job ðŸ˜ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Decided to take up a hobby.. I'm going to learn to play the ukulele]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nooooooooo why do spiders feel the need to take up residence in my room, fuck off outta here!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's so so sad how much we get shut down for expressing our feelings, whether it be a lover, a parent, a friend, or a boss. Its wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[October: tickets for @youmeatsix and @bmthofficial 
November: tickets for @Slaves and @frankcarter23 @therattlesnakes fuck I love gig season]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still can't get over the fact I cut all my hair off ðŸ˜‚ love it tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh man, codeine is fantastic..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beyond fucked off with making fuck loads of phone calls trying to sort out tax and chasing up my last employers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Omg yas, so excited for some of my best baes coming to visit me this weekend @buddyluii and Molly and my brothers ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I honestly recommended everyone works in a gig venue at least once in their life..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still don't understand unsolicited dick pics.. Like no.. I give you no reason to send them.. So please stop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually worry about myself ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting away for a week due to problems, sofa hopping between Bristol and London, Â£15 to my name. Fuck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes when you've been fighting for so long, the only option you have left is to run.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is it so hard to be happy ðŸ˜”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sleeping on my shitty mattress after being on a water bed all week doesn't feel right and I don't like it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such an amazing week in Newcastle, genuinely upset I'm coming home ðŸ˜”ðŸ˜”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't wanna come home on Friday ðŸ˜”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want a water bed, they're so comfy and fun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hi5swandive omg that's hilarious ðŸ˜‚ ðŸ˜‚ ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I've broken my toe.. But I'm not sure how.. It just hurts like I have.. I don't recall breaking my toe today.. But it hurts..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leishauh to Newcastle or Italy? Because I just found ones to Italy for Â£70 ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is it cheaper for me to fly to fucking Italy than it is to Newcastle?!?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Soooo ready to come home, so ill ðŸ˜”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That moment when you become really ill on holiday and you're potentially not fit to fly home.. Oh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unbelievably happy ðŸ˜Š ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lizzie_bryant @taya__bryant girl you need to try sipsmith gin! Pricey, but definitely worth it ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you said you'd wake up early and do something for your mum, but you didn't, and you know she's gonna be pissed all day now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It irritates me to see people with poor quality bedding]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leishauh I know ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ ps I miss you ðŸ’”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHY HAS IT TAKEN ME SO LONG TO LISTEN TO THE DILLINGER ESCAPE PLAN?!?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was suppose to have a friend stay over tonight but she couldn't, the only reason Im gutted is because I went to the effort to clean my roomðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck this shit I'm having a spliff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is it so fucking hard. Worst fucking two weeks of my life, I've never needed someone more than I have right now I'm so alone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Red Hot Chili Peppers new album, spliff and a curry on the way ðŸ‘ŒðŸ‘Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to be in Barcelona already, these past three weeks have been the worst for a very long time. (apart from Download) I need out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It would appear I have gained myself an obsessive cockney stalker. Well fuck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leishauh that's what I intended to do ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leishauh yesyesyesyesyesyesyes I can't fucking wait]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love my job so much, and couldn't be happier with where I am in life right now. Cardiff was a slow start, but a great change in my life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never appreciated tips as much as I have since working in waitressing, literally means to world to me that people appreciate my service]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been working in the restaurant for two weeks (5 days open to the public) and they're making me a supervisor. So proud and happy for myself ðŸ™Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's something about getting high as fuck and listening to Pink Floyd that is just so fucking chill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's so amazing to hear that I've been having the most and best feedback from customers to management in work ðŸ˜ I love my job so much]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leishauh yes please â¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In that crucial moment of needing to quickly decide if I'd rather chill in bed longer or if my appearance is more important for work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insidious is scary because of the fucking music]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crying like a baby at The Supervet.. Why am I doing this to myself?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cannot wait be back in Barcelona in July, in the mean time someone take me away for a few days ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The temptation I have to just up and move to Glasgow is ridiculous..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never been this frustrated by someone before.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's gonna be one of those days. Still haven't slept.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Morocco episode of Archer makes me want to be back in Morocco.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShenissaGovani legit wanted to punch her ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The temptation to shave the side of my head again and get it tattooed is ridiculous.. But then I would have to deal with shaved side upkeep.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShenissaGovani I thought I was the only one ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hairdressers Friday ðŸ™ŒðŸ™Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate living in a student area. Stop fucking singing it's a Monday night your cretins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leishauh same that's why I really wanna go ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leishauh that's a good deal ðŸ˜™]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't believe I got tickets for The Museum of Curiosity. I get to see @noelfielding11 the day before my birthday ðŸ˜ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So excited to be spending this bank holiday with @leishauh ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ first bank holiday I've had off for a while, pls can we go to grillstock tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got woken up by my mum multiple times today, all because she was putting my laundry away and cursing while doing so.. Where's the logic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way some people spell really grinds my gears, I can understand the odd one or two spelling mistakes but some people really take the piss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dude I was not expecting Sia to look like she does..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nearly 4 years later and you still fuck my head up. Cunt. Download is going to be a weird one this year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just went to crazy stalker mode real quick. Bitch I will hurt you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so glad it's gotten to the point of feeling sick whenever I have a cigarette]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The confidence is literally drowning me atm, I feel fucking fantastic ðŸ’ðŸ’]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This morning got me like.. https://t.co/gCWA37MzeO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't remember the last time I had a drink (apart from alcohol) that wasn't water.. My skin is so thankful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No food in the house so fish and chips it is ðŸ˜‚ again.. Work hard at the gym after this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My life is so fucking weird ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone asked me what I do for work, told them, they said they've never heard of it then simply replies with his number.. Bye felica âœ‹âœ‹]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>