<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Always pleased by an empty BA flight. \ω/ https://t.co/d0ebIKuzwP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@securitybrew I think a formalized process should be devised for this. An acronym that is based on the sound made when you get an excuse:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@securitybrew That is very true, we need to be aware of this when making jokes! So we add a 'swift whack with a mallet' as a precursor :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@securitybrew Can we not at least entertain the idea? Maybe temporary digital paralysis before complete removal for further infringements.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dermot86 Silver 5 atm, trying to get back to gold. Not played nearly enough though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dermot86 20/0/20, Perfect KDA. We expect it of you Dermot! Bronze 3, today Masters tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh god this is hilarious, in a terrifying kinda way. https://t.co/jLngkPTRcl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lets go @onfireScarlett you got this. Come support the foreign hope :D https://t.co/TVZPI4rCyG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cpt_Barricade But... but, the have no IPv4 left.... Who am I going to steal internet from.. https://t.co/qaZriRr7O8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@0xGradius Its a conglomerate of Chinese businessmen dedicated to giving you a great Reddit experience. Because china cares #alernativefacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daraobriain The baron Harkonnen was unimpressed with todays sportsball. https://t.co/cpVAbvvFqa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidrook We should ask @_ruby about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @discordapp why is the server channel order a server side function, rather than independently configurable per client, you make sads :'(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aidan_XOXO I only see GITS or XXX in cineworld, where you looking and i can check times? Not heard anything about new Underworld Movie tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aidan_XOXO Sure, when?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still seeing people I know using the Meitu app, can only show them the risk so many times, this is how identify theft happens :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RLewisReports @JacobNWolf Argumentum ad hominem, shame. Good to hear your side of the situation though. pce.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RLewisReports @JacobNWolf So instead of having a flare we've got to add tags for every pro/team/rioter/CC to RES. Such drama over nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RLewisReports @JacobNWolf or anyone else involved in the community NOT just rioters. That is the implication im trying to show. /3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RLewisReports @JacobNWolf than B3 Azir, this just aids that ingestion of information. The same is true for content creators /2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RLewisReports @JacobNWolf If I'm reading a thread about playing mid and I see a post by Bjerg i'm going to trust its content more /1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RLewisReports @JacobNWolf when someone who actually knows what theyre talking about is posting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RLewisReports @JacobNWolf Personally aside from a few I cant tell one redditor from the other, id like to be able to see more easily /1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RLewisReports @JacobNWolf I guess I have a trust that it was done genuinely to aid interaction. Maybe I'm wrong. Time will tell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RLewisReports @JacobNWolf If you wanna put it that way ok. Its starting with Pros and teams, the exact people is alas out of my control.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JacobNWolf @RLewisReports Agreed, Id prefer both had it as I've mentioned, visibility of content is awesome. Gotta start somewhere though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RLewisReports How that is handled at the time shows a more true reflection of the intent. At least in my opinion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RLewisReports Personally I would rather see some interaction with players rather than non. Its open to abuse, any platform is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jedlet123 I fully agree tbh, but it has to start somewhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RLewisReports but if the something gets a reaction like this, then whats the point? /4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RLewisReports like this? Im not in esports or a CM, these are just my thoughts. Just thinking that something is better than nothing. /3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RLewisReports enough so it was upped, now because they get something it makes it unfair to start there for reddit to make an action /2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RLewisReports Personally i'd like to see any pros. But they need to start somewhere. Teams in our leagues get cash, first it wasn’t /1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RVinceZeSports @RLewisReports Personally I think they would be great for content creators too, I have no input in reddit though. v0v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RLewisReports Maybe I read it incorrectly, but its appears to be a more focused at players / teams, Rioters are still under the riot flair.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RLewisReports Does it matter? Potentially boosts engagement and prevents impersonation. I thought that would be a good thing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So many tweets today, implying that politicians haven't been outright lying for years. This is nothing new :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@m19official I guess you missed the part where it sends all your personal info and phone data to china then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't use the Anime App guys. Its sending all your personal information to china...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FionnOnFire @RF_Legendary That app sends all your personal data to china btw ;) https://t.co/GRoRigLoDV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@0xGradius @MDisraeli Yea, that could be cool :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MDisraeli @0xGradius Time to crack out my HOTAS again. Lets see how it goes ^_^ I think my handle was CMDR Nymia. maybe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MDisraeli @0xGradius Though ive not played it in a while, may see if its changed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MDisraeli @0xGradius I was a combat pilot in eve, so I kinda took to that in ED right off. But it just feels so stale after you pop a few.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MDisraeli @0xGradius Couldnt get into E:D, it feels so, empty. Im hoping Star Citizen fixes that... when it comes out....:'(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@0xGradius @MDisraeli Not playing EvE... Still sits on jabber shit talking :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Regiteric Ooh nice, I may have to... borrow some of that ^_^]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MDisraeli For the most part I can say 'At least I dont play EvE any more.' but then @0xGradius comes along and makes it so tempting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MDisraeli Hah, yea and guys at work are like, come play WoW its gotten better again.... I have little enough time as it is &gt;.&gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will probably crack out another blog post soon on the ELK+Suricata setup, was good fun and who does love a good looking set of logs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MDisraeli Hah, yea its been a moth or so since I've sat down with it too. Lots of time off soon to catch up on everything; QC, Rain, MA3 :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RiotNymia Experimenting, breaking, re-configuring, playing. Its the best way to learn more, take what you play with and implement. #infosec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally finished setting up ELK + Suricata. Creating logstash filters and custom Suricata alert rules. Learning more about certain protocols]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MDisraeli Once a weeb, always a weeb :P I think I slept for about an hour the night I found QC. That was a long one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MDisraeli No, it could be gone by then, must read now. Tomorrow can be sponsored by Nescafe :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MDisraeli Yes you must. Don't let rationale get in the way of comics :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cabe_bedlam @ImJesicat @Leozaur You being the expert on the matter would know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paperghost @MadcapOcelot The only thing I have in the house is Tesco's own teabags :( *Angry Hissing*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MadcapOcelot save us Diarmaid, you're our only hope.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh god I'm out of coffee. Is delivery coffee a thing :/ https://t.co/BpEJZ84dON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenderCareDrL You need to curl that mustache a little bit more. Go full Salvador Dali for maximum evilness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sleeplesstwo @davidrook If you need advice on fail cascades you can try talking to @TomcatEvE :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SwiftOnSecurity cc @0xGradius *heavy breathing* :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[iNcontroL left EG? That's pretty era ending.. wow. Dont follow as much sc2 any more, but I thought he'd die there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seanconover Dont you enjoy feeling close to that last stranger. :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryancmoon Just gotta trust in your support to peel properly then :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryancmoon They have one. Its called a vayne. :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryancmoon Bitches love Rengar, so we made more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new Warwick looks sick, cant wait to give him a go :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ESEA was hacked at the end of December guys, if you used this site, your creds are very probably in the wild. #infosec #csgo #credentials]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@idolMariya we are but humble weebs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@idolMariya @Greavesy94 Every time she moves there is a special bag for @Perempt_ https://t.co/86KSqwmrPX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@idolMariya Add it to your wishlist &gt;.&gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having a discussion about #2FA and #password security on reddit, and some players are actually getting it. Victory :D #LeagueOfLegends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@M0ng00se77 If I wanted gruff comments, I wouldn't be coming to your lovely twitter, there are far grumpier grumps available :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a productive evening, got ELK setup and logging Apache, now to find all the other things to log... :D https://t.co/1wp1bMlnox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tatrix42 nah was more for tweets that go over 3/4 individuals, not long enough for a separate page. meh v0v :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hmmm, an app that lets you just type and then splits your tweets up and posts them for you.... please. &gt;.&gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Juliet_Shen @InfosecWomen Np, If you've done basics the Network+ may be suitable for you, if not the A+ is a bit more basic as starter, GL!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Juliet_Shen @InfosecWomen After you've look at that you can start to specialist more, there is so much to look at.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Juliet_Shen @InfosecWomen You can find them for free with the legends over at @cybraryIT ^_^]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Juliet_Shen @InfosecWomen Are a good start, some people dont like them, but depending on your level they can be a good initial step 2/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Juliet_Shen @InfosecWomen Depending on your level and who you ask you'll get different answers, but the CompTIA A+, Network+, Security+ /1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes please cc @0xGradius https://t.co/GJpVEhVOve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coffee plz. https://t.co/ps2jsHymHn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidrook The failure is ripe here, two tokens giving different codes, both work. Wut.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A wild tibbers has arrived at @riotgames  @MadcapOcelot https://t.co/otMg5SDm1K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyWilliams Tbh I have the same, any time I talk to a psych I over analyze it. Draw a house, a tree and a person? Time for an art degree]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gsuberland Have you tried looking backwards? Its always in the last place you look... huehue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidrook OH IM SORRY, AM I DISTRACTING YOU.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidrook You'd be sad without me about, admit it :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last day of holiday, I can finally go back to work tomorrow without getting yelled at. woop :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@0xGradius Implying you have to log into EvE to play it...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@securitybrew @theroxyd Hell yea, and if you don't get given that task, go find it. I don't get how people can be bored, doing what we do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theroxyd @securitybrew Working within your comfort zone is an unfortunate way to stay exactly where you are :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theroxyd Agreed, these are the best kinda tasks, means you can learn something new and give you a chance to appreciate what you do know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Greavesy94 @matrixlover12 @Albiiiiiiii @idolMariya Its party time :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@idolMariya Woot, strim time ^_^]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy New Year everyone! &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markofu @davidrook @riotgames They should have a man-off, we could gather lots of heavy things; tyres, weights, @MadcapOcelot playing Annie]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>