<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I work in pharma and this is very risky. https://t.co/sFqVcGnfOh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@guardian Selling arms to facilitate war crimes? Persecuting the poor, sick and disabled? Tax cuts for the rich, spending cuts for the rest?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join the club! Everyone who is anyone is in it. https://t.co/aF7E9j1rWM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@C_KAndrews @thecourieruk Absolute nonsense! Any evidence to support this ridiculous claim?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RuthDavidsonMSP @ScotTories You lot are terrified aren't you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottishlabour A lot of people want Independence to get away from right wing Tory rule, hardly an SNP obsession you morons! You]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I sort of miss the Tory boy idiots tweets since he blocked me. https://t.co/RkThNzpQO8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Humanity strikes back at @realDonaldTrump. Join the #WorldToTrump open letter that’s sweeping the planet! #Trump https://t.co/g7tpktzOwe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@torychum Unelected Tory spouting lies, who woulda thought it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not Britain's, Englands excruciating embrace, May with Trump today was pitiful. https://t.co/yxNKNcedCL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@denmarkinuk Nothing about your support of the barbaric pilot whale slaughter in the Faroes? Shame on you!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fucking state of that. https://t.co/WImKph6Xee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hoe this is true but from bitter experience I doubt it. https://t.co/AjQ34Nixik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank fuck I live in a soon to be independent Scotland and can ignore fascists like Banks https://t.co/AaIUoYNdXb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's because @BBCScotland are a bunch of Britnat propaganda merchants. https://t.co/QYe2O4m0ex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bbclaurak You are damaged goods but credit for keeping the right wing propeel guiltyaganda going.Do you feel guilty for your lies?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Filthy whale slaughtering scum, supported by the hypocrites @denmarkinuk . Hppy to have this psychotic slaughter De… https://t.co/g5ZC3P8cG4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@denmarkinuk If you didn't support this slaughter it wouldn't happen.Shame on you hypocrites. https://t.co/msOxOpE48k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know but it scares the fucking shite out of me. https://t.co/pY22VCZ4iX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Particularly relevant in these dangerous and worrying times. https://t.co/uQ7zqWLioF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think we are visiting up your way later this year. https://t.co/aM7DiugvHK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m proud to support @onekindtweet #SnareFreeScotland campaign. Join in by writing to your MSPs here https://t.co/MdkHgubIis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See how he likes it, he will probably be 'OK'. https://t.co/dDP6ncYDPL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RuthDavidsonMSP must be pleased that her boss is over ( bending over ) for Trump, desperate for any crumbs from th… https://t.co/CB47ZmTHqu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dream on! Tking votes from the hapless Labour morons, miles behind the SNP. https://t.co/pyVTcI6h4Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 months to come up with this? Jesus fucking Christ on a bike! https://t.co/bOIPDIloTd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lettertodaddy 56 of 59 MPs in the 2015 GE isn't winning people over? There is an idiot and it's stupid Britnats like you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilTrumper @AngusRobertson @bbcquestiontime Top Tip Phil - avoid appearing a thick idiot by not tweeting about things you don't understand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamieRoss7 To be fair to Toby, he is very confused about the concept of thinking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Projectile vomit into a bucket, morally bankrupt, clueless quasi fascist morons. https://t.co/LvHHCgOsMF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The credit is all @howlieT 's https://t.co/Raputju1KN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well right back to 1707 is correct, not a union but a takeover. https://t.co/TuK8NYpGui]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only by right wing scum. https://t.co/0xykwhB4Av]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LadyOfAlba @AngGallacher Certainly not the good sort, possibly a nasty cocktail of self loathing and hatred of change.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shedboy23 Yes of course. It's just been turned up as more Scots see what has been going on. FFS I was in Labour once,in the 80s.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plant yoonatic. https://t.co/tbM28wEOOy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The deceit and lies have been full on since the SNP triumph in the 2015 GE. https://t.co/aewW2W5hKG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey I'm fifty fucking eight! I don't know what a hashtag is 😞 https://t.co/1yYDNH0y6T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agree totally in Indy. But he did humiliate Thatcher on the Belgrano sinking in the Falklands, https://t.co/qZfLQ7ZtPX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meaningless nonsense. Just like the bible. https://t.co/VMDWDAKF7l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FFS! That's an image I want to erase from my brain now. https://t.co/a9HSr9Fiom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nigel_Farage But then again, you are a despicable fascist fuckwit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarchOnLaddie And I was out the country heading across Ireland to the Dingle peninsula. The Irish don't care about the Scottish Cup!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was cool with you winning, mainly due to the team you were playing! https://t.co/bUoRHE7Q4l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll pass on this if you don't mind! https://t.co/YQOftrxmEs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey yoons! This is the pitiful state of the scum you want to rule our country. https://t.co/w5GDSC4l86]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tories and rational thought don't go well. https://t.co/eZTGrBzmFj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They are Tory cuts you idiots and everyone knows it, try and have just a little bit of dignity and self respect eh? https://t.co/sclzXvopUx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just dropped by for a laugh at you pitiful, deluded losers. I think you're lucky to have 15% in the polls. https://t.co/p7E3tbzhgo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Definitely need more in Edinburgh. https://t.co/LgL5Bdnogw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need a laugh? Look at this batshit crazy, deluded Britnat bullshit. Couldn't be any more supine and pathetic if the… https://t.co/xw2s8VcFgL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Tunnocks mallow with some yoonionist Polonium added. https://t.co/zLhRrSfj5m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An all out attack on the poor and disadvantaged by an increasingly fascistic govt. https://t.co/rkU4SrksE8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sure it will go well so no need to wish you luck. Ask for Propofol as the anaesthetic. https://t.co/R3PYh9Ixdv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought he used lard. https://t.co/K2KPQk50v5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheScotsman Unelected Tory Britnat vomits bile and you report. Not long to you go out of business now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tank with shouty Ruth 'astride' the gun. https://t.co/jbhOkEB2zO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is your imaginary god better than their imaginary god then? https://t.co/APayHEfblq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dogshit in an envelope. https://t.co/TC2dQe3E2r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best crowd they've had for a while. https://t.co/pxvJ4Iq2sO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@2010LeeHurst You could do your act, he would have given up well before an hour.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just another right wing comedian but not as funny as Boris. https://t.co/nHhcm0fwOq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never underestimate the venal stupidity and spitefulness of the Britnats. https://t.co/wRgTIN7JO6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Problem is Scotland gets what England votes for, insular right-wing xenophobia. https://t.co/DEWEFoWFdm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop trying to slither out of your responsibilities. Well you are totally pointless in Scotland anyway. https://t.co/RlzfpqjUoF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only way of letting a few Libdems slither their way into Holyrood. https://t.co/5XpVT3VxRh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Avoiding the liar Carmichael I see, ashamed of him or what? The bar for shame is pretty high given your coalition w… https://t.co/NvE5Bt0jNx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Either way you guys are finished. Incidentally Scot parliament system was put in place by UK govt to prevent overal… https://t.co/CEyhWewdOG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biggest ships can't reach Grangemouth either. https://t.co/Y3LUL36yWI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only 1 in Scotland and that is the odious liar Carmichael, you must be so proud of him. https://t.co/OLIf1mlrhe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bluecatbar1 Sad that nowadays Farage is never off the BBC, especially QT.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or the Yemen where civilians are bombarded by the Saudis using British arms and trained by the Brits. https://t.co/fafOLvpJmp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gregalach @MrMalky @KnightAngel45 @moe2mac Me too. She is obviously deranged.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LassieLmr @yhWildfire @rampitchfork @RogueCoder250 After all, could a Paris patisserie seriously compete with Greggs?? 2/2.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LassieLmr @yhWildfire @rampitchfork @RogueCoder250 It's just lucky that no EU country has any heritage in making tasty cakes have they? 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are a fucking moron. https://t.co/wWWJWACkTs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hazelbagend I could head for Ireland for good if we lost another Indyref.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's my point. Why are these ports much quieter now? Scotland needs a container port for exports. https://t.co/XMNuTJWBnk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Point is we have lots of potential on both coasts. Strong position. Grangemouth docks were always busy in 60s and 7… https://t.co/uktM6tdTA9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didn't realise that, thought it was in the past. Must be lots of potential on west coast. https://t.co/rIvOhafrqX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Potential of Leith, Grangemouth, Rosyth, Dundee , Montrose, Aberdeen plus Glsgow on west coast. And many others. https://t.co/rNwgWL1DYt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BillNorAngus @0604Arb1320 @Dowanhillshark @scottishfirst @ScotlandTonight As a Portonian, Grangemouth is the biggest. I moved away though!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Human vermin proud of their pointless slaughter. https://t.co/phMvfTMYk4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's a rag bag of bile and hate. https://t.co/yNfwMrDpDC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whatever 😀😀😀😀😀😀. Look I can use emoji too. https://t.co/K0lnlnEzCq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arennie44 That's a non sequiter. tut tut.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google it, you probably have to do that a lot. https://t.co/h8OFRucA1C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What are you coming across as? https://t.co/bpQ5Dee6WO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for that comment, very helpful. https://t.co/zopNN8bbsJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's wait for the disaster of Brexit and leave ourselves open to unfettered fascism with no employment or human ri… https://t.co/xzSn6yKoC3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get fucking in!!! The wee team next. https://t.co/oCJUhM9sMw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are an oxymoron, and a fucking sad moron. https://t.co/Af5Ff9deDX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your twitter feed is basically one long scream of right-wing self loathing, I pity you. https://t.co/Af5Ff8VDMp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well why don't you pitiful Britnats put that to the test with a 2nd Indyref? You are bricking it as you are liars w… https://t.co/MHEEQJtCYQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SNP have 120,000 in Scotland alone, but then again they never collaborated with the toxic Tories. You are a joke in… https://t.co/U6DzTgvso6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus fucking Christ Hearts!! https://t.co/WeHHFuFOYT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of these has a fixed grin and hasn't got a clue, the other is a cardboard cut out of Hilary Cinton. https://t.co/cBVqzxjeMm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rampitchfork @RogueCoder250 And tea. Don't forget the vast tea plantations in Yorkshire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A what a wonderful union we have! Scotland will be in the EU so if England has a trade war with us,, it is taking i… https://t.co/vmvm5a4RcW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes I remember the Blair govt repealing Thatcher's anti-union legislation...errr  wait a minute!! https://t.co/EjSM0H2a5j]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>