<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovely drift on holeinthewall bar, meyler giving the tony martin horse a 'questionable' ride there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every mot in a pair of air max thinking they're a fucking fitness model. Will yis fuck off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tap night clearly not enjoying himself anymore, do him a favour and retire him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dopedhorse i really liked the look of him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GetYourTipsOut goes JLT, yorkhill wins arkle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thats a cracker of a ride from de Giles to be fair, not much more he can do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grown men with a players name and number on their replica jersey will never not be tragic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GetYourTipsOut agree that he's very hit and miss. Him and my beloved Cue Card only real value though. Thistlecrack wont win]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Betracingnation petit vs yanworth be run at some pace i'd imagine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Schweini, top bloke and player]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Betracingnation just watching it back now, thats a serious gallop to be fair, and kept it up too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Betracingnation not for me personally, footpad far too close]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Federer but those 'injury' time outs are cheating. Legal, but cheating]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rafa wins from here doesnt he?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colbisonlawlor absolute knicker sniffer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frampton worth a monkey here?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David haye would batter me but would defo throw a sneaky dig. Or swing a shovel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Lar11_ suits has been scrapped for this prick mate! You ever been to ratoath? https://t.co/TwCWxuPwSx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Lar11_ only starting on season one, already contemplating wearing a waistcoat everyday. Zero interest in ufc, doesnt touch boxing imo bud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Lar11_ bored on the couch after a few pints, watching suits, waiting for the boxing and contemplating over 35's football mate. Sad ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has frampton won yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dermonolan91 ah dermo. That cuts deep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arrogate blahdy blahdy blah! Reruns of many clouds is where its at. What a bloke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dermonolan91 boat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colbisonlawlor yes he fucking does! Love all the american horses on crack ðŸ™ŒðŸ¿]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dopedhorse @cardiffrevs he also said in a postcast thistlecrack was the best horse he's ever seen. Absolute chancer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OliverSherwood so sorry for your loss sir, went out on his shield like the warrior he was. Loved him. RIP Many Clouds, great bloke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colbisonlawlor if cue card gets his ground and runs to form he'll beat thistlecrack with the extra two furlongs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did Jacob really just say 'they'd die trying there?' Jaysus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah fuck no #manyclouds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colbisonlawlor hopefully many clouds ok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First top horse running to true form outstays him. Bubble burst for me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would listen to Ruby Walsh talk about horses all day long]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Betracingnation really looking forward to seeing uxizandre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always thoroughly enjoy a man wearing jeans in the gym]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If charli parcs keeps drifting i might just have to back him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday rafa and dimitrov gave us 5 sets of the best tennis i can remember. Serena gets a 20 minute cake walk. And gets paid the same. Mad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcus161 lovely stuff, mate i'm an absolute cripple these days ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcus161 deadly, ill try pop along and not hurt myself ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcus161 ah balls ðŸ˜© When is training? Moved out to ratoath so be interested to get back playing ðŸ™ŒðŸ¿]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcus161 mate you still playing ball?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AtTheRaces have a look at the ride on war goddess in the 8:30 there ðŸ˜‚ If thats not looked at theres something wrong!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RAFAAAAAAAAA! What a match, some man. Unbeatable when playing at the top of his game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Literally creaming myself at the thoughts of a Rafa/ Fed final]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some amount of stupid on that m50 everyday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lawlor100 really? He looks somewhat back to his best buddy. You watching?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dermonolan91 what a bloke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do blokes actually think that matching gucci caps and over the shoulders purses look good? Jaysus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Muffri'Ha surely the bet in the next at meydan?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Probably mentioned this before but the ruby walsh fan club after an odds on loss is always good for a giggle #clueless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bet365 it's the 3 o'clock at gowran]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bet365 have you really just taken a rule 4 on the race when a reserve has been taken out?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nadal will murder Fed if they both get to the final]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ev_Kane9 me and @sedakov were literally just saying the other day that you're our favourite ever bloke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatthewLysaght tweeted about that before, we or you when talking about prem teams is a no no]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can understand people hating liverpool but if you dont like klopp well then you dont like football. Simple]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatthewLysaght i'm blocked for some reason ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ What does it say?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mane a huge loss to that team]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GetYourTipsOut legend, thiese just the 365 ones ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/IAeBCi6HMk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That bon jovi song would drive somebody to murder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dermonolan91 gurteen has broken my heart this season]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ruby walsh hit squad out in force again today ðŸ˜‚ Stop backing 1-2 shots you eejits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rafa and Fed anywhere near the top of their game are literally leagues above everybody. By far the best ever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Throwback to this ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ Legend of a bloke https://t.co/z0yNfTlvdP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure we'll ever see Annie Power on a racecourse again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dopedhorse i'd cream myself with a rafa/ fed final. Where's douvan gone?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He has his forehand back! Mon Rafa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raonic one of those tennis players that will never get any love from me. Awful to watch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cant be just me who thinks Gordon Elliott entering 64 horses into every large handicap is bad for racing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still the best thing to ever happen on twitter https://t.co/rlIIuxsVxe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any danger of automatic dispensing petrol pumps anytime soon? I fucking hate having to get out of the car in a garage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colbisonlawlor fucking come on rafa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Rafa getting his forehand back? My all time favourite shot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Must read for anybody thinking about backing yorkhill. Would love to see him run in arkle myself https://t.co/ZanH8oAxR7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Jessica Harrington talks a horse up you listen and back. Nice run from Oscar Sam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stellar notion should be hard to peg back here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would love to see yorkhill in an arkle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the lads crying when their â‚¬5 odds on ruby walsh acca goes down is never not funny. Of course its a fix mate ðŸ‘ðŸ¿]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GetYourTipsOut i'm a nightmare for backing horses i like, al ferof springs to mind ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GetYourTipsOut one of my cliff horses so didnt go big on it ðŸ˜© https://t.co/V2dYnhQnqg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colbisonlawlor either Rafa or Federer to win this would be bewwwwwtiful, C'MONNNNNNNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federer and Nishikori shaping up to be a cracker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UpNorthRacing keep it for heartbreak city at leop tomorrow mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colbisonlawlor chancers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theres worse value bets than bristol de mai for the gold cup after that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to seeing the new one finish stone last at cheltenham now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[L'ami serge is an absolute bottlejob of a horse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GetYourTipsOut @HAYDOCKRACES 2 lovely horses to be fair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeejayOV2 @wheresparko @dopedhorse well he could have won to be fair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anybody tipping Alary today is an absolute chancer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Regardless of how this match against Nadal pans out, Zverev has a few slams in him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rafa should have got rid of Uncle Tony years ago]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GetYourTipsOut waiting patiently is a lovely price]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GetYourTipsOut @Chepstow_Racing slowly slowly paul maloney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anybody else buzzing to see Michael Flatley tap dancing on a nuclear warhead flanked by apache helicopters? Make it happen @realDonaldTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelMonan1 @Channel4Racing gave me goosebumps everytime watching him, would have hosed in in the GC in my opinion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelMonan1 @Channel4Racing thought he was good after the deloitte but supreme made him a superstar. I got him at 9-4 for the JLT ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Channel4Racing @MichaelMonan1 jesus i loved that horse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RatoathHarpsFC hi guys, recently moved to the area, do you have an over 35's team?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bduke77 harrys on the green decent for late night sports sir]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>