<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Slootbag keep it up dude, rooting for you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lordsome people still use names like that in 2017? LUL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter how old I am these pokemon games are always fun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pepe the Frog rigged the election to get back at Hillary #ElectionNight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LoLZirene @Jeff60338516 new prophet PogChamp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is it so sunny, wtf Wellington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need some help with my weird obsession with traffic cones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Sum 41 album 👌🔥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck man, @LoLZirene looking fly son.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NeoNectars you felt pretty because you are pretty, 😊]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best kind of obsession is a green tea obsession.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teenager playlist, I choose you! https://t.co/Bwt3VjB3G9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NeoNectars @corgicoregee if you feel a connection to the name I'd say go for it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@corgicoregee @NeoNectars Yeah I'd probably go for Mercys too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NeoNectars thanks, &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not possible to describe how good and bad it feels to get back into the gym after a decent "break"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Frodan @TempoReynad @TempoGaara that was one of the best HS casts ever, good job lads]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New comp mode for OW is strangely addicting.. Playing solo seems like the go to strat tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hit max level on the division, pretty good so far and end game is supposed to be better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fushaaan good amount of content for the price, the story is pretty generic but the combat is pretty fluid and fun, especially with friends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Low key off my face for 3 days straight https://t.co/w6I4UvZ3JL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SirSlayerr @Snoopdify how times have changed. X)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Snoopdify I was the leader with Kam of eMG back in the day when we still played that god awful game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Snoopdify @SirSlayerr dunno who you are but you definitely forgot us..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should probably sleep but worlds...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy shit TSM vs Liquid what a game. #LCS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shadz0r plays cod =/= feels good. Pick one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GTA on pc is great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DstarOrange Well played dude!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fushaaan PC gaming much less frustrating :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fushaaan lots of PC games, gym and actually going back to uni, but no console anymore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Maulshi @Lordsome the whole franchise. Played through about 8 times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lordsome @Maulshi that's how I racked up 700 hours in mass effect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Funny seeing all these Oceanic people playing WoW with the new servers being up. I've been on this grind for 8 years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DDOS attacks, holy crap RIP Blizzard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkumbagChrizzle I hope you're following 420 people on purpose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MEGAEminence @_khooie Playing COD, wut Khooie?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First time back at the gym in 2 months, my advise? Don't take a break.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheHypezy west ham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That Tuesday night after the pub feel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiting for the flight to Hong Kong. http://t.co/dwI1RmQF5u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lordsome in my opinion? Agüero.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lordsome he's good until he gets injured I wonder who that reminds me of? Haha.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lordsome I officially hate you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lordsome our pre-season was good + season was bad last season I'm hoping for vice versa this time ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lordsome would not recommend visiting East London if you're linking that m8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lordsome you what m8?!? http://t.co/8Q5xCzjsqi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got to watch West Ham verse the Phoenix and Newcastle verse Sydney. Was awesome. http://t.co/udl0bjhnlg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sleep during the day, up during the night. Man these sleep schedules.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zilzey @busty_nz I remember that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well then Germany.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zilzey well that's just fantastic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greece is playing brutally.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Eviictus Gmod is an essential part of steam, Portal 2 is also great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zilzey it's disappointing isn't it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zilzey yeah, very bad mannered people though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zilzey I was just playing it out of boredom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TRAiNzPS @xMilooo @Chaiinnn lets be honest boys I'm drunk and don't care.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ForceJT Blitz_Burn, 9 years strong bro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hold the Heathen Hammer High http://t.co/l3c6b4Jgky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AVANT_khooie good job bro, come enjoy life with the rest of us old boys.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get to go home to England next month for 4 weeks to visit the family, pretty keen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amazingafroman didn't even know about it so I guess so, haha. Seems interesting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They're making a new Star Wars trilogy? Oh jeez.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lordsome Haven't played COD in nearly a year, feels great. Life is so much more hectic without it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lordsome I can understand that. Uni being really time consuming for you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lordsome I swear you've tweeted more today then in the last 2 months haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1C outside, yay work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Raw_Blazn welcome to my life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Raw_Blazn It's healthy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nv_Claw Personal trainer and coach.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The zzzz today is real.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BioAcid yeah it ain't pleasant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BioAcid welcome to my world zzzz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zilzey that tense]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LookAtMeCarry and this is why I don't play much league anymore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StyledBrah England in August for me, feels good eh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zilzey we on it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zilzey miss you to mate. How goes it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My city is full of hipsters. Ugh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Public drinking fines &lt;

Rip me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love the looks I get when people leave work in suits and I'm in gym gear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate holiday withdraws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love League of legends twitch chat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BioAcid @OpTic_NaDeSHoT @ProSyndicate that dude hurts my brain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been on so many flights this year to go get drunk...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holiday and no work starting tomorrow afternoon till Monday :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 in the morning and I feel like death, it's back to bed after gym I think]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[qtpie is such a carry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being woken up at the sound of people leaving your lecture theater]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Tyrion dies after that episode I will cry. Dude's a beast. #GoT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing beats actually seeing progress. Hoping to hit the 80kg goal sometime relatively soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhoisRob_ you get used to the early nights and mornings,  healthy way of living]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man, Will Smith is a boss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait to drop down to Dunedin in the Holidays to get on it for a few days, good break from University and Work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BioAcid Apparently Thief is the biggest let down of 2014, tell me how it goes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LookAtMeCarry apparently they're banned?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[apparently there's a troll mode for league only for today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zilzey not trolling, good job on getting a job yo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zilzey you're actually working there? man I feel sorry for you.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>