<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisAlanComedy Aw snap really? I've seen you a bunch of times at undergroundcomedy stuff! It's the owl mask isn't it? haha.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisAlanComedy if by diminutive black woman you've sometimes seen at DC open mics, yes haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honoring the achievements of blacks this month will be considered a success if Trump doesn't use the word "the" in front of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That moment when a man is blaring an awesome electric guitar version of "Sara Smile" outside Dupont Metro but you have no $ to give him :-/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MIC NEWS ALERTS GOING HARD IN THE MOTHERFUCKING PAINT TODAY https://t.co/XSKL6oDv9W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You guys. She's only hope. This is where we are right now. https://t.co/EV9gZMVVpY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy shit. It's a Poopopoly. https://t.co/otPJDs8MSn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope you can make it out to @dcimprov this weekend! I'm emceeing! @Jimmythecomic is featuring! https://t.co/slbMfw2amW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good thing Trump doesn't announce the SCOTUS nominee til Tuesday. My CVS can't restock posterboard &amp; markers until then anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn Uber is wasting no time (and this was after the app delete) https://t.co/c5MN6bUon4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For all the ppl who gave me blank stares over the yrs when I said I used Lyft instead of Uber...your pink mustache will be in the mail tmrw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd hate to be Trump's personal shopper. U know when he asks 4 something to get rid of blackheads there's a 30% chance he meant Neutrogena.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Normally I'd be happy I reached my daily step count. Not today. #NeverMove #EverythingHurts #WhereDidAllThisShitComeFrom #SaveMeRaptorJesus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I don't change my position very much--except on the Mexican people like 3 minutes ago--but other than that" #Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We're going to be working on a fair relationship, a new relationship" - Trump

So we're in marriage counseling with Mexico?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["DAMMIT I COULD HAVE USED A STARWIPE" - Person who just found 2nd vid of Richard Spencer being punched after editing 1st one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lindseywoho me too! It was her and Khadijah James from Living Single]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On school nights my mom only let me watch 1 (maybe 2) shows in the 8 o'clock hr on Nick at Nite. 1 of those was the Mary Tyler Moore Show.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you've never been in a Lyft driven by a defensive driver who only plays classical music I recommend it. Equal pts soothing and terrifying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And here to close out this women's comedy showcase is...Ashy Larry from Chappelle's Show?! I mean...I'll DEF take i… https://t.co/g5hA7IRZEC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever wonder if Trump will keep signing things just to make it look like he's busy? There's gotta be a kid's "F" grade history test in there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Shenanigans in AdMo tonight for @olmikeb757 &amp; @WeWantMooreNow's Ladies of Comedy showcase, hosted by… https://t.co/4RlGGqIWaD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the love of God no one tell Sean Spicer about mochi. He will lose his shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like how it took nearly every Steeler to stop Blount #PITvsNE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KenLlew thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lindseywoho Thank you!! :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lindseywoho YOU WERE THE 1ST PERSON I THOUGHT OF WHEN I WAS ADDED 2 THE SHOW! Tix were sold out by then but I knew u'd freak out either way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So unbelievably honored to be a part of this show. Thank you @2DopeQueens! https://t.co/l4G55v3coV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WomensMarch https://t.co/iHSjygQeah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really regret not making an "All I really want is zero gloom gloom gloom and no doom doom. DON'T FUX WITH TRUMP" sign. #WomensMarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard: You're so nice!!
Not overheard: Take us with you!!
#WomensMarch https://t.co/9H5YBWUXxm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WomensMarch https://t.co/hKmGTSguCf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That feeling when you find the secret bathroom in the museum #DontBotherAskingWhereItIsNow #PeopleCaughtOn… https://t.co/KIjUAyckKk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WomensMarch https://t.co/1gSBrZZ16k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WomensMarch https://t.co/Mh6flIXbIY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing will get you through a crowd faster than standing behind the woman pushing a stroller #ImWithHer #WomensMarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(Bundled up woman at #WomensMarch) Her: "What happened to the 55 degrees they promised us? Another Washington promise broken"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's with a heavy heart that I announce the death of Muppet Sam the Eagle, sacrificed in the name of patriotism to… https://t.co/CcpRzi38Pi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The crime and the gangs and the drugs"? Trump sounds like a middle school DARE counselor who didn't get a background check]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[::alarm goes off::
::remembers what day it is::
::hits snooze button until 2020::]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OK is it me or are people just straight up not flushing anymore? Why am I seeing your life story in this Chipotle's toilet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I don't know where people get these standards for cleanliness and dressing and such" - Roomie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(watches cabinet hearing)
American: Jesus take the wheel
(Jesus looks up from ordering Uber)
Him: Sry it's about to be peak surge in 3 days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["OH SURE LIKE IT'S *THAT* EASY" - Every dude that walks by this in Giant Food https://t.co/vducgKEFTZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Telling jokes to raise $$ for @PPMW_DC WEDNESDAY at @habana_village. @lousyhumans = host! Sheila Wenz of… https://t.co/n6Cln4Fo0h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like how open-ended you're keeping this invitation, Wendy's https://t.co/axqnr2Voms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It sucks Trump loses the one singer whose signature song's ACTUAL lyrics are "I'm not going" and "YOU'RE GOING TO L… https://t.co/Zo60lS1pjQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SheriMamaGG3 YES. Had to screencap it so I'd stop doing a double take]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That 3rd bullet works as long as you're a HS student running for class president. https://t.co/KHbnxVjDI0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cook just now. #DALvsGB https://t.co/2kSF6tcdR8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Telling me I can watch the #Terps on ESPNNEWS until WVU v. Texas ends doesn't exactly help when it's the only ESPN channel you don't get :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fact they picked a color bright enough for us to sharpie whatever we like speaks even further to the idiocy of… https://t.co/7GgYZJfJiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FUN FACT: This actually just yells "You broke ass motherfucker" instead https://t.co/EfyBm0mPfk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone ever order a Lyft to chase the bus you just missed? Asking for a friend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How @naomikaravani found me in the hallway before going on Watching the Hawks. I have a problem. https://t.co/SQCpi5GgCh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over/under on how many black families pull out of Family Feud after this? https://t.co/UiPzghGYUk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope you can come out to the DC edition of #50FirstJokes at @bierbarondc hosted by @UNDRGRNDCMDYDC! Tix info:… https://t.co/XcE8T33VNR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ran to sitting bus that hadn't moved at green light.
Driver makes eye contact with me.
Doors never open. Bus drives away.

I will find you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Katy Tur's "This shit again" face was strong #TrumpPressConference]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cody_clifton_81 @RedactedTonight thanks cody!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lindseywoho OMG HIS EYES. HIS EYES LINDSEY!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DON'T BE A LOSER! Come out to a FREE Summer Camp Show WEDNESDAY 8p at @TheWonderlandDC &amp; be among cool ppl, bits, s… https://t.co/jsBjjZzKfN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHAT'S WITH ALL THESE INSTAGRAM ADS?
::sees one for fleece-lined leggings on sale::
OK nevermind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn. This is just salt in the wounds of people who didn't get tickets. https://t.co/5Iy1BVoDbA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the inside #nationalchampionship https://t.co/GLriMfHN10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bthny @lindseywoho ProPublica JUST relaunched a podcast where they talk about their series on those tests that I cited on the show!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of many comics hoping to raise $$ for @MSF_USA to help Syrians in Aleppo THIS Tuesday 8pm in Falls Church. Hope… https://t.co/tnMjSPjrFa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @donkimsays :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People like Donald Trump are the reason you can't edit your own Wikipedia page.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can these moving companies update their websites? Shit's looking like Geocities. #ZeroTrust]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haha why am I looking at recipes online as if there is ANYTHING left in my supermarket right now #DCsnow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A MUCH needed road win. Very glad Big Blue didn't make me blue #Terps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@calimerho @LeeCamp Thanks Naomi!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things me and the Cap'n made happen:
(x) 'Beetus
(x) My newfound appreciation for 18th century naval history
(x) Oral surgery]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@racatiwood Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OK the ending to this Thelma &amp; Louise sequel needs some work. https://t.co/7UvYN1sEK2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The tedium of a job with no chance of career advancement in which you drink daily to numb the pain is SUPER KAWAII!… https://t.co/wAALGV6puA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @daveshofer!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can there be so much wrong in just one headline? https://t.co/lRelcnvvV9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey Baltimore! I'll be telling jokes at @charmcitycomedy's Prim &amp; Proper Showcase at Zissimos this Friday w/ these… https://t.co/ZnPUn3JCk6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All that touring he did with Chris Brown is starting to catch up with him :-/ https://t.co/F9mYKltmT8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEW YEAR RESOLUTION: GET 8 MINUTE BABS https://t.co/kx0d3JrENA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[::laughed when I realized liberal tears mugs are made in China::]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @Tostitos for finally making it socially acceptable to drink salsa in public. https://t.co/bu8MlXDC7X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["CAN YOU CALL MY PHONE CHARGER?" - How someone in a sequin tube top prob started 2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HUERTER PUTTIN A HURTIN ON EM #Terps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(Docent leads tour through museum)
D: We now move into the "Black men who were entirely too confident they wouldn't… https://t.co/FbyRl3Ca03]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That Gchat happy new year animation got a little too real yesterday. https://t.co/qKJ5ypDeTu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Year's Resolution: To be a fraction as happy as this fox whenever I gchat someone on a holiday. I'll settle for… https://t.co/UvcFqrUxp6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[::posts 9 pics of bottles of wine i drank alone this year on IG::
Me: I think I did this wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going. You should too! https://t.co/7N9SP5Zq4J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If u saw my tweet about that fatal car crash, my friend (driver) has critical injuries after a seizure. Their story: https://t.co/BZYEpPxUzx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FaleUniversity theory lesson courtesy of Professor @Thatblack1 https://t.co/tsJb0QlGxS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@benjyhimmel's #FaleUniversity music history lesson enters the 1980s https://t.co/b9OVO0jWgP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reporter: Should the US sanction Russia over computer hacking?
(Suddenly has cockatoo on shoulder)
Trump: DID Y'ALLL SEE THIS BOMB-ASS BIRD?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leninstomb This was the perfect GIF for that dumb ass quote.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christ you guys IT'S NOT EVEN FUCKING JANUARY, LET ALONE FEBRUARY https://t.co/fe6Idcl9nu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus Christ. 2016 is NOT fucking around. https://t.co/3PP6GtlX28]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My HS classmates' mom :-( Please send good thoughts if you have a moment. https://t.co/r0G500YlN8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My uncle is about to get a LOT drunker now #RavensFlock]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>