<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@MitchMcConell You lying hypocrite! https://t.co/WzdsfjLzE0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN What this administration is doing to CNN is wrong..Be America's Best News Network and hold this administration to the truth be ruthless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lawrence Obama was there for the Little Guy all the time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sen_JoeManchin This is what you support....You need help! https://t.co/sAA2agtd97]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More and more leaks need to happen https://t.co/jS5EIXchZf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You get what you voted for https://t.co/LBZUazvK2m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes we need to know now! https://t.co/kcsU5xxyg3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a fucking Wacko https://t.co/Cg6I9NcpHZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh God help us! https://t.co/N8Ft6Ja6YL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They didn't do this for Obama https://t.co/U5HWyv5YcE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ABC He's High]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Schwarzenegger Yeah Arnold! Way to Punk down Trump!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John McCain: Trump's Dispute With Australia 'Unnecessary and Frankly Harmful' https://t.co/QdXKXoEwHq via @nbcnews@]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenJohnMcCain Thank You Senator for being a Mature Adult.....I sure hope God is Blessing the United States of America]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeithOlbermann @realDonaldTrump Seriously]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sen_JoeManchin Very disappointed in you Senator trurning your back on the right side of history. A Jay Rockefeller you are not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Twitter How come I no longer have the ability to search for people on Twitter? I no longer have the little magnifying glass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timkaine Thank You Senator]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimjefferies Yes she is a Cunt isn't she...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lying Weasel Faced Dick Head! https://t.co/JtJoNnmDEs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ABC Save The United States Report the truth keep up the good work ABC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do you expect from a Hypocrite https://t.co/kTaDBzMgAu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenFranken @POTUS Keep up the Good work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ABC @ThisWeekABC Don't let Bullshit ABC and the US he is all in with Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It amazes me....that they think Trump will honor the US Constitution. https://t.co/xt6WE9pK2T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MSNBC  Republicans need to be held accountable please question them in public about their stance on their Muslim and Immigration Ban.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sethmeyers Republicans need to be held accountable please question them in public about their stance on their Muslim and Immigration Ban.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhillyInquirerRepublicans need to be held accountable please question them in public about their stance on their Muslim and Immigration Ban]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenFranken Republicans need to be held accountable please question them in public about their stance on their Muslim and Immigration Ban.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@repjohnlewisRepublicans need to be held accountable please question them in public about their stance on their Muslim and Immigration Ban.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkWarner Republicans need to be held accountable please question them in public about their stance on their Muslim and Immigration Ban.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCWorld Republicans need to be held accountable please question them in public about their stance on their Muslim and Immigration Ban.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlecBaldwin Republicans need to be held accountable please question them in public about their stance on their Muslim and Immigration Ban.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenAffleck Republicans need to be held accountable please question them in public about their stance on their Muslim and Immigration Ban.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RonWyden Republicans need to be held accountable please question them in public about their stance on their Muslim and Immigration Ban.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lawrence Republicans need to be held accountable please question them in public about their stance on their Muslim and Immigration Ban.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chucktodd Republicans need to be held accountable please question them in public about their stance on their Muslim and Immigration Ban.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jaketapper Republicans need to be held accountable please question them in public about their stance on their Muslim and Immigration Ban.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TIME Republicans need to be held accountable please question them in public about their stance on their Muslim and Immigration Ban.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorLeahy Republicans need to be held accountable please question them in public about their stance on their Muslim and Immigration Ban]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DalaiLama Your Holinesswe need your guidance and direction Please make a statement on the US policy on its Muslim and Immigration Ban]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pontifex Holly Father we need your guidance and direction Please make a statement on the US Muslim and Imitation Ban]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Working out nice Pal! https://t.co/aPfTITORPj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteveDraz people mass tweets for this asshole https://t.co/BJGE8CDo5L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteveDraz This proves your not human https://t.co/vMOnZ8OSIg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteveDraz You Sir are not at True Pol.
Polish Immigrants don't need your representation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteveDraz What kind of person are you? Are you even human? I don't get people like you Sir you make me sick! Add that to you stupid list]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HWNDUS Thanks for the photos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck The Wall!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MMFlint Keep up the Good Fight!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCWorld @BBCNews Thank You BBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HWNDUS Keep up the Tuff Fight be a Voice for All]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not all Trump supporters are Evil.
But all Trump supporters are Republicans!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timkaine Thank you for being Our Senator!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanRather Prayers for Willy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BostonGlobe So Mexico just raises its prices on Good sent to the US]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpeakerRyan I didn't want your Wall I sure as Hell don't want to pay for it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BettyBowers That's something Hitler did]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Evan_McMullin Keep up the Good Fight Sir...Extend to a more vocal and National level]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ken_Rosenthal Don't forget President Trump on this one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for the Tax Increase! https://t.co/v8e2Hdzct1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepCummings Sir ther is way to much Politics in the work place. I am a Federal employee and I fear for my job because of my political views]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpeakerRyan Thanks for the Tax Increase Ass Hat! Behind door number 2 A new Wall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@POTUS Thanks Pick up the check American people and Trump supporters Suck! https://t.co/pl89DnvBMC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpeakerRyan You will be on the wrong side of history the Trump presidency will end shamefully]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenatorCollins please vote against Ms DeVos she is not qualified]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wallmethzarare @epeakin Do they understand.....probably.....what is more important is they don't give a shit!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mmfa Spicer Secretary of Bullshit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lawrence Why does Trump believe there is voter fraud but does not Believe Russian influence the election]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ryan says this now but he will cave to his Daddy Trump https://t.co/yxMGn5V7GX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lawrence We need to ask Mr Spicer the Secretary of Bullshit exactly where he gets his Bullshit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nytimes You need to ask the Secretary of Bullshit Mr. Spicer where he is getting his Bullshit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nowthisnews Spicer is the Secretary of Bullshit!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jaketapper @jeffzeleny @DavidChalian You need to ask the Secretary of Bullshit where is he getting his Bullshit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timkaine With all due respect sir....Spicer is the Secretary of Bullshit.... he's doing a hell of a job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@POTUS Mexico is calling you out Pal. https://t.co/d5p6Yn1gA5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He is in for a fight https://t.co/4FzAdFyrZd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost Why is it that Trump believes there is voter fraud but he does not believe Russia influenced the election]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is she taking heat? https://t.co/ynGvowl0kf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RawStory More from the Secretary of Bullshit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NARAL @voxdotcom Spicer is the Secretary of Bullshit!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nytimes Why does Trump believe in voter fraud but not that Russia hacks influenced the election?
Question needs asked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is disturbing https://t.co/uEECqCfEFN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@POTUS How does it feel to have China be Your Daddy
I forgot Russia is your Daddy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ass Hat! https://t.co/Jtr3ssRAtV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McConnellPress Once again you show how Spineless you really are you cave to your Daddy Donald Trump...You are an embarrassment to the US]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jameswest2010 @MotherJones The Secretary of Bullshit!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SethMacFarlane Mr.Spicer is the Secretary of Bullshit!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billmaher Mr.Spicer is the Secretary of Bullshit!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheYoungTurks Spicer the Secretary of Bullshit!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill This is Censorship and a violation of the First Amendment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBSNews Spicer the Secretary of Bullshit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBSNews @margbrennan Please continue pointing out this mans Bullshit and the Bullshit of this administration thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexnazaryan @nowthisnews Spicer is the Secretary of Bullshit!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PressSec Man you sure know how to Bullshit people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CWAUnion @phillydotcom I thought Trump said he would create jobs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill Who pays for this and why?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MotherJones Secretary of Bullshit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IntelligencerWV Any coverage on Trunp Lies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RawStory Fuck Scott Baio]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>