<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Tom Lawrence doesn't score dull goals! https://t.co/vBp4Ol30Vt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IndecentJuice @dafyddfrancis @shaftoflame Can you drop me from this thread please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@orj80 Thought I had him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SilvanoMoroBL @WalesOnline What?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomESPNscrum Such a class act.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ImKateMc @phog6189 It would probably be more nuanced to say the Irish attacking lineout which Barclay stole was the turning point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnFrancisBC Not the first time...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phog6189 @ImKateMc Not if you're Scottish!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColmODonoghue At least he has English family]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ianto_blaen @IndecentJuice The strangers bit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColmODonoghue Does he actually have any Irish family links?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ianto_blaen @IndecentJuice Trying to rise above that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ianto_blaen @IndecentJuice This is the one time it is probably pertinent given the comment about a lack of understanding of the internet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rubbish_No3 @dafyddfrancis @IndecentJuice @shaftoflame He hasn't played there much in fairness!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dafyddfrancis @IndecentJuice @shaftoflame From https://t.co/sI8fGfTf29.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanDavidson82 He was my tip for player of the tournament.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RTErugby @Scotlandteam Oh dear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IndecentJuice Just waiting for a reply to my DM, that's all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rob_Whitefield @JNP_83 @balders2 Have entered before. Don't bother any more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoetersFourTwo Is this true? @IndecentJuice I do like making people happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JNP_83 @Rob_Whitefield @balders2 There is a separate category for regional journalists. I didn't enter. Never win!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rob_Whitefield @JNP_83 @balders2 Sorry, I meant there is a separate category.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoetersFourTwo @IndecentJuice @shaftoflame As long as he is happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IndecentJuice You over in Wales at all in the coming months?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IndecentJuice @shaftoflame I don't dislike Geraint. He is very bright. Drop me that DM if you get a chance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IndecentJuice But if you send me a DM we can have a chat face to face.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IndecentJuice @shaftoflame And I repeatedly tell anonymous accounts I will not continue engagement. As I do with you. Nos da.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IndecentJuice @GoetersFourTwo @shaftoflame @TheVietGwent No, one of his gang is what I said. There are traits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IndecentJuice @shaftoflame Oh Lord, I've just realised, you are one of Geraint's gang. Apologies for being so slow on the update.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IndecentJuice @shaftoflame As I have pointed out, the key issue here is you are hiding your identity. You are yet to explain why.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IndecentJuice @shaftoflame @piersmorgan Not a relevant comparison, as the other person wasn't hiding their identity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IndecentJuice @shaftoflame Neither of those hide their identities like you do, so not really relevant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IndecentJuice @shaftoflame Having just seen your comment about Saints-Scarlets, I know everything I need to know about your rugby knowledge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IndecentJuice @shaftoflame No, I have that many followers because I have engaged with people as a real person, unlike you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephenjones9 @ST_Sport Shocking by Doussain at the death.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IndecentJuice @shaftoflame Probably not when he has 16,000 followers to your 6.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IndecentJuice @shaftoflame As I say, put a name to your comments and we'll talk. Why hide?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IndecentJuice @shaftoflame Oh dear. Well at least you haven't had to put a name to those misguided comments, so there's something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alijmcc @gman569 @Beckinder @FionaKHunter I will get my coat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IndecentJuice @shaftoflame Unreliable and AWJ do not go together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gman569 @Beckinder @FionaKHunter Head down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaftoflame If you need persuasion, you can't have watched him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NTallack Fancy paying my subs?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A new term for subs from Dylan Hartley: "Finishers".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was a missed opportunity for France. Better team overall. Picamoles, Serin, Gourdon, Spedding and Slimani excellent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shocking from Doussain with that failure to find touch from the penalty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaftoflame AWJ first name on team sheet if you want to win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sounds like another cracker! https://t.co/2FeVu5YfDg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An incredible 28 tackles from Jonny Gray...a second row!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the Centenary Quaich goes to Scotland!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@No2Hooker @ed_walker86 Lol. Hats off to the Scots. Great start to the Championship.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A special word for @scarlets_rugby back rower John Barclay. Made a big impact off the bench. Some really key interventions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a great game to start the Six Nations. Fantastic result for Scotland. Really shakes things up from the outset.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Six Nations is upon us and here are my thoughts with the tournament about to get underway. https://t.co/q4OMKnviiy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My thoughts on six key questions which will be answered in the Six Nations. https://t.co/q4OMKnviiy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Radio Wales in a few minutes talking about some rugby tournament.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RhunapIorwerth Bit of an odd one certainly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcusrichards3 @AssirattiNeil Very impressed with his scrummaging and work in the loose - not to mention his singing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great stuff https://t.co/4rUd1AsWcU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Adastra10 @ed_walker86 Watch out for Gourdon and Serin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Adastra10 @ed_walker86 They were much improved in the autumn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I will just let this GIF run all night. https://t.co/dCXWPUcUT1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wasn't too shabby a debut! #MOTM. https://t.co/ewO0ADKVQE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sandy Denny. Just magnificent. #singersongwritersattheBBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If anyone is up and about early tomorrow morning, I am on @BBCRadioWales from 7.30am talking Six Nations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Munster go top of the @PRO12rugby table with a one point victory away to Edinburgh. https://t.co/5iTmdyDXRI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Land of song! https://t.co/i8oCJW8D07]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Adastra10 @ed_walker86 France look a different animal this season.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keithwperry @davidhiggerson @stevewollaston @ed_walker86 How very dare they! Imagine it, producing material people are interested in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ed_walker86 They beat SA, NZ and Aus in the space of six months and are at home to England.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ed_walker86 Ireland first, England second, France third, Wales fourth, Scotland fifth, Italy sixth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonphipps81 @davidhiggerson @ed_walker86 It still exists pal. I work with a hugely dedicated, hard-working group of quality journalists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ed_walker86 Well said that person.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@welshman001 It was on S4C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching early Roxy Music on BBC Four just now. Brian Eno looked like he was from outer space!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sourdust Especially when the ball clearly went backwards!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevefenwick08 The ref gave that one it seemed to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What on earth was the TMO playing at with that last Welsh try out in Milan! Well done to the ref for over-ruling him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A good 27-5 win for Wales U20s out in Milan in the end. Two great finishes in the second half given the conditions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattSilva70 Really pleased for him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to @Llandaff_RFC product Aled Ward on coming on for his Wales U20s debut out in Milan. A lovely muddy initiation for him!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danielstone13 Not seen enough of him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right, in case you missed it, here's that finish from Scarlets winger Ryan Conbeer for Wales U20s. Just gets better… https://t.co/o4m6dV2fmi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@buck_mitchell Who is blaming a lack of talent?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a finish that was from winger Ryan Conbeer for Wales U20s out in Milan. You won't see better than that in the senior Six Nations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good to see the pitch has dried out a bit in Milan for tonight's Wales U20s game. https://t.co/uaE4WJ2Mt5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dai7jenkins @yclwbrygbi Bring on that Desso pitch at Rodney Parade. Just need someone to pay for it now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's my look at Six Nations new boy Nicky Smith.
https://t.co/3874CWMaiR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IanStaffs @talkMacca @SixNationsRugby Steady!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@moggsy95 Only have eyes for the egg!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ickythomas Need broadcast rights for that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was a pleasure to be involved in this tonight. A huge thanks to Lee Byrne &amp; Graham Price &amp; to all those involved… https://t.co/KpFfKPn2V4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mh_mhearne I didn't say I agreed with the selection!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to taking part in this evening's rugby debate with @byrney_15, Graham Price &amp; @andyhowellsport. Will be plenty to talk about]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheGiftOfGreeno No it's not. BT are showing Sarries v Leicester.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GarethTheHop Not great for supporters who might want to watch both games though. Ospreys go through if they win, so important for them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ceritheviking A freshen up? It's like a revolving door here. I have been to leaving dos of people I have never met!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have just realised that the Ospreys' game against Wasps clashes with Italy-Wales on Sunday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrahamMcKechnie @nosylocaljourno @JeffersonLake Should have thought of him before.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nosylocaljourno @GrahamMcKechnie @JeffersonLake I said that one earlier!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>