<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[February is the best month ever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arrrg where be me rum #BlackSails final season. https://t.co/yUxf5ZFSQV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ohnoitsewan Pretty much every acca I have ever done https://t.co/vy21s1lkGW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thezoverlord Hmm well that doesn't fill me with confidence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thezoverlord The 1st episode I found strangely all over the place. Maybe it needs time to settle down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This #SilentWitness is pretty gripping stuff..but a bit far fetched!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ozric Tentacles - Kick Muck https://t.co/S73gtcGLc1 One more for the chair dancing. Staple of them parties in late 80's ahem..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Orbital - The Box (Full Version) https://t.co/45JXxnZYO1 Here is 30 odd minutes to full up those Headphones- turn it up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Future Sound Of London - Papua New Guinea https://t.co/Qdpu8w0XyH  I am in total trancey mood. Weav'in and groov'in chair dancin...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Ken Clarke: Why I'm voting against Brexit https://t.co/biubROR702  heh the faces of the Brexitgang arf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[STEVE HILLAGE  Entity https://t.co/1euafQfzA8 Mon' the world is going to hell in handcart. Lets Trance Dance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish we had that server.. https://t.co/Ax2AorPUhQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[oh that is a pretty good shout actually. Not sure how much she would be up for it though! https://t.co/2NQPntIetz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another gone to the Great Gig In The Sky..RIP https://t.co/OiyobBsuzC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThisJayThomas @RenZelen @TheCricketingDr @Lokster71 I think I was thinking of   Chang Chen  and then there is Qi Shu..!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RenZelen @ThisJayThomas @TheCricketingDr @Lokster71 Hayley Atwell? There is asian actress who I am desperately trying to remember her name.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonder where I will be going on those days! https://t.co/Lt232ZDlcc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cousin of mine who lives in France shared this on her FB. #TrumpProtest #Trump https://t.co/TfhdrHGK4M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Funniest protest signs from the British #MuslimBanProtest https://t.co/axl87fTsr4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well at least they are not disapearing them to some gulag in Texas...yet. #TrumpPurge https://t.co/Kc1rumdOQU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Trump_ton You have not been using you incognito browser option have you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dedbutdrmng been thinking about watching it..any good?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[would of been a peach if someone had the "Careful Now" placard  as well .@Glinner https://t.co/JiGIBSq2LV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@NivenJ1 better still they make Trump sit through a hour long Prince Charlie boy talk about climate change!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JeffreyHayzlett in Scotland we go one better though https://t.co/V9Mj9NuEK0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slackers in Space? https://t.co/2Cf9k89qdF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gaun yersel ma hame city. https://t.co/478Gsr0OTh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@flutterbyfjl I see the apparent often and it aint pretty. https://t.co/MklZjidvDb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scottish football on  #DeadlineDay prt 2 https://t.co/UcHl7mORn9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Greece free kick was from a rather dubious award I seem to mind https://t.co/LNFRC360lb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alt_doj @KTTunstall ..tick..tick..tick..ok just ONE BIG TICK..truth is depressing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@flutterbyfjl Probably a few hundred Trump flunkies and Nige Farage with "make pussy great again"..oops I mean "Make USA..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@io9 Help ma boab..it will be a real mess if they do that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@flutterbyfjl No probs with that. What will be funny when nae one turns up to see him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RenZelen @ScreenRelish when Ive been in That London the tube is more like this.. https://t.co/NbpVM1CaBa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RenZelen @ScreenRelish Ha if only all tube journeys were like that. Nor in my experience in Lahduhn anyways]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frantic dolphin tries to stop divers ripping baby away and 'selling to aquarium' https://t.co/Te7zCcBDTm effing dispicable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sethrogen @distant_cities The sound of vacuum cleaners humming the Hill...Yep they got the message.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichelleTopham1 @Joannechocolat @HuffingtonPost @realDonaldTrump @HuffPostPol Can't see it. I'm afraid as long the… https://t.co/rXnjn1NElM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emilynussbaum I think she had a couple of glasses and a bit squiffy..Lovely lass !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonathanHaynes I have been telling peeps to let him come and then everyone empties London and goes have massive pa… https://t.co/V97VxzlNNT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SnideRogue Ach silly me..retweeted them all anyway😆]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SnideRogue I wish there was a way multi retweet all of that. It was good reading and insightful!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Oliver__James @RenZelen From the trailer they seem to re-enact a lot of the  best bits of the 1st film]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@flutterbyfjl @theresa_may Clowns r cool. No problem with an official visit. Just no sooky baws pomp. https://t.co/CqvlsmdfP5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RenZelen @Oliver__James t I guess this is very much a mauldin middle man aged angst film about regret. I have not seen it yet or read bk!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@flutterbyfjl @theresa_may really, there are instances of world leaders coming and not calling it "state visit"- they can call it "official"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@flutterbyfjl @theresa_may we wouldn't be snubbing him at all, he can still come, chat, back rub Farrage. Just don't call it a State visit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Oliver__James @RenZelen you know put a bunch of middle aged men in room and that's pretty much all we can talk about]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@flutterbyfjl @theresa_may Its not about not letting him in,just about not giving him all the State pomp-press can ask him proper questions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@alanknox .@Smicht For her to squirm she would need to have a conscience. Evidence suggest otherwise, so suspect she cares not a jot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scottish football on #DeadlineDay https://t.co/vGyQsueHCw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carltonreid The petition is just about preventing a full blown state visit. He can come without all the pomp pish which Trump enjoys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@rogan_lisa heh well if we have an empty London it would be a start! #TrumpBan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think when/if Trump comes to the UK we should all stay away, and organise a big party somewhere else far away from him. #TrumpBan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liam Rudden: Trainspotting a lost generation https://t.co/j6POOmbjDp an alternative view, you should read.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Smicht I was a bit hmmm about that line as well. But signed it anyway as it's about stopping a "State visit". Nae pomp fir Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. If this is true. https://t.co/Z3dpbUgHCH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Correct me if I am wrong.We are essentially seeing the Exe branch of US gov at war with the Judicial branch. Won't end well. #TrumpBan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@garywhitta .@GOP a melt down faster than can draw up the impeachment papers...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump petition is up past 600k the last time I looked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does anyone else heart sink when a film/TV blurb  mentions "A group of 20 somethings..." #FilmSpeak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TrumpBan He is scared of stairs? Explains a lot. We should put him on one of these when he comes to the UK
https://t.co/dzyhnBC6Ra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@KTTunstall put him on this
https://t.co/dzyhnBC6Ra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@major_starman @chris_sheph ahh welcome back. Your time off meditating with the guru's fae Methil have paid aff then https://t.co/TCDx6KETyx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THE ALIENS MAGIC MAN https://t.co/FQUQWhdQtw See what I mean...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Aliens - Boats https://t.co/YEOPHZoPHc I had forgotten how good The Aliens were. Totally underrated and overlooked. Criminal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Happy Song - The Aliens https://t.co/SX6bmuQ0TW We need cheering up don't we.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Tennant Assures Us That Everything Will Be Alright - The Last Leg https://t.co/6D4zrnv0kR via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scottish Premiership Title is done. All about who gets relegated and who comes 2nd.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RenZelen @movieweb I was tad disappointed with the movie. The plot was a bit dull. It looked great tho.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hearts look like they have gee'd up. Disappointing. Can we start the "League is won already" #Celtic v #hearts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rather banning Trump we should let him in and then put him up at a cheap hotel and make him eat at a Wetherspoon #TrumpBan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Unthinkable2711 how was the supper last night? Sorry I was Man-Cold up. Could hardly speak &amp; did not want to give everyone the plague !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Unthinkable2711  indeed I think its mental thing  as well that managers are still going there and not trying to lose.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We should put him up in one of them Easy Hotels as well. https://t.co/gybpCJzSDw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Petition: Prevent Donald Trump from making a State Visit to the United Kingdom. https://t.co/Yv9oV2NF1g it has reached 100k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did the TV cameras 🎥 turn up for every single signing of Executive Orders for other Presidents?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saw the trailer for the adaptation of SS-GB that is going to on the BBC. Enjoyed the book so looking forward to it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing like a disembowelment to liven things up. #Taboo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top trolling of Trump by other world leaders. I wish  another certain PM would as well. https://t.co/uwoha83o6w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@sennydreadful now add a slosh of whisky...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Kezzang69 that was taken yesterday in the USA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Madness. We are living in mental times. https://t.co/7dWz1dEAMn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am now totally engrossed in the high octane sport of World Indoor Bowls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am in my dressing gown watching  The Posiedon Adventure. #sickday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thatsmabhoy 1st one was a stoner the 2nd was 50-50. Both teams scrapping but not much footy 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Red cards are flying out of the refs hand. #motherwell v #Rangers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pissed off that I cannie make it to the Rovers Supporters Burns Supper..The cold has got the better of me. 😷]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good on them! https://t.co/8cHgTUbesM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heavy cold has got the better of me. Staying in bed today and coughing a lot. I do have a well sexy gravelly voice tho..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Kezzang69 at least you kept your clothes on in the bar and did not attempt to do the full Angus....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And this is the man that we are told will give a us "good deal"- yea right bend over more like. https://t.co/zrXjylqq6f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...and so the carve up starts... https://t.co/yR1HQAJh4s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Bell on the special relationship – cartoon https://t.co/z8AkokmLuy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hmm #fortitude 1st episode 2nd season. Hmm...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Kezzang69 this is you every morning https://t.co/Ip1kkoGKai]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Kezzang69 you are still hungover aint you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kerrrching...this was of course the big plan from the get go..Next Workhouses... https://t.co/6cjoXhDmlG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HAWKWIND Spirit of the age https://t.co/36qcA3rmec Mid week groove out..]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>