<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Hmm.....who to believe?

Favourite - Suspended
RT - Cancelled https://t.co/Iw9A3KGjtG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joannaforest Lovely interview and singing again. x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HollyMcguirexx Maybe worth another trip?  I know it'll be the 7th time, but I can't see that it'll do any harm. x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HollyMcguirexx Have you been to the doctors? x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HollyMcguirexx Sorry to hear that you're not well, sending hugs and kisses and hope you get well soon. xxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a 🔔🔚 https://t.co/zefLAyJKUP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No lack of vegetables at my local supermarket.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VogueWilliams A shame, I was looking forward to seeing you on The Jump.  Wishing you a full and speedy recovery. x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElouisePlease Stop off on the way and treat yourself to a packet of biscuits and / or chocolates.  Or even a combination of both. x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right, off to buy some vegetables.  Wish me luck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had a giggle when I saw these trending next to each other. https://t.co/rgbqYW3SaH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Squishies_JJ Anytime. x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[£50?!  This deserved a custodial sentence of at least a year plus being forced to pay for at least half the cost of… https://t.co/XK8MKyZHyx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kategarraway @benshephard @GMB What an excellent interview with that brave soldier, and such an incredibly humble gentleman.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlysonMcKenzie Morning, Alyson. x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How anyone can cheat on Kylie Minogue is beyond me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never heard of him. https://t.co/gbw8EEytBZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's weird, I've not seen any protests, marches or demonstrations planned or any petitions started. https://t.co/lASgBMzgZt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UKCelebPics Lisa Snowdon, Alex Best, Susanna Reid and Ferne Cotton.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UKCelebPics I am, that's for sure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheProdigalFox Missing you in the #cbb house. x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRealKirstyG Looking beautiful. x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Squishies_JJ You're you and that's what makes people love you. x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What @NicolaMcLean said about women's rights is spot on. #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Straps around his shirt? #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just been playing air drums (don't ask) and done something to my shoulder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElouisePlease Fancy a nibble? x https://t.co/RbQ2XSQvVX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TBT The stunning @alibastian because...well, do I have to give a reason? https://t.co/L3jhKI70Mg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rnd3l What is it with Emmerdale and male strippers at the moment?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now this I can relate to! https://t.co/IgyaKzcGYT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile, in America, there's going to be a stiff breeze heading from the south west. https://t.co/Ij3lPL8P0N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TBT The lovely @LucyWeather dealing, in a very professional manner, with some unfortunately placed wind direction… https://t.co/9NgxacQXRG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hodge_Isabel Loved the way Victoria gave Chrissie what for tonight! x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll always amazed at how high on his body Mark King played bass. #totp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UKCelebPics Jennifer Metcalfe, Perrie Edwards, Gemma Atkinson and Holly Willoughby.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UKCelebPics Already replied, I'm confident of three of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UKCelebPics Jorgie Porter, Perrie Edwards, Lucy Pargeter and Holly Willoughby.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HannahBrooks25 Tits out Thursday? x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know about you, but I honestly can't tell them apart. https://t.co/T26Wogei1o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did anyone see Chris's reaction when Tamsin got the Tulsa question right? #TheChase]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a fan of fry-ups I've just had @SamanthaQuek's healthy one.  Check out the recipe on her timeline.

Simple and delicious.

A bit like me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Studied Music A Level and wasn't sure who composed the Brandenburg Concertos? #tippingpoint]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About bloody time. https://t.co/lGn71medij]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ammes2001 Farewell. x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ammes2001 Been using them for a few weeks now, no I'm on the laptop.  Goodbye. x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ammes2001 Yeah, I know.  Just messing with you!  Laters taters.  Or should that be laters potatoes? x 😬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ammes2001 But you still pay £40 for a bag of spuds! x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ammes2001 That's what I meant, yous lot. x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's amazing how much better your PC performs by simply clearing your cache.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ammes2001 Yes, I know Surrey's posh.  You lot think that a crèche is what happens when you accidentally rear end someone. x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why, every bloody time I log onto Twitter, do I get an e-mail from them telling me that I've logged in?  Often from a different place in UK?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HannahWoolmer CDs are all well and good, but for me there's nothing like the thrill of a live performance. x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ammes2001 OK, I'm not bloody perfect!  And I didn't know Tesco potatoes were so expensive. x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ammes2001 Nothing I enjoy more than wondering in a supermarket, basket in hand, surveying all on offer.  Gives me a warm feeling inside. x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ammes2001 Fancy some company?  It'll be the highlight of my week. x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HannahWoolmer Meant to ask, did you enjoy your day with the six year olds? x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamanthaQuek Increasing the quantity slightly, I'll be having your delicious healthy fry-up at least three times a week as a main meal. x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lucyzaraxx @MaccaGlamTog Enjoy your spa break, hope you have a lovely relaxing time. xxx (kisses for Lucy haha!).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlysonMcKenzie Mmm...would love to suck your nipples. x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlysonMcKenzie How I'd love to love to have your nipple in my mouth right now. x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClassicalTour4U @CalonFM Looking forward to Sunday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClassicalTour4U @CalonFM Loving @JonAntoine and @char_jaconelli on your show tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClassicalTour4U @CalonFM Life On Mars, great track from @joannaforest now.  Thank you so much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UKCelebPics Sian Welby, Coleen Rooney, Tina O'Brien and Sam Quek.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClassicalTour4U @CalonFM To the best of my knowledge, this is the first time you've played @DanielleLThomas on your show.  She's amazing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClassicalTour4U @CalonFM As much as I love @joannaforest you've already played this tonight.  Gremlins in the system? x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1CharlieBotting My pleasure, Charlie, will do all I can to promote to artists such as you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UKCelebPics Please!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClassicalTour4U @CalonFM Thanks for playing @1CharlieBotting tonight.  Love his version of Empty Chairs and Empty Tables.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LenaNPiano I'm not surprised, Rachmaninoff had a finger span of over an octave! x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClassicalTour4U @CalonFM Aww...bless you, Jan.  Listening to @Affiniti_music with the sublime vocals of @EmerBarrySop is so relaxing. x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClassicalTour4U Always tune in. x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClassicalTour4U @CalonFM Seen and noted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tune into @ClassicalTour4U on @CalonFM online from 9 for some great classical crossover music and interviews.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simmo1ks10 Thank you for your vote. 😃]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh well, less than two weeks to the second most commercialized time of the year.  But the good news is it's under 11 months till Christmas!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TallMartinH Sounds like the title of a song.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The problem with listening to Ravel's Bolero is that as the piece goes on you have to gradually have to turn the sound down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElouisePlease I've got an unopened pack of chocolate digestives, I can deliver them to you by about midnight depending on the trains. x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UKCelebPics Cheryl, Ola Jordan, Shakira and Jesy Nelson.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is beyond embarrassing. https://t.co/rZPXCabPAg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[England men's cricket have had a long history of mid-order collapses but today's abysmal performance tops the lot. #EngvInd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElouisePlease I was wondering what you wanted tugged until I opened the photo haha! x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lucyzaraxx @Porchiaxx @HollyMcguirexx @LeviBabestation New month, new sexy photos.  Glamour wherever I turn!  Have… https://t.co/5wjiHxEFO7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@isaguha @CharlesDagnall Timothy Dalton played James Bond twice, The Living Daylights (1987) and Licence To Kill (1989).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ammes2001 No worries, put your feet up and have a cuppa.  Glad to hear Katie's wrist is healing OK. x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, one of my new years resolutions is going the wrong way, must try harder this month.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ammes2001 Good morning, my dear.  Looks like you enjoyed yourself last night.  I trust all's well with Katie's wrist? x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@susannareid100 The enthusiasm in your voice enquiring where the wine was did make me laugh. x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TallMartinH Morning, you're probably already aware but there are apparently severe delays on the Metropolitan line.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UKCelebPics Rachel Riley, Luisa Zissman, Laura Whitmore and Catherine Tyledsley.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nessun Dorma on #cbb is something I thought I'd never see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UKCelebPics Fearne Cotton, Luisa Zissman, Laura Whitmore and Catherine Tyledsley.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UKCelebPics Davina McCall, Luisa Zissman, Laura Whitmore And Catherine Tyledsley.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UKCelebPics Christine Bleakley, Luisa Zissman, Laura Whitmore and Catherine Tyledsley.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With emojis being used more and more on social media, are we regressing back to communicating by hieroglyphics?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UKCelebPics Myleene Klass, Luisa Zissman, Laura Whitmore and Catherine Tyledesley.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UKCelebPics Sorry, Caroline Flack, Saara Aalto, Kara Tointon and Kirsty Gallacher.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UKCelebPics Caroline Flack, Iskra Lawrence, Jennifer Metcalfe and Kirsty Gallacher.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UKCelebPics I've got a feeling that tonight's competition is going to be a very short one.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>