<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@fkhanage bigger question is.. why aren't we going all out to sign him?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Johner02 he's a calamity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I honestly hope Jon Moss dies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never ever a red card]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jon moss is a fat horrible shambles of a ref who shouldn't be allowed to do kids games at the weekend let alone be a premier league ref]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Adriankel84 fight me ðŸ’ªðŸ‘Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonmikesav8 ye but the rolling around holding his face is another thing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @DailyMailUK have a snapchat story about Kendall Jenner having acne like that's "news" these days. Kill yourselfs you mongs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatieTaylor @FloydMayweather @TheNotoriousMMA whatcha yourself Katie he's fond of battering women]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was a dyer tackle on nacho #arsenal #afc ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jayhegarty we gonna have this UFC knock or what]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McCiaran2 I'll fight floyd for 100 euro don't mind 100 million ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McCiaran2 I dunno floyd has talked some amount of shit to be fair, don't know who started it, love to see Conor snap and choke him out ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McCiaran2 haha he's all talk man, he knows that the only way he wins is in a boxing match and staying well away from Conor's left hand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McCiaran2 @FloydMayweather @TheNotoriousMMA @espn he's easy work til he decides fuck this chasing shit and sparks him with a straight left]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyFootball what about if there offside goals hadn't of counted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll tell ye what... I hope the fucking Garda helicopter crashes. The fucking noise of it. Useless bastards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesFrancoTV is too fucking funny in that why him movie! Great craic ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johncrossmirror unfortunately nobody else is hurt like him by throwing away pints, the players at arsenal a long time are used to it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ufc #205 masterclass from mcgregor, Joanna outstanding, and wonderboy vs woodley was amazing! Shoutout 202 as well though! Good year ðŸ‘ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arsenal have been absolutely awful the last couple of months, top four at a push this season]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we were shit it would be a massive improvement.. shambolic football club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#twitch just made an account MartyParty90 feel free to join Bitches!! #xboxone #cod #Xb1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@John_Kavanagh I can't believe you called that. Put that it the next book ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@J_Farrell1 your goin for a ko?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@J_Farrell1 I Done a treble out 15 on dillishaw Cruz by decision and Rhonda sub bud wbu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@J_Farrell1 100 percent agree Agee she ran a mile, holly holm destroyed her and she ran away, should be good either way though pal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@J_Farrell1 ye man that's it could go either way still fancy Rhonda, she might retire either way win or lose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@J_Farrell1 all miesha Tate was BJJ though.. means nothing, Diego Brandao has a BJJ black belt ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@J_Farrell1 hard to say if Rhondas heads not in it then it's over but if she's at her best then she's tapping her out man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@J_Farrell1 she's managed by the company that bought the UFC and has the same agent as Dana it's madness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For all the shit Rhonda has got over the last year make no bones about it she'd still get plowed into oblivion ðŸ˜ #ufc207 #fearthereturn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bmcdublin  nice, just watching the embedded now if mma doesn't work out for her Nunez could work the door in finches]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bmcdublin nice ye going to stay up for it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bmcdublin bastards! Ye he has serious punchin power for a 35er, I've a treble on Rhonda sub Cruz decision and TJ for the win ðŸ¤ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bmcdublin ye he's due a big operation I thought it was after the Werdum fight ðŸ’” hope garbrant gets battered the handsome bastard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bmcdublin ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ for Rhonda to get back in the good books they should make her do 5 mins with Cain Velasquez ðŸ’ªðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bmcdublin haha ah stop she'd be living in a mountain somewhere in Dakota ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bmcdublin but she deserved it no one talks abou how easily Holly holm dealt with her it was class and it was takin away by Rhondas carry on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bmcdublin exactly no one cares that she lost happens to everyone Mighty Mouse Dominick Cruz everyone she just ran away for a year, madness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bmcdublin ye could go either way.. I think she's better than the other 135s she just handles herself like a clown and Dana let's her do it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bmcdublin stop man she nearly got head kicked into retirement ðŸ˜‚  on Ellen crying n all then given out because rogan n all talked bout it ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rhonda does NO media for months and it's fine, Conor misses A press conference and is kicked off #ufc200.. madness #ufc207]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arseblog I don't think we've moved on from Oli blogs... we're still stuck on forth mate ðŸ™ˆðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#arsenal about as useful as deep throating a cactus these days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@101greatgoals that smile is worth 300k p/w alone ðŸ˜ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alwayssunny boom cannot wait best show on the tv ðŸ‡®ðŸ‡ª]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love @alexiwobi â¤ï¸ hope he stays at arsenal for his entire career #AFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevgannon @AccaTrackerTM @Squawka gone be the days of soccer italia ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevgannon @AccaTrackerTM @Squawka is definitely a better league, Italian is shite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AccaTrackerTM @Squawka so what your saying is united new this was as good as he gets and still paid 90 million ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danielstorey85 piece on Arsenal today is unbelievably harsh. One away defeat in 9 months, that we "capitulated" is bollox.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joerogan people love a common enemy.. Big bad Russia seems to unite people .. that and mcgregor is going to fuck up Khabib ðŸ’ªðŸ‘ŠðŸ‡®ðŸ‡ª]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NathanKelly_ he looked like a forty bus trying to sort his feet out for West Ham's second]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Andy 25/1 to score next come on Andy ye cunt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyBet im trying to withdraw 100, I always have this problem can never make withdrawals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyBet I want to withdraw money from my account but it is saying I don't have enough to withdraw? Any suggestions?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZeeshanSajid1 copied that off @FunnyGooner ðŸ˜‚ðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZeeshanSajid1 literally just copied @Arsenal tweet ðŸ˜‚ðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@footbalIfights that's a horrific challenge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fkhanage Bang average. He is too careless with the ball, gives it away a colossal amount, Fantastic engine though,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@derek_noonan @ZPGIFs I seen that he just fight at a higher weight the dope]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAmJericho @J_Farrell1 @WWE your control of the English language is commendable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McCiaran2 we're going to win the league ðŸ’ªðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McCiaran2 ye haha just a scrap for top four ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McCiaran2 ah good luck turning into arsenal here ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McCiaran2 fucks sake man 3 of got injured in the space of two weeks when it rains it pours]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McCiaran2 we have to beat Dublin bus now big time, is Karl injured as well?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McCiaran2 ye I think so far don't go the physio, it's a pain in the bollox man, ye what happened there were we just had? Big game man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McCiaran2 hoping to be back training next week bud, I'll send it on tya now man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EAAccess UFC 2 that went on today can't believe it's on it top stuff out of you lads]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EAAccess is best thing in gaming in years unbelievable service ðŸ‘ðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Xbox keeps telling me my purchase can't be completed it's devastating]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iwobi off alexis out left giroud up top. #AFCvTHFC #afc #coyg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McCiaran2 ye if we win it puts us right in the mix and they weren't great last time we played]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McCiaran2 ye the physio reckons he's done something to the ligaments on his foot. Ye big time and we missed a peno! Was an important win]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McCiaran2 I got broke up bud ðŸ˜‚ no I don't think I'll be able to play for a few weeks me ankle swelled up like a balloon still sore to walk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Ryan19_ he looks like he's about to have a breakdown man he's stressed to bits, needs his big players to get goin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Ryan19_ stop man what's going on there for the manager the fans wanted he got the players he wanted just not happening is it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Ryan19_ stop man where looking at the league cup or nothing haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Ryan19_ I doubt but hopefully.. I just wanna win the league again or champions league like fuck me it's not hat hard ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Ryan19_ that's why I'm hoping we get two more seasons, don't think so but he's like can and khedira n all there turkish/German immigrants]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Ryan19_ I think at best we get two more years said he wants to play in turkey the lunatic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Ryan19_ stop his one last week when he finished with his right foot was ridiculous he's ice in his veins just how he signs on the cunt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Ryan19_ he was at the Euros he's only 22 young defenders always struggle at some stage if he's at barce he must have something about him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Ryan19_ awh stop bud where did that come from ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Ryan19_ I'll take it though ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get in there Basel #afc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Ryan19_ @piersmorgan @PeterNickeas I'm just glad they'll never win another major trophy as long as I live]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Ryan19_ @piersmorgan @PeterNickeas only thing there is they will want someone before the end of the season cause there English mongos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Ryan19_ @piersmorgan @PeterNickeas I really think he'll go to England or France as international for a year or two the retire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Ryan19_ @piersmorgan @PeterNickeas I think this is it I think he wants an international job to be honest, I think it will be a surprise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Ryan19_ @piersmorgan @PeterNickeas he looks the part of he got a mid sized job next see how that goes then bring him on again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Ryan19_ @piersmorgan @PeterNickeas he does to be fair but so did Martinez and he looked dreadful at Everton. I like Howe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Ryan19_ @piersmorgan @PeterNickeas big gamble. Same kind as moyes, utd board didn't back him and arsenals are way tighter bud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Ryan19_ @piersmorgan @PeterNickeas but who only fela at the top level is simeone and he won't leave I wouldn't be so quick to jump the gun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Ryan19_ @piersmorgan @PeterNickeas course bud but have to be realistic as well, and to be fair at the minute we're as. Good as anyone else]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Ryan19_ @piersmorgan @PeterNickeas we'd be absolutely fucked ðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Ryan19_ @piersmorgan @PeterNickeas he's not. United were the best team in England look how far they fell as soon as fergie retired??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Ryan19_ @piersmorgan @PeterNickeas nothing would make me happier he's a tool man]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>