<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Huge congrats to my bro, @Oriza8Riza on his appointment with @leytonorientfc. The official https://t.co/jEM5OicNpZ.… https://t.co/2MXfNBCOR9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love it, Jack! Different lands, views, styles and ideas.. plenty to learn from out there! @JPR_25 https://t.co/9PCtUNFS43]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moved house in July, and still no internet. Thanks @SkyUK. Pre work not done so engineers keep turning up and saying I can't be connected.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bit of practice defending on the line for indoor short corners with some of the younger girls at @HaileyburySport… https://t.co/73ZzLra1e5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bit of training indoors with a group of 3 @HaileyburySport girls tonight. GK on @CrazyCatchUK and other 2 working… https://t.co/exnr85UJiY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Working with @beacon_school on understanding roles in attack and defence depending on overload or underload.… https://t.co/UxsjIqYxsb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to be back on the field with @EnglandHockey U16 Boys yesterday. They seemed to grasp the principles well and… https://t.co/SNKGOrEHS6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited to head over to @ManiKochar's @Beacon_School this afternoon with @HaileyburySport to deliver a coaching session. #roadtrip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good luck @SiegfriedAikman! #TAPWestAfrica #HWL2017 https://t.co/1mAqJKa7Sk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donaldvinson how about if the 'trick' wasn't playing the ball with your body, which is so far removed from hockey, but just involved stick?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I personally love this video. Thoughts on learning 'tricks' and other things not used in games to help with familia… https://t.co/XPE7u3S8i8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see @irishhockey and @SA_Hockey being successful in their 1st round application for @FIH_Hockey league. https://t.co/f0fnZ9omBN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Training with @cchcuk was cancelled tonight so I trained with my preferred option of @HbyNetball. @englandnetball M… https://t.co/RNCxDvlXke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlexScott Have fun! #backtowinningways]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GKs at @HaileyburySport - check out the flexibility needed to be the best of the best. Great save @daveyharte https://t.co/SE7sEZDaRD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoaleeGuru @Arsenal Cheer loud, pal. #COYG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good luck in South Africa, Zara. https://t.co/AuAOvmfRJo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This morning we have @Hbury_LowerSch Girls Inter-form tournament followed by Main School Boys' fixtures vs @harrowschool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unfortunately Ben is injured, but we wish Christian and @OldLoughtsHC success at the National Indoors this weekend.… https://t.co/f62Dl8WTZ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If filled by hockey people, they'd also join my coaching team: @WappingHC @WHHCUK @West_HertsHC @StAlbansHC… https://t.co/fiJc0ie5Z0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If filled by hockey people, they'd also join my coaching team: @EnglandHockey @CoachAndInspire @FIH_Academy… https://t.co/DBLqPefGPz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Potential jobs for hockey people.. @SouthgateHC @OldLoughtsHC @Hertford_HC @broxbourne_hc @PottersBarHC @cchcuk - j… https://t.co/hwglTfAzVl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoaleeGuru Goalee Cage is a great idea.. especially when equipped with things I've been searching for!!… https://t.co/P6RYa5ruqU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JOB ALERT: @HaileyburyUK are recruiting and I'd love the roles to be filled by hockey people. #HockeyFamily https://t.co/OMjeAK6wqv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any hockey people out there looking to work as an English or Geography teacher? Let me know.. #HockeyFamily… https://t.co/um04M6HVwL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ability to tap into the experience of @DaveGM4P was a major influence.  A huge thanks also to @HaileyburyUK for their support.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited about accepting an offer to study at @UCLan. I'll be joining their Prof Masters in Elite Performance course.. #nextstep #thebestme]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JOB ALERT: @HillHouseSchool are looking for a new Director of Hockey. For those interested, please get in touch with them. #greatopportunity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats on being appointed the Final of @LisbonEH2017 @baz2756. https://t.co/tDSVGpCGdD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to Rose, Sarah, and Dan for being included in the @GBHockey Central Programme for the next Olympic cycle. https://t.co/4TrPteCi18]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks, Ed. Today was the first day of Boys' Hockey season so had to put everyone in A and B teams.. PLENTY of ques… https://t.co/YiPIycHefU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andyhalliday3 @Samuel_Ward13 actually red is central line = central contract #simplesam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Get @aaronramsey off.. he's rubbish!".. Rambo does it again.. Great finish boy!!! #arsenalfanssupportyourteam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emceejay2 @ppgannon @EnglandHockey As they say: Aim for the moon and you'll at least reach 3/4 way up a floodlight. https://t.co/wRn56YbiGl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A day spent in (not so) sunny Lilleshall gaining our IPAF MEWP 3a Operator licences. #skyisthelimit (well.. 33ft wo… https://t.co/6CSq0HzvS0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A really useful session from John. Thanks for the effort, and @CoachAndInspire for putting it on. #nightschool… https://t.co/o3ajo45tSP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please check out this interview with @pmorganwales as he talks about building a #learning and #development #culture
https://t.co/4tDLa3ltqy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had an amazing conversation with @pmorganwales about his 20years experience in Learning and Development.. https://t.co/YxTHp513Wf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Post Olympic year means both players and coaches leave the programme. It means opportunities open up - and this one… https://t.co/xtVqIFHQCm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huge news for @EnglandHockey and @GBHockey. Wishing you the very best in your next chapter @cc_keegan!… https://t.co/OrMzcUUhn4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love a bit of #madbehaviour playing in the background as I do some morning writing. @IzzyBizu has the most beautiful voice!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rule should be changed back to original version or scrapped completely. It'll open up the game and allow more attractive play]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot say the player is not interfering when standing offside; it changes behaviour of defenders and keeper.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This offside rule is nuts. Not only was Ibra off, but there was a player even more offside who blocked a defender from making a tackle!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adrianjclarke Because it hasn't been tried, tested, and proved amazingly useful in other sports.. oh, wait.. https://t.co/88eIvuR8A9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrNigelMitchell See you then, Mitch. HNY!! #COYG #startofanunbeatenyear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thought provoking article by @toddwilliamsuk - Get players better, not just the best players. #coaching https://t.co/o1HAFF4apU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@harrysingha HNY bro. See you in a little bit. Have fun this morning. #addingvaluefromdayone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fair play to @easyJet - to make up for wanting to charge us for safety, they let Rarity land the plane. #safehands… https://t.co/dsqyZk0Nit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Safe on the plane. 1 hour delay and a £125 charge for a booster seat for Rarity. I'll risk it! @easyJet… https://t.co/rdbwubEAj6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heading abroad for New Years and Aisha is upset she can't join me, so.. Rarity, her fave toy comes instead.… https://t.co/9Ncg3Rnavl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MJGold I think that if someone has to undergo athletic development to compete or gain an advantage in their sport, they're an athlete.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll go ahead and assume the equivalent applies in hockey: corner specialist opens up higher percentage of goals no… https://t.co/DwtUmyhe7f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making a difference.. Great work @AlexScott @AFC_Foundation @save_children #MBE #honourslist https://t.co/MSUyOg6TQR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats, girls! Much deserved! #NewYearsHonours #InspireAGeneration #HockeyFamily https://t.co/EDPFO2bhJi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any hockey people out there know where I can pick some of these up from?? Thanking you! https://t.co/DFusf334Hr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaveGM4P haha.. well I'm flying with EasyJet tomorrow and this is a pic from last time I flew with them.. #easypet https://t.co/IC03IiSnJ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaveGM4P "A huge improvement" say others..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laura_tott Merry Christmas, Laura. Have fun!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the 5min workouts from @shauntfitness but today it was BabyBel who joined in. "That was hard, but fun!". Thank… https://t.co/dQF5jDHjrv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pictures lie! Moments after this photo I had won the fight by knock out! #DarrenAndGoliath..  @FrankBuglioni I need… https://t.co/KEPyxIRDvM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toddwilliamsuk @Danfox450 He has a 1st class batting average of 73.75?? He's never mentioned it.. Congrats on you Int hockey innings Foxy x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colinnell Don't be so hard on yourself. We all love you, bro x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tommaldinho @CBeebiesHQ haha - not quite, but I'm sure I'll have to suffer that in the coming days! #daddyproblems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A stunning performance of The Nutcracker this afternoon. I'm now fully into the holiday spirit and ready for the ne… https://t.co/FaAPy4Xx0g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having observed a kids' training session, I left with some serious questions about the coach and my own coaching.. https://t.co/0vObQFvlih]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @FIH_Hockey are launching a new League. Interested to see which countries make it in. https://t.co/m2WrMzRZxd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Super performance of 'Teacher' by this little actress in the Christmas Play today at her school. Love the person sh… https://t.co/e1yfHFQXOh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you for being such a fantastic role model. Happy Birthday / feliz cumpleaños @Alexis_Sanchez… https://t.co/sKnByZboJl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to friend and brother @jcruehr - keep doing what you do! https://t.co/H95mRqahmd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huge congrats to @OldLoughtsHC U16 Boys who won the East Regional Indoor Championship today to book place at Nation… https://t.co/BvTYlFDNXq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More Awards.. @Hbury_LowerSch Player of the Season for Boys and Girls. Congrats Will and Becky! https://t.co/SpOYWINfcV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huge game. @hockeybe looking for their new crop of Olympic medalists and @DHB_hockey on quest for 3/3 JWCs.. https://t.co/2zERB9KvJT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last, but not least, I want to say an eneromous thank you and well done to our U6th leavers. JL, IS, and Captain ES… https://t.co/qJoMzHEnG3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huge congrats to SN who has shone since joining our school this year. Training Points Winner 2016! Thank you… https://t.co/4BKlUj1nkY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[End is Season Awards for @HaileyburySport 1st XI Girls.. Player: ES, Players' Player: LB, Golden Stick: BD. Congrat… https://t.co/K6mhyUDqHm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've just returned home from the most remarkable Lower School Carol Service, orchestrated by @HaileyburyMusic. Traditional yet breathtaking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a saying that we change behaviour due to inspiration or desperation.. we had one of those on Sunday - https://t.co/PScEQjcQqf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really impressed with the U21 boys today vs @SA_Hockey. Big performances and looking like a tournament threat. Congrats guys! @EnglandHockey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There we go.. top work @jontygriffiths! 4-2 and back in control]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow.. a backhand goal for @SA_Hockey through Crowe out of nowhere and suddenly they're back in the game. 3-2 @EnglandHockey. #finishthejob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trained hard all season ✅
Stand out player for Bs ✅
Debut today for As ✅
Debut goal for As ✅

KFS, well done! https://t.co/nniWzb09Aw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Medals around necks, smiles on faces, memories in bank.. Congrats girls. #keepmovingforwards https://t.co/SFO5HgDMed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The girls are with the board again and they have a message.. "We're going to Nationals!" #learning #nexttarget https://t.co/NdlMOFV6Ka]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girls continue to take responsibility for their own journey and I may be out of a job soon. 5-1 win vs a good… https://t.co/tzToHUdXa8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don't lose your first game of a tournament".. guessing @newhallhockey were told the same. A goal at the death of e… https://t.co/5Yvf1Mt4n7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pitch at looks beautiful, but not fit for hockey. So.. we're taking the U16 Girls to play in the East Indoor tourna… https://t.co/qGeIot1tnX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2nd XI lose 2-0 in their dual with a very good @FelstedSchool team. Great to watch (hockey and the scenery) https://t.co/YuAQeunYdQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1st XI warm up to get them focussed for the battle. Must have worked.. 3:1 win vs @FelstedSchool. A really good, co… https://t.co/yHLFk9YdGW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A nice little session with our Girls 6th XI before jumping on the bus with 1st and 2nd XI for away fixtures at… https://t.co/fz6LewlaE7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another morning of @Hbury_LowerSch fixtures: U13A Girls lost 2:1 vs @chigwellschool and U13A lost 5:1 vs… https://t.co/3kuq4Wh1PA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some good early intensity in the press from @EnglandHockey. Keep it up girls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GER vs ENG in the classification games.. A big performance needed from the girls to bounce back. #letsgo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Super proud of the U13 Girls today. They took ownership of their game and played so well. Didn't make Semis by smal… https://t.co/GHuGF7mpk6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This small quote is so powerful and speaks to so many youngsters out there wanting to climb higher. @AlexScott you… https://t.co/wU3vtx4oEv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow.. that was a fairly decent corner flick. Top corner. 5:3 and not long to go. @megcrowson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting for me is how comfortable Spain seem to be with the ball just off the floor. Makes it much harder to press with flat sticks..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great carry, turn and shot from @megcrowson - lifeline??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spanish looking very excitable at the minute and seem to be smelling blood. Astonished at the technical skills on show from them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And there's the fifth..]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>