<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@UnaMMB @jamblemb @UnaMMB LA  is such a bind for customs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why the rich are running out of money https://t.co/HON9a4chNU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamblemb @UnaMMB Hugo is looking forward to someone helping him with his stick. https://t.co/fV4Ga0iTuh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timeshighered @UnaMMB must be a @realDonaldTrump thing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamblemb I just hope @UnaMMB @una doesn't fancy a nibble enroute. We have stocked up with crisps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Western Bay's $802m tourist spending spree https://t.co/Z6CM06yzeW via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Genetic potato material sent to global seed vault https://t.co/HZcpeva9Pj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Half of academies fall short on funding https://t.co/8x7B1hC258]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This remote Scottish island is coming back to life https://t.co/vLryNaktay via @BBC_Travel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overhaul of UK train ticket pricing to be trialled in May

https://t.co/8baesj7Bg2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - The long-distance learners of Aleppo https://t.co/9wn2GHHwvK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who should host the Sevens? https://t.co/gv8cBKb733]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fellowship is back: Lord of the Rings cast reunite after 15 years https://t.co/Lqdt0YBgd1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weird and wonderful spa tourism
https://t.co/Jopw71t2Gx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tourism and gentrification
https://t.co/HcElaDGOOl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bloody tourists and cycel trail - a case of council spending https://t.co/v0G5pQi2In]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - No, this isn't Trump's brother https://t.co/WwHaoqF6WC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I ❤ Donald. As they say in Sheffield he's a great Duck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jihadist groups hail Donald Trump's Muslim travel ban as a victory https://t.co/Jvhdeajzia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - The Irish model: How low should taxes go? https://t.co/McoceSQgbv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump promised disruption and we got disruption https://t.co/GxqbVTzvkA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Airbnb offers free housing to those hit by Trump ban https://t.co/fotBa0OVbq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even Knights of the realm are banned by Trump! 
Mo Farah calls Trump's travel ban 'ignorant and prejudiced'

https://t.co/V2c5htni7i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Could Scotland really have a spaceport? https://t.co/Bg4n5mgoQX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Newcastle pipped Sunderland to the international airport

https://t.co/zuQQyTNYzD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this story from the NZ Herald Android App
https://t.co/RdzY9cOiFf https://t.co/apThKi90RA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vinyl makes a comeback - in pictures

https://t.co/A9sSapNKOY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rosamund Pike: ‘I'm happy being No 2. The guy's usually No 1'

https://t.co/jtXCpRj2H6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network at 40: the flawed satire that predicted Trump and cable 'news porn'

https://t.co/ZdRm7eFESC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From driverless cars to space tourism: what's the future of transport? https://t.co/ylwWcdpoxu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barcelona cracks down on tourist numbers with accommodation law

https://t.co/A6fSFpUNV6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The US safe haven from Trump https://t.co/czs2AvDcUG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this story from the NZ Herald Android App
https://t.co/QxXtZ2l47J https://t.co/1s7m6n9Aj8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what the election of Donald Trump is unleashing - Trump fan charged with hate crimes over JFK Muslim attack https://t.co/1gqOjiTjI8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How East and West think in profoundly different ways https://t.co/0kLoF5fyT9 via @BBC_Future]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Avocado anxiety over Trump's border tax https://t.co/x8pM1WnPgX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The private lounge https://t.co/w7IY0XWzj7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Free soda: France bans unlimited sugary drink refills https://t.co/gFcw4eylpK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yorkshire fish-lovers set up first ethical sturgeon caviar firm

https://t.co/f9ucxK5lZx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hammondfuturist @nwtls taking the piss!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Channel_View @AcBookWeek special offer on forthcoming and yet to be commissioned on the future of @SunderlandAFC toutism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wef @maurizioi you forgot about @RealDonad_Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The country where unwanted food is selling out https://t.co/pGQ78DbxFH via @BBC_Future]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Euro 'could fail', says man tipped as US ambassador to EU https://t.co/EcHwjInjtt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There might be a gap in the wall ie all of the California border. Check out this story from the NZ Herald Android… https://t.co/IUcnBCmr1S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Americans can no longer speak the Dutch. Great. https://t.co/OyuDak6mV6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to move abroad? Try here https://t.co/OoakquEskC via @BBC_Travel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Airbus warns over Brexit free movement https://t.co/ZLAt7m5k2G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - In pictures: The Pole who works in a UK hospital https://t.co/ihZTP2CWZv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - English B&amp;Bs dominate TripAdvisor 2017 awards list https://t.co/yviVM76Y1M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Will tourists pay nearly double to enter Angkor Wat? https://t.co/Ck2tqX0DGs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing soon: ecturer/Senior Lecturer in Tourism Management at Victoria University of Wellington https://t.co/5HNq8rn21L #jobsacuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YOU LOST! Brexiteer rips into BBC guest who says Remainers are 'GRIEVING' over May speech https://t.co/qeXlj1CL5l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's 70 with cancer; her husband has had 7 strokes, so she takes on two jobs to pay bills https://t.co/s6uWx2p7oo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what someone told their Muslim neighbour after Donald Trump's inauguration https://t.co/ew80Yupo6K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Will Make China Great Again https://t.co/hrAJzcItWg via @barronsonline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Older mothers: The birth of the 'retirement baby' https://t.co/cB0VfnGgLe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Queenstown to Te Anau commercial flights to boost tourism https://t.co/OHvjt1fmAV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: A Pacific Rail Trail – the best in the world? https://t.co/PJJMsFiBJB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freeze-dried food and 1 bathroom: 6 simulate Mars in dome https://t.co/HCU6SfsCti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - How the barcode changed retailing and manufacturing https://t.co/wfCUPGe8Ew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Village Roadshow warns spending and theme park visits lower since Dreamworld accident https://t.co/E0z8r64dex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the ball: Football strikes on rugby's NZ turf as kids vote with their feet https://t.co/URfSosWurl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UNWTO Seminar on the Future of Tourism: Innovation, Governance and Critical Paths https://t.co/2yMkHdWxzB via @unwto]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Globelet lifts its sights from festivals to whole cities https://t.co/LE4QT0VM5Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paula Bennett: Let's make diversity a priority https://t.co/no7TvTJj79]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Sorry cats, doggos run the internet now https://t.co/MBF2BW5HuF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Australia eyes relaxed UK immigration under trade deal https://t.co/idednuJ4nZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's make China great again https://t.co/Y44PA0Sw3A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parks already having the @realDonaldTrump effect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World rebellion begins - Donald Trump begins overhaul as first executive orders signed https://t.co/KPobwCiO0d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunderland the first place to vote Brexit. Well Nissan do the same. 

https://t.co/JfFq7EXNDZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC Sport - Manchester United: The commercial power driving club to top of Deloitte money list https://t.co/1NteqHFfWc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Light relief from Trump: - US frisbee team captures frozen lake crossing https://t.co/WmvKqqQ7uk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Guardian readers are coping with the courgette crisis

https://t.co/2Rust0NjMq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harrods stops taking cut of tips in its restaurants after protests

https://t.co/dlvnl5uIIu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Bank exodus? https://t.co/E0HJkGhyEL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Pummelled by turnips at Spanish festival https://t.co/w6qfTbFNtS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's pray -  Six found alive in hotel after Italy avalanche https://t.co/xMDbMplSDo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why your children will be the first generation to be worse than you 

https://t.co/XJpSxEn6Cu https://t.co/mPdq4dML3l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For PhD students. The difference between limitatins and delimitations https://t.co/45J134esm8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Reina attack highlights widening chasm in Turkish lifestyles https://t.co/1v6KlBdT9s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Pretend you're in The Italian Job or get the bus? https://t.co/xp1X4nWE0R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - From bombs to bytes: How Beirut's tech scene is thriving https://t.co/wWm1Cv5scT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - The dying officer treated for cancer with baking soda https://t.co/POymxbrZ92]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Sir Patrick Stewart: Poo emoji role for Shakespearean actor https://t.co/0dNGpvVFbX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - 'Pussyhat' knitters join long tradition of crafty activism https://t.co/PFhA2QeHxa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UnaMMB @bookingcom See you in a fortnight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UnaMMB great day in Amsterdam at https://t.co/ocUseiZ07u AGM. Science fiction rocks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inauguration Eve: Trump juggles work, play, prepares to party https://t.co/eO9C1vR6I4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla avoids recall in probe of death linked to Autopilot https://t.co/NJnvnrZ6RF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheEconomist @UnaMMB Not that i am using them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant day at https://t.co/ocUseiZ07u staff day exploring trends and the role of science fiction. Presentation https://t.co/ltR6fB144u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Tunisia attack: Tour operator TUI 'not aware of security risk' https://t.co/4OMnacuA5R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I saw this on the BBC and thought you should see it:

Aeolus wind mission heads for test and launch - https://t.co/APdM3LMU3I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amsterdam attempts to stem its tourist flood and regain its soul https://t.co/TKtXdZ6Un9 via @POLITICOEurope @ETFI_APostma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The places that ‘don’t exist’ https://t.co/wXiJjqpxzr via @BBC_Travel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future of theft in Canada. Maybe they are Russian? https://t.co/XK5A7yNJBu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York hotel arrives in pieces from Poland, some assembly required  https://t.co/nMirCIRP1F via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Restaurants have taught me who I am’

https://t.co/92l1kSZxwG]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>