<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[What the crap does it mean when windows 10 does this ? https://t.co/p8eOM7n5It]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I'm old and grey I'm going to hang a cellphone on my belt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Optus Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Optus happens always. Easily reproduceable on any T1 T2 line, seems like cell towers are not handshaking between sites]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know you are on shitty @Optus when calls drop approaching Strathfield Station. Cmon fix this now already]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why bother with NZ summer. https://t.co/C8e4UWGTE0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Apple magic all right because they are impossible to find a store that sells them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nate @stevebiddle #alternativefact what an bumbling idiot has no idea how the technology works]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CyrisXD what is in that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matthewc1465 that didn't last long]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevebiddle I am sure you just spent it all trying to sort that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevebiddle @Rosspnz @scottjpalmer @flying_geek @zkarj this shitty weather should stop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevebiddle remind me again why you were trying to register for OneSmart? @FlyAirNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matthewc1465 stop wasting from the Koru fridge. :) @freitasm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@freitasm @matthewc1465 why would anyone want to drink beer when there is wine and bubbly especially when in J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a sign! I got my AirPods during the #Inauguration https://t.co/nABdVwttbA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billbennettnz was there yesterday. Will travel back again tomorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billbennettnz works fine for me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Screen saver a bit broke in SYD lounge https://t.co/V9wnrNFTTf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@freitasm that's for me!  But mine usually routes via Auckland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thatjohn @stevebiddle  @staralliance can @FlyAirNZ move to OneWorld please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevebiddle and what rules were they bending? @lancewiggs @benkepes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevebiddle still don't understand what the fuss is about]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SwiftOnSecurity is this like lung cancer protection for cigarette packs?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeremybank gave up and ordered from US]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeremybank such a shambles of a release]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevebiddle @ajobbins for how much longer? Try going down and experience it :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevebiddle hm, poor value for dollar spend, nothing relaxing about their confined rooms @ajobbins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevebiddle Yes. That shoebox. @ajobbins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AstroDamo Can't - no more physical time to travel with existing bookings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevebiddle with much dismay. Hilton next wee as well. @ajobbins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ajobbins @stevebiddle 70 points is about a membership year with QF club so not end of world]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ajobbins @stevebiddle yeah with all this travel is physical time I don't have.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[70 credits short of renewing Gold in QF. Much sadness @ajobbins @stevebiddle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevebiddle @antoniosk their intelligence batch process must have completed and ready to accept yours now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevebiddle Glad I have done mine before they introduced the optional "social media" questions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevebiddle sadly I have work to tend to, would love a job that lets me watch flight radar 😉]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevebiddle so much anticipation and suspense]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevebiddle @flickkky or just learn to drive. Suitcase are/should all be standard sizes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pifflevalve at least it isn't your resignation letter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Noise cancelling headphones so you don't have to listen to hippie gluten free mums bragging about their 1 year old in a plane]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the typical queue for priority boarding on QF flights. Quite a different experience to @FlyAirNZ where half… https://t.co/akftoBuMuw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DylanReeve I should know this given the charge card I have, but I don't. @stevebiddle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevebiddle @DylanReeve have used and know of people who claim travel insurance from credit cards. Good experience really]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jordantcarter people still watch live tv?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Wellington summer gets any colder we might just save ourselves the trouble and go live in a canister of liquid nitrogen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Funny comments about pretentiousness from a pretentious reviewer Mr Burton https://t.co/dSy4wAYi38]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm pretty sure this was a given https://t.co/HzOSEKVQjy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevebiddle @scottjpalmer possibly but @ajobbins might be comparing a flagship QF lounge against a satellite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevebiddle @scottjpalmer I've moved on up to Centurion Lounges....pity none for domestic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Side effect from too much travel is being able to read out booking numbers and names over the phone using the NATO phonetic alphabet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jordantcarter @Koennz erm mine were all decent and pleasing to the eye 😅]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jordantcarter based on the sort of snaps that get sent to @Koennz ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Syntax errors aside, I'd also fire any developers for improper object naming https://t.co/Sg3TlOEsAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeauGiles most degrading experience is booking and turning up for a @AppleSupport genius appointment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelloMissPotter but will pray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelloMissPotter I left them for this, far better value with 2deg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dabigjim or more like a cut of beef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deprecated: The Ars 2017 tech company Deathwatch https://t.co/aeXbdNj1ss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KiwiforGmail I paid for a license and now get an error requesting to download from the Mac App store. Why am I being asked to pay again?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevebiddle case in point NZ can't be allowed to have anything good. SFO never went below 8ºC all week the middle of winter @PhilipDuncan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevebiddle @matthewc1465 going to miss this no routine days. Sigh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billbennettnz it is all about the school zones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YourLegacyNZ @eliterate Yet I've had clients demanding me to publish availability of consultants over the break. Why don't we do the same?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WLG on a summer's day is more disappointing than a cold winter's day in SFO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ellenstrickland just saw this - congrats!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pakistan top for gay porn. Nice to know https://t.co/apgYAvObxm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plenty of empty J seats in NZ7 tonight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevebiddle still at dinner. Not sure where to head to after.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevebiddle 3 hours to go in SFO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Average wines really https://t.co/bJ9hw0YGwS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kim Crawford wines heavily marketed in SFO https://t.co/B20cNhtgye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ronsoak Then it is just reddit?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emmawehipeihana those who badly treat staff have never worked a day in their lives in hospitality]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiting for Luzia https://t.co/Y2Om1BIRyD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every holiday ruined by children https://t.co/cm0YJ628NP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SFO public transport is as bad and as Portugal. Just don't bother and get @Uber instead and save your sanity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@flickkky yeah such a culture shock - tastes like mushy pavlova]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Divinity candy https://t.co/ftJLmQIpl4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Restroom facilities in SFO are a tad bit disappointing. Let alone fine one in the first place. @sfgov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SFO on a good day beats Welly https://t.co/rbWk5f6xoj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevebiddle in and out https://t.co/LywNYv5cQQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlyAirNZ 10 seconds boarding call for Business an Elite isn't enough. Please sort this out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @FlyAirNZ what a farce boarding NZ8 tonight. So disappointed every time, dreading boarding calls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dylankbuckley I find solace in the skies. No one can reach me.  😀]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[End of the line of an insane year of flying. cc @stevebiddle going to beat this? https://t.co/3DQJi9fa0m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Given we have regressed so much this year in 2016, we should officially welcome 2015 again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matthewc1465 in all seriousness take the box off. It will fit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matthewc1465 return for a smaller one?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who needs Boxing Day sales when you get to spend time at 36000 feet? https://t.co/LF0ciiIcy0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Voxox having problems connecting to international calls from cloud phone. Any  ideas?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ow 108 per hour :) 50% cheaper now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ow €217 per hour?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AshleySaturday some use the term "defects" at work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@C_B_82 I think some incompetent  @UberEats drivers are rating me down. They are extremely incapable of reading delivery instructions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@C_B_82 ack!! 4.95!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@C_B_82 is there an easy to find out these days ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ow it is not challenging if it is in business 😉]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@troyhunt no Reddit hmmm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SthIsRoss and to you!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>