<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Replace all television programming with this https://t.co/hgw83gZZ1e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bannon successfully wormed his way onto the NSC by correctly betting Trump would only read so many words of an EO he then signed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Capitalism has gotten very strange very quickly https://t.co/CsAc7uXsOJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah typically you should want politics to be boring and not "exciting" https://t.co/f4mWsFL4O4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's "going on" Marco? https://t.co/uwzjNJnnCF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danpfeiffer or they decided general positive messages about diversity will win over more than they lose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worth noting Trumpers getting mad about any diverse representation proof their real target is multiculturalism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish I knew enough about football to write the plainly necessary take on the homoerotic relationship between Tom Brady and his male fans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My laundromat is very angry about the stolen SCOTUS seat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like if the cost of living in a free and multicultural society is you have to press 1 for English at the ATM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The weirdest obsession of nationalists will always be the complaints about immigrants and language.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[tag yourself I'm "quantum of risk" https://t.co/pmSSuXQREV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GillBranstetter this is the kind of legal argument you get when you fire the AG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thwarting the EO is the damn point https://t.co/ksqaq3mX9q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McCarthy's Spicer is the kind of impression that ruins a person]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy crap she's perfect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean it's definitely making me want Totino's]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You guys Andy Stanley gets me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottbix typically I look for advice from thrice married serial adulterers and sexual predators]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And she dropped an F bomb!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kristen Stewart is wearing my favorite outfit ever as of five minute ago when I first saw her wearing it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a third way https://t.co/m782ikuRKj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TelegraphBooks @michikokakutani just read Grief Is The Thing With Feathers and that should be really up there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sadydoyle Nazis kinda roped them in but it's all the same traditionalist BS--Gamergate was one of many wellsprings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Steven_Hyden here you go https://t.co/5TMIHZnrH2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At this point there's enough fake BGM tributes future historians will get Pulitzers for writing about it https://t.co/6ixLSH5eAb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just found out the super bowl is this weekend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So this is a great essay about Elon Musk's preference for scifi utopia over solving real world problems https://t.co/AueGYsXbw7 via @aeonmag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fool blames others for making a fool of them https://t.co/Z2h56W7nPB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The president who wants to make the world respect America is losing an argument with Arnold Schwarzenegger https://t.co/d04rBUE0Vi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oliverdarcy what are the odds he invites Milo to the White House]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/bFBP0yE1AY: The #1 Most Trusted Resource for Ethnic Backgrounds of Private Individuals That Could Never, Ever Be Misused]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone else really freaked out by https://t.co/bFBP0yE1AY ads?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not repeal, not replace, but https://t.co/r5jpJy7Epr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danharmon Is it possible he's the world's first stupid narcissist?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a thing we completely forgot about https://t.co/D8zX6U5Fhz via @slate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Forgotten Man https://t.co/uw2001Zgn1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Confirms theory DeVos is going to close all the schools and enroll all kids in Lumosity https://t.co/WIQectH48R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GillBranstetter Article aptly points out Bannon gave '14 talk suggesting WWI&amp;II and end of USSR validation of Christian virtue/dominance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GillBranstetter Fear of Islam tied to fear of changing sexual/societal norms. It's less a wave of nationalism than one of traditionalism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GillBranstetter @TheAtlantic tl;dr Putin/La Pen/Trump/et al are tied by a belief in the impending doom of Christian nations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this is the best and scariest thing today https://t.co/qTUyG0Zws5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This man has zero idea who Frederick Douglass was https://t.co/zaoAlaj2PT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying Come Back From San Francisco by The Magnetic Fields ♫ https://t.co/uOijmaV8N6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a thing https://t.co/KJydEeqbeN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The front of the horse has agreed with the back of the horse https://t.co/chole8RmlI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder how many protest sign Pinterest boards got started this week]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the Bannon-Trump relationship apparently works https://t.co/A9QnnnNLjz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile https://t.co/GiETA3VsY4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turn on Fox news right now and try not to vomit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GillBranstetter he's a Rand obsessive who's sole operating mission is a belief the poor are not worthy of his respect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Ryan will allow Trump to do anything if he helps the Speaker take health care from poor people https://t.co/MSp1Tbllcx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember the time a judge stayed an Obama order and it was a political crisis?

Trump just had his first stayed order on his eighth day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So still not a Muslim ban or https://t.co/rpimeger8Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GillBranstetter "Hey! Trump's not so bad. Here's a list of brutal tyrants who do the same thing"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glad to know what kind of leaders Trump is getting his inspiration from https://t.co/m68hu5Egyv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the reason any Dem who votes yes on Trump's SCOTUS nominee should be primaried into a goddamn oblivion https://t.co/tZEY1ubKwk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHY IS DICK CHENEY THE VOICE OF REASON https://t.co/9syA1yDmw3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are convincing no one and embarrassing yourself https://t.co/A7a3PzeHgz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Bannon's "opposition party" line includes Breitbart, no? Or is he tacitly admitting Breitbart is not journalism by any traditional sense?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so what are you going to do when lettuce cost $20 a head https://t.co/PdDEld25YO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morganmpage it's the new empowerment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fmanjoo saaaame. I'm hoping for a design contest a la WTC One]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just published “The Power of the Irrational” https://t.co/MaMN2ngvTC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving this article's assumption that the US has ever had a moral high ground https://t.co/6GJThbuRvZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not enough traffic from Breitbart, I guess https://t.co/fpfr94cvdp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Touting ACA, PA Gov. Wolf Invites Ryan to Drug Treatment Center https://t.co/cJn6f13PIe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tbh still listen to "Love Is All Around" to cheer myself up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GillBranstetter "But as for me/I'll sit and eat a buttercup sandwich/and wait till the shower is over"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GillBranstetter I'm just exhausted. This was the plan, I guess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GillBranstetter People are going to be actively hurt by everything the President has done and it is Wednesday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GillBranstetter but censoring research? Insulting journalists? Wagging your ego about?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GillBranstetter some is normal--pipelines, health care. Elections matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been following politics with a microscope all my life and I just can't consume all the awfulness of this moment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weird that NASA telling me about the atmosphere is a rebellious act https://t.co/3EIh8kELO2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AkilahObviously that's optimistic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why not just stab me in the neck and get it over with https://t.co/rrj7EMgho1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Wouldn't it be great if we got along with Russia?" https://t.co/wkoltp1qr8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe we'll have a new Press Secretary every briefing like Emily Gilmore's maids https://t.co/Dqd9GAXiKi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's 10 https://t.co/Bl8OB2zwL4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every clue thus far indicates the overall theme of Trump's presidency will be his insatiable lack of self-worth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JennyBoylan "She's A Rainbow" though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tommen is the son of King Robert. Period. https://t.co/yhPmhsJrYA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eddard Stark was a traitor. Period https://t.co/I6nV7KvlwE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tyrian poisoned Joffrey. Period. https://t.co/25TVbRTTpa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sean Spicer gave that briefing like he had just been Force-choked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GillBranstetter millions of people are protesting the president and his response is to complain about tweets and camera angles!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What in god's name did I just witness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT IS  NOT THE JOB OF THE PRESS TO MAKE YOU LOOK GOOD--THAT IS YOUR JOB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHY IS THE PRESIDENT SO PETTY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GillBranstetter brb digging up my "NO BLOOD FOR OIL" hoodie from 2003]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That "empty field" Trump is saying the media showed is actually a cool place called "The National Mall" https://t.co/Kssj0rJ7rE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thetomzone did they forget women are people or]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SoccerLimey more pointedly: Trump holds less sway in Congress the less popular he is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SoccerLimey the point of the marches is that it is relevant--and should be taken as such by lawmakers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SoccerLimey yes but he is also a sexual predator who lost the popular vote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3) This man really cares about crowd size and losing the popular vote. Exhibit A https://t.co/Kcogj9Qg5E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2) Trump lost the popular vote by wide margin and needs to prove his functional ability to speak for or act on behalf of the people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But these are different for a few reasons 1)show veracity and motivation of anti-Trump movement (these were planned in TWO MONTHS)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So crowd size is typically a bit silly--we all said about Sanders/Trump that crowds don't equal votes]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>