<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@NiamhyKenny Ah I'm having such a good night with the ould insta x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OrlaWbu oh god, I thought she still had the bar. I'm so behind the times #iknowbestforme]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OrlaWbu really and truly though, this is the greatest caption of our times https://t.co/k3tg1xK6eA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OrlaWbu Jesus I didn't even notice that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trisha's instagram is pure on fire this evening]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomasinamcg I literally ran to Anthony's]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OrlaWbu thank you thank you with my vast experience as a financial analyst and advisor I know exactly what emojis to use]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OrlaWbu you know it ðŸ“ˆðŸ“Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got the first ever accounting problem I did to balance so I'm ready anytime for a wee job there KPMG x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clareisainmdumb @Kirrrsty From now on I'm mixing all of my highlighters all of the time. You are a gift ðŸ˜âš¡ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trainspotting was brilliant. And I mean the first one because I haven't seen it until tonight I was so #uncultured]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I relate to Phillip Schofield on a spiritual level when I accidentally(?) get two sides https://t.co/zIMja9riiV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honestly there is a place in hell for drivers who don't dip their headlights until they're practically beside you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[in school I never thought I'd be good enough at maths to ever do accounting or finance so thank you @ UCD for making me believe in myself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Paulitics It's just frustrating that one grade can bring your GPA plummeting to the ground, but sure look. We're hanging in there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Paulitics I'm really relating to this too much right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I always feel so betrayed when CA lets my results down. Like this is the part that you're meant to build up your marks with]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well fuck everything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sitting on the 17, in a black velvet glittery jumpsuit, a Penneys zip up hoodie, with a wee plastic bag with two naggins in it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OrlaWbu The gherkins do, of course]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like what else would you be doing at 1 in the morning except talking about gherkins with Ã“rla]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OrlaWbu this is from 24 hours and 2 minutes ago hahaha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OrlaWbu I'll be right down]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got lost driving through Shercock and I'm suitably embarrassed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AilbheOC is it Platform Pizza?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone buy me some vintage Adidas Olympic gear le do thoil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@himynameisaine the same page about the whole thing I think it will be fine ðŸ˜ŠðŸŒŸ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@himynameisaine so I think there's a good level of stability and openness about it. I'm not saying it won't be hard but as long as you're on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@himynameisaine it's a set amount of time and three months is fairly short in the grand scheme of things! We've been together almost 4 years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@himynameisaine I'm going on another J1 with my friends this summer and my boyfriend is staying at home, but I think a J1 is doable because]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just read Springsteen's eulogy to Clarence Clemons and now I'm violently sobbing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course I'm not looking at pictures of Bruce Springsteen and Clarence Clemons playing together and subsequently crying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honestly few things make me laugh more than the lovely fags part of the Lent episode of Father Ted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bagofgems definitely people can be taught to an extent but some people just ~have~ the natural gift, but that's just my opinion!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardLooby But I won't end a good song with a brilliant finale like three minutes before it's meant to end]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardLooby One time a DJ cut off the entire second section of November Rain and I really could have murdered someone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OdhranMcL if that was my big breakout I'd never feel the need to wear makeup ever again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I absolutely have to get to the Joshua Tree tour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elma_forde He can detect any source of electricity within a 3 mile radius.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dad thought there was an electrical field on a spoon at the sink as he felt a strange pull, turns out the spoon was attached to my hair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bus drivers that push on through amber lights don't get enough praise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomasinamcg Thank you that gif is incredible ðŸ’–]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whenever I look in the mirror I just want to tear my face off my skin is that bad aw my god I hate myself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OrlaWbu Yes well I like this one now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OrlaWbu It happens the best of us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OrlaWbu The amount of Bunsen and burritos when you get back is almost criminal, but not quite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today I saw the dawn crack through dark clouds on a plane and I feel so complete and fulfilled]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lepriknope @tomasinamcg Thanks I was also a product of immaculate conception]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lepriknope @tomasinamcg I am always correct and it is perfectly normal to love one's own twitter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OrlaWbu Good Lord. One time I had to ring an improv comedy club in Boston to reserve tickets and I nearly had an aneurysm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OrlaWbu mid-life probably for the typical person, for me probably never]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I ate all my chicken first and now there's just a mountain of mashed turnip on my plate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mine was Richie Kavanagh - Aon Focal Eile hahahaha oh my god https://t.co/C3lBeWJV4Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OrlaWbu Class I'll have the kettle on x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OrlaWbu Same. I'm not that far away, feel free to come up https://t.co/d5oDMfr8zB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoutout to @AdrianConnolly1 for coping with me in general]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do you not feel like a total disappointment to your mother despite having a fairly good grip on your life? Asking for a friend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow I don't think I've ever felt so awful about my appearance in my life as I do right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OrlaWbu please feel free]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomasinamcg Bread loves you and thinks you are important]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomasinamcg spicy indirects left, right and centre my oh my]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomasinamcg Or tell you and your friends to kill themselves; or tell a lie and say goodbye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomasinamcg As I've said, it will never give you up and it will never let you down]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have to ring TWO BANKS tomorrow oh my god me nerves I can barely even ring my relatives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think the best thing that happened me in 2016 was learning how to play Bridge Over Troubled Water on the piano]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just hope he knows how to do his maths now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Controversial as it may be, I think that Ed Sheeran is incredibly overrated]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomasinamcg 98% love 2% extreme, unrelenting hatred]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomasinamcg And throw me under the bus at times, but sure that's what we do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomasinamcg I appreciate your enthusiasm and encouragement nonetheless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every part of me says go ahead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lepriknope Do! But I'm not back until the 23rd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lepriknope @tomasinamcg mainly because I was cooped up like a chicken before exams and I was in Laois on NYE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomasinamcg anytime love ðŸ’– Hope to see you soon by the way @lepriknope]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomasinamcg @lepriknope no seriously you have both looked much more drunk ðŸ˜‚ it's a lovely photo ðŸ’œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomasinamcg @lepriknope ye don't really it's fine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomasinamcg full of great ideas aren't I sure x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomasinamcg wow going back to college will be fun for you (side note: they are delicious)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomasinamcg quit like what are we like at all at all ðŸ’ðŸ‘­ðŸ¦‹]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My family are already talking about the 'great stretch in the evenings' RIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This morning I sneezed and a load of phlegm came out of my mouth, what a start to 2017 x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomasinamcg pray to St Anthony to see if he can help you find it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomasinamcg oh yes absolutely 110% x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomasinamcg Yeah thought that xo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomasinamcg I know it'll be after Christmas when I get back but can we make mulled wine anyway please I feel like I missed out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomasinamcg that literally only came to me now I love literature and especially Yeats (did you even know that?)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomasinamcg sure what's life without an odd/regular sesh eh? (My life before exams but all is changed, changed utterly)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jack_Corr_ Today I've travelled 1.23km, I'm in the shape of my life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I adore the Fitbit that mam and dad got me for Christmas but it does make me feel bad about being a lazy cow after Christmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomasinamcg spread the word x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomasinamcg That picture summarises my entire being and existence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomasinamcg well at least my self-love outweighs your hatred x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomasinamcg think of aaaaaaall your Facebook friends that are going to see this majesty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomasinamcg fuck sake why do I say things. It matters not that you know. The humour still stands.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomasinamcg shall I say a certain theme runs through the collage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_AltGrEimear know what you're at, you realise that everyone is (or should be) paying attention to themselves! ðŸ’ªðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_AltGrEimear definitely do! At times in the UCD gym I've been the only girl there and at times it's still a bit petrifying, but once you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_AltGrEimear that it really helped, and it wasn't nearly as intimidating after that â˜ºï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_AltGrEimear the first time I went, I went with someone I knew who knew what to do and what was going on and where everything was! I found]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bruce Springsteen is still ridiculously hot holy sheeeeit]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>