<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh like you're so hot, RehabJunkys staff writer https://t.co/d6HBAAMxRN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh my god my friend's flatmates found a dead puffer fish and put lip gloss on it https://t.co/w9bRbxlQBq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look at the camera you small idiot https://t.co/dUPJiFEKvA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perth's a bit of alright aye https://t.co/4YYdNxhZEx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@giaisonline it was also awful when I lived in hataitai and walked through super hung over on my way to work one weekend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@giaisonline yeah it's actually a bylaw and I'll have to report you to the mayor for breaking it sorry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one sings my feelings so accurately or passionately as lyrical genius @AngelOlsen such a treasure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just saw two little boys wearing trilby hats. Is it wrong to hate a child over a hat?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FranPaulKennedy yeah but he's an actual Nazi. Punch him in the face heaps I don't care his world view gets people killed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_hi_tide @__catpower "nice drink. Shame if someone were to.... LAP AT IT"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IMO Jim Jarmusch can get bent. Paterson sucks butt don't waste your time and money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@__catpower heehee I love Apple and his silly little face]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah yes, having to work at 100 years old, very inspiring, heart = warmed!!! https://t.co/FpM6YIGo5A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColeyTangerina hahaha omg had this made it's way to Twitter?! I hear about it a lot when doing weather stories]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me worrying about my weirdly square butt: is my butt weirdly square?

My friend: I mean my first thought was boxy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nimbiwit yup, newsroom just called]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nimbiwit lol it was in in a shop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know you're hung over and need a nap when listening to Get Up, Stand Up leaves you feeling extremely emotional]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding this portrait my friend Bec did two years ago is the highlight of my trip so far https://t.co/rJOsj9DJS8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mum keeping us up to date in the family group chat https://t.co/ytPIwrW2vd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tnichss kind of amazing being a journo in NZ and comparing our stuff with Murdoch press over here. Immediately noticeably different]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy shit the Herald Sun is.... next level awful https://t.co/tz1bsdd1Pw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually, I love it https://t.co/LOBZaTAgUf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndreAlessi no she was talking about practising tattooing on them. They are very hard core they smoke a lot of weed you know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tnichss oh they're on a tinder date. I hate both of them I hope they get together]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insufferable couple sitting near me at bar. how insufferable? This is how one of them just described bananas: "they're fleshy as fuck, dude"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently my Melbourne friend's step mum thinks tattoos are a national tragedy. Yes, that's Australia's national tragedy for sure...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Definitely one of the more obscure brand cross-overs I've ever seen https://t.co/N5OdgbEKe6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A hash brown at the Auckland airport Maccas costs $2.40. I'm furious. Outraged.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jess_McAllen hahaha, me as a parent. "My incredibly handsome pilot son who got all excellence for his ncea level 2 english exams...."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good snapchat from the brother. Relevant @Tim_Batt  @guy_mont https://t.co/MhPlDzaG4u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the best responses I've ever heard  IRL was when i asked a woman i know if she'd met Noel Fielding
her: "darling I've slept with him"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@__catpower omg blue powerade. I have now thrown up twice in the garden
 Why am I like this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me last night: beer before wine you'll feel fine amirite guys?!

Also me last night: spewed three times out my window]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[asking comms person for an expert to talk to for a story, her: "couldn't you just google it"

lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jess_McAllen I routinely say lol in emails to people i want to help me in a professional manner. IMO it's actually fine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NeilReidnz too right Neil!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am reminded of that @thomas_violence  graphic about mistaking your interpersonal problems for social justice issues almost daily]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophiealiceryan omg! did they tell you to fuck off? lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nimbiwit sounds so superior! You've been saved from yourself IMO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Six months ago I messaged someone to see if they knew anything about a story i was chasing. Today, they accepted my… https://t.co/3kMKD0yViz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nimbiwit you are a sick individual]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nimbiwit please delete your account again immedaitely]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It becomes more annoying when you're talking to people about where they've been travelling to" https://t.co/Bv0Iy5nkOp via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jess_McAllen must be my youthful spirit! Na it's probably cause I got into journalism after you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tnichss sorry to be that guy. But]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know Trump is terrifying but this whole "Obama is the nation's dad, don't leave us dad" thing... remember he did actually bomb the mideast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How I feel when I tell people I'm "just going to add some fresh herbs and chilli from the garden" to a dish https://t.co/mH7gfIctoz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jess_McAllen how old are you jess? I thought you were early 20s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The booze for @commoben 's wedding has arrived https://t.co/dfVcsTHCfY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[aw, lovely answer https://t.co/wosQkum9en]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sashaborissenko tbh more outraged about EXTORTIONATE wine prices. i did a sneaky BYO refill in the toilets, v traditionale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pop Up Globe is defending all male casts by saying it's tradition-yeah well I bet in Shakey's day they didn't charge $12!!!!! for a sav, so]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kirsty_johnston @Warney investigations power couple]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[mum just told me i texted her at the time saying this was the best day of my life: https://t.co/qBrKBMXe3z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool story! I wonder what the comments are sa- oh. Like how did it even get to this? Tiring. https://t.co/BvCt4OosLS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@someofmybest this is your boyfriend at your 21st https://t.co/QTgwqpmgiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mjnickless removing the red devil aka the blasphemous cherry ripe. the heathen's time has come]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mjnickless pretty sure mine would be gross to tbh. Many crumbs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mjnickless "under our desks was gross" cracks me up so much]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then your back for two seconds and all of a sudden Trump loves golden showers. Dang gotta stay more vigilant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[loving these tweets about the latest rattle #eqnz https://t.co/o3Wo8mc6XQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaliaShadwell told some old codgers in sport how much it had upset me and got told to toughen up lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaliaShadwell on mine I accidentally misquoted a man, had him ring me up very angry after I'd clocked off &amp; spent the whole evening crying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ravenous_wolves tbf she was a personal finance journalist for ten years. But wtf I can't save more than like $200 a week even under urgency]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ravenous_wolves also i think the point was just to see if she could. Boring]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_hi_tide yes @michaelsergel if only people would just have free ones from the machine aye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_hi_tide I'm also salty having failed to meet my savings goal by a cool $1500 with one week to go before I'm on leave so there's that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ravenous_wolves dahling I'd rather DIE than give up my daily flat white]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tnichss like she said she had a great time and learned a lot, but]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ok so this woman saved more than $38,000 in a year doing this, but what was the true cost? https://t.co/BM3ZxuKnA2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this is ya mcm's qualification https://t.co/OVKVdfHLAS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerful Women We Refuse To Critique In Any Meaningful Way So We’ll Just Call Them All Badasses https://t.co/rbN7u27U1z via @reductress]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I say to Bill English don't be a spoilt child and run away, come to Waitangi." https://t.co/LmXsauwN00 via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ravenous_wolves @mjnickless lol same. You just said PolSci degree, didn't say if I had to have done well in it. hear my C Grade opinions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SusanStrongman In Mexico. She said instead 'my fat legs are rubbing together and it hurts" and apparently the pharmacist understood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SusanStrongman I wanted to send it to my sis when she said she didn't know the word for chafing in Spanish but was getting it real bad....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SusanStrongman OMG WHERE IS THAT. @jam8391 tweeted something with it recently I'm sure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SusanStrongman wait what were you hoping to find?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lukeappleby "great article.... NOT! Actually didn't read it"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fin, yes, I will click on this https://t.co/yWGGJcmpSX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mlle_elle @guardianstyle thanks! Have gone with Guardian-approved vernacular although singular plural makes them sound more distinguished]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hey @mlle_elle is the plural for emoji 'emojis' or is it a singular plural like sheep?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSpinoffTV smh why aren't the MSM reporting this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it possible to be subtweeted by a @nzlistener cartoon? https://t.co/TSbKGd7kC6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually kinda agree with this family first position on paying parents to stay at home and it's making me feel weird in my soul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Left on Kim Kardashian's insta. God loves a trier https://t.co/RgVqgz6Kli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AotearoIan frankly it's the least i deserve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tnichss cc: @FirecommNZ fanx for the tippp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unexpected passenger hitches a ride in pilot's monsoon bucket while fighting fire in Far North https://t.co/7ypklgBJ5c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mjnickless US baking "recipes" online r fucked. Rich chocolate cake recipe:"Ingredients: one egg, aunt betty's cake mix" Bone app the teeth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fancylettuce sucks when your burn gets somewhat negated by auto correct. Happens to the best of us Fiona DW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_hi_tide fucking Harold and his shit yarns I swear to god]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[left on the Herald's FB page. No one tell our much-loved reporter Harold I guess https://t.co/QwwyaUsWN1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mjnickless of what it's like to be a parent!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mjnickless totally. I would always get upset when my brother was little when kids his age died or got badly hurt. Imagine that's a fraction]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mjnickless I have stories like that too. I still think about those kids who all died but one when a slip fell on them as they were swimming]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well I guess I'll take his word for it then https://t.co/bhX6B0KRAd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it's always heartbreaking to read about people grieving for their loved ones, this one is especially moving I think https://t.co/FYx4NWMxuc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColeyTangerina what would they know anyway]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>