<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Alex_Panetta Well to be sure -there are a few other major things going on !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[POTUS tells CEOs he wants lower drug prices and pledges to speed up drug approval times. https://t.co/OpCpmptes2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Roosevelt Room, pharma execs await POTUS. https://t.co/uIs9DxmP8d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going home now. Do I have to watch out for the bobcat? I lost track w all the other news.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump fires top lawyer who defied immigration order with @JuliaEAinsley  https://t.co/a1twZTwx9x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our final story tonight on chaos, anger after POTUS halted entry for immigrants from seven countries, refugees https://t.co/vutwTSjItF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's our final take for tonight on the Trump refugee order, by @robertarampton and @ewstephe and @micarosenberg   https://t.co/FTWMCzxL6e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump administration seems to have the hang of the Friday night news drop right from the get-go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justinsink @AndrewBeatty are there pints there? Because could use one or five.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What British PM May will see when she comes to the WH today. https://t.co/yxUqT8dN9t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gird yourself for a flood of tweets about POTUS first Marine One ride https://t.co/kmvgbuUSP7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[POTUS is about to speak to DHS employees. He signed two executive orders related to border security / public securi… https://t.co/1RGPeNMT4f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auto CEOs here to meet @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/znq509oVyP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drphyllis Marillyn Hewson, CEO of Lockheed Martin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshledermanAP you are sweet. I will miss our travels. You are the only reporter I know that could do this 👇and st… https://t.co/JKIJG00xft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of the CEOs - Underarmor. Whirlpool. International Paper. Dow Chemical.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business leaders gather to meet with @realDonaldTrump in Roosevelt Room. https://t.co/YBQfJbqg6B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewBeatty Sort of surprised you haven't provoked that kind of  reax before tbh 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On his first full day as president, Trump heads to CIA after feud about Russia hacking https://t.co/vPsMvdtPm3 w/ @jeffmason1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judiciary Square station - long line waiting to go up escalator. https://t.co/GFpX8g15Eg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fri: my Metro stop full of people going to the Mall to cheer Trump. Today: packed with people going to protest him. https://t.co/q7ZNrYGLIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now Commander-in-Chief, Trump salutes at the end of the waltz. https://t.co/Iux9lQhNyg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@apodkul ha yes there are more than two. I see eight from my perch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is talking to troops in Afghanistan at this ball. https://t.co/pDkr3EwJPD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I like the fact that you all voted for me," Trump tells the military ball. https://t.co/DNMdFbzQJB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The presidential seal was just affixed to this podium. These remarks to the military ball may be longer? https://t.co/0ccYd2J1Jg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These are the largest Corinthian columns in the world apparently. https://t.co/2Ia8PUTlzh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I do have a little bit of vertigo up here though. https://t.co/uHu1sQfTW9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The National Building Museum is one of the nicest buildings in DC https://t.co/canx0qmbU5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two balls down. One to go. https://t.co/atTAOp0iSf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Folks were packed in to get a glimpse of POTUS. https://t.co/a9s745n3UR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's hard to show how cavernous this room is. https://t.co/CMIdeghPKY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Purple Rain ahead of POTUS appearance at the first ball. https://t.co/U1gX8wbWMs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loud cheers at My Way. https://t.co/FczLuQ9mVR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[POTUS chief of staff Looking for his spot. https://t.co/yVBi0vjyUs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also never seen so many people giving the presidential motorcade the finger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This may be the longest motorcade I've ever been in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm off to the balls with @APkfreking and the @realDonaldTrump pool. https://t.co/WqFIYK2sby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These folks are within earshot of St John's Episcopal where the Trumps are attending church. https://t.co/on0z1cmBVd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not what you usually see at Farragut North. https://t.co/ytrGSqTaiO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["He's here for the working man." -Adam Coletti, Plainfield, CT 'Renegade Pig' heading down to @realDonaldTrump inauguration on metro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["He's taking away from his lavish lifestyle to straighten out the country." -Sal Didato, E. Haddam, CT, 'Renegade Pig' before inauguration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adam knew he had to come to DC today the moment he heard Trump won. "You have a man who's tired of the same old political scheme."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sean Ruane, Adam Coletti, Sal Didato of the Renegade Pigs - a law enforcement biker club - taking the metro down fo… https://t.co/JfD1GKkQX6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retweeting to say thanks to wranglers and advance folks retiring today who saved us from giant ice sculptures and o… https://t.co/HJQvT62m89]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justinsink at least I know I'm free @ayesharascoe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. The power and the futility of a letter. https://t.co/O0o9ZclG20]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But former Canadian PM (and Reagan pal) Mulroney was not exactly on the Trump train during the campaign --&gt;  https://t.co/b938NJaB2X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting: Canada enlists former PM Mulroney for upcoming NAFTA fight with Trump administration https://t.co/P7rm7vt8IQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What I've learned about golf on the WH beat has surpassed my wildest dreams -&gt; "In 100 pages, Golf Digest examines the new Golfer-in-Chief."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["She was cute, she was likeable, but she wasn't professional enough"   https://t.co/CfcGA6Pxf9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peak Bo and Sunny just now in the briefing - or maybe peak @PressSec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justinsink he looks like I felt the whole time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justinsink is there someone aggressively patting visitors down on their way in and out of the booth?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lawrencehurley they serve beer so it might be ok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[POTUS walking across the street to Blair House. https://t.co/zaa72JqgUF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@akcdn I might have to go back and buy it on Boxing Day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's actually a pretty good antidote to all the music I heard while shopping today. https://t.co/xhIshKCWa5 via @youtube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@claire_mcnear Yes Stan is terrific! I hope you remembered to put a copy of 🔽 in @justinsink stocking. https://t.co/AQdCwEhoSl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justinsink I should have done a Facebook live right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OH in line to pay: a detailed explanation of why "I'm not big on pickles or mustard."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lawrencehurley There are a few copies if you want to put one under your tree.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may be getting a little off track here. https://t.co/9wycRZYfBX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dec 24 panic xmas shopping would be ok if people were silent as they did it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Presented without comment. / Peak Canadiana: Alberta man takes Zamboni through Tim Hortons drive-thru https://t.co/CWmC3ugfJt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshledermanAP So happy for you, but it's bittersweet. Wire One won't be the same without you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OKnox @justinsink @AndrewBeatty @StCollinson Will it be [INAUDIBLE] ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justinsink will the next AF1 be big enough to accommodate a certain massive blue duffel bag? Cc @agreilingkeane… https://t.co/5TQFrPjVlH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Via @georgecondon a short history about the long tradition of presidents chafing at press following them everywhere https://t.co/m2IEze7Tn2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justinsink hey don't stereotype]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justinsink @joshledermanAP @ToluseO I've noticed that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are a dedicated journalist to watch this briefing from NY. Or https://t.co/BUl1rEBQmw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Word of the week: metrics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swheaton I think there would have been an insurrection.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I decided not to ask my follow-up on CMS. You're welcome. https://t.co/eAWDwVPzQK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump unveils his team to overhaul health care via @steveholland1  https://t.co/H4LMpBBeQh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump picks Obamacare critic @RepTomPrice and Indiana's Seema Verma as his health 'dream team' https://t.co/N4kVVqtCtq via @steveholland1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump to pick Seema Verma for CMS - a role central to his pledge to overhaul health care via @steveholland1  https://t.co/mrHvu0pMZb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PEOTUS was wearing a red MAGA style ball cap emblazoned with USA   and 45, my photog colleague @joeskipper reports.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dozens of buzzards fly over Mar-a-Lago as we wait in the motorcade for PEOTUS to come out for return to NYC. https://t.co/AHOUTGYrBY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiting for PEOTUS https://t.co/pTtvkrjJp3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today, Trump adviser @KellyannePolls - Cuba policy has not been decided. CoS @Reince - some movement" needed fr Cuba https://t.co/2TaXzxsAAm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even on Thanksgiving, I updated this story.  https://t.co/CrCWeVsnPn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was working hard, even on Thanksgiving, to write this story. https://t.co/CrCWeVsnPn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the pies:
Banana Cream Pie, Coconut Cream Pie, Pumpkin Pie, Apple Pie, Pecan Pie, Cherry Pie /3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also on the Obama menu today: turkey, ham, prime rib, chicken wings; cornbread stuffing w/ chorizo, and oyster stuffing. Mac and cheese. /2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From First Family's last Thanksgiving menu in the White House: chicken satay with peanut chili dip, mini crab cakes, pigs in the blanket /1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's the best way to spend Thanksgiving! https://t.co/ryHLfQkqqE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh just down the road from Mar-a-Lago. https://t.co/QJPG77bzqp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am just all torn up to miss the turkey thing and Xmas tree delivery. https://t.co/ZAM025Kt4J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President-elect Trump lands in Florida to spend Thanksgiving at Mar-a-lago. #transition https://t.co/0iltJWSk7X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see @ChrisClaytonDTN agsplainin' the election on MTPDaily today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off to Kissimmee Fla. Just can't get enough Fla. https://t.co/1DApqoL87w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama speaks up for Trump protester, but Trump has a different version of what happened https://t.co/2jLgfaUJNq with @ewstephe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Blurred lines' playing before POTUS to speak. errr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiting for POTUS in Charlotte. https://t.co/gbSNUhqFjU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[POTUS and Roy Cooper, Democratic candidate for NC governor, in Charlotte NC en route Clinton rally. https://t.co/1HWX0aM9pe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This swing really does have the "farewell tour" feeling. https://t.co/FMTkB77aIF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama told crowd to "settle down!" when they booed this Trump fan. "We live in a country that respects free speech!" https://t.co/40TGkJaOC5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It might be a Clinton rally - but it feels like one for Obama. https://t.co/S2AI1m3TkG]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>