<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for the warning but I find it very hard to slip on wet carpet. Also, this carpet isn't… https://t.co/iAgvipdHLv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I ran out of hands when doing tonight's kitchen run so I holstered my Santoku in my Baggizmo… https://t.co/1rtjgLQvLj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pub platters! Sausage roll slices, hard and gooey cheeses, pickles and chutney, asparagus,… https://t.co/FPd6Rb9N4i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This walls here are covered with strange and interesting artefacts #foodinightsafari @ Mamasan… https://t.co/p1M5E9Rvcl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Astroboy wielding his mighty hammer-lamp. On his hip is a pistol he acquired during a Dirty… https://t.co/XRUjYAAFEa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now we're talking! Fried fish with edamame, and pork and duck dumplings #foodinightsafari @… https://t.co/Q7ezEG2HIx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So many flavours! Pro Tip: match the colour of the dot in the middle of the cupcake with the… https://t.co/zCSwl6qAfM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This company juices just about anything with cold presses in Melbourne and ship them in to the… https://t.co/32leG9jA0C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First stop was in a chocolate shop for some raspberry chocolate bon-bons #foodinightsafari @… https://t.co/MO7HfUFREX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First draft of things for me to work on in 2017. https://t.co/wtcQOqklhW https://t.co/kzpLzpxgj8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After everyone has left for the weekend, that narrow window of legitimacy between fridge raiding… https://t.co/VNkGIgRLBK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret to converting an American burger into an Australian one is turning it upside-down @… https://t.co/31N9MuKXWD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch you don't step on the flamingoes, they're sharp! @ The Royal Botanic Garden, Sydney https://t.co/SD5ulM693m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bee tasting the blue @ The Royal Botanic Garden, Sydney https://t.co/1sKJ5hXfNC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunburned flowers @ The Royal Botanic Garden, Sydney https://t.co/0Rv2tM6Hl2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loud and proud @ The Royal Botanic Garden, Sydney https://t.co/vzq0lj0uzB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool new addition to the gardens: a wildflower meadow! @ The Royal Botanic Garden, Sydney https://t.co/BiJLLpH02x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Make a garden of every sorrow you will never outgrow" https://t.co/BmU3JTGDeU… https://t.co/dxYS3sCzem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This bakery is so modern that it hires local marsupials to harvest the wheat to make their… https://t.co/Y4HTPKjlUy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoying a zucchini-carrot-chickpea frittata and an ice cold beer for lunch with my gaming buddy https://t.co/aJtjsaln5K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight's dinner: Shepard's pie! https://t.co/zGp5vj4WA4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This image showed up on my Chromecast background today https://t.co/OK8jvbfWYQ https://t.co/Z4MrQtm27c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Magic cards in the bathroom: that's hard core! #magicthegathering @ The Games Den https://t.co/Ymdbkiaelo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OK, which of you time travellers didn't watch their step? @ Central railway station, Sydney https://t.co/5brljmPQn7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vera Rubin, perhaps the greatest astrophysicist of the 20th century, passed away on… https://t.co/2p5qFU7psl https://t.co/mXfVRKdL5Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Sometimes you have to go backwards to move forwards...always". 

That's the corny last line of… https://t.co/Qn459H4ufF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stuffed lobster shell, roast potatoes, capsicum, salmon and butter beans #boxingday https://t.co/AqLqsJvlqj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm riding the Party Christmas Bus! #lightsforkids #boxingday https://t.co/0rEY92g7iN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas! #paella https://t.co/aFIq8pboz5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This probably violates some culinary law: Tasmanian salmon in Japanese BBQ marinade, stir fry… https://t.co/fjAglvtl1T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn those wascally wabbits! @ North Ryde, Macquarie Park https://t.co/BqBuJqJdqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lately I've been focusing more on career training than gym training but I'm not going to give up… https://t.co/pUvdfiFJ7W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bet cavemen had to run really fast to catch wild rolling meatballs for their #paleo dinner;… https://t.co/AcZhIcHAVU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[However the Panna Cotta cup is the truth. https://t.co/6JMO4lxK4g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Curious on what this greased-up 25-pin D connector near the corner of an old restaurant kitchen… https://t.co/Pch5b0tRDw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So last night I went to the kitchen to cook dinner. The lights were off so I went to switch them… https://t.co/gPW2u7wnib]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lemon-and-herb lamb loin chops with eggplant, garlic green beans and tortillas https://t.co/vNWV15CtvR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pigeon waiting at the bus stop with a prize twig to decorate its nest with #christmasshopping @… https://t.co/zxtA29yXQT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phew, looks like we missed that disaster. Thanks, socialists! @ The Goods Line https://t.co/OeQaEaRfBm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cool Thanksgiving story that has nothing to do with the President-elect https://t.co/oJPFiMjcLf https://t.co/IzFhLa5Wsd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like he partied too hard Friday night and passed out on the front lawn… https://t.co/QBzwCQ14sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["My what a big smile you have!" says the monkey to the crocodile #showercurtain https://t.co/bu4r4LlKfN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My crib may be tiny but I can still turn it into a man cave: behold my HD screen, stereo,… https://t.co/b6gXHiKMz2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After negotiations between Santa Claus and the Elf Union on pay and working conditions broke… https://t.co/eJgJOL7ZgJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I normally love a price reduction, but 3 cents?? Really, #aldi? https://t.co/8sO6HROZ1E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm curious about the event that caused this sign on a indoor metal stairwell to be necessary https://t.co/5mGy9ZfhTL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boy, that's one fancy-pants automated espresso machine you have there! https://t.co/DQcCaR4xAW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Footpath chicane @ North Ryde, Macquarie Park https://t.co/mbGqYJ5nKD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Room with a view https://t.co/jvPoj3JBOV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A friend has gifted me a couple of these bandages, so if I cut myself while cooking again at… https://t.co/4JKFIxTpWB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hurry up with our coffees, will ya? Woof! @ Brewristas https://t.co/lDgRsnwYAf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today I turned the magical crispy rice from the rice cooker earlier this week into awesome… https://t.co/HSeen7A3sd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After many previous attempts, this is the first time that the egg mixture became puffed and… https://t.co/8uEfPzoo4p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just discovered that the thumb fingerprint security on my phone is not compatible with kitchen… https://t.co/kkw6NJI55k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got a rice cooker, never had one before. Someone asked me why bother, what's wrong with… https://t.co/pwWnc4K3Di]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Translation: Anglo-Australian cuisine served at this establishment @ The Unicorn Hotel, Paddington https://t.co/5IQsXjlzZi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gelato in a cup is way too practical for my taste. The mess of having it melt over your hands is… https://t.co/JSxhHHnx4D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ladies and gentlemen, we have fire! https://t.co/WZwAA36KSP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HMAS Adelaide. The white writing on the hull says "BEWARE ROTOR WASH". Just an FYI in case you… https://t.co/598zBHqkqo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weak password? Are you SURE about that, #ubuntu? #diceware https://t.co/rRygpefioz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Odyssey challenge accepted! #Ingress #LuxAdventure https://t.co/X3dL7hCK2b https://t.co/kQ3fSjK18t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pay what you want and support the Electronic Frontier Foundation! https://t.co/eXbaIvlWUM via @humblebooks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Maps app lets me turn frequent destinations into shortcuts? How did I not know this already? https://t.co/li4npZPdXw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whatsapp deleted chats are recoverable with forensic tools https://t.co/NlTZF1O6T4 https://t.co/uYZrB74qzx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last year Mathias Karlsson discovered and responsibly reported a LastPass autofill exploit.… https://t.co/z9caWXENCo https://t.co/1SM5i7OvC6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fellow student took some photos of me during Xing Yi practice last week. https://t.co/sLioTOHH4G https://t.co/S0iJhqX5l6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Random password lists that are better for humans https://t.co/7U0QrbPjWr https://t.co/Cqu67cuNKQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EFF @josephbonneau Nice work! However I do need to report a bug: the EFF long list contains both "yoyo" and "yo-yo". Too similar!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A blow-by-blow of how in just over a week #brexit triggered a crash of the British pound, a… https://t.co/NTpZ7wWnnE https://t.co/jmjxi1DF1h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Urban Ops Casualty Carry: Our Finest Hour https://t.co/h7Rrn98PH6 https://t.co/If2v480iWa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have the dubious honour of being the 1st voter to admit to a ballot screw-up at my… https://t.co/AeNsH2b3zl https://t.co/D0IJMAh7OT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Relying on perimeter defences for network security is extremely risky https://t.co/94YXU9C4Fn https://t.co/JUHYPyrdth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I discovered that I could be smart and capable and valuable for something that had nothing… https://t.co/7ZLyJQYvIV https://t.co/NhNL7Mdidh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading up on what to expect for my Stealth Ops and Urban Ops challenges for Aegis Nova… https://t.co/3YneC3sS7E https://t.co/5cgAjzErqq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ruckgressing is always more fun with friends! #goruck #Ingress https://t.co/xaGH1ABCOR https://t.co/QDylULvEYM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A friend convinced me to sign up to WhatsApp for instant messaging. https://t.co/21eIQNUTRd https://t.co/9zAQw43x5Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've started preparing for the GORUCK Ingress challenges scheduled for June in Sydney by… https://t.co/IbKIMsobd6 https://t.co/LERoZk1u7j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TIL that brush turkeys don't dig up gardens for food but for sex! https://t.co/RGTbDgaOOM https://t.co/KSewYClsKK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A couple of months ago I started going to a gym with an exercise room, so I decided to use… https://t.co/A4ZGVG3g4R https://t.co/2MolnP1osX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[tl;dr - Google performed an extensive study of its highest performing teams, and found a… https://t.co/rqt6NaqERN https://t.co/M5N1JYrJuC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder how common such cooperation between random strangers will be in Pokemon Go, an… https://t.co/RkDwatrnsU https://t.co/gFpR9zCHFU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is why I don't engage in climate science arguments from climate change deniers. https://t.co/TlnHF91CxP https://t.co/7BvbSRsehS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aaron Diaz followed up his martial arts comparison post with one that explains the key… https://t.co/gFXT4d7xSe https://t.co/feUnzDSCjT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a surprisingly good comparison of various martial arts styles, and advice on… https://t.co/Sq9Xtd6SfC https://t.co/h7Qry13vyB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been going through a mid-life adjustment since the beginning of the year. https://t.co/YUZ2EIV92M https://t.co/eLm5NTPZc2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Juicing" is popular with people who distrust modern processed foods and want a healthier… https://t.co/JvaBMjBZKM https://t.co/ZbUCxQVxWk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ingress Australia trivia https://t.co/vPjrty1kN7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TIL from Wikipedia that funnel-web spider venom is highly toxic to primates but not very… https://t.co/xL0DJJV38B https://t.co/3XfwAJOWfO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JM77 not as bad as "looking at pictures of your ex". First time I got it it was wrong &amp; weird. The 2nd time was true and creepy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy 2016 from a rooftop in the Eastern suburbs of Sydney, Australia! Here's a crappy… https://t.co/prmi0uUQOX https://t.co/LnAQHvko9l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#StarWars #Spoiler Remember all the fuss from the first trailer about the lightsaber with… https://t.co/orsirqrY8Q https://t.co/Y2HAdsH5hh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If there are things you wish you had seen https://t.co/0yXedipon4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tiny beautiful creature, which like many tiny beautiful creatures in Australia, is also… https://t.co/puUd2El2sz https://t.co/JDs0FG7bV0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last week my instructor Sean Kavanagh of Bagua Academy International graded me on my level… https://t.co/94fyXa3kJL https://t.co/AolMLkK05o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Notes recently discovered from the maths genius Ramanujan show that he was even more of a… https://t.co/J0hPs0iTJ8 https://t.co/dZv7Tr2iB5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the Tapeworm's Journal of Medicine: https://t.co/2NejWJw8Qz https://t.co/0px0FJGYpK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We had a fantastic day in Canberra with a total of 161 agents completing the required… https://t.co/QddCOEdz0n https://t.co/fu7ExaVRkT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Added photos to Mission Day Canberra, Australia. https://t.co/vZxhCtT4d0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Ingress #MissionDay #Canberra begins! https://t.co/L5S8coNXUJ http://t.co/SqTcncHiTS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ignorance is assuming that Frankenstein was the monster. https://t.co/F1cOjO3cb2 http://t.co/8p58k8SY0g]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>