<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Successful Content Marketing In 8 Steps - Brand Quarterly https://t.co/3MRzhH66rl https://t.co/cKgcwKNKxr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What AI is revealing about the sales process https://t.co/yQ9zNrj2T5 https://t.co/EhOi74gA3r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 Pivots B2B Marketing Strategies Need to Create Compelling Experiences https://t.co/kDEVaHihsP https://t.co/rpA5ThrNjN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8 Must-Read Employee Engagement Articles - The HR Gazette https://t.co/1VHO4vFHUW https://t.co/GL84mQStyD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Marketing Tactics to Stop Doing This Year - Tim Brown https://t.co/Z2MAevFzsv https://t.co/R0xAncvQXs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Center-Brain Marketing: Preparing For A Future Of Cognitive Technology https://t.co/kcbcDm2Xyz https://t.co/XTnyw7pW30]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snapchat Marketing Strategy 101: Getting Started, Building a Community, and Generating ROI https://t.co/kSGFO9ERjL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing with Strategic Empathy — Author Interview with Claire Brooks – Actionable Books https://t.co/6WaOJvtGc4 https://t.co/6qxsAoOq0V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go From Average Joe to Pro With These 5 Marketing Analytics Power Moves https://t.co/hLvSdCpHYc https://t.co/pbmHHkZscX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 9 Management Myths That Leadership Needs To Nix https://t.co/wEeOItnaak https://t.co/u8rDcNonGG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creating employee experience - 10 HR trends for 2017 (I) - Graphic Online | Ghana News https://t.co/HCzgQgRR6i https://t.co/pb8G1tkVqA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Building Marketing Campaigns with Buyer Personas Content Marketing https://t.co/KeHjeVY7Yu https://t.co/eAW5DhZQ4Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The One Page Business Strategy: Streamline Your Business Plan in Four Simple Steps - - https://t.co/Dcyho8tSSV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A brief history of a marketing masterpiece: branding the anti-abortion movement “pro-life” https://t.co/bmyeQKhwn2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What’s Next for Digital B2B Marketing - Edelman https://t.co/2pD9DnIE10 https://t.co/dMbaWaOq21]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does Your Business Plan Need An NDA? - https://t.co/5U8izrSNPm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[63% Of Employees Don't Trust Their Leader -- Here's What You Can Do To Change That https://t.co/tYbY964cuf https://t.co/QHHsZH5yOt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What I learned from a purple cow – Actionable Books https://t.co/sLXCih97x9 https://t.co/yDf6bl3Cwd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Management of Meanings: When the Gears Don’t Align - https://t.co/6Qniaz1LVG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boomerang Employees: an Untapped Talent Source? https://t.co/yA7ejWfs5O https://t.co/zIpEDxQIAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Email Marketing Important For e https://t.co/66MG5fFRwU https://t.co/Bw2qrDz1Ek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does Your Organization Think Strategically? - https://t.co/r3EeEXT0v5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why You Need Advanced E-mail Marketing in 2017 https://t.co/AfIX4c4dzx https://t.co/G84utx9oru]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9 Examples of Live Action Marketing https://t.co/p34ovU2ezP https://t.co/3Wc0ksA8xg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 Reasons Employee Engagement Is Declining -- And How Managers Can Improve It https://t.co/M1bkgx2B93 https://t.co/R8lQuYSPWm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Executives and Salespeople Are Misaligned — and the Effects Are Costly - https://t.co/MRaYOjxC3O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 4 Stages of B2B Marketing Performance Management Maturity https://t.co/CpXYZ26LlE https://t.co/wt995CtA0E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Solutions That Can Boost Employee Happiness https://t.co/DjYOhpeqSD https://t.co/xaiQMGYObn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creating Connection, Community and Compassion at Work – Actionable Books https://t.co/i7zurQYWpW https://t.co/guSz1D27gk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rethinking Buyer Personas In An Era Of Digital Transformation - https://t.co/dSHQk83tpQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMNICHANNEL STRATEGY BUNDLE: Your guide to engaging with shoppers on multiple channels - https://t.co/W7uYzVx1xD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Do Brands Want to Waste Time Building Marketing Software? https://t.co/mnKC4TLXl4 https://t.co/YbCEYkXYk1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Move Your Digital Marketing Forward with These 3 Steps https://t.co/gORNgyzhgH https://t.co/exC8184n2c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ROI of Better Conversations https://t.co/rUZ412C1ht #actionable https://t.co/ou1FUDv9oq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advice For New Leaders Infographic — Ask the Experts | Actionable Consultants https://t.co/6mwfMabKJf https://t.co/jte2wnJULL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The story on Learning Management System https://t.co/n2afhkX73g https://t.co/YKzNqJ8nSE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8 Tips for Aligning Sales and Service - https://t.co/HD0S8c0iwL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why bank brands are taking a more purposeful marketing approach https://t.co/9vjjD58JE4 https://t.co/en59ard7Mh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How busy organizations get results. https://t.co/zG3YLjYaGN by @PrioritySolutio on @LinkedIn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're the Boss Now. Here Are 10 Things You Should Do - https://t.co/RI1Qb6LWkW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Use Visual Content In Marketing Your B2B Startup https://t.co/YP5o9gqSbJ https://t.co/E0uh1KDqVi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video Marketing or How to Make Your Video Make Business Sense https://t.co/iClprkqqDZ https://t.co/iBbZ9ZF2J8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stephane Kasriel, machine marketing, and the future of work – VB Engage https://t.co/3hN4sREJEs https://t.co/NXLkujQgxP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is There Still A Bias Against Female Leaders? - https://t.co/D3vPzNJrCN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advice For New Leaders Infographic — Ask the Experts | Actionable Consultants https://t.co/6fhY3O4Aok https://t.co/tbJYrxKoIz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding My Tribe—Why It’s Ok To Get Personal At Work https://t.co/SIoUU9j9h1 https://t.co/5xD7qOTB4Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Hey $FNAME” is Dead. Here’s How to Personalize Marketing in 2017 https://t.co/37cNOY8FAK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Performance Principle — Author Interview with Mackenzie Kyle – Actionable Books https://t.co/jcuefuivBO https://t.co/h6H63Qa81l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 EMM predictions for 2017 - https://t.co/gOQDNE6KBb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Differences Between Enterprise and Consumer UX Design :: UXmatters - https://t.co/Ca1QyvJIeJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will Marketing Survive the Future? https://t.co/uaCDatJYkp https://t.co/DLGVokO0xm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Week in Content Marketing: The Battle for Custom Content https://t.co/etOUyRGQYP https://t.co/uaoWgRRzbu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can AI Make It Easier to Reach Real People? - B2B Marketing Academy https://t.co/ochrHZf8m5 https://t.co/rES0NvBigJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creating Connection, Community and Compassion at Work – Actionable Books https://t.co/tNhDcZObGs https://t.co/ksQodVyxko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beyond Books—Our Favorite Actionable Content – Actionable Books https://t.co/a3EilcjmyT https://t.co/AHF7cADYWi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 reasons social media is a much-needed marketing tool https://t.co/ACJzVf8PFe https://t.co/RbujkYKdgB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Power of Positive Sales Habits - https://t.co/TLOBHaA5Cl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Successfully Engage Employees in 2017 - TalentCulture https://t.co/LZItlKe18t https://t.co/6FPtS4LWwF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Secret to B2B Sales – Identifying Your Prospect’s Pain Points - https://t.co/cp1nGmqRb1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Four Simple Marketing Automation Tricks You Can Put to Use Right Away - GetResponse Blog https://t.co/qvFKjyHIJv https://t.co/qW02DTSk1m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why entertaining customers should be part of every business strategy https://t.co/FflPIzpVCt https://t.co/R0BXPH0wfX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introducing Facebook Ad Campaigns MailChimp Email Marketing Blog https://t.co/6mhb3WqUKN https://t.co/R7F8JzR11Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's the Number 1 Reason Employees Quit (It's Not What You Think) - https://t.co/cjXRBnEP1B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Employee Turnover Rate Is High for Young Workers https://t.co/j1QyvTphwU https://t.co/jHoBhqRGVF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Virtual Reality Could Change Content Marketing https://t.co/Uoj1Cs13Or https://t.co/tnHeS33ig8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Design thinking for HR: Why is it relevant? https://t.co/8V5QuN91cH https://t.co/gEYlTLiRt3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The “Big Bang’ Lead Generation System - https://t.co/e6h032BMCj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top Social Media Networking Sites Vital To Your Marketing Plan https://t.co/W7ymSfT4qZ https://t.co/5z4XSiFOWC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 pressing problems that AI marketing can solve https://t.co/GYj1lOwL7l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Content Marketing Is Critical in the Age of Visual Marketing https://t.co/nS6OBWsPwx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Constructing a Sales Compensation Plan That Works - https://t.co/xZMwDPTpX0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 Top Leadership Trends for HR Managers in 2017 https://t.co/egxY22kH3D https://t.co/OYu5tsnQEJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does 2017 hold for marketing technology? https://t.co/OsvSAA5VSK https://t.co/z8My303met]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are Your Employees Stressed? You Need to Embrace Transparency. https://t.co/G1IDQMuFAo https://t.co/RONUjtwpnw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Things Every Great Sales Manager Should Do to Turn Talented Salespeople into Performers - https://t.co/EB05jC7t8Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A B2B Guide to Content Marketing https://t.co/6Rkw1Z2eYb https://t.co/0IHPWarbct]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Types of Tech Hires You Need to Make Now - https://t.co/YfUlLb4H2t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11 Tools to Launch Your First Content Marketing Campaign https://t.co/6wi1hda6s9 https://t.co/sVCLId5g03]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[20 Pros Reveal What Makes a Perfect Twitter Marketing Strategy https://t.co/6u3xPpHRPe https://t.co/ISo7xXYWfY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 7 Deadly Sins of Manager-Employee Communication (and How to Avoid Them) https://t.co/BNlEBYG3Jc https://t.co/J0gZypedRC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pain-Free Performance Reviews? Possible. Here are 5 Tips for Getting There. https://t.co/1Sjj1nwOcP https://t.co/7IpLmUpQ1Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Type of Content Marketing Gets the Most Social Shares? https://t.co/RutOjDIgfC https://t.co/YakZj9tB82]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7½ Must-Consider Tips for B2B Publishers’ Ecommerce Business - https://t.co/9C8r8Nh8Jb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developing the Employer Value Proposition https://t.co/xF8oJ9YCH4 https://t.co/dOJSXH2ZkX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why CEOs must lead big data initiatives - TechRepublic - https://t.co/RwINxIujul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Boost Productivity &amp; Profitability with Digital Marketing Training https://t.co/j7Pe54c8Hr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take a Break From the Marketing Action to Think About Strategy https://t.co/lNCayO3aAg https://t.co/kcp6OCoi5I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Create a Content Marketing Strategy for the New Year https://t.co/ZS8aCJ8pVm https://t.co/DZfW9Z94Aa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want Better Relationships? Keep Promises and Make Clear Requests https://t.co/LRLJYGLnaA https://t.co/FOokCeD7UG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rise of the chief marketing technologist https://t.co/9ZPTjnpSyJ https://t.co/cY9ssk5J2x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Steps to Kickstart Your Account-Based Marketing Program https://t.co/Na9lTCEptG https://t.co/fkcDKC9veM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Featured Account-Based Marketing Tech Stack: BetterWorks Terminus https://t.co/V35LdM5Gzw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terminus Account-Based Marketing Names Todd McCormick as Chief Revenue Officer Terminus https://t.co/XvDFL3EyIF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Affordable Paid Search Engine Marketing SEO Freelancers https://t.co/xs1FQRlIMr https://t.co/oxfvtzkFoF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 3 Most Common Mistakes Businesses Make with Marketing Automation and How to Fix Them... https://t.co/hripygyZEF https://t.co/DiCYFsD2Nl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intel Invests in IoT Retail Platform for a Smart Shopping Experience CRM Daily https://t.co/qDkdfIx9Nz https://t.co/B8ejykbYW9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should You Caption Your Marketing Videos? 3 Reasons Why You Should Start https://t.co/GrKeFJ4QsT https://t.co/02Vf0v3bIF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hubcast 124: Lucky Orange, Video Marketing and HubSpot CRM Tutorials https://t.co/CzbGSoJ5w0 https://t.co/ngLXKll04I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Best Practices To Create Twitter Content Marketing Strategy for business https://t.co/gzV8S50cBx https://t.co/flA48B5X01]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leveraging Data Science for Deeper Marketing Decision-Making https://t.co/uvgujwB4ma https://t.co/PgyNhOK1fH]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>