<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@AklTransport it's so frustrating travelling West-South, via Newmarket, arriving trains need 2B here at the same time. Always miss by 30sec!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alison__wright's Martha from @TheAmericansFX is the character I want to see come back stronger and more powerful in S5 this year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewshubNZ sure thank you! https://t.co/vTgxGOU1np]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nkean Sure! Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Major incident southbound southern mway at Greenlane. Bus on fire multiple fire &amp; police units in attendance… https://t.co/eyyGE43zZg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another MP resigns from @NZNationalParty, with English at the helm, is the ship is sinking? @formerlydaniels https://t.co/inPVUnpqUP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AklTransport Every stop letting passengers off, "keep smiling and have a wonderful day!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AklTransport your driver of #NB4154 this morning (Route 223) was so awesome, greeting pax with a warm smile and cheerily sending them off!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TransportBlog @AklTransport @phil_goff Suggestion to catch people already parked in bus lanes up to 20min before t… https://t.co/7aRQh3rbUL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TransportBlog @AklTransport @phil_goff I hope this will mean longer duration of bus-lane/Clearway signs! I'm on th… https://t.co/dE6w10Dwsv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@henrycooke haha woo! Retroactive twitter 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZGreens what about banning companies like sanatarium from adding sugar to cereal? 40tsp/actual serving size is a joke!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woohoo! @jacindaardern you have our vote in #MtAlbert look forward to seeing you around again! @nzlabour @NewshubNZ https://t.co/r2A0vLj67E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@google can you please contact us and help us fix our address? Your automated service does not affect what we want corrected]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelwoodnz Congrats! Wld hav voted 4U if we lived in MtRoskill, are well-served by @DavidShearerMP in MtAlbert. Bring on @nzlabour 2017!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@google Centre" a building that was not only never at our location, but also no longer exists 2/2 "Havana House" #NZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@google why can I not correct the address of my google business? Your side link on google search says "located in Downtown Shopping
1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulHenryShow wouldn't a more common American pronunciation be "dah-da/dadda"? #tomaytotomahtoe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulHenryShow not that we're anti-Xmas, we have tons of decorations at work, &amp; aren't home each year for Xmas so feel it's unnecessary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What type of Christmas tree do you put up in your home? Where is the "None" option? https://t.co/vn2fbVfNLr @PaulHenryShow @thebumbleveee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpotifyCares Little problem, trying to sign up &amp; site says email already in use, so i try to log in but no account exists with that email?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thatonequeen I was literally just looking at this. Direct election beneficial ovr proportional representative, how r more votes worth less?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@appleinsider @verizon @vodafoneNZ have a range of open-term 4G plans at reasonable prices. Also Term Plans availab… https://t.co/9NeKovAPwj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@appleinsider @verizon welcome to the present day large data caps are a necessity! Had 5-15GB plans in NZ the last 3-years for smartphones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I definitely agree @Apple shld be seriously considering the advantages of killing #lightning in favour of #USBC
https://t.co/g5euKSvsky @BGR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best #Siri #WeatherFail @brentJstewart 😂😂😂😂 https://t.co/bKuUB4Ch9p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HengeDocks I know it’s early days, but wld u guys have a dock solution before end of year for the new 2016 MacBook Pro with Thunderbolt 3?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eslivka great tip, thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MacRumors @eslivka that's great, but would it not be just as 'spoiler-free' via the AppleTV Apple events app?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AklTransport is there any way short of leaving a note on this person's windscreen to let them know they're doing i… https://t.co/dz9mXQlZvh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just in case you were wondering, yes we are open today, however on public holiday hours 10AM-4PM… https://t.co/RRRJiPCFrh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CarrotCake #GayBaker #treats #cake #delicious https://t.co/4cynCwqwsW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#summer is on its way! Yay!!! https://t.co/TDZc4A4wkD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulHenryShow not to split hairs, but India is the largest democracy in the world with 1.25b or 17.5% global pop, not the United States 🤓]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BNZ ah fantastic! Was thinking a settings option to change these balances to show: closed bal, pending bal or available bal wld be awesome!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BargainBoxNZ the silver lining is though, as we have our fav recipes from prev weeks, we know what to shop for!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BargainBoxNZ cool, we're flying back &amp; wld miss delivery by hours, so will hv2 suspend for a week &amp; shop for ourselves! 😅#firstworldprob 🤓]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @BNZ, I've just noticed CC balances on the main screen now exclude pending txns, would you be able to say why the change?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @BargainBoxNZ! We're absolutely loving the service, (with since Aug), just wondering if you will have other delivery days in future?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FelicityHuffman I miss the show in its entirety! @EvaLongoria]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MacRumors @TheCW why not avail. outside the US? Distribution rights shld be owned by the network alone. Users want this all over the world!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulHenryShow I wld hardly call #MrsPeregrines suitable for 5yos, maybe 10+? It's an M rating! It's a fantastic film though! classic Burton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulHenryShow, you say trump has dainty/women's hands? Maybe it's really Hillary in a Trump suit debating with her… https://t.co/WYtfJvajc8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulHenryShow Try compuls voting with a no-vote option that cripples % of power gained to incentivise politicians to actually engage voters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frm Business to co-host @NewsNadine has been the brighter part of mornings 4 the last several years. @BreakfastonOne https://t.co/yKTsxm6o7D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So sad to see the @BreakfastonOne crew breaking up 😢 all the best @RawdonChristie https://t.co/enu4LC7w1y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wishing u the best @RawdonChristie for the future! Going to be sad to see u go, such a wonderful personality over the years @BreakfastonOne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@formerlydaniels I'm upgrading from a 5S (2013) so definitely worth the upgrade!! Tho wish there was a 64Gb option! (Will go 128Gb)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@formerlydaniels definitely agree! iP 7 is approx 2 hours better than 6S, &amp; iP 7+ is about 1 hour better than 6S+ https://t.co/8YVgHgC1q9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@formerlydaniels both iPhone 7 &amp; 7 plus come with a wired pair that connect by lighting connector, the AirBuds sold separately avail. in Oct]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@formerlydaniels Stacey! One lens of the iPhone 7 Plus is a telephoto lens, the other is the same wide angle as the iPhone 7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AklTransport here are your frustrated passengers waiting for the last 30min at Stop 8215 #Delays @TransportBlog https://t.co/wUxlKb7Dnk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AklTransport my next bet is the first bus to go past will have #BUSFULL emblazoned across the bow. 25mins waiting now #ServiceDelays]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AklTransport apparently the 8:36am service is due in 3min (currently 8:56am) #frustrated]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AklTransport no busses for last 20min at Stop 8215 and #TrackMyBus is down? #RealTime board keeps dropping services like flies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@9to5mac well that just added weight against me buying the #JetBlack #iPhone7 #iPhone7Plus #Apple #AppleEvent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RawdonChristie the AirPods are sold separately, you get given in the box the wired (Lighting connector) headphones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#iPhone7 #NZ #Prices confirmed #Apple #AppleEvent https://t.co/UWZSof2nHY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any serious fan of @MelanieCmusic MUST check out her music video to her latest single #Anymore!!! #Music #Premiere https://t.co/HAuv0GUxK2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely LOVING #Anymore! Such a smooth-beat track, @MelanieCmusic is back!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Magical #sunset over the #SouthernAlps #flying up from #christchurch to #Auckland tonight on… https://t.co/ne9IuvDmwL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to tucking into my #chocolabau creation! White #Chocolate, #Maltesers, Caramel… https://t.co/gEWx23uC54]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#RIP Peter Gossage, the Author of the Maui books I read as a child https://t.co/12Ka90uVI9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewsNadine people who buy alcohol for underage people need to be prosecuted as wld a duty manager/licensee wld be @NewstalkZB $10k fine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Classy #antipasto platter for our #wineandcheese night! https://t.co/4SMFZZz70A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CarrotCake v.2.0 must say is a darn fine 2nd attempt! proud of that yummy lookin' #CreamCheese #frosting! #cake https://t.co/7NzU8h0rjk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First one was a trial run for tonight's final! this is #CarrotCake v.2.0 which - I must say, a… https://t.co/QFgVu1rnNh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BreakfastonOne how about restricting immigration to ONLY those jobs NZ needs? Skilled migration would better help the issue @NewsNadine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brodiekane have a wonderful birthday trip! You're only 30 once so treat yourself! Hope nothing bugs you in Bali! @BreakfastonOne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Wartortle &amp; #Charmander spotted off #Devonport #Auckland #PokemonGO @PokeVisionGo @PokemonGoApp #CatchEmAll https://t.co/WMacHK4xN2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Pikachu is in #Devonport #Auckland #NZ for the next 10 mins! #PokemonGO @PokeVisionGo @PokemonGoApp #CatchEmAll https://t.co/vNEFRvFmLy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Porygon in #Newmarket #Auckland for the next 5mins! @PokeVisionGo @PokemonGoApp #PokemonGO https://t.co/QOQ2QbVCDQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just died.... All these within 10mins run from me!! 😱😱😱😱😱 I love this new #Pokéfilter! @PokeVisionGo @PokemonGoApp https://t.co/3InhB0dglO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First #CarrotCake out of the new #KitchenAid stand mixer! This is a trial run on a recipe I may… https://t.co/f6sV4OIJsh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Pokemon are out in force in #Auckland #NZ Get up &amp; #PokemonGO outside &amp; #CatchEmAll! @PokemonGoApp @PokeVisionGo https://t.co/OuQDTHymv3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Snorlax and a #Meowth having an evening out in #HerneBay #Auckland #PokemonGO @PokemonGoApp @PokeVisionGo https://t.co/SWHG24O8P7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It appears a #Blastoise is on #SaffronSt #Ilam #Christchurch for next 10mins! #PokemonGO @PokemonGoApp @PokeVisionGo https://t.co/WzcNZVxFK4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Wellington sure is pulling out all the poké-stops tonight! #PokemonGO #pokemon @PokemonGoApp @PokeVisionGo https://t.co/kUQ8TvskEW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a #Venusaur in #KelburnPark #Wellington! @PokemonGoApp @PokeVisionGo https://t.co/5Z1uD3GsY2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are many #PokemonGO #pokemon #specials out 2nite in #Auckland! #NewZealand @PokeVisionGo @PokemonGoApp https://t.co/6ttmur350b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TradeMe that was an awesome little #EasterEgg hunt! The last one (F1 Driver) was a goodie!! https://t.co/YcE2n9Pvqe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@trademe awesome little #EasterEgg hunt! The last one (F1 Driver) was a goodie!! https://t.co/JJLLfxbTRj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AklTransport What are these grey areas on the new fare map? theres small ones and big ones with no explanation? https://t.co/2ZKOqjrryZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My man knows my priorities! A sweet spot for and wonderful choice of #Lindt #Chocolate and… https://t.co/2uaO0Mq3pI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#OMG #yaaas #foodporn @alsdelinz #Mount for lunch today! @ Al's Deli O'Connell Street https://t.co/L1ZeCLnLs8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BreakfastonOne If #Russia cheated as a host of the #OlympicGames, their morals know no boundaries, #BanThemForLife @BrendanTelfer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New addition to the family! My #KitchenAid #Artisan in #EmpireRed! @kitchenaidausnz thanks to… https://t.co/jtqVe83iIV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ONENewsNZ @BreakfastonOne what is wrong with the app this morning? The stream is jumping all over from 7:02, 7:08, &amp; over to ad breaks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TV3nz @NewshubNZ why doesn't the channel stream the whole channel and TV3+1 with ads to an AppleTV app? Our aerial is OOO 4 next few wks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BreakfastonOne @ONENewsNZ why doesn't TVNZ stream the whole channel and TV1+1 with ads to an AppleTV app? Our aerial is OOO 4 next few wks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suzannepaulnz happy anniversary!! Wishing you both the best and Hope you have a wonderful weekend and many more years ahead! Xxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such a stark contrast to the day we moved into this #apartment. Such a #beautiful #Winter #Auckland day #VIEWS #nz https://t.co/9H05ohyDhf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Goodmorning #Auckland, #movingday is here! today is our last day with this #stunning #sunrise over #TVNZ &amp; #SkyCity https://t.co/RtqJhy2SJ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehitsnz can you help please, where is the link to the news mentioned at 5pm re: removal of #KiwiSaver restrictions for 1st-home buyers?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ASBBank thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ASBBank something wrong, app constantly cycling asking 2 #upgrade as current is unsupported, can't log in at all! 😢 https://t.co/Rol38TXqJv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CJ_NZ not talking about using the artwork anyway, the discussion is about a stereotypical island body type @NewsNadine @BreakfastonOne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CJ_NZ nothing scary about it when I was 3-7 years old! wld easily be possible for Disney to use this body type @NewsNadine @BreakfastonOne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewsNadine 4x of the Peter Gossage books about #Maui that were prevalent in NZ pre-schools/primary @BreakfastonOne https://t.co/oOqVmjgRqR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BreakfastonOne The Maui we grew up with in Kindy/Kohanga &amp; Primary School was a lithe, muscular man @NewsNadine https://t.co/T52OY6Bfqw]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>