<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Excuse me for one moment... https://t.co/bijMlLYaqG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was being optimistic when I was hoping for a 3 setter. Literally on struggle street right now tho!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tegal1234 enjoy watching the cricket tomorrow while everyone else (that's not in Auckland) is at work! Now you can stop having a moan ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tegal1234 Fed came all the way from Switzerland and Rafa came from Spain! Don't hear them complaining]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shit that picture is amazing ðŸ‘ŒðŸ¼ https://t.co/X6rRUZmn9b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tegal1234 you aren't watching the tennis?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really need to learn some golf insults ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/atXOgU6mMg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter who wins the tennis, Nike wins.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*runs to the ice bath*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JayHarvie I really don't know! How they don't question playing in that heat in general is strange. Doesn't straya have H&amp;S laws?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JayHarvie technically there should be drinks at 90 minutes yes? ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They should just leave the sprinklers on for the rest of the game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kyle_barnes15 I was literally thinking exactly the same thing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZPhotomac definitely needs a name change lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZPhotomac do you just have a folder on your computer labelled 'Jojo' filled worth pictures of Doyle? Cuz that would be hilarious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZPhotomac oh stop it (no please don't)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZPhotomac I just can't deal right now. My god he is beautiful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fact. https://t.co/16mWDkcIGZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This. https://t.co/8BFUcrDXDJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where the fuck did that come from!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How long do we reckon McGree spent doing his hair pregame?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryans_Rovers a-rods are yellow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryans_Rovers because they are red?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's ok, found it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where's my football?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For my sports bra at the gym today. Just trained legs. Deep sumo squats hurt my ankle, i forgot this. It hurt. 

Lesson learnt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iluvnix17 @yomcat my eyes are scarred]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ps I am gutted my Sixers didn't win. And Venus. 

So lame!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scorchers âœ”ï¸
Serena âœ”ï¸

Now we sleep to prepare for another day with more amazing sport.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dam Serena making me teary hearing her praise Venus #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know it's still early, but this game is underwhelming me which sucks because I've been so excited for it. Nerves ya think? #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tegal1234 haha yea would have been awkward!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tegal1234 some of my best work!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tegal1234 oh I'm sorry, so you have work on Monday morning? ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tegal1234 I'll be up all night anyway lol. I'm dreading how late tomorrow could be, I feel that'll be 5 sets!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tegal1234 @Ryans_Rovers I've got the iPad on the cricket and the tv on the tennis. Why must they do this at the same time!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tegal1234 @Ryans_Rovers I definitely wasn't thinking of the 7s. I can watch the block delayed tho so no clash tomorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tegal1234 @Ryans_Rovers I remembered what it was, but it's not sporting related ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ it's the block #guiltypleasure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tegal1234 @Ryans_Rovers yea I only mentioned today. Tomorrow nix, fed v rafa, i feel like there's someone else, then Monday black caps!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But first, I shower!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As much as I'd love to see the underdogs take it, I think Scorchers to take the BBL and Serena to beat Venus. And that's just tonight!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm actually ridiculously excited for all the sport this weekend, and it's not even football dominated for a changed! All starts in 30!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your train was suppose to leave at 7:02, and it's 7:06...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And my alarm is going off in 6 hours, so I need to sleep now (if this tennis doesn't keep distracting me). So earth, calm the f down please!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Token delayed earthquake tweet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryans_Rovers I feel like Obama aged because he cared and out everything into it. Trump doesn't give a fuck. Plus plastic surgery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryans_Rovers health reasons... are you predicting an assassination?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashtastic05 I haven't finished it yet, but just hearing Hamish describe his worm burn, I was thinking 'I've heard this before...' haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashtastic05 have you listened to 2008 Day 4 yet? Hamish got "worm burn" and it totally reminded me of @iluvnix17 ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ I was in tears]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZPhotomac well you should!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashtastic05 that's so freaken amazing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZPhotomac @WgtnPhoenixFC I always behave!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZPhotomac @WgtnPhoenixFC hhhhhmmmmm someone appears to be missing...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tegal1234 @Ryans_Rovers I don't even want to imagine. It's good to hear that the injury isn't bad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryans_Rovers @Tegal1234 I watched it then had instant regret. Got to be one of the most horrific sporting accidents I've seen. Poor guy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shitballs! What a game! Don't see the Sixers beating the Scorchers tho. Ok sleep time!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course. Super over is Baz v Abbott. Fml.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryans_Rovers I can't handle this tho!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryans_Rovers Henriques just smashed it. Cutting bowled poorly and Munro did sweet nothing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a huge super over! I don't know if Baz will have it in him to bring it home!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The suspense is killing me right now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tegal1234 I don't know if I can handle a super over!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My heart is racing. This game!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh but out comes Abbott. He's gonna smash it and win the game for the Sixers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heat back in it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryans_Rovers they're still well ahead, they are 142/5 and Heat were 128/6 at the same point]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryans_Rovers haha he caught Baz!! Totally my fault!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryans_Rovers not looking good for the heat...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Baz catches Munro ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's happening to the Heat! Like seriously!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baz caught by Abbott. I knew that was gonna happen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because that's what he does.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not an ideal start from the Heat... Baz needs to fire up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SmithyInWelly then watched the cricket and I would have been 100% happy. Having to choose was tough. WHY ARE THERE STILL ADS?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SmithyInWelly lol that's my dilemma tho, if the Sixers were batting first, I probably would have watched the end of the movie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I forgot how much I loved the movie "Never Been Kissed" and now I have the dilemma of the cricket about to start.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's weird to think that today is Wednesday and I've only just realised the 7s are THIS weekend. Like Thurdsday... Friday... Weekend. 
Snap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's windy out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I appear to be having some sleep issues currently.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tegal1234 that's a bit harsh in the poo emoji isn't it? ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your friend just realised Trump is president ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚

Ps it wasn't, I just thought it'd be funny to say that https://t.co/8nHGkiKR6Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tegal1234 all of the above? Lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tegal1234 SHUT.THE.FRONT.DOOR!

Also important (and topical) to point out that autocorrect tried to change shut to shit. Well played phone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tegal1234 the poo emoji knows I still love it ðŸ’©ðŸ’©ðŸ’©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tegal1234 probably helps that the current/old one was quite shit and ugly. The poo emoji would have been an improvement on that logo ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ’©ðŸ’©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This cricket tho ðŸ‘ŒðŸ¼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IamNotJonahHill ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ 

That.Was.Brilliant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is happening in this cricket ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ a double wicket maiden... oh my!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danthekiwi sssshhhh you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That moment when you've just finished my preworkout then my boss rings and I speak stupidly fast and I'm pretty sure he thinks I'm crazy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you start seeing muscle definition in areas that you've always been self conscious about, makes the hard work totally worth it!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZPhotomac @patrick478 haha let's chat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZPhotomac @patrick478 you did which is awesome, but Bunny St is probably more key for your listeners!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrick478 that was good. Talking about bouncing however... and @NZPhotomac still plug Bunny, same owner so win win!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrick478 when I saw you, I hadn't heard the bit where you were talking about me... oooohhh you guys are lucky ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_Nighthawks my hood is coming in so handy right now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the 200m from the door to the bus stop, I managed to get soaked. Hurry up bus!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryans_Rovers @IamNotJonahHill yea Baz against my Sixers, so no matter who wins, I win haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wednesday night people! Lock it in! No matter who wins, i win ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #BBLFinals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IamNotJonahHill how exciting would that be!!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>