<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump shut your ugly face you dumb jackass!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump shut your orange asshole that's on your ugly face.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pukspers @_nGuilTy_ @PlayHearthstone @bdbrode spoony is my best bud. https://t.co/U3af9Le2E9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottjohnson (((trump))) is the best president!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump you're such a jackass!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CalebNeal76 dear Caleb, please eat some 💩]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump you're such an ugly loser!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tedharvey why would I defend that racist prick trump??? Why does a billionaire need money anyway??  Is he getting money for comrade Putin??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Tirion would smite you if he existed in this world! https://t.co/c0TGYZ0TTt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I bet Jesus Christ would shit all over you but you'd probably like it cuz you are a filthy disgusting pervert!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I bet Jesus would spit in your face you cowardly fake christian!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump how can you be such a cold, heartless prick?? I hope all those refugees get to drown you in piss in another life!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I bet Putin makes you toss his salad after he scarfs down a big chipotle burrito and you like it you sick fuck!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump dont you feel bad being such a racist, sexist, traitorous son of a bitch?? I hope your parents killed themselves in shame!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump you should fuck yourself to death with a red hot poker and make the world a better place!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump why are you such a stupid asshole!  I hate you and curse you to get gout and AIDS! 🗿🗿🗿]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump you racist cheeto!  Stop effing up the damn country!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stoneipaisgood @Lmoneyfresh @directvnow I have Netflix!  It is good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @MiamiHerald you're a big racist dope!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lmoneyfresh yeah!  You're a rich republican!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump liar!  You're just gonna sell us to the Russians!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump do you feel guilty being around them you draft dodging coward?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @TheLeeGreenwood are they stupid racists pricks like you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump lol. You look like a real jackass!  I bet you don't even know how to read and write u orange dipshit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump your such a dumb asshole!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump go fuck yourself u orange prick!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump who is gonna perform????  Anyone good?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker you sound like a real jerk!  I'm not gonna vote for you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@InvictaFights @TJDeSantis @julesk_fighter @UFCFightPass make tj button all his buttons this time!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JustinRYoung mcgregor could beat all three of those chumps!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump they are probably all orange perverts like you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lmoneyfresh Martha!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I bet you like to eat yellow snow u weirdo pervert!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump your a weird pervert!  Your no roll model!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump why is your govt still focusing on pot when billions of children die every year from heroin???????????????????????????????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottjohnson sweet chili is the best]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MoTownPhenom @MMARoasted I'm gonna save this for when u lose!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrantJKidney man, u tweet a lot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrantJKidney you think rousey is gonna win tomorrow?  she took a tough loss last year but she looks in great shape]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrantJKidney that sounds like the plot to captain america 2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesdpitley @GrantJKidney i just saw a thing about him on usatoday.  he's some breitbart guy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrantJKidney all the white people or just one in particular?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrantJKidney who's milo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@G2Thijs don't forget to answer my tattoo question!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrantJKidney how the hell can you want this flushed down the toilet?? https://t.co/lILNOg276G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrantJKidney you're gonna show us your dick?? What a pervert.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lmoneyfresh I thought it was pretty funny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MFG16 I'm gonna miss you after your last UFC!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lmoneyfresh what's wrong with white wine??  Just add an ice cube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sherdogdotcom @JSantoliquito couldn't you have found a better photo?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you! https://t.co/wpW2aSeBrk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump did his mom drink a lot when she was pregnant with him?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump who you gonna nuke u dumb orange bastard????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@williedills I will give you another twitch prime subscription to cheer you up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lmoneyfresh is that better?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump why does it cost so much to fix my roof!?!?  You are making this country terrible!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Sage Northcut lost!  Wtf!  I swear you are making this country terrible, not great!  So sad!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Why was CBD oil classified as a schedule 1 drug???? I swear you are the worst president ever!!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump you're a loser!  Why was traffic so bad yesterday?? Some president you are turning out to be]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump why don't you make the iPhone MARIO game free!  U jerk!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I got the Mario iPhone game and had to scroll WAY down to pick USA as my country! u were supposed to make USA great again!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crime Wave Sweeps City! #JadeLotus https://t.co/NbWaSz44FG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottjohnson I remember you were sure they were right too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottjohnson you touched his wiener though!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonnyBones u gonna do any pictures or stuff like that in Portland???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JustinRYoung I just cut the cord. Netflix seems like enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @CNN didn't you lose the popular vote by 2 million?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JustinRYoung @ContenderGame never heard of hackernews.  looks like reddit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My mind and body are strong. I dedicate myself to the #JadeLotus! #Gadgetzan https://t.co/g7RGRowvA1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lmoneyfresh they look in our stuff and make us go through a metal detector!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lmoneyfresh I've told you to get one!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this item I just got! [Prydaz, Xavaric's Magnum Opus] https://t.co/7auB13nKyL #Warcraft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have embraced the INCREDIBLE POWER of the #Kabal! #Gadgetzan https://t.co/g7RGRoeUbr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JustinRYoung I don't know what this means]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PlayHearthstone can you put hearthstone sounds on iTunes so I can use them as ringtones and alarms and stuff?  Plz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonnyBones you should start a twitch channel like rampage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottjohnson I'm on my first break of my night shift!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bdbrode the $50 pre purchase is a bit too steep for cheapos like me. Ever consider a $25 version with no cardback and 5 bonus packs?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JustinRYoung @acedtect i'm glad my daughter is grown up and can take of herself. it seems like a dark time to bring new kids into the world]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JustinRYoung @acedtect its kinda funny how life is probably better for the average american than ever before but the future looks so bleak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who will win – Alvarez or McGregor? Order UFC 205, Nov 12, live on Pay-Per-View from @XFINITY. https://t.co/xLvSG910Z1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lmoneyfresh shut your mouth!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lmoneyfresh just buy some shoes at Costco like a normal person]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonnyBones who you gonna vote for?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottjohnson I've been up since 3pm yesterday!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonnyBones you should get a job at Starbucks or something while you wait to fight again!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lmoneyfresh whats a TL?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bdbrode @reddit those guys are a bunch of negative nancies. I wish there was an alternative that was as big]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JustinRYoung the fantam awakens?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottjohnson I don't see why u hate Clinton. She seems qualified and sane.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottjohnson pence seems like an evil person. Trump is just an immature dope.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JustinRYoung I don't understand this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottjohnson is Utah a swing state?  Are you going to have to vote for shillary?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackSlackMMA I was there and I fell asleep.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottjohnson i dont see what the big deal is, you have someone qualified for the job and not crazy vs a crazy person.  the path looks clear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@filmsack it was ok. Lacked the bite of the original]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lmoneyfresh the movie?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lmoneyfresh network adapter!  I don't know what that is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lmoneyfresh pretty good. More mature and unhinged than the other tick shows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lmoneyfresh I watched it!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>