<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@djlauralux id be pretty pumped for you if you did! You're a joy to interact with :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConanOBrien @dwightfreeney @YouTube @NickCawker the end of this is priceless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvanonHB if he ends up on the market and the Hawks don't sign him I will actually flip over a table]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigCPDX almost certain @mikeroftholmes should own this shirt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can understand why people don't want pets in their rental unit but I always think it's shitty at the same time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jushin I missed you too bud. Also I promise to flood your TL with as many dank memes as much as I will politics 😊]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mickermack85 I 100% agree with that. Mental health is one of the most underfunded and not properly addressed issues in society]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mickermack85 if not for the safety of the public, than to keep them safe from themselves]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mickermack85 fair but I also think it's important to keep guns out of the hands of those with mental illness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes because his stupid ass VP signed a similar law. Get bent Trump https://t.co/65XrvrCKhV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigCPDX once I'm driving I'd love to come back down. I had an awesome summer trip there with @LeggoMyMeggoYo and a labour day trip too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigCPDX I know the feeling dude....beyond when I have to, I'm limiting my visits to Washington state only]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm seriously considering signing up for this and many other papers! Knowledge is power https://t.co/Ve6nzMcwqv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lenabug_ @mickermack85 it's all just alternative facts really but I too wouldn't want my doctor talking about me lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mickermack85 @lenabug_ knowing Trump he probably would talk about it anyways...some tweet about how it will "make America great again"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This account is too good 😂 https://t.co/NdQlIBLodf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ultimate plot twist: what if all Trump is doing is alienating his global allies and forcing people to actually like Russia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@littlemissmagi honestly feel your pain. I'm currently looking for rental units in the lower mainland....🙃]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CourtneyTailor besides house hunting...pretty good got back into the gym to work on legs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@littlemissmagi WHAT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This https://t.co/XpvOxwUeCd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Currently me https://t.co/VcZDe2WsWJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So basically he wants to unlawfully occupy another country 🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔🤔 https://t.co/BqMeArYI2u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHY WERE NONE OF MY TEACHERS THIS LIT🔥🔥🔥🔥 https://t.co/yeCYMRA8R1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gaychel22 most people in America don't believe in the first amendment if you A) don't agree w/ them B) are an athlete]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mickermack85 he and that Richard Spencer douchebag are why people are concerned about the Alt-right. Among other reasons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean you can't reform a process with no definitive plan to correct the issue. I'm okay with this https://t.co/b9RTYjyeOn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Bannon is terrifying. A crazy man guiding another crazy man https://t.co/u1Rkxaetjw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emmj3 @dave_ride @JRadMKE world class form hahaha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marshawn is literally the greatest of all time https://t.co/XRTmPFy7hI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brittanylee_3 wait for the 8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@antmay because the coal mines will save America!!! It's the only way 🙃]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hashtagsutton Gus is pretty fantastic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TulipsAndHockey @JuanPaBackPack but what if they lose 👀🔥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuanPaBackPack @TulipsAndHockey hahaha I'll be seeing you there fam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuanPaBackPack @TulipsAndHockey first of all nope. Secondly...last I checked someone lost a SB bet to me 👀]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TulipsAndHockey @JuanPaBackPack World issues &gt; Tom Brady and the Super Bowl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the outside looking in America pretty much looks like this right: https://t.co/t8EbKu2BCi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@djlauralux camera angles at times were horrid. Had the camera lock up on me in a dungeon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This makes you wonder how quickly the political establishment will put up with Trump's nonsense https://t.co/PunjDn3yyK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mickermack85 far from it. I'd say he is somewhere in the middle but with some controversial opinions. He is a friend of trumps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know Trump has gone too far when Piers Morgan thinks he has.... https://t.co/glt9hrVGgu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@antmay how ass monkeys like Richard Spencer have a platform to voice an opinion is beyond me. Hope someone plants one on his chin again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gaychel22 WHAT 💀 https://t.co/TvnRzQ0GY0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lenabug_ apologize for nothing! I'm looking forward to this https://t.co/U8HhUYJBlh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@antmay I could totally use some tacos....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First off, it's Sunday. 

Secondly, people have the right to freedom of speech and peaceful protest. It's in your c… https://t.co/ThQ7dccM05]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @lenabug_ I noticed we'll be in the same place in March 👀]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My heart goes out to those families impacted by the shooting at the Mosque in #QuebecCity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chelsea__Rose you and me both Chels]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kcco_cammy hey st least they are taking the game seriously and want to win. I find it hilarious personally]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chelsea_tino92 I can't breathe 😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The internet remains undefeated 😂 https://t.co/diDHbrHUix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hahahaha it isn't a football game if @mosesbread72 goes offside at least once 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikefreemanNFL 49ers hiring Lynch is clearly Kaepernick's fault!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only organization making more baffling moves than the US gov't is the San Fransisco 49ers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty sure this is restoring my faith in humanity https://t.co/UYJeuDXjjC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kayla__Ann the finesse skills are real and respected]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BR_DougFarrar I've see a lot of dumb ideas lately.....this is pretty high on the list. 

I blame Kaepernick for this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @ElanElizabeth 

Pretty sure this is something you may be interested in https://t.co/PZdOgpI524]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Part of me feels like being on the internet these days is an exercise in not losing my mind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love my prime minster. #thankyou https://t.co/GKRx4dWXsl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please read this thread https://t.co/V8uEFNpu4v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikefreemanNFL I may not like turkey bacon but I respect your liking of it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This gif is internet gold https://t.co/BeBqNccaas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BTupinit people are just being stupid man. This is the most shenanigans thing I've seen thus far]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gaychel22 they need extreme vetting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@antmay hahaha I've reached peak twitter post. Almost certain if @mikefreemanNFL saw this his reaction would look l… https://t.co/H2EpjYrlLs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@antmay I'm sorry I will promptly log off after this 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@antmay once you go Klingon you can never Kling-off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like the rest of the world and most Americans look at America like the parent who says "they aren't mad just disappointed at you"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gaychel22 i mean Baylor has such top notch recruiting and people. Trash city is what that situation is

https://t.co/8aIbQ83TrU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Alexbloomquist also to be fair I cheesed the dungeon 😂😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dave_ride @adanooope @BTupinit @Darius_Spencer yo I can hook it up with some down as fuck snacks from Canada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaylugh gotta love how politicians can just flat out lie and try and be cool about it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is some heat 🔥 https://t.co/ZHN9K2hRVt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gaychel22 I'd still take the gamble if I were a student who was assured my work was being published and my name was getting out there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gaychel22 I mean, if youre a journalism student w/ the opportunity to be published in a major newspaper while in college? I'd do it 4 free]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well then https://t.co/3AAkY5MOjH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not like the US Gov't in their existing tax structure can't do it? So why not just steal an old idea(s) and make it better 🤔]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be like "eh we are going to make health care more affordable. pre exsisting conditions? Don't worry fam! Lower premiums? We got you"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's all right there for the republican to be like "Ah we have a better plan" and just make improvements to the existing plan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I were a mastermind and could steal someone else's idea that's already in place and make it better and call it my own....I would]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What about this idea....why don't you just turn the ACA into what it should have originally should have been 🤔 https://t.co/8TzAmUbkti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrDropDab @hyruleLoLo no better place to spend sin time than sin city. What could possibly go wrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hyruleLoLo I got 3 weeks of paid sin time. I'm game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me on twitter today https://t.co/dYLl54U5lL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_AwakeMySoul I totally see it https://t.co/Jqowixk3g9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The "Ah fuck this guy" Face https://t.co/E3yRfQlLTO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adanooope "how do we recruit this kid?" "Let him know we got some down as fuck white women" "brilliant! Do that, we won't get in trouble"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adanooope @hashtagsutton @RobotRandy_ fitting because it's constantly fucking most of America every 4 years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hashtagsutton @RobotRandy_ @adanooope at least they can properly separate Florida from the rest of America 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well I guess if you were to ask "where the white women at" we now know the answer https://t.co/8aIbQ83TrU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BR_DougFarrar @ForTheWin Has Brent Musburger not learned anything this month about talking about poltitical or social issues?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GalaxyDescends black liquorice is the Donald Trump of candy. No one likes it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GalaxyDescends ONLY THE BLACK CANDY MATTERS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BTupinit go see what I said to Richie lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SOMEONE GIVE ME THIS NOW https://t.co/8CqhUz9iHh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mickermack85 with Trump he may just fly off the handle with that power.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mickermack85 I would agree with that but I trusted Bush and Obama more to use their executive orders fairly responsibly.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>