<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@samfromwgtn you should get the morgan foundation to look into the work of @garytaubes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razibkhan @Peter_Turchin more credence to bannons 80 year cycle?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MorganGodfery @GuyonEspiner maths no longer compulsory after year 11, STEM is important for lifting living standards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MohnishPabrai its too easy for us mere mortals to fall for cognitive biases when doing qualitative analysis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScottAdamsSays what do you think of @RoguePOTUSStaff 's inside account of trump?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ritholtz get him on the podcast!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS @EricCrampton it's a temporary ban and the 7 countries were chosen by the Obama administration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricCrampton they'll argue low labour force participation rate and high amount of part time workers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billmaher @ScottAdamsSays flooding the playingfield]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jaydotchan @Cernovich and peter thiel is my 4th slot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cernovich @BreitbartNews who are the other 4?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatthewHootonNZ it was clearly just banter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@primalpoly is coscientiousness also similar?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ritholtz the trump rally went against expectations, but stocks are expected to bounce back after a crash]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterboghossian @Cernovich i like the @sapinker quote about the left wing pole, anything that deviates from it is right wing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricCrampton if you reject big 5 and believe its environmental, and hence volatile, you wont bother to do the modelling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricCrampton the stability of personality over a lifetime is what gives it predictive power]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricCrampton @AntiDotePharma left wing blank slatism makes then antagonistic to personality research, cause of genetic heritability aspect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clairlemon this article explains the phenomenon well https://t.co/q8wSSh98em]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AEAjournals @EricCrampton whats the crime rate of african american citizens like?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JayMan471 get the genes of the hunter when you're ovulating, get the support of the nice guys the rest of the time?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clairlemon brave of them to not write it anonymously]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JayMan471 @EPoe187 short term alpha fucks, long term beta bucks?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joerogan @davidludwigmd @RobertLustigMD @drjasonfung would all also be great guests]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@primalpoly maybe kryptonians were high investment K selection parents]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JayMan471 @Mangan150 i recall something about facial symmetry and health, broad chins and testosterone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mitchacre @EricCrampton they need to read @charlesmurray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScottAdamsSays its been deleted, what did it say?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@acquirersx @Greenbackd do you think it is a good time right now cyclically to start a deep value investing strategy? or wait for a crash]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joerogan @garytaubes nice, cant wait to listen!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KirkegaardEmil i recall reading waist to hip ratio being even better than waist to height]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nntaleb what do you think of value investing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_cingraham @paulkrugman what are the raw/nominal numbers?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ezraklein @davidfrum same reason hillary didnt release wall st speeches]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoingOurBitNZ 27% on benefits after 5 years? nice spin!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattyglesias the official ones are made in america, fake news!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dpfdpf why change what won him the election?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonHaidt @franks_lawyer there'd be more empathy if you were allowed to talk about genes. People dont mock the disabled]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Scaramucci @wef @Davos you're a great communicator]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricCrampton survey time was 2002-2010, there was a stockmarket crash in 2009]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MWStory @hbdchick social justice sanctimony receiving a bloody nose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@razibkhan if you dont have oil money to fall back on, you need to allow women to participate in labour force]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan for the click revenue, and pure lols]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@esoltas @ATabarrok makes sense, need the labour force participation if you cant live off oil money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clayroutledge @CHSommers took long enough!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drjasonfung is the lean mass from training or change in hormones?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BritishInvestor @ritholtz @BV maybe he's just a good stockpicker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatthewHootonNZ @wto @realDonaldTrump i think you've fallen for fake news]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Neuro_Skeptic @tylercowen confounding with openness to experience personality trait?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Steve_Sailer glad to see meritocracy prevail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JesseLucasSaga @JayMan471 @clairlemon conscientiousness would have some effect on looks/grades though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RCAFDM @JayMan471 confounding with IQ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bendolnickbooks have had some humble pie and apologised to @ScottAdamsSays?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScottAdamsSays do you think arnold schwarzenneger is a master persuader? successful in many fields, supposedly reads a lot of psychology]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@trengriffin @Greenbackd @MugatuCapital @nachkari historically low interest rates, incentives for debt rather than equity?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@trengriffin @Greenbackd @MugatuCapital @nachkari globalization, internet make markets more efficient. tech innovation = more volatility]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anishraju @nntaleb wheres this from?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creating Economic Assets out of Nothing by Scott Adams https://t.co/Fb2mRbWMwP via @ScottAdamsSaysl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JiMannering @jordanbpeterson the data speaks for itself, plenty of unequal countries that do well, equal ones that perform poorly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JiMannering @jordanbpeterson the spirit level has been debunked, stats were cherry picked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlekstheRealist @MohnishPabrai love the quant approach a la deep value by @Greenbackd and greenblatts magic formula]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joerogan would love to see you interview @garytaubes on the podcast!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@trengriffin i recall reading somewhere that the only area of growth was adult colouring in books]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GadSaad @RichardDawkins didnt he recently suffer from a stroke? i think he's cut back on all media apperances and just taking it easy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonHaidt theres a strong case to be made that academia can use some quality control @RealPeerReview]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garethmorgannz you ignore administration costs that'll lead to deadweight loss and capital flight https://t.co/cCswIrh2kU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewmeows if the 1st year stuff is more reflective of what the job actually entails, could be a good idea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewmeows all they're doing is moving the practical stuff to the start of the course, women currently still do it, just later]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewmeows if they're being held to same standard, i dont see that as discrimination, a lower gpa to get into course for men would be]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewmeows or it could just be more graduates in total, but higher % of men, considering he's saying theres a shortage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewmeows it might encourage the people that would've dropped out after 1st year to stick around]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewmeows im happy with individuals following their personal preferences, rather than trying to get quotas of 50/50]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewmeows differences in personality and brain development is fact. im saying its not affirmative action/discrimination to change course]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewmeows it was hyperbole, but in the general pop we can see there are more part time or not working women, same in med and law]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewmeows i dont think theres anything wrong with exposure to practical stuff first. both sexes still go through the same course]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewmeows mathematically, if they work the same hours up to 30, comparing from 30 onwards will give you better picture of the differences]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewmeows but it seemed obvious to me he was talking about hours worked rather than the quality of the veterinarian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewmeows the gap would be larger than 37 vs 45 hours if you started measuring at age 30-35 rather than all ages.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewmeows women in 1st world countries already can do whatever they want. some people dont seem to accept that differences exist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewmeows part culture, part biology. social justice types tend to ignore  biology, and assume all differences stem from oppression]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garethmorgannz from your own website https://t.co/EhDuuOKTMZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewmeows genes and hormones have huge influence on behaviour, if we're gonna compare the 2 sexes, you have to generalize]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewmeows evo psych: men have stronger incentive to seek status and $, women value work-life balance more, consistent across cultures]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamPerkinsPhD or marshmallow test]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewmeows if you add up total hours worked and compare the 2 groups what does it come to?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewmeows he's generalising about sex differences, only blank slatist ideologues ignore biology]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@medickinson @andrewmeows @MasseyUni yes, women on average value work-life balance more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garethmorgannz Your wealth tax was disastrous in France. Why not a land tax? https://t.co/q2xEJcIO1R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshgans @EricCrampton nike shoes and iphones didnt get cheaper for the consumer after outsourcing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelshermer isnt ideology also a tribe?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mizjwilliams @dpfdpf is this real?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatthewHootonNZ @EricCrampton @honbillenglish true, but key had enough charisma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricCrampton @MatthewHootonNZ @honbillenglish 2 white males probably bad for identity politics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clairlemon doubt he's read it but he probably gets these thing intuitively]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls @ScottAdamsSays A-B testing "Trump likes encouraging a public airing of conflicting views when he is unsure of what path..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@guywilliamsguy @Biorealism Come on guy you have to try harder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@guywilliamsguy @Biorealism he totally disavowed, you're uninformed. Guy, take a week off tweeting this weak shit please!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@guywilliamsguy @Biorealism u think he meant mexican children and women are rapists? Try harder at context and interpretation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@guywilliamsguy @Biorealism yet you call people that want to copy canadas immigration policy racist, xenophobic etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid @Noahpinion another hoax poll?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>