<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Text of Tillerson's welcome remarks to State Dept employees: https://t.co/tPkWvdqoz9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thread from @tcwittes--overall take on Tillerson's State Dept debut: https://t.co/gAxltt2pky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scientists discover long-lost ancient continent under Indian Ocean in Mauritius https://t.co/QZh4mx4gKd via @indiatvnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Workers race to clean India Chennai oil spill https://t.co/9g2D17OMvE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bannon’s ‘Strategic Initiatives’ Cabal Inside the NSC Is Dangerous Hypocrisy, by @derekchollet and @julie_c_smith https://t.co/jSRvhUYCmg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do we help POTUS start employing the Tillerson management principles? [1: accountability; 2: honesty; 3: treat… https://t.co/RtyBZJWNDj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@krshya I encourage you to take a look at his ethics agreement with OGE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ammaradurrani The live webcast, which is on my timeline.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tillerson's debut at State: calm, gracious, signalling commitment to the workforce. Like a quiet calm after tornado.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshrogin On the other hand, if you benchmark against the Black History Month and Natl Prayer Bkfst remarks, this was just right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tillerson asks all to uphold high standard of ethics. He has set a good example with his ethics agreement, thankfully.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tillerson's management principles: 1) accountability; 2) honesty; 3) treat each other with respect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this for real? Black History Month turns into Trump-memoir, now at Natl Prayer Bkfst praying for The Apprentice? https://t.co/EAjPykB1jT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pakistan imposes travel ban on Hafiz Saeed, 37 others from JuD and LeT  @htTweets https://t.co/eQmGHeOJ0h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Berkeley violence was wrong. But will POTUS stand up for free speech from others? From CNN? NYTimes? Or just Milo? https://t.co/PUWASbk4vM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does this mean? And if arena for action might be UN, then why these unclear statements from Flynn and POTUS bu… https://t.co/QuWG3NMDbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Incomprehensible-THIS IS ONE OF OUR CLOSEST ALLIES. "On call with Australian prime minister, Trump badgers &amp; brags" https://t.co/fiBKrZXuQs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@BRRubin on The Art of the Deal in Afghanistan https://t.co/WmFaxq2jIl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great review of @JoshKurlantzick's new book, A Great Place to Have a War https://t.co/GD1EQ9OM4W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too bad Lonnie Bunch of @NMAAHC wasn't there to provide some opening remarks, set the stage.... https://t.co/9hj0CiOsKT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here at jury duty watching the Trump meeting on Black History Month, which has turned into reflections on his campaign successes &amp; media]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ripple effects of Trump's H-1B visa reform (incl on India) via @axios https://t.co/wgBtoChsL6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoa. https://t.co/BRTEEloAHR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never Again: Muslim Ban Echoes Authoritarian States, by @sarahkendzior https://t.co/d3sypGPCQ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does anyone believe Trump really studied Scalia's writings closely?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Painful to read. https://t.co/VPK17tbeGn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe the judge Trump doesn't choose will get a consolation prize. The Deputy AG position is open.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fundamental principle of govt ethics is not to choose favorites. https://t.co/DQJZrwpMKL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It can't be that Trump is going to decide live at 8pm. Which means he is making someone *he knows he won't choose* join the spectacle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Is he confused or are you confused?': Spicer grilled by reporters in heated exchange over Trump's travel ban https://t.co/t7On9DOdA7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indian pharma hasn't heard abt this yet: "Trump says foreign countries need to pay "fair share" for drugs" @axios https://t.co/HJ2F2HPuyF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevenacook As I wrote that I realized it was way way out of step with the times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The kinder path would be to let the one not chosen stay out of the media glare. Is he going to have both there together? @stevenacook]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isn't this embarrassing for the 1 not chosen? Trump Summons Top 2 Supreme Court Candidates for Prime-Time Unveiling https://t.co/c4Nk7upjCj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Linguistic anthropologist analyzes how to tweet like Trump (start with a derogatory noun, add gratuitous modifier..… https://t.co/VnWCRMlsGJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Health whodunit in India, with a surprise culprit: Dangerous Fruit: Mystery of Deadly Outbreaks in India Is Solved https://t.co/OiV9PiVXM0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New H-1B Bill in U.S. calls for doubling minimum pay  https://t.co/IsYcFpqbFi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Trump's Reshuffling of the National Security Council Means, by @kellymagsamen  https://t.co/mretjIA21X via @defenseone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How long before Hafiz Saeed is fully back in action, leading another 30k-person caravan in the capital of Pakistan? https://t.co/mw3mDu3Ry7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@nytdavidbrooks "The Republican Fausts" https://t.co/ZfWErJiAYW https://t.co/3eYQJFJaEp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bangladesh pushes on with Rohingya island plan https://t.co/kpZZ9gdrgF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A message from the PM of Bhutan which could have application in US: https://t.co/XVLvC0BWAq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isn't Germany our ally and major trade partner? https://t.co/yZrjsZUMRK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatAdeney Last 10 days a whirlwind of disbelief.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many urgent national security and economic matters deserve POTUS's limited time--not things like this: https://t.co/TeKMzcQt6U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe if I keep looking at the peacefulness of the Golden Temple, all the Washington craziness will melt away...... https://t.co/d3KgdROwog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is amazing: https://t.co/vfEKHawUV5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Milbank: Republicans are alarmed to discover Trump is doing exactly what he said he would https://t.co/1RXnpxZQXi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good piece by @sam_vinograd: You Have the Wrong Enemy https://t.co/wkJx87lL3G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG on the process fouls here: "Bannon Making Sure No WH Paper Trail" https://t.co/SV9TyG5QlN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congress has oversight function--can't just "not talk" to Congress! https://t.co/EEslvWjlnJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full text: “Letter from National Security Leaders on Refugee Executive Order” https://t.co/PXMmBlfTLG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I stand with this letter. Do you?: Ex-foreign policy officials urge agencies to push reversal of Trump refugee orde… https://t.co/dlBWfdeFJy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Dangerously Isolated President https://t.co/YqDHYaWmp5 via @newyorker @benwallacewells]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thread: troll insults @kalpenn, who starts fundraising for refugees in response....more than $350k raised so far: https://t.co/xgGRUmDbox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silicon Valley’s Ambivalence Toward Trump Turns to Anger https://t.co/6SHcmtXxyS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@lyft stands up for American values, donates $1m to @aclu: https://t.co/7U0hHMXVwX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protest Grows ‘Out of Nowhere’ at Kennedy Airport After Iraqis Are Detained, via @nytimes https://t.co/rXvK4le2Ty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Must-read @benjaminwittes: "Malevolence Tempered by Incompetence: Trump’s Horrifying Exec.Order on Refugees &amp; Visas" https://t.co/qT1hT6JfBF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Kabul on edge amid standoff between Afghan government and Vice President"  https://t.co/pSri7c6jFh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great news: https://t.co/eBObo6LSWb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mattis the Great, Mattis the Exploited, by @EvansRyan202 https://t.co/H15tNoNRBS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@IgnatiusPost: "Trump is his administration’s own worst enemy on foreign policy" https://t.co/tgVcEnStGg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moving personal experience of @rcallimachi on being a refugee in Europe, then immigrant to US: https://t.co/LxCxEgsIb5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unfair insinuation of "aiming to sneak in." Ashley Tellis has never hid his positions or "sneaked" anywhere. https://t.co/zjABJjtqpM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indian courts tackle urgent matter: "Footwear without back strap is sandal, not chappal: HC" (ht @saliltripathi) https://t.co/pfrWnT8ABm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take a look at @ShamilaCh's photoessay: 4 refugee families from Iraq &amp; Syria, making a new home in Toledo, OH. https://t.co/rBFE98AqMF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For those who see American openness as "among the greatest sources of American strength—this will be the biggest te… https://t.co/VFBDuN1oQO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s Immigration Ban Is Illegal, via @nytimes https://t.co/5gwWomO8oJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wish he would also boost the State Dept: https://t.co/PfhBefhgHi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even the Teen Vogue Writer Who Took On Trump Gets Stage Fright https://t.co/MvSpXVEMVR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jenniferbussell Take a look at @AltNatParkSer and all the feeds it follows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazed at the number of "alt-USG" agencies now on Twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nikki Haley Puts U.N. on Notice: U.S. Is ‘Taking Names’ https://t.co/FJa5Bc4hmr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting: "Impact of demonetisation will not be significant," says Nomura https://t.co/9yqMzBSita via @economictimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great list of foreign policy books, all by women: see @fpinterrupted FPI’s Books of 2016 https://t.co/5ioxKdaTt1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rahulkanwal Bharawan da Dhaba with a huge cube of butter on top!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tcwittes @StateDept @shebacrocker It's like there's no thought to sequencing departures to provide transition leadership.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see @Vsiv featured in @forbes 30 Under 30 Innovators! https://t.co/fyuNQotcBn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(Including "T-shirts from Bangladesh"): Counting the Winners and Losers From an Import-Based Tax https://t.co/jRJyjYAXok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s Lies Pave the Way for an Assault on Voting Rights, via @nytimes https://t.co/EHQN3E5RyN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Voting Fraud Inquiry? The Investigators Got Burned Last Time, via @nytimes https://t.co/yFfth7YIzb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Politics of Cowardice, via @nytimes https://t.co/tfGh1SUDag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Odd obsession, wrong to pressure: "Trump pressured Park Service to find proof for his claims abt inauguration crowd" https://t.co/yK029BbDh2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The State Department's entire senior management team just resigned, by @joshrogin https://t.co/ffUTU5FyIo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advice from the newly revamped Shadow Government blog: "What to Watch Out for, Mr. President" https://t.co/6g45MyXHHT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pakistan, India feature in @BulletinAtomic decision to move doomsday clock 30 seconds closer to midnight: https://t.co/qHUGn5WjgC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't accuse Indian media of only covering women politicians' fashion: "The Prime Minister’s pagdis" https://t.co/jQhKGSjld3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon expands into ocean freight, its latest move to build out its delivery business  https://t.co/F4E4sXNbdf via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sent Home for Not Wearing Heels, She Ignited a British Rebellion, via @nytimes https://t.co/WUmY6Wx5ZF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pressure Builds for Modi to Overhaul Indian Campaign Finance, via @nytimes https://t.co/IIMAyCRKh2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Political Jolt at a Literary Festival, but Courtesy Wins Out, via @nytimes https://t.co/a8ehUOxIC1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harvard prof Ali Asani &amp; Coke studio artist Ali Sethi pay ode to regional poets at ‘Misaq-e-Ishq’ https://t.co/eOASpMrxZR @epakistantoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy #RepublicDay to all friends in India!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PM Narendra Modi may visit the US after assembly polls - The Economic Times https://t.co/IeNfrfmoDp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't see how this will help the U.S. lead globally: "Trump Prepares Orders Aiming at Global Funding and Treaties" https://t.co/kaeifdhzGo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - US President Donald Trump invites Narendra Modi https://t.co/uCQzbPUiae]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KanchanGupta Thanks so much!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Bad Reasons for Pulling Back From the World, by @EliotACohen https://t.co/lGRFdhQ6mR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Trump 101: What he reads and watches" from @axios https://t.co/Tehdg7ytuN]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>