<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[fact or fiction? https://t.co/Lg5IZaomuK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will not be your father https://t.co/Rhvo2QCDWw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When autocorrect insists you are going on a ducking walk https://t.co/wtH8ksXf7k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Believe it or not.  This parrot was arrested for hurling obsenities at an 85 year-old woman in India. https://t.co/WwgbgXYwqU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some person asked this question. https://t.co/uKBcgWAxHe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one way to determine the slope of a line https://t.co/qxChyWsRXw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take a trip to Istanbul, Turkey in April and May to see the Istanbul Tulip Festival, with 3 million tulips blooming… https://t.co/gO4VnHySss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[messing with the wife - not smart guy https://t.co/C14KeLxlUX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eurofighter Typhoon is the world's most advanced swing-role combat aircraft offering agile performance, interoperab… https://t.co/dXbKsW0OcM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This boy's got swagger https://t.co/bwL6jSvuM3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dont think this was designed to slice apples. Works though. https://t.co/jCIpPysp1N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please not now. https://t.co/Tm2PSeef8H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great way for kids to get some exersise in Phy Ed class. https://t.co/xkYMwOXSut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What were these two agreeing on? https://t.co/H92M72ndAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now where do you think we should put our new trampoline? https://t.co/VzVwgumm0o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now that is one big, contented cat! https://t.co/FdFQIR0DXq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just patiently waiting for the next wave https://t.co/0u13vKMFJd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Busch Gardens Tampa - All You Need to Know Before You Go

https://t.co/XAW8oxoLvn https://t.co/0hVqOderYc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As you can see, my areolas of expertise are as follows... https://t.co/wIIZPKTjJC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aoraki Mount  Cook is the highest mountain in New Zealand - 12,218 feet

https://t.co/AngrZAgoib https://t.co/qUca1jatQD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Up in the coconut tree, one happy puppy https://t.co/hisHFtC0jW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A river runs through it https://t.co/bXd8Gvli32]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to a recent pole people prefer shade. https://t.co/y2mbJx0GT2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[17 Chocolate Recipes You Don't Know Your Slow Cooker Can Make

https://t.co/71dUIkz3ZR https://t.co/lhJz6NRPhw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[24 Things You Should Never Order When You Eat Out - A large popcorn

https://t.co/TdPr9vfwgT https://t.co/68oyedGwrC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the World's Smallest Birds Survive the Winter

https://t.co/ZJOVV5wZd4 https://t.co/lBt7eRDh3C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quebec passes law that requires automakers to sell a minimum number of electric cars

https://t.co/xUgiDnoRcj https://t.co/uma1p9wjWn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fake. That young, that hot, and no cell phone in her hand? Fake. https://t.co/NbHwArfucp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Melissa coordinating gum and shirt to match her pretty eyes https://t.co/vdaBojzzKb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The stupid part is that the customer actually complained to Domino's customer service after this. Wants a joke, but… https://t.co/BIvX1bVkr1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Akashi Kaikyō Bridge is a suspension bridge, which links the city of Kobe on the Japanese mainland of Honshu to Iwa… https://t.co/pFT0WiWPR7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shanghai, on China’s central coast, is the country's biggest city and a global financial hub. https://t.co/Q6Kryjwgom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ice climbing in Canada https://t.co/aQpfpte2pe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pragser Wildsee, or Lake Prags, Lake Braies is a lake in the Prags Dolomites in South Tyrol, Italy. https://t.co/1FTDphG6Dq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Battleship USS Wisconsin, an Iowa class battleship, one of the largest ever built for the U.S. Navy, now berthed at… https://t.co/lYDbHrYhEX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canyon Calling, a photo of sunset over the Grand Canyon. https://t.co/szVOWNJTxE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nassau Harbour Lighthouse, Paradise Island, Nassau, Bahama https://t.co/zN9EsqCxwR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My diet on cheat day. https://t.co/mS6SpFu8eo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you've given up on trying to find a boyfriend and now you just feel defeet. https://t.co/aVFI74uKP0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Point Reyes Lighthouse stairs https://t.co/Q2rWMMQk4z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This drunk girl is resting here face on a slice of pizza. Everything get better with pizza. #pizza https://t.co/cGzTu5Lmhl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[a head with a view https://t.co/EaYymUzuk1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Dancing House,, or Fred and Ginger, is the nickname given to the Nationale-Nederlanden building on the Rašínovo… https://t.co/uXQzc7KdW7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A rustic bedroom with a fireplace https://t.co/I0NnotXIRy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Refraction https://t.co/1WlaPAEsNr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maldives huts on water https://t.co/3QxElR0Cu6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Optimus has fallen on hard times since the last movie. https://t.co/RZv3lQMTFO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taste the rainbow https://t.co/dxlmFSFc40]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Noelle Foley, daughter of WWE's Mick Foley https://t.co/YUYTqamGWM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[how to ruin what would have been picturesque https://t.co/dlTz2qOm8R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andrew Desjardins of the Chicago Blackhawks enjoying a breakfast of Lucky Charms in hockey's Stanley Cup. https://t.co/3JNEz5ebC0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[temporary firepit https://t.co/5G4RJrt5md]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's one for the many cat lovers https://t.co/RKqxFFWruZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Funny but I'm not a fan https://t.co/xOKMFELr7k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clever responce https://t.co/2jAxfD9FTj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A very happy pet https://t.co/EBhFoWlXxy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Image of Saturn could not have been taken from Earth. No Earth based picture could view the night side of Saturn… https://t.co/PbZVEhn4wL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two of the most prominent reflection nebulas - dust clouds lit by the reflecting light of bright embedded stars.… https://t.co/WU4eIuyFjw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Bonneville Flood struck 17,400 years ago. Twenty Missoula Flood deposits sit on top of the Bonneville deposit.… https://t.co/5if8UELHax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beach Drainage - snapped on Corona Del Mar's beach in southern California. Ocean water receding to the sea… https://t.co/YeTffL7S19]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i believe Trump's mandate is to make America Great Again, not to suck up to Hollywood or please the press. @realDonaldTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Were they protesting in Antartica?  @mcspocky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tuff Stuff - carved out of consolidated volcanic ash (tuff)

https://t.co/wZIaRieAPn https://t.co/OMV6xlYDVO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winter Hexagon over Manla Reservoir 

https://t.co/XgdPTCp9yf https://t.co/Po2MipPfQb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Triple Divide Peak (8,020 ft or 2,444 m), located in the southeastern part of Glacier National Park, Montana.… https://t.co/2KkOFlDktJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[13 Tips to Help You Hit Your Daily Step Goal

https://t.co/r3Ev7Re5oJ https://t.co/95uNogoqY7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never in Canada https://t.co/SrJGRzWpQW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[alternative fact eh? https://t.co/2aU4u4qmNC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He looks completely real to me https://t.co/ebaQqsENov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hopefully we've seen the last of this in Vancouver and the lower mainland of British Columbia. https://t.co/amrZPqrdew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[turtle or tortoise push ups - not sure https://t.co/nPziUQGHkP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My gang, "we're hardcore". https://t.co/dXEsEhGmI5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[a couple of dogs enjoying the good life https://t.co/7VgirnlCwX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying again.  Another great sunset. https://t.co/RlrxD1C5Gf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another great sunset]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[seriously? https://t.co/ERkdN4Tzpy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just an old guy and his cats https://t.co/2rfN6nQZuC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eight Futuristic Foods You'll Be Eating in 30 Years

https://t.co/uQ1CXFvkCL https://t.co/EjSZhojDiJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Japan’s trains are in a league of their own. 

https://t.co/mdgwmb7qwu https://t.co/law0Qy3aTR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Thousand Year History of the Nose Job

https://t.co/duvklVnx2n https://t.co/j5SX2zQM2I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greenery named as Pantone's Colour of the Year 2017

https://t.co/g6LJq5zPja https://t.co/Wlfrf3x6Hw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Happens If You Stick Your Head in a Particle Accelerator?

https://t.co/tARwIXg2XG https://t.co/urA2HDcqJk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Lemons Are Helping Women Fight Breast Cancer

https://t.co/lAUrFkTuC1 https://t.co/edAGXmuiLI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[16 Things You Didn’t Know About Avocados

https://t.co/VV7Im6NrWh https://t.co/JpYrYDw9Jr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who’s a good boy?  you might ask. But does your dog care?

https://t.co/DmuYkuV6vb https://t.co/8FRWgyee5Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Switzerland, You Can Be Denied Citizenship for Being Too Annoying

https://t.co/sEadxx2MQG https://t.co/tJGZri974n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 Old-Fashioned Housekeeping Hacks That *Actually* Work — and Why

https://t.co/w93vadmqdx https://t.co/3Hu8cAINmD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sugar, explained.  First it was too many calories. Then it was too much fat. Now there’s a full-on war on sugar.… https://t.co/zN89ctHAOQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These Utopian cities of the future will help you re-imagine life on Earth

https://t.co/uQYFHRt3ti https://t.co/zBmwGeTuiZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wrong https://t.co/ik5h72vIMs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The photo above shows columnar basalt along the edge of the Bras de la Plaine River on the island of Reunion… https://t.co/9fZlTDv1g2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Simple Trick for Defrosting Your Windshield in Less Than 60 Seconds

https://t.co/9cI7MIvcrT https://t.co/h5TwFYbnQz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Is How A Finnish Education Platform Will Scale Innovation For The Next 100 Years

https://t.co/6Phw6L2T8I https://t.co/gHUXSnUqcP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pixar Just Confirmed That All of Their Films are Linked  

https://t.co/OYlmti9Dbj https://t.co/3ToJ2L012s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Incredible Military Issued Flashlight Now Available To Public

https://t.co/cNoPTU5RXj https://t.co/Z2ORUmkmVD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9 Lessons From Around The World To Create The Perfect City

https://t.co/yttDCsnPo3 https://t.co/HSweL7Ky0v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dhaka, Bangladesh,Muslims pray at the start of the world’s second largest annual Islamic congregation on the banks… https://t.co/VYyzzBJmqa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Farindola, Italy, Firefighters search for survivors at Hotel Rigopiano after eight people, including two childre… https://t.co/GXngYgI6c2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IN Kolkata, India, Civil defence personnel take part in a full dress rehearsal for India’s Republic Day parade.Phot… https://t.co/mwGOZm6AEv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Gondar, Ethiopia, a man jumps into Fasilides pool during the annual Timkat Epiphany celebration.  Photograph: Ca… https://t.co/YN7om2Bky8]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>