<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Having co-founded two companies with skilled migrants, it's sad to see a once proud nation turning back the clock on a lifetime of progress.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reality Cheque. The journey from startup to success is a long one. https://t.co/keQmbMyomC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Age Concern. My @radionz panel session looking at how older entrepreneurs are achieving success https://t.co/6sxF2RL9im]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thrilled to spot my first Saddleback today. Hard to photograph. The baby Tuatara cute also. @zealandia doing a wond… https://t.co/W4G4uPdBPZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IRD are pitching their $25M KM system spend as a "New Zealand company" when in fact JV between two foreign owned multinationals. WTF?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelloMissPotter That place should be renamed Moreish Wilsons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consider myself, quite well informed, but only just figured out who our (rather low profile) governor-general is: https://t.co/u7TxPF6Cpx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caught up with fellow "entrepreneur activist" @leancto over a beer &amp; curry recently. Here's what he's been up to. https://t.co/fzb5xNtuZG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrCuriosity Unfortunately they seem to get a lot of airtime.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you look at the parlous state of media generally, are "celebrities" really that qualified to be dictating moral guidance to the nation?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoyed the presentations this year. https://t.co/uHy3YgZEim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agree with @treitnauer. Independent voices are more important than ever. https://t.co/SLhS9VrRUe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Regional councils &amp; effluent lobbyists @DairyNZ complicit in destroying our rivers. More public activism needed. https://t.co/5s0HbUKfZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nznativefish @adzebill Exactly. So why are Dairy NZ and all the other cow shit deniers winning the argument?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ohyoufox ... only if you let it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why entrepreneurs should focus on innovation and effective, incremental change rather than disruption. https://t.co/AlbDs5Dlna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@farmgeek It's a great shame that our national day has become such an embarrassment. I like the idea of letting other marae host.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My brief appearance in a James Cameron production today. Long story. Tasty, ethical food &amp; friendly crew.… https://t.co/BW4UXP6zUv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The realities of building $100M in revenue. It's a zoo! https://t.co/RpsWmRWHvR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzherald Typo in your @AndrewLittleMP article. I'm pretty sure should read "Waitara Valley Methanol Plant".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Blog: Ashes To Ashes 2016 and how @audreyt gave us hope for 2017. https://t.co/nmlUJYBleL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @liel click-bait rant neglects one vital detail. NZ society may not be perfect but it's peaceful &amp; socially integrated, unlike Israel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My recent interview about our successful experience deploying @siftscience. https://t.co/m5Fu6x4Cjc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jethrocarr Now you know what my car looks like 5 minutes after I washed it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pancakes by Van Gogh. Dining in our household has taken on a pleasing design aesthetic these holidays. https://t.co/0kP4sUkVE6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life's a beech. We had a lovely Boxing Day walk through the Muritai beech forest above Eastbourne village. https://t.co/9otHlRs7SP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice to meet @MMacLeodSmith @the_icehouse. Last day for @fluxaccelerator applications today. https://t.co/lP1oUc4nBg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cafe breakfast in Parnell. When in Rome.... https://t.co/OJtoyrW1Tv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was a thrill to see Catalina ZK-PBY airborne over my hometown at the weekend https://t.co/tel3ZiLaW9 cc/… https://t.co/6JY1cYjkSn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operating a global internet business mostly from home. No sign of ADSL2+ or UFB in our street any time soon. https://t.co/3O4BkPXETD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quick visit @radionz studios today to record panel session for summer series on entrepreneurship with host Lynn Fre… https://t.co/M7JhhTeG5O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starting up in the Capital? The @fluxaccelerator crew are @BizDojo WLG on Tues https://t.co/6QFZMeM7gt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prof. @zingales proposal on how to deal with the Trumpocalypse https://t.co/bM6cTWcgKw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCWorld omg please shut him up! This guy isn't "expert" in anything - especially aviation. #bbcnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My handsome son the racing car driver. https://t.co/BmqPcyVzST]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Renea @DevelopsterTeam @imagin8iv I should have known there'd be fish &amp; chips involved at some point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to hosting Joel at Machine Learning &amp; Data Science lunch meetup today https://t.co/7dL9XgTdcG https://t.co/YH2ZJp6RcR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wet weekend ahead. Hack some code, make new friends and enjoy delicious free food. What's not to like? https://t.co/GApK70MZlc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of takeaways from @founderconnz today. Thanks team #founderconnz https://t.co/Me5ZybzPwh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sulufiti Sorry I missed that one. Been a big day. @iwantmyname is #startupgrg supporter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If this is any indication of the talent in the room @founderconnz then should be an amazing afternoon. https://t.co/awPfHsLOb9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sulufiti Thanks for sharing the article!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are having issues with your Wellington CBD office space, check out co-working in the northern suburbs @sub_urban2015]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's the brash and opinionated but anti-VC @davemcclure has a plan https://t.co/BJRZg7dKKU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JCE_PC Good old NPBHS. How were they?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nigelmcnie @toby_etc @nzherald But the science is never "done". That's my point. Precuationary self-evacuation should be primary response.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @toby_etc earthquake piece makes some good points but neglects the fact that seismology is not an exact science. https://t.co/zHmx9q4zHC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Subtle &amp; intelligent political statements from artists such as this carry far more weight than silly, theatrical ra… https://t.co/LTy7oNgXI9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gtiso To be fair, there are other 24/7 agencies tasked with assessing tsunami risk and issuing alerts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rafmanji Certainly in the short term at the very least this must be under consideration.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MnstryofAwsm ... with unicorns employing No. 8 wire to punch above our weight, going forward?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SavIsSavvy All ok so far. Minor damage in CBD. Home with kids today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sulufiti @TV3nz It's been all downhill since Campbell left IMO. Targeting the kiddy demographic won't work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deborahjcrowe btw here's the rationale behind my comments :-) https://t.co/Q33jKJ6eez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sulufiti Apparently the sun shines out of his messianic arse and he's @TV3nz last hope for redemption, according to some reviewers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deborahjcrowe I heard it was a great event. Let's make BOP the centre of collaboration ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deborahjcrowe That's great but we actually need to move away from parochialism and start networking innovation nodes. EDAs don't get this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@asherfoster That's right. Damn those swamp people!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New blog: Mrs Clinton Misses https://t.co/ln9TOYUy8s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SavIsSavvy @charlessumner08 I warned you TP's are addictive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to re-launching this meetup. https://t.co/C81i9dy0JJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Renea @ETMOofficial @DevelopsterTeam I'm worried that those stick-kids seem a little bit malnourished]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great article @UCE_NZ explaining @kohknowcolab process &amp; young entrepreneur success. Amazing leadership from @renea https://t.co/SvO4tmGOIK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Working on a project with @SavIsSavvy to whom I owe a debt of gratitude for building bridges &amp; being influential in changing my life design]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solve problems that are "100 miles deep" says @gaijindan and reach customers on an emotional level implores @SavIsSavvy #nzsmj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why we need pragmatic thinking, not fluffy, unfocused positive thinking. https://t.co/0Om7znbW9G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Featuring @NZFinTech @SoftwareNZ @KiwiLandingPad #nzsmj @R9Accelerator @finnotec &amp; more in Tues NZ @StartupDigest https://t.co/4iVt5tUXGT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JennyKayNZ Banning cool label designs definitely nanny state. NZ society fails miserably to inculcate young with social responsibility.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JennyKayNZ That seems more like a parental control issue to me. Modelling responsible social behaviour way more significant IMO :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JennyKayNZ @TheHuiTV3 Of course if she was Republican, you'd be skewering her for lack of action/empathy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More importantly, we need a discrete iottp:// net in order to isolate billions of vulnerable devices from the exist… https://t.co/wnrY3Kn6Np]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SavIsSavvy Yep. We have sooo much to talk about next week!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great place to visit. https://t.co/Ek0fw9mblP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@where_is_anna Touch base with @NakiEcommerce @Taranakichic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just heard that @pledgeme road tour visiting my hometown next week. Heads up @SWTaranaki folks. https://t.co/VfI9SaZdpC #swtaranaki]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexandraheber codeshare partner slots are very clearly indicated when you book @Qantas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidleeWCC @justin_lester Great to see these appointments. Let me know if I can help with community engagement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaylorMooreK @radionz I quite like their approach to "a day of reflection conversation and entertainment" https://t.co/yAVgvjBLwe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaylorMooreK @radionz On the contrary. How delightful it would be to have just one day a year when the media did not mention global wars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bull &amp; Beer. Since kids cannot purchase beer, why are creative label designs an issue? More PC madness. https://t.co/EyIqClplVQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jethrocarr Terrifying when you discover one in a dark, forgotten cupboard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RNZSunday Talking to a Stranger - Hunters &amp; Collectors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Booked my "Kiwi Jam" spot. Always great insights for entrepreneurs around growing globally. #nzsmj https://t.co/ks7MRdYKEC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine running your global business from beautiful Nelson. Meet some folks who do already. https://t.co/jt9aSwe6Pq https://t.co/gmOjt1jP8j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome group of people @VRARNewZealand launch this evening. Made some valuable connections for @Polanyi0 project. #nzvrara]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LozhkaCooking Back in Wellington for now, but have shared with friends in NP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like how Olena Williams is offering ethnic cooking classes with a twist in Taranaki @LozhkaCooking https://t.co/Oig6Ita5R5 #swt2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huge thanks to all of the mentor team who have supported our @SWTaranaki teams brilliantly #swt2016 https://t.co/yb67m4pblP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chairperson of the Startup Weekend Veteran's Association. This is my 20th. https://t.co/mFF3vNsyiT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Validating hypotheses. Please help our scientist entrepreneurs with their online surveys. https://t.co/2UhmJiXlmh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Entrepreneur scientists @SWTaranaki you may find this Startup Weekend toolkit handy. https://t.co/ggjxt1kvko #SWT2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@metservice I think he means machine-readable. @grantsargent https://t.co/0fwKHhio6g Free @niwa_nz but requires user agreement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrisbaneAirport The fashions may have changed, but your arrivals hall still looks like this in 2016 btw.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New blog: Is Lean Thinking Killing Creative Thinking? https://t.co/MZW7DDgkM7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@traceyrcooper Not true. The charges were different in the case you quoted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Energy &amp; Fintech the focus for new accelerator programmes. Nice work @LightningLab @CreativeHQ https://t.co/JrjHOK1wV7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaunmcgirr Immigration box ticking is flawed. We need to move NZ up the value chain. Perhaps she should have got a job in an orchard? ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WCC &amp; Infratil already signed up a Chinese construction firm displaying contempt for consent process &amp; public conce… https://t.co/GJUIIme902]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My favourite time of year. Botanic Gardens looking fab. #WhyWellington https://t.co/jn0ECP8PIN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had fun researching #StarTrek baddies for this article. Classic sci-fi. https://t.co/P6fc0JISPJ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>