<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@CapilanoCourier Speaking of which, you found like the ONE pic of me playing w/o sunglasses. I can't maintain a personal brand like this!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CapilanoCourier @CapilanoU I didn't even know I was nominated. #honoured]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So proud to be living in the city with the world's BEST pickpockets :') https://t.co/vWocjTSiSZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MCPacAsWell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dropthep Be the change you want to see in the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you know John Goodman is in The Emperor's New Groove?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thought I heard somebody's headphones playing metal. 
Looked over and realized it was just an old lady wheeling a basket along the sidewalk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yo @VSOrchestra, what's the name of that last solo piano piece @alexandergavryl played as his encore? It was insane!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEW WEBSITE NEW WEBSITE NEW WEBSITE
https://t.co/XEONSjtfRm
BOOOOOOOM!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Are you waiting for the 210 bus?"
"Yep."
"Did it come by?"
...ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Geektox damn, that's some chops right there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It [possibly] worked!
Super stoked! https://t.co/TaKJiT2hPf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I agree with this. 
@Strange_Fellows  https://t.co/MsIRYTqgh9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I made a very stupid and very hilarious thing last night.
https://t.co/ljvt9ZMRsE
@alienantfarm @SpiceGirlsNet #mashup #whydididothis?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Geektox Ok I'm trusting you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Geektox So it'll work?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @Strange_Fellows, if @cantalooped and I tweet at you enough will you bring back #Goldilox?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gilliandthomson Uh oh... This might happen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You have a hangnail, I have a fungal infection."
#ThingsHeardOnCommercialDrive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gilliandthomson @dropthep Get back on, then help me find six sax tubas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Geektox They're jewel shaped ice cubes cuz I'm a balla.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Submitted my first grant today to try to get #SpaceElevator recorded. Celebrating with @flordecana. Delicious. https://t.co/lFxApLTBBV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dropthep @gilliandthomson Why not six?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gilliandthomson @dropthep Know what else is fun on the King Korg? Literally everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dropthep @gilliandthomson I do indeed know. 1836 I think is when he invented it. 
Fun fact: the first sax he made was the gigantic bass sax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KamasiW Was releasing your album on Brainfeeder, a non-jazz label, a conscious decision to reach a newer non-jazz audience?
#AskKamasi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dropthep You better not be having that Kenny G episode without me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @shootyskies, new update, new font, # of coins clips into the boss gauge if you have enough... https://t.co/YR7iPp3Nkt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Preparing for tonight's #HardRubberOrchestra show by listening to @FaithNoMore 
...that'd probably be a joke for any other big band composer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@theResidents playing in #Vancouver tonight. 
No one knows their identities. Wonder how many people have run into them without knowing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #HardRubberOrchestra led by @KorsrudJohn is playing one of my compositions. 
It's gonna be rad. 
#BigBandMetal https://t.co/uX6WHOiRKF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got a very large saxophone yesterday. It is beautiful. 

#basssax https://t.co/pfPYMSOpmQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eddylumedia I was right on both accounts, weirdly enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From a rehearsal for #SpaceElevator's show last month. 
#music #jazzmetal #bigbandmetal #jazz 
https://t.co/1awj9SLVjk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Geektox the bad part is this isn't even the worst.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok @MeekMill we only got two days to beef before the concert. 
We gotta get this going!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dropthep Nope, it was all for you. 
Sorry @VancityBuzz &amp; @CJSF, next time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to @CJSF_Arts for letting me go on their show and talk about myself forever. And origami.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feb 11
Crazy experimental big band concert I'm putting on at @FoxCabaret 
https://t.co/y1FtZtR93Z
@MeekMill this is what we're beefing about]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm trying to promote a concert. 
Hey @MeekMill, wanna beef?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Geektox Drink more and see if you can cause another one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JKCorden can you post the footage of @reggiewatts belting out "Ironic" after you guys finished? THAT'S the highlight for me!
@latelateshow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obligatory Tweet about #stupid Richmond #stupid morning #stupid @Jimmy_Sax's students

Gotta keep up traditions, eh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haha it's a joke! Nobody gets tired of free-jazz!
#EasyListening am I right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I just need a break from free-jazz, you know?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just saw a little kid dressed as Santa with a machete in his mouth, super weird. 

Halloween is TOMORROW, kid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don't kill people. It's just too much trouble for what it's worth."
The advice I give my students in their lessons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My phone just tried to auto-correct a typo into an emoji...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fred Durst feat. Matty B Raps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @CrossyRoad, just spent 5100g (that's 51 tries) on the prize machine and still didn't get any new characters. 
Glitch? Or terrible luck?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just saw a bird and plane in the sky. They looked significantly different from each other. Neither could've been mistaken for a flying man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Geektox Waaaaaait, I don't recall having SoundCloud automatically post to my Twitter... Although it IS a very good #sound]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My new sounds: Cap'n Crunch https://t.co/GSCMOhliGg on #SoundCloud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You always see lost dog posters with the gender of the pet but do they ever consider what gender the dog IDENTIFIES as?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know what's even better than pop music?
10 year olds singing pop music.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is for @Geektox 
#wert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had an 11 hour rehearsal yesterday. It was exhausting. Good thing today only has 13 hours of teaching, recording, and performing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching @TheMuppets videos while waiting for things to finish exporting. 
This is what we call "work" in the film business.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Geektox where is this from? I feel like I should see this movie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Played jazz and punk rock for two different bands at two different shows last night. 
Gotta love being an open minded musician.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Geektox its the best jam.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Geektox @ItsKyleMc They were incredible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @weirdestband, the other night my sqwonk-noise band #KeyToAbyss opened for Weirdest Band golden boy @a_n_p 
It was incredible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Geektox you already know the answer to that question.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got this album not knowing what it was. Turns out it is shredding solo classical #accordion. Stoked! http://t.co/f6cSQr5mnM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EyesofErin @Geektox If it ever actually happens, yes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Geektox, @EyesofErin is always arguing about stuff. She would probably fit in well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Geektox we could have a podcast where we just argue about stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From one of those toy vending machines: That is Lego Superman and Lego Spider-Man. Both welding guns. http://t.co/C6a0MxhJN7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Geektox and not wussy BotB like judges vote for you, no, you gotta be better than the other band. 
Faster. Louder. Crazier. Out play them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Geektox Ok 100% serious can we do this? There's been a few that have tried, but let's do it here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Geektox I would get home, I would smell it, then I would immediately turn around and go to Subway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fun fact: @CBCVancouver and I are Twitter BFFs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Geektox @CBCVancouver What do you guys think?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today I'm recording at @100Powell for @JoshRamsay 
Am I a famous studio musician now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @CBCVancouver says I'm a celebrity then it must be true. 
You heard it here first, folks! https://t.co/JptixgxEde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eddylureport @CBCVancouver It's official. I guess I can start referring to myself as "Mike Allen, Celebrity"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just did a short interview for @CBCVancouver with @VVagabonds 
Am I a rockstar yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coastaljazz I also see nothing on the website... What are the dates?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spongebob is the only fry cook at the Krusty Krab, so how does he walk into work so many times where people are already eating?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, I don't think I've ever been happier to see someone get off a bus. 
That's the end of tonight's episode of #ShittyBusRapper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dude is literally just yelling shit on the bus and rhyming a couple words every so often. 
#ShittyBusRapper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, don't clap for him, you'll encourage him to keep going.
#ShittyBusRapper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or maybe it's Italian? Hard to tell, he's very drunk. 
#ShittyBusRapper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now he's rapping in Spanish?
#ShittyBusRapper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember that bad freestyle rapper from a few days ago? He's rapping at me now. Still bad. Still loud. Mostly bad. #buslife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I typo'd while typing "check" and wrote "ceck" which my phone then autocorrected, not to "check" but to "McDicks" 
Cuz why not, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never mind, the best part of Top 5 was @DMX singing. Wow. Just wow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best part about Top 5 is @JerrySeinfeld in a strip club. #OutOfYourElement]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dude's been freestyle rapping (badly and loudly) on the bus now for about 10 minutes straight. #buslife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why were these the suggested hashtags on my last tweet? http://t.co/2m5DIU1Rh7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[D'Angelo cannot be properly hashtag'd. 
Not sure if this is a genius move or a foolish one...
#D'Angelo? #DAngelo? Wrong!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@KorsrudJohn's Hard Rubber Orchestra once again blew me away today. Bought the new album and loving it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess Nickelback is Maroon 5 now...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just released on Postmodern Records

http://t.co/U4llnuzPd9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I found a bunch of song stems online... Then this happened... Not sure if I should be proud of myself...
 https://t.co/3fNjDJAIcx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My new sounds: The Dumbest Thing I've Ever Done https://t.co/4A2ApRTNgw on #SoundCloud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gosh, it really is too bad about this whole #MacklemoreJoinedISIS thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a busker downtown playing Wonderwall on his guitar. 
I didn't think people actually did that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Ok but music isn't actually WORK, right?"
Nope, that's why I'm still working on this soundtrack at 7am.
Totally not "work". All fun &amp; games]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>