<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Touching. https://t.co/u1vVaJBFAF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bopmafia yep. Couldn't help but laud his decision while it was working but in retrospect you gotta back the no11 to get a single.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bopmafia I don't reckon it really mattered. He would've hit it for 6 if he wanted. But only wanted one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bopmafia yep definitely felt like that last ball of that over was pretty much the crucial one. Glad Kane finally took a chance!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never seen someone shielded from the strike so well. It was bound to end appalingly but still impressive stuff… https://t.co/rp63yXKMsY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You guys need to get the guy involved in the next commentary @TheACCnz so goddamn bloody close! https://t.co/36Ao5CageH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuxGolfToursNZ @heelturn Yeah probably. How and why can a team be so inconsistent?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heelturn @LuxGolfToursNZ you've been decidedly quiet lately Rauru. Head in the sand?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryans_Rovers @Yakcall called either 1-1 or 2-1 on Facebook but didn't back it with cash.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryans_Rovers @Yakcall I was slightly chicken shit and took the 0.5 goal start. Paying $1.95 though - ridiculous value.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryans_Rovers didn't realise it was that bad but I agree. Already got on the jets who are surprising underdogs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outstanding hashtag. #stopbeINshit
Sorry for the spam of all the retweets but this needs coverage. https://t.co/Sp891dTpMw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Football/sports lovers please read and share. Paying customers being shafted and worst of all not communicated to https://t.co/wBlejzv4Xu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heelturn @LuxGolfToursNZ good banter. Amazingly untrue though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heelturn @LuxGolfToursNZ yeah I just got pipped against top of the table. Shouldn't have played Martial over Herrera.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heelturn @LuxGolfToursNZ great news. Haven't seen the incident. Not sure I want to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heelturn @LuxGolfToursNZ wholly shit. Hadn't heard so just googled. Awful stuff. Freaky.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heelturn @LuxGolfToursNZ ha I'll be doing you a favour this week. Pegging those leaders back. #muppets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Salvatori_ didn't know you were a cricketer though could have guessed. Our Last Man Stands team often plays Liardet Street. Wed nights]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuxGolfToursNZ @heelturn Chelsea, Tottenham, Liverpool, Man United.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuxGolfToursNZ @heelturn the good thing is its unlikely City will make it. The bad news is Liverpool probably will. And I'll lose our bet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuxGolfToursNZ @heelturn now we're talking mate. Much better. Might be overused but it genuinely is different this time. Arrogance is back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuxGolfToursNZ @heelturn still on holiday aye? A bit bored? Your troll game is pretty weak.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuxGolfToursNZ @heelturn absolutely. Next season. Further strengthening in squad, year under belt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuxGolfToursNZ @heelturn I only have one answer. And it's not going to be a surprise to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuxGolfToursNZ @heelturn yeah that was a week ago. Leeeeet iiiit gooooo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hopefully 3 games, 8 days, 9 points! https://t.co/f9hOeVwMaz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuxGolfToursNZ @heelturn I didn't even bother clicking the link. Seriously who cares who would make Klopps Liverpool team. Not me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heelturn @LuxGolfToursNZ we're only half way through the season. My team is about to hit its straps.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heelturn @LuxGolfToursNZ haha we all know you'd be attrocious. Dugout is a pretty good indicator of that, then add the fact it's rugby.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuxGolfToursNZ @heelturn Yeah I saw that yesterday too and had exactly sane thought. I'm keenish. If someone else is commissioner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beINSPORTS_NZ @_Salvatori_ I can't believe how awful your service is BeIN. What an absolute nightmare for paying customers. Up your game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRealBozza @adampeacock3 @YellowFever_NZ do we still bring nothing to the league Mark? xng]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuxGolfToursNZ @heelturn well, press and counter. Pool didn't create as many clear chances so gutting from my perspective. Wanted 3!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heelturn @LuxGolfToursNZ harsh mate. It had a level of intensity I haven't seen in a while. Pool relying on counter did affect game though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuxGolfToursNZ fair enough. No messages from me either way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuxGolfToursNZ Yeah ok. Should be straight forward for Mou but you just never know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuxGolfToursNZ guess that's a chance with your keepers but I'm picking a one goal margin. Man U to win 2-1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuxGolfToursNZ I can't see a smashing either way. It's going to be tight. Very interested in both starting line ups.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuxGolfToursNZ Yep which is why I'm feeling the pressure. A win is like triple value. Beat pool. Points for table. And Pool lose. #ideal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuxGolfToursNZ shit really? How the tide has turned. We need 3 and 3 only. Time to really step up Zlatan!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuxGolfToursNZ yup. Massive. Really hope it doesn't fizzle into another bore nil nil (&amp; yes I'm aware if that happens it'll be coz of Jose)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryans_Rovers I guess. Just that hit rate is pretty low. First time all season I've seen him do anything. And it was CCM. Rather some youth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryans_Rovers seems more than a rumour. How/why everyone so confident? Just cause family moved? If gone, much point playing him now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryans_Rovers @pineyzb what's the deal with Roly? Seems well accepted he's off to Melb City next season but nothing official? @NZPhotomac]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryans_Rovers @pineyzb drop barbarouses. I don't care how much he's on. He's been pants.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuxGolfToursNZ @heelturn just watched spurs ext highlights. Pretty impressive. Kane could've scored 6! McAuley had a nightmare.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heelturn @LuxGolfToursNZ but just checked and Jerry has incomplete team so his 'win' over league leader will be wasted. Idiot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heelturn @LuxGolfToursNZ happy to talk dugout. Giving the brofessors a right old spanking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuxGolfToursNZ @heelturn cool. Good to know. Ta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuxGolfToursNZ @heelturn how you guys catch highlights? I'll be waiting until highlights show at 10am.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heelturn @LuxGolfToursNZ Yeah, guess we wait to see what Zlatan does now - might match him...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heelturn @LuxGolfToursNZ nah haven't seen yet, but yes social media tells me you're not bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heelturn @LuxGolfToursNZ although every other player listed failed and almost all I brought in scored, so far so good. Hatty but only 14?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hailcheaters @FPLStatto @artemidorus_1 I had to wildcard. Had Payet, Costa, Walcott, Son, Milner, Kane. Now this.… https://t.co/K0W1T0FJEs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heelturn @LuxGolfToursNZ it's done. Wildcard gone. Team was a shambles. Payet, Costa, Walcott, Son, Milner, Kane. Had too happen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heelturn @LuxGolfToursNZ just looked and wouldn't have affected my sell price anyway. Was 10.7, down to 10.6, I get 10.3 either way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heelturn @LuxGolfToursNZ shit did he actually drop. I hadn't got around to actually doing anything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is me. Except I can't grow a beard. https://t.co/psrNWCoPD1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heelturn @LuxGolfToursNZ that wild card is very tempting. I'm not so against using it. Understand DGW use but that's not everything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heelturn @LuxGolfToursNZ I've only done the one. But have Payet and Costa so will be some late research tonight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heelturn @LuxGolfToursNZ this Liverpool ain't as free flowing anymore. Not convinced about Costa just yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heelturn @LuxGolfToursNZ bus parking? Get with the times mate. Jose had moved on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heelturn @LuxGolfToursNZ Haha good luck beating Arsenal for the first time in a hundred years. Loser.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuxGolfToursNZ to be clear. I'm not saying he'd necessarily go and buy him. But in his squad he'd laud the availability of such a man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuxGolfToursNZ think Klopp would find a way to get quality use of Ibra. And not to detriment of Mane, Firminho, Coutinho or Lallana.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuxGolfToursNZ aside from being a barf-inducing wank fest I get the point, and it's hard to argue with the scoring record, but I still...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuxGolfToursNZ @heelturn yeah but you don't think Klopp is that inflexible do u? I get he has a 'way' but he could fit Pog &amp; Ibra 4 the +'s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuxGolfToursNZ @heelturn don't even try to compare Sturridge/Origi with Ibra. Now who's having a laugh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuxGolfToursNZ @heelturn cannot wait. Same for Pog Sure team built around him, but we'll worth it. Tell me Klopp couldn't work with that 11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuxGolfToursNZ @heelturn I'd love that question to be asked of Klopp. I honestly cannot see him declining. He is mobile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuxGolfToursNZ @heelturn Ibra is not some aging immobile has-been. He's an amazing all-round striker who almost any team would have.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuxGolfToursNZ @heelturn Fair point to a degree although I personally don't think you could leave out either Pogba or Ibra. No matter mgr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuxGolfToursNZ Carrick; Henderson (tough on Herrera), Pogba; Mkhitaryan, Coutinho, Lallana; Ibrahimovic 
Cc @heelturn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuxGolfToursNZ thoughts? Midfield is tough. Assuming no Mane and Bailly (AfCoN) I'd go De Gea; Valencia, Matip, Jo… https://t.co/COQmIfghlY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FOXSportsAUS hi any chance of Smeltz being added to fantasy A-League? He's already played a game yet still not ava… https://t.co/bHGU1bCovO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FPL_Fly @artemidorus_1 @hailcheaters @FPLStatto so maybe somehow multiplying points scored by inverse table position. So Chelsea = ×20??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FPL_Fly @artemidorus_1 @hailcheaters @FPLStatto yeah that's probably fair. Statistically need to perform against 'top' teams.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good stuff as usual fellas. Still reckon we need someone to create us a "fixture proof" measure. Defoe vs. Aguero? https://t.co/TRLMcgPJmW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heelturn good way to look at it. Embrace being a selling club.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FOXFOOTBALL hey when will Smeltz be added to fantasy A-League?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryans_Rovers @wibblebutt @wellywolf @kyle_barnes15 @patrick478 you're welcome Patrick!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heelturn Yeah sounds like cover for CB, wing back and CM.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heelturn @NickGoodall_ nah I'd rid. Can always get back in. His value will drop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heelturn @LuxGolfToursNZ I'm pretty comfy without him. Apparently you'll keep all four but next time you txfr one trfr has to be CHE player]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuxGolfToursNZ @heelturn toyed with wild card the other day (1 Jan). This is what I came up with. https://t.co/aEY3kXW5La]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hailcheaters thoughts on Giroud and Alli/Eriksen?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Salvatori_ @LeighboNZ @KloppGoff @AndrewGourdie @liam_hyslop @pineyzb @beINSPORTS_NZ that's a start!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeighboNZ @KloppGoff @AndrewGourdie @liam_hyslop @pineyzb @_Salvatori_ @beINSPORTS_NZ yeah surely someone can get a better answer than that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone able to do some serious questioning? @AndrewGourdie @liam_hyslop @pineyzb @KloppGoff just didn't make any se… https://t.co/HRR0Zho1I0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuxGolfToursNZ @heelturn especially for leagues third best defence aye?! ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheACCnz how was ACC head grot Lane not included in the three though?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heelturn @LuxGolfToursNZ terrible management picking a bunch of injured dudes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heelturn I guess rotation. But Rashford hadn't been that good of late. Lingard had actually been decent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heelturn hey just evening it all up. Zlatan should have had a goal allowed the other day. Plenty of reds gotten away with (incl. Rojo!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuxGolfToursNZ @heelturn Haha pretty much the albatross of facing stupid free kicks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Salvatori_ @beINSPORTS_NZ @skysportnz @p_l_pass yep 'fraid I have to agree. Initially liked having back on satellite but now not so much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heelturn @LuxGolfToursNZ yeah rough on someone in a bad pad patch due to injuries. We need something to change to catch bloody Bryce!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heelturn @LuxGolfToursNZ yeah what's the dudes name going to City? How do the Jan transfers work for in Dugout?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heelturn @LuxGolfToursNZ bloody tempting though aye. My squad needs a refresh, but I'm getting by.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>