<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Big pizza slices ! The ones we eat at the Jersey Shore aren't usually this big....but almost! ;) https://t.co/3b1rLeACVc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just looking at this makes me want to..... (Insert) https://t.co/E31MRTWxf4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A big thanks to Di @ https://t.co/4EFGGAJTLp and Michele Redmond @Taste_Workshop for the shoutout. Check out... https://t.co/SOx36P2TXJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to Di, a dietitian based in Canada who blogs at https://t.co/4EFGGAJTLp for this shoutout. https://t.co/TNq1mjzi6u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Special occasion resto that will surprise and amaze: Papilles et Insolites, rue Alexander Taylor. https://t.co/ONxJfOdSxi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Special lunch at Papilles et Insolites, rue Alexander Taylor in Pau. If you get to Pau you must eat here. Today's... https://t.co/e4LqGD35Qd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are free Sat evening , check this out ;)! https://t.co/uj22JdNufv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Second friend leading a cool workshop. This one on writing and set in Italy this summer. One of the staff is my... https://t.co/XYAIsrwEBQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scottsdale foodie friends -check out this knife skills workshop taught by my friend Michele Redmond, a very... https://t.co/riGmkv1LmP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See something wrong here? https://t.co/VHbxc2sxGi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These are ADORABLE https://t.co/OnQIMI7HNA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is why we need artists, especially during times of human and economic crisis. It also gets me angry when I... https://t.co/uOSd6nmItg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes- prices too over the top expensive and my personal opinion: too many people prescribed and take medicines as... https://t.co/iG8YBUgTrZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Written from France but about health, food, wellness.   https://t.co/K6duDmEqaC -check it out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My son's 16th birthday cake request was a fruit tart /cake from the bakery. Too bad this picture doesn't show its... https://t.co/n6gE3rWSVd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad for saucisson lovers in France, but I had to happen: France just changed health recommendations to decrease... https://t.co/N3qzNFUgdd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks a lot to @dianamchard and @Taste_Workshop. Can't wait to see your new blog Michele! https://t.co/2LPHCkK0WE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most Medical Doctors lack nutrition knowledge; this is why dietitians are the nutritional experts ;) https://t.co/O9TzFylbmN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[France health agency changed their recommendations to reduce meat intake, specifically sausages and other cured... https://t.co/aEpuQZxHA5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I woke up and felt unstabled. I go to sleep feeling hopeful. Not one of my friends here on FB read my call and... https://t.co/mzNOG9SJRK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MMFlint thx Michael- I'm an American living in France- watching from the 'sidelines' but w/U all where it counts. We adore U in France.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We love Canada and I have never met a Canadian I didn't like. It is just so fxxking cold there in the winter. https://t.co/Xi1J25UYep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday was #WorldHolocaustDay. https://t.co/J4kjkyfTfi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love my Italian friends.... https://t.co/Me7atrH0rP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too many of you to tag! Dear English friends that live (or especially have retired) in France and Spain please... https://t.co/wd7SeMo5bT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@louloufrance I absolutely agree....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sigh. https://t.co/PasTgcAYMO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aromatic Stir-Fry - Tasty, Budget-Friendly https://t.co/jxqL63DKqC via @NutriSavvyGal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a useful article on how to cut spaghetti squash easily ! https://t.co/iLF1FzJQi9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you pay taxes you have a right to know what your money is funded for - and this includes research results on... https://t.co/urBlTCBMXE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you pay taxes you have a right to know what your money is funded for - and this includes research results on... https://t.co/1cPG9V7HBk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This month's recipe challenge and newest recipe on the blog: how to cook a meal for less than 3$ a serving. I... https://t.co/QIFLih28kp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Future goal: volunteer in a food bank to help families to use their food 'efficiently'. It is possible to eat... https://t.co/v4HvGbcsO7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vegetarian French Onion Soup https://t.co/bItgF7z1MM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whatever you think of his dad, negative comments about kids are off limits. He is 10 years old and didn't ask for... https://t.co/UEdXFQ7po7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#womensmarch #womensmarchwashington – attending Women's March followed by Candlelight Vigil in Toulouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EllAyLech thinking of you - with you 100% ! Be strong &lt;3!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will be with you all in spirit. Going to a global march with my two daughters, in solidarity with #womensmarch . https://t.co/ENt7fIHyxt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And I told you portion sizes were BIG in America ;) https://t.co/G7RHGhIlH5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WomensMarchWednesday Eleanor Roosevelt - and your female inspiration ? Share with hashtag #WomensMarchWednesday https://t.co/FS4i780jQO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Famous Faces Joining The Women’s March on Washington https://t.co/IoIbk2Ye2e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My 10 year old offered to make dinner- big hit- we shopped together for the mini pizzas- whole wheat English... https://t.co/xV94Sa6Tlv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's be kind. Everyone is going thru their own 'secret' struggle. https://t.co/DfSz65PH3E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is my friend's sweet dog, her name is Colleen. It was cold during our powerwalk, tomorrow will even be... https://t.co/D2s2egY5Hg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In honor of International Italian Cuisine Day: how to make an authentic Bolognese sauce -from Bologna https://t.co/1H5BJSaICC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will be in spirit with everyone who is participating worldwide....everyone: women, men, of all races, religions... https://t.co/mub8C8Ddrh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A common Twitter mistake from reading too fast and retweeting by error...something that might Brighton Your Day... https://t.co/YJ5EnXIfEw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was looking at obesity trends in the US and found this statistic (2013-2014 data): 70.7 % of adults are... https://t.co/NwFtKMBzOV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My 2017 professional goal: write a guide book on how to encourage and provide hungry teenagers a feeding... https://t.co/dve45KnJE4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last night I made Pot au Feu using poitrine de boeuf. (Beef stew/soup using beef brisket .) I cooked 3 pieces of... https://t.co/vghC42Dj4u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're In? You're In? (Urine, Urine). 
This sketch is so funny I almost you're in - ated. https://t.co/H0LFIred3S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a great food blog I follow. Here's Donal making dog biscuits for Max. His dog arrived yesterday to LA to... https://t.co/oEC1kC6Y6e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pau is gorgeous, especially when the Pyrenees look like a footprint 👣 away. Happy Friday 13th. Always a lucky day... https://t.co/akVouVGJQH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friday 13th....wishing you a lucky day. In Italy, 13 is a lucky number- it's my favorite too. To make you feel... https://t.co/9ldIbnf0VY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kurteichenwald Bravo....continue ! We need you :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Influenza epidemic in France. No offense on the culture of 'Les Bises' (cheek kisses) but maybe we should all... https://t.co/uGLmdLiauV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's newsletter about fake (nutrition) news and fad diets. Thanks   @ColoradoStateU (top nutrition... https://t.co/JiRb18RzvT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[False Nutrition News and Fad Diets https://t.co/TTBESF2S64]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[False Nutrition News and Fad Diets - https://t.co/8QNNzQqNUc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who likes finding the fève charm more than eating the Kings Cake? I can't be the only one. https://t.co/WkCFASNwXi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[French or New Orleans style ? (or both!) Galette Des Rois French Kings Cake Has Delicious Traditions  https://t.co/VHCsKPhwwZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[{New Article} Heading over to France before January 31st? You still have time to taste French Kings Cake, but the... https://t.co/iazdBP4mnd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sharing updated security info for the Women's March in Washington DC on Jan 21st. https://t.co/QkZXIigoSi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was just checking stats on my blog and saw that BrightonYourHealth has nearly a MILLION visitors since it... https://t.co/jvUiDIzrne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goûter ~ Snack time in France. What a difference 2 minutes, a beignet, café and canele makes! Chez Paul.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to mon amie Lynda Corazza whose book will be published in September! Bravissima https://t.co/0dxDizztRE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want a good laugh? Check out this piece from Comedy Central on food in America :... https://t.co/EMOOhQPEQB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NPRFood @NPR This is happening where I live in Pau, France too. Fantastic idea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheese good for you? The French would agree- drink a glass of red and you have all bases covered. https://t.co/VZHQZJv1Bk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing is better than Italian caffe. Need a mini lesson? Check out 'come preparare il caffé' https://t.co/NbmccHyLMv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Media reporting today on a link between Roundup (Monsanto) and liver disease in rats. Note that the main... https://t.co/yckUFOnJCR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A beautiful blog and this recipe sounds delicious. I am happy that butternut squash is now available in France. https://t.co/cowvRir8VS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally making this! https://t.co/EEUogaNeCy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A very talented friend of mine who illustrates and writes in her daily experiences with ADHD. Check out her site... https://t.co/R7jntHZVID]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Galette Des Rois French Kings Cake Has Delicious Traditions https://t.co/VHCsKPhwwZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adorable. Thanks Leen for this one ;) https://t.co/GvW3UJeump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mystery- can anyone help? https://t.co/3U7ty2ZtEC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Americans spent more than 3 trillion dollars on healthcare and life expectancy lowered despite this huge... https://t.co/T5eYW8BIPj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the blog : New Year’s Resolutions: Focus On The Why For Successful Change WHY and HOW here:  https://t.co/DzF6rwACj6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the archives: Focus on your mission statement to keep those New Year's resolutions. Why -How? Check out how... https://t.co/aYxxTbxW6e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This goes to show you that anything is possible and age is only a number ! Bravo Mr. Marchand! https://t.co/rFX8RZKJtp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I also think Mike will stand up and get back on the ice again, and this dad's story will fill your heart and eyes... https://t.co/9qWbV1AxFe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Pau and Bearn peeps: in the process to organize a 18th birthday party for my oldest for the end of May. We... https://t.co/fFySfBdide]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is fantastic- a https://t.co/WbxzgUhkXg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After 2+ weeks of eating heavy, this raw fennel, lemon, red onion, feta salad tasted fresh. Perfect mix for a well… https://t.co/brAfKu0ONx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad news - 13 year-old French girl dies from the flu on Saturday night, after being at the emergency room the day... https://t.co/EMnqmdbICT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Istanbul last night : 35 dead and 40 wounded in an gun attack in a nightclub. No words :-( Thinking of the... https://t.co/dcx5h5yion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An excellent idea to decrease #foodwaste and #hunger. Freeshop France, a box has been set up in #Pau. Leave food,... https://t.co/EvahMktNlM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent idea that I hope can inspire fir other towns: a Freeshop France box has been set up by cours Bosquet in... https://t.co/SaEt2UXZmP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best way : in pain perdu - French toast.... https://t.co/his0yRIzqi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good info on bringing cheese back in America from France. Thank you Wendy Lyn https://t.co/20Z2pd0ukv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wishing you all a very joyous holiday and Merry Christmas. https://t.co/q8o1hfs6W4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[French Front National extreme right party asking Russian banks to fund her campaign for French presidential... https://t.co/mSUgmPqBFn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need a present for a foodie that loves outdoors? I am definitely pre-ordering this book: it's written by my dear... https://t.co/HIZ4R6EBRl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@frasermatthew @guardian I follow /respect @kurteichenwald - what happened is unforgivable. Happy he's pushing for consequences 4 this act.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump American living in France, French pity me because of you. I'm embarrassed/disappointed everyday. U say it best: Sad! Wrong!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nytimes I needed to see this tonight. Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_AaronKlein_ meaning I love the nickname ! Not him!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_AaronKlein_ love trumpty dumpty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nprscottsimon I live in France&amp;attest that French chocolates are très bons!+shout out to NPR, I download your news /listen on pwrwalks,THX]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>