<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm missing some clothes, at least three pairs of pants, and it's frustrating the hell out of me. I've looked everywhere at home at 3am.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I liked a @YouTube video https://t.co/85WBfY7Iks Waxing Presidential With The Late Show Road Show]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I liked a @YouTube video https://t.co/VARPkyCwwd The Tonight Show Starring Johnny Carson: 06/07/1977...Tom Snyder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever feel tired, but can't sleep?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope with the upcoming snow in Vancouver, Christmas comes with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think if you're over 13, one should comport themselves knowing that wrestling isn't real.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the cab to work, I spotted a local TV anchor walking on Main street. They're not as tall as they appear on television.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisgailus Were you on GDNY when Jim Ryan and that reporter started arguing on the air?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I tend to think the stakes are different, so perhaps one can vote yes one time &amp; another no. Then again, it can also be political.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it a legitimate point to say, because a senator confirmed a judge for a lower court, they ought to do the same for a higher court?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's my interview with Tim Carlson of @Conspiracy_Now on Foreign Radical opening Monday at Studio 1398: https://t.co/hxvfOh5gIH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's with all the Yiddish Ryan Gosling uses in La La Land?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I talk to @Conspiracy_Now's Tim Carlson about Foreign Radical opening Monday at Studio 1398: https://t.co/hxvfOgNFk7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's an old Webster! from 1982 that includes @RafeMair &amp; @GordieHogg: https://t.co/EnhIIQQZtw #bcpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to @LizSmth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gee, it's cold out, eh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JillKrop Why don't the @GlobalBC reporters say which city they're in when they say "Global News." The guy in Kelowna does.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought after the age of 11, people weren't supposed to eat chicken strips. Well, I did but they were from Juke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think Trump wanted a hug. https://t.co/ezQnZnbV4U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theArtsClub I emailed about arranging an interview regarding the Audience. Would that be possible to arrange?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lidsville I saw a list online either this morning or late last night. Can't remember where or who had it though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another winner from @bychrischeung; a piece on Kingsgate Mall: https://t.co/hT6SKacDNL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've read Peter O'Neil's work for many years &amp; only got to know him recently. He's as good a reporter as he is nice. I'm sorry to see him go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was fun taking a look back with Dave Gerry on his 40-year career in TV. Talented guy; nice guy too: https://t.co/Vr3YawFcV5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aren't all the same people upset at CTV for firings &amp; switching to Global, the same ones who switched over when they fired people last year?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The great Dave Gerry reflects on a 40-year career in television: https://t.co/Vr3YawWOjF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Half time at Cavalia's Odysseo. It's been quite entertaining so far. #OdysseoYVR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@poneilinOttawa @VancouverSun Sorry to hear this, Peter. All the best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm at lunch and the waiter says highballs are $3...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidpball @AndreaWoo Yeah! But also I think we're all learning, the consumer &amp; the journalist and it's good to see evolution if any.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndreaWoo Yes, because very often in one's opinion you can see how knowledgeable they are on a subject.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I talked to @docdanielle about her new book Better Now: Six Big Ideas to Improve Health Care for All Canadians: https://t.co/mc1kMwBVbR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sorry to hear about Coleen Christie being let go from CTV. Always a class act at the news desk. https://t.co/lwWfAfynPe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BreakingChesky Does that mean you won't be on Sundays with @MichelleKOMO anymore?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FDR by Jo Davidson. Roosevelt was born this day in 1882. https://t.co/3mJwvyg7Xc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmv Probably not anytime soon. I can't see how one would look good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[eBay sent an email saying they've found a John Adams bust for sale cheaper than I had expected. I'm debating whether to buy it now...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A favourite Lily Tomlin film is the wonderful The Late Show with Art Carney.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As good as Hidden Figures is, I think the SAG award for best cast should've gone to Moonlight, even Captain Fantastic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fionamorrow It's a parody account.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People decrying fake news have also retweeted @DenaldJTrumpJr tonight, adding their own commentary not realising it… https://t.co/pFIDBzOr9W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SunCivicLee All the best, Jeff!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And no, I will not be drinking booze from a plastic bottle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm at the local No Frills. I do wish it had a frill or two.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been sitting at Manitoba &amp; 1st for the last 15 mins. One guy's come up saying I'll, "never beat us." Whatever the hell that means]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I heard Emmanuelle Riva died. Did the husband have anything to do with it? I hope it wasn't anything like in Amour.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just saw someone with a white cane, looking at their phone. Can we use white canes for texting now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such layers to this story. And so many questions still. https://t.co/BhsZjrFXYC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am I the only one thinking about brunch right now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Natalie Clancy report on a paramedic on the front line of the drug crisis is riveting stuff. https://t.co/hIXlhDdHVf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@i_on_food_drink @smh I used rollerballs for years but prefer fountain pens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought HMV had already closed in Canada years ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theArtsClub I'm just following up on a couple of emails I sent Amy on the 10th &amp; 18th requesting an interview. Did they not go through?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy birthday, @HowardMortman  (Hat tip: Politico's Playbook.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I knew that second cup of coffee yesterday afternoon was a bad idea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JLewisGlobal @GlobalBC Best of luck!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheAaronChapman Thanks Aaron; I appreciate it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yvrblogger Thank you, Peter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The funeral for Nestor Planta is tomorrow at 11am at St Patrick's. My uncle was a remarkable guy https://t.co/JQySoOdvdR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keithbaldrey Millard Fillmore. Ran again in 1856 for the Know Nothing Party.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keithbaldrey Trivia: What 3 presidents had failed third-party runs after their presidencies?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BobKronbauer @Lazin_Ryder Did you stop buying pizza from 2007 on? And why?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is an appropriate and timely tribute to Mary Tyler Moore. https://t.co/P3LwH2P1YZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's the consensus on Donald Trump's signature? Hate or like?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tintie4 @simisara980 Found this clip: https://t.co/HtCCQ6gMA2 Swoosie Kurtz was on it too. Dave hated this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tintie4 @simisara980 She tried her hand at variety like Carol Burnett and Keaton &amp; Dave were part of the cast. Bombed unfortunately.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maxfawcett Do you shout out questions as you watch?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBCVancouver @AndrewChangCBC @JWagstaffe @BIVnews They look like they're debating each other.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, if I go to Butchart Gardens, I can't use my selfie stick while dressed in old-timey clothes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a big fan of @MayorStewart. He's shown great leadership on a number of files.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tintie4 @simisara980 It was a rough time. After MTM ended she tried 2 other shows that didn't quite, 1 that had Michael Keaton &amp; Letterman.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tintie4 @simisara980 Her son Richard died just after the film came out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the fare box is covered in a yellow bag (out of order), I shouldn't have to tap my Compass Card. @TransitPolice?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@astrachanphoto I was hoping for something like We Have a Pope, which even though was amusing was insightful about how the Vatican works.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@astrachanphoto I've always thought critics ought to have their criticism reviewed by other critics, even audiences.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@astrachanphoto I had high hopes, because I thought it would be interesting about the church; and I liked Youth too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I saw the first episode of The Young Pope. Do I need to watch the others? I feel like I'm not missing much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheImusShow You see this from The Simpsons last week? O'Reilly's Killing Hannity book: https://t.co/fldAy9NMLx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where my monocle at?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jenn It is. It's a parody account. I'm CSR at Busters and that's certainly not a sentiment the company has.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jenn @Busters_Towing @VanMayorsOffice That isn't a real Busters Towing account.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The acclaimed pianist Vicky Choiw is with @musiconmain for @PuShFestival tonight. Here's our chat on her work &amp; more https://t.co/JlxY25Ts2q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In this podcast I refer to Fences as being set in Baltimore. Fences is set in Pittsburgh. I apologise for the error… https://t.co/2rsuLE1LFR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winston Churchill died this day in 1965. I interviewed biographer Paul Reid about him 4 years ago: https://t.co/Im6ss7zAVk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I finally got around to seeing Captain Fantastic. It's outstanding, Mortensen &amp; the children are wonderful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The t-bone steak waitress in Hell of High Water, Margaret Bowman ought to be as well known as the chicken salad one in Five Easy Pieces.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really like seeing Anna Maria Tremonti on @CBCVancouver right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got off the phone with Danielle Martin. Her new book Better Now is a highly readable, urgent book on healthcare https://t.co/NeUUkaUGs3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I talk to @vcpianos about her appearances @PuShFestival tonight &amp; tomorrow: https://t.co/JlxY25Ts2q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two P's in a Podcast returns with @jackiepierre &amp; @Planta talking about stuff: https://t.co/8fedOPQb2Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was Tuesday Weld born on a Tuesday? Did she have a sister named Wednesday?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great film performance overlooked in recent weeks is Stephen McKinley Henderson's in Fences.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one's taken me up on my bet that Ryan Gosling won't get nominated for an Oscar on Tuesday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, I can't wait for #5. Though it'll be a long one, because he's going to do the whole presidency in one volume.… https://t.co/BiB3mNYMDA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emma Thompson's two Oscars were both presented to her by Anthony Hopkins. Rigged!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[30 years ago Budd Dwyer shot himself to death on live television. I've never seen the film. It's on youtube if you're inclined.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Legal question: Do the recent presidential pardons have an effect on future sentences for similar crimes i.e. changing legal precedence?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Garossino I thought so too, but I think she was just following the tradition that Michelle Obama started.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Garossino Why's the gift meaningless?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lyndon Johnson died this day in 1973. https://t.co/bjTha57qKd]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>