<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Markgsparrow Emotionally needy, verbally and pictorially incontinent and ... vulgar, vulgar, vulgar.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulBurston He's what he's always been, a leftwing fundamentalist. All fundamentalists are vile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Markgsparrow I really wish they wouldn't do that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pableshiff @howtoojj @jk_rowling The rabble-rousing Daily Mail is suddenly on side of good? Hm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@randallwrites @SarahGPerry Worst of that ilk are the writers who forget to stop for lunch/supper. Doubly infuriating.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As always, far left and far right close the un-virtuous circle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonnyGeller Arnie would come as a blessed relief.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israel's Supreme Court ruled settlement built on private Palestinian land, illegal. Massive police op demolish settlement. Rule of law.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ken Clarke on #Brexit vote: "We live in a silly unreal world."  Whatever one's views on the issue, it would be hard to argue with that one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theresa May to Jeremy Corbyn, "He can lead a protest. I'm leading a country." She has a point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perhaps Trump was sent amongst us to show us the error of #Brexit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaolaOeste @Bobosvensk @fabianhielte My old university. :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bobosvensk @PaolaOeste @fabianhielte Yes, don't go. Or if you must, go straight to Lund.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NJCooper_crime Exactly - and philosophy ... idiots! *pulls head in*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's cold and it's wet https://t.co/5ex8SAzySD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DebraFerreday and she made a lot of sense re danger wo democracy if future leaders are closing themselves to ideas of which they disapprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DebraFerreday I agree on the whole, but just heard a very impressive woman academic - whose name I of course didn't note, on the subject]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Daily_Express @OwenJones84 I can't believe I missed this. *rushes off to catch-up.*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simon_schama Plus ca change, I'd say.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DebraFerreday I'm such an ignoramus I don't know what you mean by HE students. :-(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DebraFerreday I meant my contributions l, not yours btw :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DebraFerreday But it's awfully hard to discuss complex issues sensibly in 140 characters :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DebraFerreday What we are talking about here is students demanding to be sheltered from any opinions but their own. Dangerous for democracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DebraFerreday people like Germaine Greer, Peter Thatchell and anyone "suspected" of supporting Israel. Hate speech is already outlawed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DebraFerreday Majority of incidents of banning speakers etc happen in London unis with large no. of Muslim students. Speakers banned are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @thetimes In case you missed it, it's not only British citizens who pay taxes; UK, non-British, residents  pay them too, thanks very much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taking break from Trump, to rage about the ridiculous safe-space, (e.g ban anything they don't like) snowflake-tyranny at our universities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theatre reviews: Death Takes A Holiday and  Us/Them https://t.co/QnaxgHtZxk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Casserly_Rock I agree wholeheartedly with everything you said so eloquently.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KirkdaleBooks It's beautiful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KirkdaleBooks EP is much more readable today, I think. I'll investigate translations. As we know, it's 60% or more of the work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KirkdaleBooks of Portugallia by Selma Lagerlöf? Seeing we're on to Swedish classics? (Which reminds me, I'd better get on with my own :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KirkdaleBooks Ah, I think I inteded to as hearing about it made me re-read Glas, but then I sort of forgot. Have you read The Emperor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KirkdaleBooks Dr Glas, a wonderful novel. I of course read it in the original Swedish. (OK so I actually am Swedish, but still ... )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deray @sarahchurchwell @rosesurnow @BarackObama You really do ask for an awful lot, don't you? :-(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simon_schama feels, the more he'll withdraw into his bunker and turn to Bannon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simon_schama I utterly abhor what is happening and what Trump stands for, but isn't it better to have a dialogue? The more slighted he]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeahFHardy @MsAlliance @Bobosvensk This is why I love twitter; from world politics to skincare in one easy step :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsAlliance @LeahFHardy Mine too. Roche - Posay is physical barrier, I think? And Clarins sun and pollution screen 50?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeahFHardy @MsAlliance which ones are as good as they say re UVA while not being 100% chemicals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeahFHardy @MsAlliance Oh great. I can't tolerate the sun - result of three months on kibbutz with no sunscreen at all. I never know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeahFHardy @MsAlliance Brilliant, thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsAlliance @LeahFHardy *pops head out* Leah knows best but according to my derm, it's yes if it's sun induced, no, if it's rosacea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsAlliance @LeahFHardy *butting in* :-) Go for retinol instead. ROC does good one. *pulls head in hands over to expert.*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsAlliance @LeahFHardy As I said previously, even having a discussion like this feels surreal. Who would have thought ... :-(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeahFHardy @ChemiShalev Is this the child of the vile nightmarish Der Sturmer? Makes me feel sick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsAlliance @LeahFHardy I hope and pray and yes, trust that America will not stand for that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeahFHardy Agree. It's awful and surreal. What I'm saying is, cool heads &amp; scrupulous adherence to facts are essential for good to triumph.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeahFHardy @Green_Footballs for having appeared on same platform. Trump is vile. All I'm saying is that hyperbole and false analogies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeahFHardy @Green_Footballs links to some pretty abhorrent organisations. Wonderful @SadiqKhan was unfairly tarred with terrorist brush]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeahFHardy @Green_Footballs That man is abhorrent. Nevertheless his links to Trump are tenuous in the extreme. The Labour leadership have]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeahFHardy @Green_Footballs Those people are beyond vile clearly@but Trump's son-in-law and close adviser is Jewish. It's all insane.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeahFHardy Hitler's aims were clearly laid out in Mein Kampf written years before he came into power. Trump is vile but he's no Hitler.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeahFHardy 2) introduced the Nuremberg racial laws and suspended democracy and rule of law.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeahFHardy 1) I really really object to that comparison. When Chamberlain was appeasing,  Hitler had opened concentration camps like Dachau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@is_cam_24 @Whyjay99 Oh poor you! Rest and feel strong again very soon. X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Won't rescinding invitation to Trump simply drive not only him, but America, deeper into isolation. Is it not better to have his ear?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Whyjay99 @is_cam_24 I know but I think his concerns are groundless. For many others though it's real. :-(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@is_cam_24 @Whyjay99 on a general level but on his own account. On a general level it still sucks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@is_cam_24 @Whyjay99 Sorry pre-mature send. Saw that earlier and it's bery strong but I still think he is worrying unnecessarily - not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@is_cam_24 @TelegraphNews But article states this affects dual.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bestboomer It's a good paper. We've had it for some time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkHemi82 Now tell him what you really think of him. :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jethro_Aryeh @RF_P0TUS That is almost the scariest thing yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@is_cam_24 Of course mood not improved by weeks grappling with forms applying for permanent residency, something I was granted in 1975. 😤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@is_cam_24 Gosh - when did that happen? Is he asking for the entire population of London to be kettled?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@is_cam_24 Same here. Civility and mutual resoect is key. (And anyway, we're not that far apart on this one.) :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@is_cam_24 should be OK. But who knows. It's all mad mad mad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@is_cam_24 with the facts or we'll be going down Trump's post-truth path. As it stands, and that's what we've got to work on, Mo Farrah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@is_cam_24 That is all speculation about possible future regulations. I hate what Trump is doing but I do think we need to take great care]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@is_cam_24 Thanks, will read.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@is_cam_24 Pakistan, Turkey, former Soviet republics, are not affected and that accounts for vast  majority. Still stinks of course.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@is_cam_24  1) Nope - it's a bad bad thing and those affected are Muslim but, Muslim Egypt, Lebanon, Emirates, Saudi, Morocco Malaysia,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@is_cam_24 @Whyjay99 It's the interpreters I worry about most. Their lives are in acute danger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@is_cam_24 I'm still hopeful that it isn't so. White House issued statement saying this was not a ban on Muslims.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SCynic1 @BBCBreaking It struck me that even having this discussion is surreal. Smoke's coming out of my head.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@is_cam_24 He should be as he holds only British citizenship but maybe that reporting was wrong. Crazy times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Whyjay99 Exactly. But Sir Mo has only UK - so they said. (Even having this discussion is surreal.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@is_cam_24 I know but news also said only duals will be affected - total confusion and people trapped in middle. Insane @Whyjay99]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SCynic1 Such confusion; same @BBCBreaking said only those with dual nationality are affected. Not a well thought-through policy this ban:-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Sir Mo Farah as said, has UK, not dual nationality, why report he might be barred from returning to US? Ban bad enough without fake news.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a different note, I wish Sir Mo would come back to live in the UK. As a role model, especially for new arrivals, he has few equals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SCynic1 Ah but my assessment is obviously the correct one. *hides under the table*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ulrikagood They can always move away but they don't. :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SCynic1 I think :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SCynic1 to stand-by their president so such a massive slight would drive them further towards isolationism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SCynic1 I have hope, still, that decent values and good sense will prevail in Washington but enraging most of US... Because thry do tend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ulrikagood Me too re tax. I was just trying - and failing :-( to be funny.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SCynic1 He's so obviously someone who might listen to a "friend" (see his change on torture) If the world rejects him then who will speak?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SCynic1 For once I don't agree with you. Insulting and ostracising the US president will only entrench already disturbing values.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ulrikagood That's existential angst, not enjoyment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeVostreGC @nphegarty Did he actually say that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What we do to wildlife, we ultimately do to ourselves." #SeaPlastic #PlastickPeril]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@craftybookworm And petition to stop the State Visit. I can't believe that insulting and isolating him and US is going to help anything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@craftybookworm have to re-think -go further but right now, softly softly is bound to achieve more. As you say, the psychology of the man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@craftybookworm I don't think he actually connected the two though :-( But clearly if Trump goes further down this road then UK gov will]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@traineedogsbody Call me a misguided Pollyanna but I think it's the former. Also think ban will be lifted or seriously amended very quickly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2) It would *feel* good to make a lot of noise right now but it would most likely be completely counterproductive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1) Theresa May is able to influence Trump -she did re NATO. Going in all guns blazing would achieve nothing other than feed US isolationism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesMelville Of course not. This is just another voter-pleasing stunt. One with awful consequences for many innocent people.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>