<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to the housekeepers and guest-room workers involved in this effort! https://t.co/9RYhX9Uh8c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@randalltrandall Straight capitalism has never been tried. Neither has straight socialism. But more socialistic economies are best!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you instinctively sense that trickle-down is garbage economics, @econjared &amp; I can assure you that you're right.… https://t.co/BhvVTboySX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tcarrcreations The police clarified before @FoxNews' tweet - which didn't mention the French guy - that the Moroccan guy was not a suspect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MLKconservative Why don't you take a look at the evidence presented, instead of disregarding things without giving them a fair shake?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MLKconservative Maybe you actually don't know "liberals" &amp; "libs" that well, because I don't consider myself to be either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While @FoxNews finally deleted the tweet &amp; apologized, did they aggressively correct the record for their followers? https://t.co/0m7tnGhk7c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The main suspect in the attack on a Quebec City mosque is a White Trump supporter. @FoxNews said it was a Moroccan. https://t.co/fUpZUpUs9M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MLKconservative Maybe you should read the study before incorrectly calling it "fake news."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In both simple comparisons &amp; with controls, @TomWongPhD finds that sanctuary cities are safer than other cities.… https://t.co/EGNOL0Bl30]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anthonyszabo It may be invoked, but Democrats should do everything in their power now &amp; deal with that possibility if &amp; when it happens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White evangelical Christianity is in decline. Trump tapped into its fear of relinquishing power. https://t.co/PEdXbNshNW HT @DavidTigabu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robbystarbuck I wanted Obama to nominate someone better &amp; wish he had. But regardless, blocking a vote on him was shameful obstructionism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robbystarbuck Only in the sense that they thought they might be able to pull it off. And they did. But the justification is incoherent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robbystarbuck Yes, it would also be hypocrisy then. It's hypocrisy no matter how you cut it; these rationalizations are all post hoc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eth_KNEES First off, I'm not a "liberal" :). Second, I don't believe in unchecked power for anyone. I believe in a better economic system!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robbystarbuck The point is that they just spent about a year obstructing a nominee. Complaining about obstruction in response is hypocrisy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robbystarbuck Noting that they didn't refuse to allow *every* nominee to the Court over an entire 8-year period isn't a compelling defense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@randalltrandall No, that's not it! But I would deign to guess that there *is* confusion among those upset about young people's views.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robbystarbuck That's absurd. "Lame duck" has a very specific meaning that is much, much narrower than over 8 months before an election.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@A2ndEnding Haha, sorry - your tweet makes more sense now :).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make sure you give @SpawnofGluten props for the awesome question that built on this factoid at the #PelosiTownHall: https://t.co/NQWAtWOTkn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["51 percent of people between the ages of 18 &amp; 29 no longer support the system of capitalism."… https://t.co/nOSAhLCDVV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couching these things as views of Democrats, rather than asserting them, makes them seem disputable. They're not. https://t.co/58GI2z86T5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fact: the @GOP's treatment of Garland was precedent-changing. Also a fact: Their statements now contradict what they did for the past year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[News outlets need to identify hypocrisy as what it is, not make things into "he said, she said" with phrases like "viewed by Democrats."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the way, this @politico piece is a good example of how *not* to write news articles about political disputes. https://t.co/qU8p7FULbm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@A2ndEnding Some are signaling that they might let Gorsuch through. @OmanReagan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mr_Aerospace Oh, he's definitely not (I was very critical of the pick). I'm saying that he's the worst Democrats should accept.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hypocrisy in @GOP messaging was predictable, but still, it never ceases to amaze me how people can say stuff like t… https://t.co/nS0TOJKhNQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Under no circumstances should any Democrat accept a #SCOTUS nominee worse than Merrick Garland. Doing would show (at best) hopeless naivete.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The media has talked a lot about the white working class &amp; Trump, but little about @POTUS &amp; white evangelicals. https://t.co/PEdXbNshNW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Christianity Got Co-Opted and We Got Trump, by @DavidTigabu https://t.co/PEdXbNJSFu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScottElliotG Disproving trickle-down is very different than saying tax policy doesn't matter. Anyway, I'm out. Have a good one! @AlanMCole]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScottElliotG Last thing from me here: That comment is very different than "tax cuts for the rich spur growth," which isn't true. @AlanMCole]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScottElliotG @AlanMCole I don't have time to get more into all of these things now, but happy to chat some other time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScottElliotG @AlanMCole It cites analyses several others have performed; I'm not sure if the Gale piece was linked… https://t.co/RIAQLHNufV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScottElliotG I'll put it on my list, but I'd also recommend you read through the voluminous contradictory evidence we've linked. @AlanMCole]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlanMCole Nobody denies that some incentives exist; the point is that their effects just don't match supply-siders' predictions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlanMCole Again, I haven't read this paper, but I've looked at a lot of data that should look different if supply-side claims were right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlanMCole Also not familiar with the specifics of Microsoft and Dublin, but a lot of relocations are paper-only, &amp; Dublin is beautiful :).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlanMCole Haven't read that particular paper yet, but I'm curious how you explain the consistent lack of basic correlations in the data.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlanMCole To the extent you think it's operative, sure. But non-economic incentives matter a lot &amp; the evidence do… https://t.co/VpZ6SRog2g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlanMCole The same basic theory underlies that prediction; I'd argue that income effects are *far* more likely to be operative for Haves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3) Supply-side tax cuts exacerbate inequality, which can potentially reduce economic growth &amp;/or lead to damaging a… https://t.co/xGLlv3mVWG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2) Offsetting tax cuts with cuts to public spending, which is more efficient than private spending in key areas, ca… https://t.co/yEjcjqtx6i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1) Economic theory is ambiguous about the effect tax cuts will have, &amp; much else besides economic incentives influe… https://t.co/IGDclsgRj0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In @theprospect, @econjared &amp; I summarize three reasons the story used to sell supply-side tax cuts is wrong: https://t.co/c1IWzCBwht]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There is no better retirement program out there than Social Security." -some truth from @econjared at #ProgressDC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shameless plug, in case our new podcast, which @econjared mentioned at #ProgressDC, sounds cool to you. 🙂 https://t.co/MnD4qvK4jR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@germanrlopez Got it; thanks (though better than nothing is a low bar, of course 🙂).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@econjared at #ProgressDC: We must not just think about our own backyard, but also about the backyards of others, &amp; stand in solidarity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How did Trump get more evangelical votes than "shameless Bible thumper George W. Bush?" @DavidTigabu explains:… https://t.co/Hwlw120ajl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@germanrlopez Is @EqualityForum's number 21 because they exclude Utah? https://t.co/q8B9GiDhSr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I learned a lot about the roots of white American evangelicalism from this new piece by @DavidTigabu. Check it out! https://t.co/PEdXbNshNW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danpfeiffer I *hope* it's not the actual strategy, as it's ridiculous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raygibbs1 See my follow-up tweets; they decided not to do it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For more information, see https://t.co/q8B9GiDhSr. We've made progress, but we still have a long way to go. https://t.co/Oto2UL18yc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today, there are still 16 FORTUNE 500 companies that refuse to write LGBTQ protections into their workplace policie… https://t.co/15iqs8dhFp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I used to work on a project at @EqualityForum where we tried to get FORTUNE 500 companies to voluntarily protect LGBTQ individuals. Many do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Employment Nondiscrimination Act doesn't include sexual orientation or gender identity protection &amp; only 21 states currently provide it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't forget that, while nondiscrimination protections exist for LGBTQ federal employees &amp; contractors, other workers don't have them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JaySchout Yeah, it actually really surprised me to read that piece. Thanks again for the update.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turns out they decided not to go through with this. Thanks for the heads up, @JaySchout! https://t.co/w3fAuEhmQx https://t.co/a5sda6axdh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @WhiteHouse is pondering allowing discrimination based on sexual orientation &amp; gender identity again. #shameful… https://t.co/85wJZNV1oe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulNVandeWater Regardless of the extent to which one agrees, "is an anomaly" &amp; "was enabled by past policies" aren't mutually exclusive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Labor Secretary nominee @AndyPuzder makes more in one day than the minimum wage workers he employs make in a… https://t.co/X95mStHCqS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can we please stop calling Trump populist? He's a faux populist. True populists don't just talk about helping people; they walk the walk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Especially heartening: 75 percent of those aged 18-29 have a favorable view of labor unions. https://t.co/2yj0hBNGfN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome that union popularity is so high these days (though weird that "business corporation" popularity is, too).… https://t.co/ZdXv1MPQUz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why the phrase "pro-life" does not belong in discussions of women's reproductive rights. https://t.co/0QtmYzfmFS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's unbelievable that the state isn't fully covering Flint residents' water bills. From @brycecovert:… https://t.co/RnoPguNXcj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The water in Flint still isn't safe to drink &amp; the system state officials have set up to distribute bottled water i… https://t.co/ZN3IR6jfiK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@a_r_schein "If only they had been crafted less sloppily by someone older!" seems to me to be a very counterproductive critique.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who spread hate &amp; support discriminatory policies don't need protection from Muslims. Muslims need protection… https://t.co/oeVU6d2Y85]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulNVandeWater I wrote on this awhile back: https://t.co/WvfLxedLia. I think it's essential to both fight this aw… https://t.co/lOT1iO4REp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulNVandeWater Of course he is responsible for his actions. The others that are named here (Bush and Obama) are a… https://t.co/0cdWp6J2SR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulBoudreau83 Taxis have problems, too, unfortunately. @ToCoLibertad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@People4Bernie @PaulBoudreau83 I have mixed feelings about it, but taxi companies are also quite bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickKilstein There's a clear implication in what I responded to. It's similar to when people mocked Trump for retweeting a 16-year-old.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickKilstein Also, I do think that, in this case, arguing "incompetence!" undermines fighting back (it's basically what Marco Rubio did).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickKilstein Experience matters, but that's not the sentiment behind suggesting a 22-year-old can't *help.* @mattyglesias @juliaioffe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickKilstein It's ageist. There are plenty of young people who are very good at what they do. @mattyglesias @juliaioffe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattBruenig Right; there's nothing wrong with a young person doing things. The problem is what's being done. @mattyglesias @juliaioffe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattyglesias @juliaioffe I don't see how "a 22-year-old helped draft them" is a useful critique. The issue is that they're morally wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@librab103 I hope so! I think calls and emails are a good first step.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@librab103 Ha, probably not, but the more the better!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's the link to Davis' webpage (his first name is misspelled in the article): https://t.co/FP0JiCct7a https://t.co/2625cVs5FU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let Democrat Dereck Davis know that his proposal to pre-empt local minimum wage laws in Maryland is unacceptable.… https://t.co/cJaU3vToSP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OvettaWashPost @bturque Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OvettaWashPost @bturque Cool; thanks! (Is "Derek" a misspelling or does he go by that as a nickname?)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@weidman_paul Hey, if you're out doing stuff now &amp; are resolved not to let it happen again, that's all we can ask for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OvettaWashPost @bturque I can't find information on Derek Davis; can you provide a link to some information about… https://t.co/OFXKFI9fiq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jsalsman I think it's an interesting idea. Got anything to read on it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome to read this. Keep it up, everyone! https://t.co/oTwZIZUNKd https://t.co/Py6mteUvTg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is heartening to see so many standing up for what's right now. But let this be a reminder that injustice always… https://t.co/7W9IfFIOgD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you support the quasi-#MuslimBan, you are not "pro-life" - regardless of how you defend your views on abortion.… https://t.co/3Yu1MWdvFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ToCoLibertad You could still use @lyft; they donated $1 million to the @ACLU in support of those fighting the ban. @People4Bernie @Uber]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is imperative that we fight Trump's uniquely awful refugee policy without forgetting how others enabled it.… https://t.co/0aLd1k0J1V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like most anti-choice Republicans, @marcorubio can't credibly claim to believe that "all human life is sacred." https://t.co/0QtmYzfmFS]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>