<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile in Canada … Things Are Just as Bad, via @nytimes Slamming Canada because we just think we're better. https://t.co/Vjo347oQTJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great piece. Trump defeated one woman but million other women sprouted in her place.  https://t.co/02cd1M0XdH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This depiction of Trump's White House has the eerie feel of end days, not an optimistic energized beginning https://t.co/K8YDfhhaNK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is one of best pieces of reporting the human side of Trump and it's ...sad. https://t.co/K8YDfhhaNK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also the essential solitary state of Donald Trump. No wonder he tweets. https://t.co/kBm3Gv8Q3d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A devastating portrait of an unhappy confused and incompetent White House w Trump wandering around in a bathrobe https://t.co/x1Cr3PB01F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where are the cries of concern/outrage from senior Dems and GOP brass? https://t.co/Nxs64n7P1N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boycott nerd prom and instead go for journalistic self-respect.  https://t.co/Czgknp4aMy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please bring Melissa. https://t.co/Ii50FCdCoo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Resistance Movement, via @nytimes Love this open hearted call to arms. Thank you. https://t.co/KNt8XtmaZF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So-called honest? https://t.co/8UGnGnZEfR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cbcfreshair @ralphbenmergui It was great to hear your voice and some great jazz thrown in as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smart. But maybe let taxpayers off hook? https://t.co/KdSYUkpssM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To the cross https://t.co/7pFkGKabJD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A stroke of comic genius that emasculated a power mad bully run nonsensical and dick driven government. https://t.co/SaDCXphUCB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes. Mosque killings an eerie echo  of Charleston. https://t.co/UPMTa8CfJh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lizrenzetti  Oh Liz. I am so sorry. He sounds like a marvel. Big hug to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only in many people's dreams..... https://t.co/O5Ro80FXIX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't make me send you both to your rooms. https://t.co/ENrVHePSEt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting. https://t.co/0hWDTiHKyr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Used to love getting up early, first sip of coffee, checking news feeds. Now news out of U.S and Trump govt = absolute mood plunge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not mentioned: our week of profound grief in Canada. Quebec mosque massacre. Accused young white man an alleged onl… https://t.co/dzvwrsHZxH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justin Trudeau, Facing Pressure to Oppose Donald Trump, Opts to Get Along, via @nytimes https://t.co/UsTFIi3kOD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump With a Tail, via @nytimes Pence's Poodle. Bannon's Beagle. Whatever. https://t.co/YChl0vLJ2N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good for you. https://t.co/adsBKgZ2Ik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Visa Ban Touches Far More People Than First Thought, via @nytimes So which is it? https://t.co/UZ2GG4ysN4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best of luck David. https://t.co/ACMnVN7KIk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerful. Undeniable. https://t.co/ey8KUHbJxe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump cannot stem tide of millions of progressives who have (finally) ramped up to oppose his government. https://t.co/8owckdWQP9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@goldsbie Actually pols underestimating dramatically quick neg effects of Trump chaos/ban/bigotry on Cdn voters.Progressives ramping way up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not allright allright allright? https://t.co/dMQzWC0T9p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didn't @SpeakerRyan recently say he was growing fonder of Trump's insane(my word)tweets? https://t.co/2N3qy7rYEe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nor did she mean to say "alternative facts." Is there a vaccination against lying Trump team can get? https://t.co/Oy7OBnNFSr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there something "personal" about appealing to bigotry? If he has been strategizing under the influence I would s… https://t.co/aEpQWfSr1h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IvisonJ It's fringe.Most Cdns reject this. I got far more positive response than neg after calling Leitch out. Don't quote losers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Canadian politicians. Less than two weeks into Trump presidency, many Canadians won't take wait and see approach to extreme candidates.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perhaps expressing this rejection directly to the public might be more leaderly. https://t.co/r3sy5EtVdP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBCAlerts Nexus travel cards being rejected at border.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Thanks Comey." https://t.co/rbToDSxGDu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jaimewatt rejected "dog whistle" politics more profoundly @metromorning than @JohnTory just did. This is expedienc… https://t.co/NABw6KPNpA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jaimewatt @metromorning Difference btw Canadians and Americans "more real" than you think."I've never lost betting on fairness" of Cdns.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should media stop repeating her threats and lies? Maybe then she'll stop lying when that red camera light goes off. https://t.co/BanSpPmY6S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Her campaign manager resigned yesterday amid much controversy over his incendiary words. https://t.co/e6IwHv3kl6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read this. Mt Rushmore may crumble in shame. https://t.co/XD3iu80jvM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnTory cannot espouse his "values" of tolerance then look away when a key strategist peddles the opposite. Winni… https://t.co/GUHLC9q1EA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Memo to alt-right or bigotry mongers: this is not America.This is Canada.Trump example will motivate many to fight… https://t.co/WqbzNcq3OQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because they get people involved. https://t.co/AmUFcDn59P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior people in Trump govt concerned about his fitness to lead? https://t.co/AOrdbgN15b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Yorker and Vanity Fair Pull Out of Correspondents Dinner Parties, via @nytimes https://t.co/BaxmpPIm5X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day of #QuebecMosqueAttack funerals yes let's have U.S anti immigrant mouthpiece Ann Coulter on Cdn tv. Heard how s… https://t.co/t952A9M6wV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Timing is .....are you serious? https://t.co/rxd8bsGVq2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone is angry. All.The.Time. https://t.co/9GLKAtoxqn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait. https://t.co/2rdAQE5f33]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aitken_beth @TorontoStar thanks for your response.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump IS the 400 pound guy in America's basement. He has hacked democracy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charlesadler What would you do as a conservative but not crazy GOP'er? Call him out? Or let him say/do anything b/c you're in power?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump team trying to overthrow, delegitimize and censor media.They're abrogating First Amendment. Will they succeed… https://t.co/DnhsQtbmBY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@POTUS tweets shd be called 'twids'.They come directly unfiltered from his id. All presidents have complex ids.His has been let out to play.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bigots must be allowed to speak! Directive/threat from Bigot-in-Chief. The morally impoverished presidency. Maybe c… https://t.co/qEzssIfaMx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need to talk about Kellie Leitch: Timson | Toronto Star Especially now in the shadow of #QuebecShooting  https://t.co/sXu53Fx5s4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spaikin of course. Auto-correct bug off! What strikes me is how many "I was a Patient" stories this evokes in my o… https://t.co/B0LNrAQ1XF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/UFNFSxoZQB Interview btw Steve Pailin @TheAgenda and @judithhjohn is spectacular. We are all patients--universal experience.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this https://t.co/K7LSnZfLyI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why didn't #gorsuch show respect to senior jurist #MerrickGarland and tell GOP first you owe my colleague a nominat… https://t.co/DcdFaIwGKM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bigwigs and execs better not be cleaning up w bonuses. This is shocking. Good luck all. https://t.co/9a1mZpjaIM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh no. Such losses. https://t.co/KGxPN6su3J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The blue hospital gown is a "very democratic" piece of clothing. Docs and patients need to hear how patient care ca… https://t.co/35Gwvik3D6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That is not even literate. More importantly WHAT is this guy w these views doing in a President's inner circle or i… https://t.co/XA4CCwMgjQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GraemeMcL5 @TorontoStar If we don't challenge Leitch's views in the aftermath of this terrible tragedy fueled by hate, when do we?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Her words need further challenging after #MosqueeSteFoy We need to talk about Kellie Leitch: Timson https://t.co/MRUXiZFrWJ via @torontostar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need to talk about Kellie Leitch: Timson | Toronto Star https://t.co/sXu53Fx5s4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Astonishing goodness https://t.co/MlegeziG2f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House ices out CNN https://t.co/j6xKLv2c3R @PressSec smears @CNN. Calling news org dishonest just makes it work harder to reveal truth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or a good latte. https://t.co/TwbMYRDQA1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COLUMN - Backlash against ‘Trump Lite’  #startouch #TorontoStar Kellie Leitch and the QC mosque massacre https://t.co/FYIttQUDVH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taking a modest but very brave stand. All that requires evil to flourish is for good people to do nothing.… https://t.co/ovF78BqcVl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COLUMN - Backlash against ‘Trump Lite’  #startouch #TorontoStar We need to talk about Kellie Leitch https://t.co/FYIttQUDVH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will disagreement over acceptability of  #gorsuch as Trump's #SCOTUSnominee split Democratic ranks? https://t.co/b6C1AzgDMf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A very good journalistic mission statement in a perilous time. https://t.co/leyO6yhxEU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COLUMN - Backlash against ‘Trump Lite’  #startouch #TorontoStar Kellie Leitch in the shadow of Quebec City
 https://t.co/FYIttQUDVH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COLUMN - Backlash against ‘Trump Lite’  #startouch #TorontoStar We need to talk about Kellie Leitch  https://t.co/FYIttQUDVH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toronto pastor Brent Hawkes found not guilty of sex crimes in Nova Scotia
https://t.co/vFRCooe1fS https://t.co/bhB7AgLsyE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So brilliant.Bravo @linwood_barclay I will buy your latest book today. https://t.co/vpg931Kl7B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Accused terrorist". We still have rule of law in Canada. https://t.co/FzSnmOZ0gE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is going to blow up soon. https://t.co/2t8TQhZV8e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alan Dershowitz puts down Acting AG as "holdover heroine" for refusing to legally defend #travelban .Trump shd "just ignore her." Really.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vigils all over for Muslim victims of #QuebecCityMosqueShooting. Demos all over against Trump's Muslim entry ban. Uncomfortably interwoven.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is brave leadership. https://t.co/iEzwEpw2LX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two panelists @PnPCBC call @PressSec link of #QuebecMosqueShooting to @POTUS "proactive" entry ban "idiotic" in lig… https://t.co/cWkziYsOMI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had this happened in U.S would he even have been alive today? https://t.co/Wt2lUmhdsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scathing words about gaping hole last night in national tv coverage of #QuebecMosqueAttack Esp CBC It was shocking. https://t.co/NPzRX29oBR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perfect to watch today. https://t.co/9aDe0COHGw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a serious media question from @TorontoStar columnist. https://t.co/zoJHdhO7o4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickKouvalis @EmmMacfarlane Wondering about your use of "cuck" -associated w white supremacy and neo nazi movement.Do you use "cuck" often?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tears watching but also admiration. https://t.co/Z1P01VauHN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Extremely moving press conference ending with Muslim prayer #QuebecShooting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Humanize the victims please. Tell us their stories.  Mayor and Mosque leaders #mosqueequebec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piya But they are being told at points of departure not to board their flights, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smart move Samantha Bee to Roast Trump on Same Night as Correspondents’ Dinner, via @nytimes https://t.co/5PLw6wpOIi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How sick do you have to be to tweet this? And he's president. Four years. https://t.co/UnIpmDec0T]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>