<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I am stopping people from having their first amendment rights because I replied to @jk_rowling three days ago. Good to know #OhReally]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AFancifulMind @SarahfromNZ and yet Peanut has never been allowed over, I see how that works LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahfromNZ WHAT! seriously? @AFancifulMind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AFancifulMind She is so sweet! Also our boarding kennel arrangements fell through last night so no idea what the heck to do now with P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AFancifulMind WHEN CAN AUNTY WENDY MEET HER!! omg you never told me she was happening!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nil_Joel my notifications are not so blessed because I replied to her 3 days ago and idiot trolls are still on my case lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For anyone lurking around ready to  pounce on my tweet from DAYS ago, I am NOT an American and didn't vote either way. Stop tweeting at me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hamish_keith @FergusVUP @ElizabethKnoxNZ @guicueilleurs Good dentists like that are as rare as hens teeth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaJohansen :) and you are probably very correct]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hamish_keith She's an immigrant after all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A few people could take this to heart and do themselves a favour :) https://t.co/cmaN75hDV3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kiwipippa lol trying not to tweet anything to do with that other thing today. Too stressed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarquisedeSark My work here is done for the night then haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cukeyishere @ohthatwelshguy cuteeeee right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mommayoung123 wedding on Friday, so much not good stuff today argh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is not working out well for 2/3rds of our family :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dancapper holy crap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dancapper wait what now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No time for political stuff right now people. My personal life is a tad more important  ( a lot more ) Wedding this week! At hairdressers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatSmart4 @Pammygirl @excavator_mum I have no time for this nonsense daughter is getting married  and I am at hairdressers with dying phone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MoataTamaira the world has gone insane! 
:(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AliCopeman @Pammygirl @excavator_mum not worth replying to :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AliCopeman @Pammygirl @excavator_mum Someone trying to make Murica grate againn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pammygirl @excavator_mum You mean you haven't already??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pammygirl @excavator_mum it was the one that got me called a ct *so proud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@excavator_mum @Pammygirl only another 700 more likes and it will match yesterdays effort haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pammygirl Well she does right ðŸ˜ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@madrunnerz go to their page and it tells you you are blocked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you realize the reason a tweet is getting so many likes is because Twitter included it in a "moments" story #SagAwards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatydidNZ @five15design @paulbrislen He quit and he also isn't dead, also another urban legend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CabbageMittens So good, Charles definitely wasn't in charge of that exchange]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CabbageMittens I like the part where the guy told Jermaine to give the Maoris back their land bwhaha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimbakerwilson @Tenani I know they all end with you might die but whatev's you won't have constipation anymore, so totally worth it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimbakerwilson @Tenani the best part is when they reel off the possible side effects to things, WTH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bex2010 Don't worry I got called all sorts of stuff yesterday because I replied to JK Rowling and they all got their knickers in a twist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bex2010 the thread haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lukeurmyson Well that's ok then, don't have to send you out to herd the sheep up this evening]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chaci and @AJemaineClement fighting on Twitter is the best thing I have seen today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lukeurmyson At least spell his name right man lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sopheakseng_ Hair and make up on point at least, lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxyLustyGrover @Peytonsnanajo @MollyRingwald I was in a restaurant with her once in LA, true story lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MonzagirlNZ He always seems to be whispering to her on the red carpet :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxyLustyGrover @Peytonsnanajo @MollyRingwald him and Frampton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amyhickey77 I never said I hated it I just said she looked like a Wicked cast member which she does]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bstnrbstr It's very shiny, I don't "hate" it but a toned down green would have been better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zrsouthcombe it's very very shiny lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrsGreatnews they let them through the airport!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nicole looks like one of the Wicked "citizens of Oz" chorus members #sagawards https://t.co/OGyrOV51Fw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephanieMarija @justin_lester We Lester's are a good bunch :) * most of us lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxyLustyGrover @ProckyHorror Awkward lol, remember that parcel I still haven't posted because life went off course. You have backups]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaseyNeistat The dangling S is a special touch ;)
#CanNotBlameAutoCorrect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Schofe I have tickets in my bag for this, thanks for the reminder and recommedation. Tissues aplenty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrsGreatnews @MelBailey Ditto, it is just all so much,so fast and scary as hell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alkalinekiwi Good morning to you :) Happy Monday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@filmguidenz rogue,vagabond AND bloody good sort ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning you rogues and vagabonds, upstanding citizens and bloody good sorts!
The rest of you please jog on out of my mentions ðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glibnotion which one? there are tons of them, reporting and blocking and moving on in most cases yes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glibnotion My notifications this morning, yikes. Scary insight in the mindset of a lot :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glibnotion It's still happening, no that response was in this mornings lot. When they have "redneck" in their name, you know it's good haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When someone asks you if you used a thesaurus to make a tweet using words you LITERALLY made up on the fly haha.
Thanks for trying! ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@five15design @jamielecomte Happy first day back for the year and good luck at the new school :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TonkWoman @L_To @robtreacher omg the notifications this morning, good grief. You know who supporters are actually certifiable half the time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TonkWoman @L_To @robtreacher 560 likes and still going, guess lots of people disagreed with him lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TonkWoman @L_To @robtreacher Which just goes to prove how fantastic you are ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZ_judester @irisshackleton I wanted to think that was a SNL skit or a parody, it isn't WTF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@L_To @robtreacher on twitter yes lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@L_To @robtreacher The one I got called today? Yup good times :/ https://t.co/I6o6Z9A8kl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ohthatwelshguy Does he have a name yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pammygirl @LegGully @Sportsfreakconz @FoxyLustyGrover well it is a word I hate so don't count on me using it again anytime soon LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pammygirl @LegGully @Sportsfreakconz @FoxyLustyGrover It's just a word Pam LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bopmafia @LegGully @Sportsfreakconz @FoxyLustyGrover I can read and stuffz eh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pammygirl @LegGully @Sportsfreakconz @FoxyLustyGrover The best part was I got called that in a tweet with @jk_rowling so it was actually A+]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pammygirl @LegGully @Sportsfreakconz @FoxyLustyGrover I was "quoting" ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LegGully @Sportsfreakconz @FoxyLustyGrover I have been using my block button a lot and I am a semi-illiterate cunt so there's that haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sportsfreakconz @LegGully @FoxyLustyGrover Understatement of the year. Crazy crazy day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LegGully left what?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaseyNeistat That isn't a word but I think it should be from now on!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threadnz Wow that is gorgous!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threadnz nice, where?? So hot today, I just took the dog for a walk and nearly expired :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peecee65 @Jon_Hassall I am staying sequestered inside, just took the dog out earlier and nope lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@A_J_Hood I am  hiding inside, just been out with the dog, omg melting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yakmoose @AnnaGConnell Next weekend for us, hopefully a bit more excited as it is daughters wedding haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peanut and Butter (Bean ) just got vaccinations on a Sunday in our kitchen haha. They are not having a relaxed weekend ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PappaHutten @MaryHadStan @jk_rowling Block and move on, they are starved for attention so don't give them any :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jubjubnz Happy birthday to him :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CateOwen So much this~]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chandy229 Well done you haha. Happy Sunday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vaughndavis @SparkNZ there are issues this morning yes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bex2010 I love the block button. Honestly so many scary fools out there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pno_nwa I actually consider it an honour to be called a semi-illiterate cunt in the same tweet as @jk_rowling.
Bloody scary mindset though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shadow_nz And we were not even engaging he just jumped in on a reply. What an age to be alive huh!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been called the C word by an angry you know who supporter this morning. Keep up the good work Twitter lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jk_rowling He gets half a point for the right "you're" but it ends there. Moronus astoundiosus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning please tell me something good about today!
Unless you have me muted in that case you won't see this,suspect that a lot do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CabbageMittens @danni_meow @brenakiwi I have had that issue a lot lately, not all @ are showing up for me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheAmandaLand I blocked some today,finally caught up on Instagram and FB after a busy few weeks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kylewadsworth All the time, I just block them eventually, after I see it happening repeatedly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewKayNZ it is only because it's the rooster year  (not every year )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewKayNZ no it's not a whole chicken with feet and head is GOOD luck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChelleHopeBlog He was/is always Quentin to me, I am so glad you appreciate that too :)]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>