<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Success of good epidemiological research –Dangerous Fruit: Mystery of Deadly Outbreaks in India Is Solved https://t.co/qGqHed3JO0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: B.C. Hydro, like Trump, takes aim at media https://t.co/lW5nGaje1I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alberta doctor tells U.S.: Canada is ‘lying’ about tar sands’ health effects via @VanObserver #climatehealth https://t.co/spWPFBwjEr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alberta doctor tells U.S.: Canada is ‘lying’ about tar sands’ health effects via @VanObserver https://t.co/spWPFBwjEr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Overdose Crisis: We Know How to Save Lives, Doctors Say  via @TheTyee https://t.co/6Wz9CRskhL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Study linking Roundup to serious disease fuels debate https://t.co/vqYDLPlgHz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ignore the headlines: a six-hour working day is the way forward | Daniel Bernmar https://t.co/JFlo2PGY6n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How $$ undermines evidence-based decision-making on climate change policy #climatehealth #KinderMorgan  #bcpoli https://t.co/ZC3Qix4kcP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finland introduces basic income for unemployed #prescribingincome  https://t.co/kwn5tTnVlq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free solar ushers poor households into carbon-free future #climatejustice #climatehealth
https://t.co/LNE5Hw0ewW https://t.co/QAHoVc9oQm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant! #climatehealth You no longer need to own a solar panel to reap financial benefits of solar energy https://t.co/B4VJRmzeXC via @qz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to Vancouver Jan 23 public event - Danielle Martin discusses 3 key rel'ships 4 health  https://t.co/932ft212eT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canadians languish in limbo as they wait for long-term care https://t.co/1HyHaDBEoA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Study, EPA Report Highlight Fracking’s Risk to Groundwater  via @TheTyee https://t.co/5wl0QDKjRj  #LNG=frackedgas #frackingharmshealth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fossil fuel divestment funds double to $5tn in a year https://t.co/wNKEq4glxr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#fortheCOAST flash mob of coast protesters #idlenomore is back!! https://t.co/imLucFWT6P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ontario for-profit LTC homes – esp those owned by a chain organization – significantly fewer hours of care https://t.co/bY4CRSckLa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staffing in Ontario’s Long-Term Care Homes: Differences by Profit Status and Chain Ownership  https://t.co/bY4CRSckLa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#C2E2lecture @CaulfieldTim addressing pseudoscience w/ calling out bunk, fighting false balance, using narrative to describe good science]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#C2E2lecture @CaulfieldTim describes O-shot reporting as great example of predatory quackajournal "scienceploitatio… https://t.co/Wsrjnt2NAS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#C2E2lecture @CaulfieldTim "cleansing" "detox" buzzwords - celeb culture's central role in spread of health misinformation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#C2E2lecture @CaulfieldTim "clearing toxins of modern day life" = popular theme in pop science https://t.co/UpyGMqPR6E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#C2E2lecture @CaulfieldTim never before r we surrounded by so much good science &amp; also by so much baloney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contracting out meals to large off-site company - Powell River seniors take stand on meals  https://t.co/nCXXI4J2A1 via @Peak_Aboo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Palliative care initiative improves clinician comfort w/end-of-life conversations 4 frail LTC residents https://t.co/bkBEdZjMNC via @AddThis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How this doctor uses postal codes to screen patients for poverty https://t.co/vOOB2a68h7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Britain's Pensioner Care Scandal: for-profit home care company exploits British seniors 
Dispatches https://t.co/hdApe28vdW via @C4Press]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former medical student of Leitch dismayed by Trump-support email https://t.co/I0TXNDkky3 via @torontostar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#climatechange #ClimateJustice @JustinTrudeau @jimcarr_wpg @Puglaas Kinder #canpoli MDs join Kinder Morgan protest https://t.co/KdLcJywk1E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#climatechange #ClimateJustice @JustinTrudeau @jimcarr_wpg @Puglaas Community says no to Kinder Morgan expansion https://t.co/lNWSTlhIqF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Healthy planet = healthy people https://t.co/DNWpHHAVvV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vancouver Doctors demonstrate concern about expansion of Kinder Morgan https://t.co/0ob6465g3Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Must read! The Trans-Pacific Partnership, health, and climate change: time to listen to your doctor via @VanObserver https://t.co/Gqvac9HApu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Study Finds Nearby Retail Clinics Don’t Drive Down ER Visits https://t.co/W7LhQOj8oF via @khnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft founder calls on fellow billionaires to help make US fossil-free by 2050 https://t.co/Xe0TvoJntg via @yournewswire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#DAPLtoKM  @JustinTrudeau @Puglaas @jimcarr_wpg Senior Jackie De Roo describes how she became climate change activi… https://t.co/bVbAUYw2cP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#DAPLtoKM  @JustinTrudeau @Puglaas @jimcarr_wpg Tara Houska notes "Standing Rock so much more than just a pipeline" https://t.co/9LOA3uoV08]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#DAPLtoKM  @JustinTrudeau @Puglaas @jimcarr_wpg Tara Houska describes efforts 2 protect unceded sacred burial ground https://t.co/0Pm3TwYTiI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#DAPLtoKM  @JustinTrudeau @Puglaas @jimcarr_wpg packed audience to discuss how to stop kinder morgan expansion https://t.co/2qK5Ex2jHi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saskatchewan doctors now checking the fiscal health of patients https://t.co/3BN5SmRBZK@]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Fossil fuel subsidies are the elephant in the room  https://t.co/2tNs1tsW4l via @NatObserver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trudeau approved west coast gas terminal based on flimsy evidence, study says https://t.co/NwHuZKoOWb via @NatObserver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Bat-Signal’ rallies 1,500 young researchers to press Trudeau for evidence-based decisions https://t.co/sbFjqKFCLT via @NatObserver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids Just Won the Right to Sue the Government over Global Warming https://t.co/4bfbHgYkq2 via @TeenVogue #climatejustice #frackLNG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@courtghoward #cfpcfmf #ClimateJustice need to put a price on carbon that is meaningful enough to influence behavior https://t.co/sSS6QkNW60]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our learners are leading the way @courtghoward notes how young MDs playing leading role in climate change and health https://t.co/NNIoxzWfNY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@courtghoward fabulous presentation to #cfpcfmf on health impact of climate change ! https://t.co/vlTTW0MuTG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[B.C. home support workers hurt at twice provincial average via @VancouverSun https://t.co/7wPtNMWGSS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cape Breton doctor hopes to help swing election for Clinton https://t.co/18ScCAIJDl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A price is right: The health case for a price on pollution https://t.co/92mKBe6Qly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jennifer Whiteside: Hospital workers union fears trial threatens universal health care https://t.co/JO9K4m86id]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canadian Medical Association Journal: Doctors call to phase out coal-fired electricity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doctors Celebrate FADOQ’s Victory vs Extra Billing in Québec | Press Releases | Newsroom: https://t.co/wHf4Rpoamm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great article on  "investigation momentum”  &amp; how anxiety can drives unnecessary tests 
https://t.co/SI9VUE2A1N via @thescienceofus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Muskrat Falls a “modern day form of genocide”: lawyer https://t.co/B7CPndoWRB via @IndependentNL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Seniors' care can't wait for vulnerable care home residents https://t.co/c5uLULiNx0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nursing homes must stop asking for drug fees from pharmacies: Editorial  https://t.co/kyW46cv9um via @torontostar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes, for the frail elderly, the less medical intervention, the better https://t.co/py98E5f6F6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“There was no world-class oil response demonstrated here today,” Marilyn Slett, Heiltsuk Chief https://t.co/hQsAgUmrbO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Selfishness is not a virtue in medicine, even if Brian Day says so https://t.co/AHvrVXbkQK via @NatObserver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: For-profit care of seniors proven to be inferior https://t.co/7wMz1eF7vZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: For-profit care of seniors proven to be inferior https://t.co/7wMz1enwEr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Private vs. public less of an issue than quality residential care https://t.co/7wMz1eF7vZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From Alzheimer’s to heart attacks, loneliness in seniors has serious health effects https://t.co/EdDz34DixO via @healthydebate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seniors at Nanaimo facility face uncertain future https://t.co/QhJI9yoH4d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MEDICINE MATTERS: A family's anguish as nursing home continues feeding vegetative patient https://t.co/tuAy0Lkady]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Math &amp; physics = worst possible negotiating partners—they just stare blankly at you &amp; carry on" https://t.co/1eGgOd18Pp via @NatObserver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman had a baby. Then her hospital charged her $39.35 to hold it. https://t.co/obkzYmwlZ9 via @voxdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FrackLNG #climatechange #canpoli Will and Kate visit Haida Gwaii with anger in the air https://t.co/VCPywj6GBP via @macleansmag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Stop privatizing long-term care': Sechelt residents angered by VCH plan https://t.co/vuGcdWn2cG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#frackLNG #fracking #canpoli Great "NO LNG" tshirts!  https://t.co/fplSXQ33WU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Injury rates for workers in long-term care sector decreasing but still one of B.C.'s most dangerous jobs https://t.co/WpXtnXymAt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Reconciliation Must Be More than Symbolic: Grand Chief Stewart Phillip Declines Invitation... #RoyalVisitCanada https://t.co/t99sB1iHnc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#frackLNG #climatehealth #cdnpoli City of Vancouver votes to ban natural gas by 2050 https://t.co/P6yzYr9u9W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[180+ MDs &amp; health professionals urge feds to reject Pacific NW LNG  pending health impact assess #frackLNG #cdnpoli https://t.co/a2XzAvpJoD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pacific NW LNG needs hlth impact assess 't say 180+ MDs +hlth professionals #frackLNG #cdnpoli  https://t.co/xhnFOh5IYE via @NatObserver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doctors urge feds to assess health impact of Pacific Northwest LNG project  https://t.co/xhnFOh5IYE via @NatObserver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICC widens remit to include environmental destruction cases https://t.co/e3DUmtu2Mm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quebec health minister to abolish accessory fees by 2017 https://t.co/a7Cl5JZBr4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice summary! 5 reasons why private surgeries won’t shorten waits in the public system https://t.co/VehnoyqB3w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seniors take centre stage at annual Labour Day Picnic https://t.co/YL1KqQ8O8q via @coast_reporter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: B.C.'s climate plan is a public health failure https://t.co/dV9P4KErNu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a predictor of early death, loneliness eclipses obesity. https://t.co/GzQyx8bxg0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#frackLNG #PLOSONE: Unconventional Gas and Oil Drilling Is Associated with Increased Hospital Utilization Rates https://t.co/TOOMQnYCiR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Study reveals ‘profound’ gaps in understanding of groundwater in northeast B.C. https://t.co/FLUSDcfO23 (via https://t.co/5vgXoNntke)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["need to broaden team involved in choosing reforms to include Health Authorities, other providers &amp; patients."
https://t.co/fP8Mm826Ug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This time around, before spending billions, need to agree what success looks like, &amp; monitor progress" @VanObserver https://t.co/fP8Mm826Ug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: British Columbia’s failed healthcare experiment via @VanObserver https://t.co/fP8Mm826Ug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clinic operator, proponent of privatized health care heads to court next week - 680 NEWS https://t.co/ZW3BOGB140 via @680News]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#climatehealth #frackLNG Leading insurers tell G20 to stop funding fossil fuels by 2020 https://t.co/3rdsqwA1hn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clerical Staff Serve Critical Role on Patient-Centered Care Team https://t.co/NCxoDXXOt9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#frackLNG #climatehealth CMA supports health impact assessments of hydraulic fracturing 
https://t.co/Y4pvqmv9K6 via @NatObserver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonderful news! - Canadian Medical Association completes divestment from fossil fuels https://t.co/Y4pvqmv9K6 via @NatObserver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#climatehealth This is what climate change leadership looks like vs. BCs let's wait to see what other provinces do!
https://t.co/mfzPb33a7y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#frackLNG Living Near a Fracking Site Is Tied to Migraines, Fatigue https://t.co/BirDuW3Xx1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Doctors tackle relationship between climate change and health https://t.co/LHz7HEwkLF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CMA resolves 2 produce high-quality action-oriented educational materials to disseminate its policies &amp; evidence on climate change &amp; health]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CMA meeting Dr. Orbinski urges MDs and CMA to "step up and to step out" to advocate for climate change solutions.
https://t.co/MP3fKdwmVt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CMA mtg Warming of climate = one of greatest threats to human health &amp; MDs must help lead search for solutions https://t.co/rya9I4SyP2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Racism in health care is 'a real thing,' says Indigenous physician https://t.co/bgFCIl6l3G]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>