<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Can you all just get out your snapper before you get on the bus?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erizabethkim get a fucking snapper, sort out your change before you get on the bus, don't fucking have a DMC with the driver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuuuuuuccccckkkk people that hold up the bus are the worst.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hypeasgus have you got this LP? https://t.co/Dk8mW7X4lX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My goal for 2017 is to wear these pants more often. https://t.co/x0g7Y3Qs8N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hypeasgus good as gold fucking sucks man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hypeasgus are you actually high?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hypeasgus what does this even mean?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GilmoreGuysShow "There's a hamster in my anus!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016 sucked so hard, but this is a nice end to a shitty year. https://t.co/RlY85nzsxT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Auckartgal what are your hours for tomorrow? (29/12/16)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why can't I have great, natural boobs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My only friend in Auckland is in Bali so all I am doing now is reading 'Pride and Prejudice'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LucyZee_ once I moisturised my hands in public before an exam and I couldn't hold my pen and it was the most stressful time of my life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@artyfilms haha lame ass man. Enjoy some quality time with Ma and Pa instead!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@artyfilms how tho!?!? What are you watchin Arty?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My parents don't have Internet so I can't watch Gilmore Girls or Seinfeld ☹️]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy festivus to you all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Korean spoken on Gilmore Girls is so bad even to my standards.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sambgrover what do I get Gus for Christmas?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @hypeasgus what do you want for xmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so constipated look at these cute puppies I saw today. https://t.co/6VaCrk156M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't have any hobbies or favourite things to do. I've just been watching a lot of Gilmore Girls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do you when you can't figure out what you actually enjoy and gives you pleasure in life?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Made some Korean chicken the other day https://t.co/8JQZXhmAJP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What am I gonna make of my life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please don't make the "grab them by the pussy" man the president.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tommymillions00 travel bloggers are the worst kind of privileged people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CRKSHNK r u high]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh man, Jerry Seinfeld tickets have a price range of $80-$200.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why even bother coming to the library if you're going to cough loudly every 5 seconds and be a public nuisance?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am so glad I took NZ history in high school.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some dumbass on the internet thought these were running shoes. https://t.co/NDM7VhI3uS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I watched six episodes of Gilmore Girls today. Six.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When people use the term "fur baby" it makes me cringe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone from high school is just so lame.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone that I thought was cool in high school when I was 14 are now all so lame.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just saw some dude badly skateboarding in jandals and on the phone. Man, that looked super dangerous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hypeasgus every time I walk past MBIE there are people singing in a group or doing the haka.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just listened to 1 Thing by Amerie 3 times this morning. No regrets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laurabkeown is sleeping in a marae tonight, who will I annoy instead?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My house is on a slant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My sister gives me shit about having lots of clothes, yet, she takes up 3/4 of her shared wardrobe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck, Berhampore is a scary place to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My life on shelves. https://t.co/LtIGIwT4zM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey, just letting you know I've got a flea bite near my nipple.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look at these shit flea bites. https://t.co/4eWK8pfF2Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The thing about burritos is that they are full of beans and then you eat the beans and then you're full of beans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good on @laurabkeown for making sure to get her vote in all the way from NZ!! https://t.co/kWUUVnHqJI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laurabkeown no, hairy cockroach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone used my razor so I got another one and then they used that too and then I threw both away and now they're back in the shower!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My day went from 100% to 0% real quick today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I watched the first episode of 'Stranger Things' today. It took me so long to spot Winona Ryder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a mouth ulcer on my tonsil and every time I swallow, eat or drink it is a little hell in my mouth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laurabkeown because bubble bath and lush bombs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laurabkeown you should have a bath.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't really say that the Govt. &amp; council are just sitting on free land. A large proportion of it is Maori land #rnzdebate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it normal for your flatmate to have their own washing pegs?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it lame that I have clothes that I wear to the library?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having eczema at 21 is more embarrassing than at the age of 6.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are laptop sleeves so extortionate?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going semi-constipated into a test this morning. Wish me luck. https://t.co/qxu5ajDW3h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not get the Peking duck crisps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where can I buy haribo turtles?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today I saw people walking past a rubbish bin that was on fire doing nothing and I was on the bus so I just watched.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My body feels like it's rotting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man I want one for myself https://t.co/fHsrvJCxC7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is not my day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The number of times people have called me 'Kim' by mistaking it as my first name has been one too many.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would like to declare my love for ramen and dumplings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing pineapple belongs in is fucking fruit salad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and the next best thing aka Kmart is only available in porirua which I have not been to in my four years here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why the f isn't there an ikea in NZ? I'm genuinely mad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now Kramer will great me every morning. Seinfeld in real life. https://t.co/xLZ24g4jyu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I use to think that Snickers was the best confectionary bar, but I really think it's the Bounty now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really want to take a photo but my phone will make a camera sound.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is an old Asian man on my bus coppin some new balances and wearing sunnies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy shit I just had the best über driver. He had strobe lights, a disco ball, a light up hat, the vengaboys, and he gave me candy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sambgrover maybe they gave me a brand that wasn't subsidised]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sambgrover at that moment I was in post-wisdom removal op pain so I was like "fuck it"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sambgrover I think I still have the receipt, maybe I should get a refund or query at least]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sambgrover yeah I thought it was strange but the pharmacist told me it wasn't funded.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sambgrover this probably happened to me https://t.co/UFbnvlyyen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[R.I.P to all the bananas that got squished at the bottom of the bag.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Monday my lecturer played a Robot Wars video. It was the best thing to happen that day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hypeasgus you should meet the thumbs up guy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you that tramadol is not funded by the govt? It's hella expensive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016 is progressing slow for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They took all my wisdom from me. https://t.co/XWzAsUbViy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I pretty much can't eat or drink for the entire day tomorrow so I've been trying to eat for 2 days in 1 in the space of tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And when they tried to filling a room in their flat someone cancelled their viewing because they lived above the dub step dudes lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This guy I know lives above some dudes that like to throw dub step parties on the reg.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too far into my degree to back out now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't even have to listen to the new drake album and I know it's trash.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kanye tryna be the modern Wagner https://t.co/bNBKyqmH12]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How long do the holes in your mouth take to heal? Oh god I'm just gonna have several craters in the corners of my mouth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My current lock screen FYI. https://t.co/3WpFEjUj7d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gonna get all four of my wisdom teeth yanked on Thursday. Real worried about being in Crofton downs after being on GA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you get such bad hay fever you feel like vomiting real hard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hahaha that was such a stupid thing to say.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>