<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@macgibbons @five15design Including one son, one daughter in law and two grandkids.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@macgibbons Probably had the phone at arm’s length and just made noises every so often to prove he was listening]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@five15design It had better warm up week after next as I’m heading your way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Phil_Wheeler Our lives must have been so boring in the years BT.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Phil_Wheeler Don has asked all female WH staff to dress like women, or something along that line.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education Readings - digital skills/ information literacy/ Seymour Papert / personalised learning / creativity 

https://t.co/42vDKInFo5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RFStew Another judge to be fired by the orange?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevens_phil Ah but according to Bill from his Ratana speech, there’s not much more the government can do. What a visionless govt we have]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelwoodnz Great role model, especially when you look at the Attlee post war government.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phil Cullen:  Skinning Cats Alive. https://t.co/VE3szXPPke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education Readings February 3rd https://t.co/9qRiia00Fn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carol_stirling Preferably after the required stand down period]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carol_stirling No put them on the ‘job seekers’ benefit for a month]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pmbillenglish So my mentally disabled wheelchair bound daughter won’t count as she can’t manage her health issues? Bullshit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kelvin Smythe: Rangiora High School: attempts to discredit Authority decision: explosive staff mtg: why Hekia… https://t.co/73HteQTwJb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please sign this petition: https://t.co/uoY9xtNYdG via @actionstation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robtreacher Hey be nice to our simian relatives…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robtreacher And that’s after one week of the orange.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelwoodnz @AndrewLittleMP I agree. Great to hear him sell a vision of how NZ will be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kelvin Smythe: NZEI has another confused, lightweight leader https://t.co/nZ7GMQ4VAQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IainLG Great to hear Andrew selling a vision!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlastairJNZ Don’t hold your breath]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kelvin Smythe: Parents, teachers, and community of Rangiora High school get a load of this https://t.co/Kly1SHED34]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dfrancishirst Another item for the to do list...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dfrancishirst I've dipped into his work in the past. Forgotten a lot so it's time to revisit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dfrancishirst Must confess I’ve never read Emerson. Will add that to my to do pile]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dfrancishirst Very good. Haven’t read him for many years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TCBGP Don’t be too hasty - he’s only had five days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@five15design No apples in PN New World this week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education Readings:  teacher 'burnout'/ creativity/ Sir Ken Robinson/ and more about Finland https://t.co/iHbyCkMSby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protect Our GM Free Growing Regions  https://t.co/Vvc4BJ37gc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education Readings January 27th https://t.co/GtPk24zVEO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dakinane Would have been very useful when I had a life. These days I don’t do enough to make use of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dakinane I like the bit about opening the garage door when the BMW enters the driveway. Only 2 probs - no BMW &amp; garage is full of stuff...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dakinane Will do but I doubt I’m prolific enough to automate anything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dakinane I vaguely understand that...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dakinane That’s the 3rd time this has been posted….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kelvin Smythe: A famous victory for Peggy Burrows https://t.co/CwBl0T1qyW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phil Cullen: Datafication of education https://t.co/u0hpzofYca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jo_moir Donations to the National Party?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dakinane I think there are elements of both books in the world of 2017, which is possibly even more frightening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[End of the “Oilocene”: The Demise of the Global Oil Industry and of the Global Economic System as we know it.  https://t.co/n6hAAiGyxj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dakinane this tweet is repeating….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phil Cullen: NAPLAN for Mummies. What is the purpose of NAPLAN? https://t.co/HpF9IeiJCV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phil Cullen: NAPLAN for Mummies Intro. https://t.co/zZQACVeRjH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phil Cullen:  NAPLAN for Mummies https://t.co/8ZXyd6W5oo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop proposed risk of polluting New Zealand's largest fresh water spring.  https://t.co/4z9jXORRRH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevens_phil That's my gut feeling and it's good to have empirical data]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevens_phil So what do these entrails tell you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevens_phil Why the sudden rise late last year?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarabeee Ask the younger set - that’s how learned about it and other similar sites.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarabeee You’ll find movies there within days of their international release, sometimes filmed off a cinema screen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarabeee As in are the movies legally able to played? I think you’ll find that Hollywood is definitely not amused.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hah. Andrew Gunn: Speak now, or forever hold your peace   https://t.co/ainwTNJjlP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bruce Hammonds: Reflecting on education - light holiday viewing  https://t.co/i3w1VaBoXo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@norightturnnz @dbseymour Please make it so...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dingfelder Going to produce a brew while kayaking? That’s taking multi tasking to a whole new level.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stsummerfield He was amazingly quick in that car.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@macgibbons Then that’s your problem. Solve it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@macgibbons Obviously too much wine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@macgibbons Only two?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@muzzashow I won the CD from Graham Reid at https://t.co/3ZE9GQaBVN    Prior to that I won the latest Van Morrison CD. Both excellent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@muzzashow It’s bloody good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenSRachinger The religions that predict the end is nigh will finally be proved right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenSRachinger I think I’ll be dead a year or two before it arrives...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matt_mccarten Great to see you on Twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JJPalethorpe Takaka Hill is fine. The views are magnificent which is challenging for the driver who has to keep focus on the road]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RFStew That's a thought provoking article that our myopic politicians should read]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@teachernz Familiar view from the days when I lived in Waikato and BOP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sign the petition: Healthy Ambos Save Lives https://t.co/AmrdP1WFfq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kelvin Smythe: Herald editorial a little gem https://t.co/FP5teYJGeZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Phil_Wheeler Nice bowling action reasonably nippy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Phil_Wheeler Look forward to seeing what you’ve got.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JJPalethorpe Stuff journalists hinted at something, so let’s see how good their crystal balls are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JJPalethorpe I agree. Let’s withhold all speculation until something concrete and undeniable comes out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kelvin Smythe:  Authoritarian and corrupted power: how it works https://t.co/HSbPJejP7A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@macgibbons Far more important people than the majority of the well known.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@macgibbons I think you can safely predict that a lot of well known people will die in 2017.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kelvin Smythe: Sir Patricio Grinch, Wekiu Tomata, Weary Gardener, and Tugger, the then PM https://t.co/tnof9MJ5eZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dfrancishirst yes. this neatly sums up the hypocrisy 

https://t.co/WJCg7O0FE1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JCE_PC @ChrisALee_NZ @Gladwell I’m not sufficiently well read about Ellsberg to form an opinion either way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch this. Very powerful and very true https://t.co/de8n1op0jB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisALee_NZ @JCE_PC @Gladwell  that's a powerful set of tweets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @macgibbons look at this.

I’ll get my coat... https://t.co/goxnGEUYa1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@macgibbons Yes. Won’t drink the suff myself. Gotta be proper ginger beer. Bundaberg not as good as homemade though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mfyfyr Obviously no dog in the house ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LI_politico Not being critical. I’ve been burnt a few times in the past by misleading news so now I’m cautious. This one seems sadly true]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LI_politico Hmm is that a reliable news source?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melulater Will send search and rescue in a couple of hours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SirWB @rodemmerson Yeah and Rod’s a national treasure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArmstrongM_ Congrats. Well done. Make it count.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShakingStick I think White wine in the Sun is better though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShakingStick That’s very good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShakingStick And the best xmas song is? Pretty hard to beat White Wine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@macgibbons Dark chocolate and red wine. Then you can pretend to be healthy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EduWells big brother ….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@solvingme The PACE nonsense from UK was very harmful. I briefly tried GET and gave that up very fast. Promising research from overseas now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@solvingme My niece is a doctor &amp; her training was very much along chronic fatigue lines, with all that entails. My GP was bugger all help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@solvingme That’s very sad. Such a life destroying affliction that non-sufferers do not understand at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@solvingme Am still waiting…. altho better than I was at my lowest in 2012.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>