<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Well this is going to be an interesting next four years of Obama admin folks responding to Trump admin in real time… https://t.co/O4u5zS1FMY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now @SenJackReed readout of call with Australians to reassure post 'Trump tantrum': https://t.co/SyTDpqDeP5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OH in the newsroom: Editor: "Who is that you were just tweeting photos of?" Reporter: "Beyonce?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The Pentagon wanted to launch the attack on a moonless night and the next one would come after his term had ended.… https://t.co/shnnDeXQuu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Lighthearted" security talks between hombres. https://t.co/J0lvnh96ki]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SenJohnMcCain writes to @POTUS urging lethal defensive assistance for Ukraine in wake of renewed Russian offensiv… https://t.co/X9roNYpB6h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But reports on the conversation with Australian leader definitely wrong, sounded nothing like this: https://t.co/uvzSewVjuZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump to focus counter-extremism program solely on Islam - sources https://t.co/y2SgdMtoHG @Reuters But it's NOT a Muslim ban.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talk about burying lede: Trump threatens to invade Mexico-"I just might send [US military] down to take care of it.” https://t.co/vrJD1aycZ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ideologues in Trump White House Cut ‘Grown-ups’ Out of the Loop https://t.co/fF1PssEfu0 @ForeignPolicy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First the JFK taxi strike, and now this?! *New York implodes* https://t.co/3fBrynEDC4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For years: How fear has slammed the door on refugees https://t.co/1TSD3eWWgb https://t.co/uRG96e6uMh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To claims US 'can't' vet: 'Iraqis, Syrians &amp; Iranians ... far &amp; away the most well-documented refugees we interview' https://t.co/tVWbBeVI8y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DHS IG opens investigation of Muslim ban rollout, orders document preservation https://t.co/0iSIYpVxHy by @rdevro @mazmhussain @alicesperi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SenBobCorker on Senate confirming Trump Secretary of State Rex Tillerson: https://t.co/0SB8ZUDtxW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NSC Advisor Flynn statement on Iran: https://t.co/AE96Svmiu8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have to read this @helenecooper story: A Washington Correspondent’s Own Refugee Experience - &amp; let yourself cry. https://t.co/F1D5B41ntg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Somebody ought to tell the Iraqis” @SenJohnMcCain to @ForeignPolicy report DHS said ban didn't apply to Iraqi SIVs https://t.co/zCWb97eTgH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“No member of the Homeland Security team knowingly ignored court order” DHS Chief Pushes Back Over Trump Refugee Ban https://t.co/zCWb96Xip9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This may be my fave @SenBobCorker -ism yet, on refugee ban chaos: “It may be that this is the way they want to roll” https://t.co/zCWb96Xip9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“This is not — I repeat — this is not a ban on Muslims" DHS Chief Pushes Back Amid Confusion Over Trump Refugee Ban https://t.co/zCWb96Xip9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I didn't get involved in correcting grammar &amp; reformatting the thing." DHS Chief Pushes Back Over Trump Travel Ban https://t.co/zCWb96Xip9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As confusion abounds over Trump refugee ban, even critics say: “It may be that this is the way they want to roll.” https://t.co/zCWb96Xip9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the Kennedy Center to see the Mariinsky Ballet. Much, much better… https://t.co/KK70XgBKAM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We ought to let a few days go by &amp; not light our hair on fire until...they and we fully understand what they’ve done" @SenBobCorker on EO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICYMI: @DHSgov says Iraqi SIVs allowed to board planes, enter US-DOD, Congress, CBP airlines just don't know it yet. https://t.co/Z3T0HrOTDs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@AP - @DHSgov told @ForeignPolicy earlier under its reading of ban SIVs shld be allowed to enter US after screenin… https://t.co/13f0Pf1zYp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Acting AG Boente says OLC reviewed @POTUS migration EO  (was disputed)"both lawful on its face and properly drafted" https://t.co/D2fWu0EsaU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Acting AG Boente wastes no time issuing DOJ new guidance on enforcing @POTUS refugee ban EO: "both lawful on its fa… https://t.co/HGat8SAgcv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Short and sweet - @POTUS statement on appointing Thomas D. Homan acting ICE director (no mention of removing Dan Ra… https://t.co/wcxRqsnDH8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JohnWDean - would love to talk to you about the implications, to the extent to which I am saying so publicly in a tweet, yes, I know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Nixon WH counsel, folks: https://t.co/cgTj14Tngk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is so true it hurts. https://t.co/6ize4bszkh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pre @DHSgov Secretary John Kelly to me in '16: Advised brass "stay out of the cesspool of domestic politics” https://t.co/iqmXDVkwv3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then SOUTHCOM command, now DHS Sec Kelly to me in '14:“I salute every order I’m given — every legal order I’m given” https://t.co/YCeDGqDS8W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full statement from @DHSgov Dir John Kelly on naming Thomas D. Homan acting ICE director (replacing Ragsdale, who i… https://t.co/pM9isLUepq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full statement from @POTUS on firing acting AG Sally Yates who said wouldn't defend executive order refugee ban b/c… https://t.co/YeEOFeSSk0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING:POTUS fires acting AG Yates for "betrayal" EO: Obama appointee "weak on borders""very weak on immigration" (though he kept her on)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow @RubyMellen for @ForeignPolicy coverage of protests of Trump immigration ban EO outside SCOTUS as acting AG… https://t.co/qSzUA62FOx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Acting AG Yates statement directing DOJ lawyers not to defend immigration executive order, per @nytimes… https://t.co/hen1QaWVty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex of delay to @SenatorSessions having real consequences for @POTUS agenda: Acting AG Yates won't defend EO per @CNN https://t.co/zdu9upFJFu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@DefenseBaron Helpful tips from the DART Center for Journalism &amp; Trauma on reporting on sexual violence! https://t.co/fgTp0DdoID]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UPDATE: DHS says Iraqis on SIVs to be allowed to board planes,enter US casebycase (DoD/CBP/Hill haven't gotten memo) https://t.co/Z3T0HrOTDs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will be interesting to watch how Congress responds ... https://t.co/tEKnBBpUeL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats will attempt to rescind Trump’s travel ban https://t.co/SwAiJVcT3i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“My 1st interpreter was murdered by Al Qaeda and we were able to get his family here...Now we have thousands stuck" https://t.co/Z3T0HrOTDs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pentagon Scrambles to Make Exception for Iraqi Translators Trump Ban's Wake @paulmcleary @Ksurana6 @ForeignPolicy https://t.co/Z3T0HrOTDs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@RepKinzinger a veteran of wars in Iraq and Afghanistan: https://t.co/OQg9TmGsOu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@POTUS continues to push back on outcry over executive order's ban on refugees and certain immigrants: https://t.co/yE32wu8XC8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[?: Would court stays have any retroactive recourse for those w/ valid visas rejected wk before EO signed? @Ksurana6 https://t.co/8iEc8C0in5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘It Could Have Easily Been Me’: Why Thousands Protested Against Immigration Ban https://t.co/reCm55xcI2 @RobbieGramer @RubyMellen @ReidStan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Defies Courts as Chaos, Protests, and Lawsuits Erupt Over Immigration Ban https://t.co/sS56D2qgm0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Someone on the call looked up at a TV...'The president is signing the executive order that we're discussing'" https://t.co/s3rUaJl9l2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@katieengelhart in my living room! CC: @CornellDailySun https://t.co/1fVQVIiJuL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@POTUS defiant on ban.Frmr US mil interpreter's child asks:'Why don't they want us in America?' https://t.co/sS56D2qgm0 @Ksurana6 @bhojanio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@DHSgov Kelly deems "entry of lawful permanent residents to be in the national interest" | Chaos Over Refugee Ban https://t.co/sS56D2qgm0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@DHSgov Sec John Kelly steps in on immigration EO: "I hereby deem the entry of lawful permanent residents to be in… https://t.co/H6mhGK6Fse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slew of current/former DHS/State Dept tell @ForeignPolicy - @POTUS executive refugee ban is legal+moral clusterfuck. https://t.co/sS56D2qgm0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sami, who worked w/US Army in Iraq, had boarded, his kids watching cartoons. |“‘Why they don’t want us in America?’” https://t.co/sS56D2qgm0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SenBobCorker chairman of the Senate Foreign Relations Committee, some 36 hours later: https://t.co/6mE8q6H0Ff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Sadly weak' on immigration, says @POTUS directly attacking two sitting GOP senators (who overall have been very qu… https://t.co/1NOJwJEat8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@POTUS defends executive order, taking swipes at media, Obama: "To be clear, this is not a Muslim ban, as the medi… https://t.co/WPdqoW97GN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SenJohnMcCain @LindseyGrahamSC (better-late-than-never?) on @POTUS EO: "will become a self-inflicted wound in the… https://t.co/J36kwbHix7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WH in Reversal Says Green Card Holders Won’t Be Barred...but border agents have “discretionary authority” to detain https://t.co/iAh7TSP6Dp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@POTUS responds, in his way, to the chaos of the implementation of the refugee ban executive order: https://t.co/uOlBZssb6a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DHS to stay on EO: Will "continue to enforce," "prohibited travel will remain prohibited," "retains its right to re… https://t.co/mheE9RAbrM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. servicemember killed in raid on AQAP in Yemen on Jan. 28: https://t.co/600rmouQRX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inside the confusion of the Trump executive order and travel ban @CNNPolitics https://t.co/f8zL4N2rQn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING:US District Court Judge in NY stays deportations after @POTUS ban bars refugees, others from 7 ME countries https://t.co/cPK64HQL2Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm curious what @SenJohnMcCain -force behind refugee program for Vietnam &amp; region after war- thinks about @POTUS EO https://t.co/UJOEhOo8JY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feb '16: Iraqi woman interpreter for US mil fled after death threats, joins US mil, becomes US citizen-family stuck. https://t.co/hzqls1aHP3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UPDATED: Ripple Effects of Trump’s Refugee Ban |"We were totally prepared ... It's working out very nicely.” -@POTUS https://t.co/8iEc8C0in5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The NY Taxi union can - https://t.co/lbIStKH0ib https://t.co/551iOgtz7Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for those impacted by ban-family/visa holders/US mil interpreters+their units/refugees/ imm+const lawyers/diplos-pls get in touch!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Ksurana6 &amp; I on immigrants w/valid visas being barred, spike in civil rights complaints wk BEFORE Trump signed ban https://t.co/8iEc8C0in5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Readout WH call between @POTUS and Putin: https://t.co/XdsAN3DNLP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Other area in Trump EO 'ISIS plan': ID new coalition partners in anti-ISIS fight/'policies to empower coalition par… https://t.co/HHVsjtzjWw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch in Trump EO 'ISIS plan': 'recommended changes to any US rules of engagement' DOD touts min-civ casualties dif… https://t.co/sgLL71TZ0B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@POTUS who wouldn't reveal his anti-ISIS 'secret' plan during elex, now signs exec doc asking gens for anti-ISIS p… https://t.co/ip2ZDXGcTe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But the key question becomes what can, and will, Congress do. https://t.co/0Gvd3gYMzf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If New Yorkers weren't mad yet (protests indicate many are, in fairness), they sure as hell will be now. https://t.co/lbIStKH0ib]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Key note here: detainees immigrants and visa holders could challenge on habeas grounds --&gt; https://t.co/fEcP2UIjga]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not a verified account but purports to be Gen Flynn's son praising "#muslimban" which WH is disputing: https://t.co/Ap5plfSYyC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump team in touch for many wks w/key State/DHS officials on Muslim EO."Everyone who needed to know was informed."Not what I'm told/seeing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greencard need 'waiver' to return. Dont know yet what 'in transit' means for refugees. Told "everyone who needed to know" at State/DHS.-WH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently WH pool got an hour long background briefing from senior admin official on refugee ban EO. Would've loved that. Highlights:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@POTUS first address highlights first week and other executive actions but leaves out Muslim ban.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Refugee Ban Has Ripple Effects Even Before It’s Issued:  Arab students deported. DHS stops refugee interviews. https://t.co/8iEc8C0in5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TylerSpenceRSEN thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing to add: https://t.co/dYx76HMLA7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lastly, today I'm reminded of an editor I had, who once told me: "I don't give a fuck about refugees." Guess it was a story after all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's the point. Both parties. https://t.co/ku0Rb4IdaE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exactly my point. And Bush have to him. https://t.co/ayWP5P0jms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EliBWatkins thanks! Couldn't find for some reason. Interesting list]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UPDATED with Executive Order: Trump’s Refugee Ban Has Ripple Effects Even Before It’s Issued https://t.co/8iEc8C0in5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing to add: https://t.co/P75mkjagLc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlanRobinsonFW Not evidence, ISIS wishlist. Got ex ISIS infiltrated refugee pop, made past screening, into US, attacked? If you do, call WH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friday night fun: Help me find orig 14 cosponsors of Refugee Act (-Kennedy)https://t.co/RbY9YeuIwu doesn't do pre'81 https://t.co/nS1OrJ79hy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome to the awesome,broad, virtually unchallenged executive power of @POTUS over nat'l security &amp; foreign policy you used to rail against]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As written, @POTUS EO based on Islamophobia &amp; yet per law, needs no other reason &amp; virtually impossible to challenge https://t.co/SSjhrlzBl7]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>