<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Great stuff Wayne and Ben. Looking forward to seeing the results. #kickingperformance @UC_RISE https://t.co/XpUcXHVQVE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New: Autonomic cardiac regulation, BP &amp; CRF: Effect of different training doses in elderly https://t.co/aQtPCYN3xi @UC_RISE @mikebotek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heart rate, heart rate variability and inflammatory biomarkers among young and healthy adults @mikebotek https://t.co/zfUgItHfLA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$60k grant to bring UC’s DNA ancestry lab a step closer - University of Canberra https://t.co/hglPJzgRuD via @UniCanberra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supplementation, muscle damage &amp; inflammation markers following DHR in females https://t.co/5q5jUO5u3c  @JessicaKohne @mikeormsbee @UC_RISE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lowering the Bar on the Low-Fat Diet https://t.co/MupbWpGTeu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Habib_Noorbhai @UCT_news @ProfTimNoakes All the best Habib!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blood from human teens rejuvenates body and brains of old mice https://t.co/hX5a6iSZbk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supplementation to Reduce Muscle Damage &amp; Improve Recovery Following Exercise in Females https://t.co/EH7RGG1k0q @JessicaKohne @UC_RISE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ithinkmad hi, you should be able to message me now. Or go to the Clearinghouse link to find UC Sport Studies Honours Application details.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UniCanberra Sports Studies Hons 2017 Applications.4x $6000 Scholarships Available @UC_RISE @theACTAS Go to https://t.co/gr21JlTz4q or DM me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UniCanberra  Sport &amp; Exercise Science Student Olympic Lifting Practical. Thanks Aaron Holt from @Ausport.… https://t.co/XtwoWROua1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations @mikebotek on presentation representing @UPOlomouc and @UC_RISE at #SMAConf16 @UCFacultyHealth… https://t.co/CBbHwq2emv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Japan study trip a sumo-sized learning experience - University of Canberra https://t.co/3wMt0qhScG via @UniCanberra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@btvaughan hope week 3 of #EmpowerRugby for girls went well today https://t.co/3pHQviXMSd @WorldRugby @AustralianRugby @Aussie7s @UC_RISE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why the Women’s 800 Will Be the Most Controversial Race at the Olympics https://t.co/DDjARUjpbj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Training camp aims to fill gap in girls' rugby in Canberra https://t.co/KSbP68B4x4 via @abcnews @UC_RISE @UniCanberra @UCFacultyHealth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#mdpichildren Effects of Cardiorespiratory Fitness &amp; Obesity on Salivary SIgA &amp; Alpha-Amylase https://t.co/oiKv1OsJXN  @MDPIOpenAccess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New paper with @MsDottyS Effects of CRF &amp; obesity on Salivary SIgA &amp; alpha-amylase in obese children https://t.co/oiKv1OsJXN  @UC_RISE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Four Things Your Spit Can Reveal by @sarahshmee https://t.co/yuuZw5ZneA via @inversedotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gender empowerment through rugby https://t.co/eyZmKF8wt9 via @queanbeyanage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[American football in #Japan played by @UniCanberra Sport Science Students @NewColomboPlan #Hiroshima #FukuyamaHeisei https://t.co/qB3CtemKMt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[American football played in #Japan by @UniCanberra Sport Science students @NewColomboPlan #Hiroshima #FukuyamaHeisei https://t.co/XLvNfSPLNd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UniCanberra Sport &amp; Exercise Science Students in #Japan Exercise also Unites Cultures thanks @NewColomboPlan https://t.co/4pjbVlCCOG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exploring the traditions of Sumo. Sport Scientists in #Japan @UniCanberra @NewColomboPlan https://t.co/FjNTAYxFDP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Walks547 @MenaspaP @ScienceforSport thanks Anthony.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chronic occupational exposures can influence the rate of PTSD and depressive disorders in first responders and... https://t.co/6spcN4gjAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out "Empower Rugby - the Rugby Union program for girls" https://t.co/XuNyATjCd8 @Eventbrite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KirstenEverett @ECSS2016 All the best for your presentation!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT decreases Th-2 cytokines in HIV-infected individuals on ART #ECSS2016 @takshita10 represents @UKZNCHS &amp; @UC_RISE https://t.co/U3LxXr2D8p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New systematic rev with UC Nutrition: Effects of Resveratrol Supplementation in Overweight &amp; Obese Humans https://t.co/8byWC1doSU @UC_RISE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New pub with UC Nutrition: Effect of Dietary Supplementation of Green Tea Catechins on CVD Risk https://t.co/gKYV27UVnf @UC_RISE @UKZNCHS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review with UC Nutrition l-Theanine as a Functional Food Additive: Role in Disease Prevention &amp; Health  https://t.co/LvaDmBGpB7  @UC_RISE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Impacts of obesity &amp; stress on neuromuscular fatigue development &amp; associated HRV https://t.co/YhdTZK8ZRn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, definitely teaching about carbohydrate, identification of amount in different foods works well in our house. https://t.co/G74lFZH8ul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading an opponent's face gives the edge in martial arts https://t.co/WP6SepKXO0 via @PsyPost @UC_RISE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perspectives on stress resilience and adolescent neurobehavioral function https://t.co/jurBanwecW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The impact of developmental timing for stress and recovery https://t.co/hWCMD3NBHY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The microbiome: A key regulator of stress and neuroinflammation https://t.co/od0SSDjRy7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Relations between plasma oxytocin and cortisol: The stress buffering role of social support https://t.co/JCNCSqoTu6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video Gaming Disorder and Sport and Exercise in Emerging Adulthood: A Longitudinal Study https://t.co/EBhcxZnAvO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stress Biomarkers, Mood States, &amp; Sleep during Major Swimming Competition: “Success” &amp; “Failure” Athlete's Profiles https://t.co/fJRrd0aGym]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salivary Amylase as a Stress Biomarker
https://t.co/zB190PZF1x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stress, salivary biomarkers, &amp; ambulatory blood pressure in parents of children with autism spectrum disorders. https://t.co/1OHJmg6YW1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Secretory IgA reactivity to social threat in youth: Relations with HPA, ANS, and behavior. - PubMed - NCBI https://t.co/xpwRWiIZYD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Family Relations, Stress, and Vulnerability: Biobehavioral Implication.... https://t.co/jp7L82vd4v https://t.co/6QDkTI5VEA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prematurity, Birth Weight, &amp; Socioeconomic Status Are Linked to Atypical Diurnal HPA Activity in Young Adults. https://t.co/fpTY7LQnGY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elderly to Benefit from Study by Master’s Saliva Researcher https://t.co/wWePdeWt4D @UKZN @UC_RISE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Regulation of Transforming Growth Factor β–Activated Kinase Activation .... https://t.co/0sWUdArKfp https://t.co/zLLXEBxU3d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tim Noakes: caught in a turf war over an inconvenient truth? https://t.co/TgxDLQlyxa via @biznewsCOM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SJSemple macrophages and cytokines have a possible role in the underlying mechanism. https://t.co/jmEwTSDroY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SJSemple got some ideas about this. https://t.co/6PxDPwqkJl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salivary Biomarkers of Physical Fatigue as Markers of Sleep Deprivation https://t.co/UxDgbuwxOU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SJSemple @benrattray interesting! https://t.co/lhPFQpXVx5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breakfasts Higher in Protein Increase Postprandial EE &amp; Fat Oxidation, &amp; Reduce Hunger in Overweight Children https://t.co/dtam6RyAal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Zealand becomes first country to specifically warn against low carb, paleo and intermittent fasti… https://t.co/sVcqCInOvn via @grantsnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Association of ACTN3 R577X gene variants with elite rugby union player status &amp; playing position @sjsemple https://t.co/vanqWqL3CV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coconut Comeback - Landline - ABC https://t.co/9AJqm2SD1x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Understanding elevated hair cortisol levels in sport and exercise science  https://t.co/k2dZ0FMR6K @SJSemple]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hair samples may help predict mental illness in children https://t.co/3gcSpipB9p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clubs win battle with AFL over GPS technology provider, league broker deal with Catapult and Champion Data https://t.co/zXTFRAMfIe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Acute immune-inflammatory responses to a single bout of aerobic exercise in smokers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blunted cardiovascular and cortisol reactivity to acute psychological stress: good or bad? https://t.co/EvMWV9ImYv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Postexercise hot water immersion induces heat acclimation and improves .... https://t.co/gsXGzL2NPZ https://t.co/gKl3MsHmTj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cachexia: The last illness : Nature News &amp; Comment https://t.co/fMiOdJ2eUy via @NatureNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salivary Hormones Response to Preparation and Pre-competitive Training of World-class Level Athletes https://t.co/gXUrncUGO4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barry Richards holds the bat with which he made 325 in a day in his right hand, and David Warner's in his left https://t.co/oPevTpavtU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done Taks. PhD Strength training in HIV infected individuals receiving ART. @UKZNCHS @UC_RISE @UCFacultyHealth  https://t.co/7TFp5Qbq9l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Takshita10 congratulations Taks. Great memories.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAJA Keeping Pace With The Times https://t.co/bk3FVQKvAt via @sportingpost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see you @waynelombard. Doing excellent work as Head of Athletic Performance Liaoning Province China Hockey  https://t.co/id9xvpbCv2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exercise immunology: a skeletal muscle perspective. - PubMed - NCBI https://t.co/aJLJBNLn5Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tim Noakes: why I’ve been waiting for this trial for years https://t.co/9AnVlJeGAA via @biznewsCOM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent. Positive role models fight the image created of Africa https://t.co/YGpYHgPfTI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see you Wayne! Anytime! https://t.co/7h6IQ5Xfhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All Blacks legend Jonah Lomu dies aged 40 https://t.co/866AksaxD4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benrattray Thanks. Very useful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Springboks: A true sleeping rugby giant
https://t.co/2IZSWdKDpH

via @TheRoarSports]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dr Nic Gill, low carb, low sugar and the, All Blacks https://t.co/GZhfL3nRWM via @grantsnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Student creates app for vets to prevent night terrors https://t.co/icadJDo1IY via @usatoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vertical Jump: Russian Plyometrics Compilation for High Jumpers https://t.co/pnd3QKZq8I via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UCFacultyHealth Sport &amp; Exercise Students learning how to coach with @Ausport Senior S&amp;C Coach Ross Smith https://t.co/GLnQfY3uSN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Added sugar makes eating healthy almost impossible https://t.co/uLL83pqFDQ via @TIME]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Effect of resistance training on CRP, glucose &amp; lipid profile in older women with differing levels of RT experience. https://t.co/CYTpazDN80]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missing out on @SASMA2015 but @UC_RISE @UKZNCHS @FSUResearch  represented by @Takshita10 @JessicaKohne @DonaldsonJaymie Enjoy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[70m 200kg Farmers Walk Event at Canberra Highland Gathering. http://t.co/KCio9VnjCJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canberra Highland Gathering - Tartan Warrior Competition. Weight for height event. http://t.co/pwqJHpNRt2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tartan warrior at the Canberra Highland Gathering today. Thats 25kgs being thrown over 15 foot high bar. http://t.co/QipIU4Entc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UC, Sport &amp; Exercise Sci Hons 2016 Info Evening. Thur 15th Oct DM for details @benrattray @SJSemple @jocelynmara1 @OlanScott @SportPsychAus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Communication key for S&amp;C coaches Ross Smith @Ausport working with @UCFacultyHealth Sport Science students @UC_RISE http://t.co/5AUPGLbVaf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[University of Canberra Sport Science undergrads in the S&amp;C Facility at the AIS Thanks Ross Smith @Ausport @UC_RISE http://t.co/GDEhozVOXl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dietary fats and immune status in athletes: clinical implications. http://t.co/Pud48awgy5 #EuropePMC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plenty of options available to study the benefits of coconut oil on health and performance #coconuts http://t.co/yK2hEJH03v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great slide showing relationship between basic science and medical research #coconuts http://t.co/muBWckScuu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Important to consider the physical and chemical changes in PUFA oil when deep fat frying. #coconut http://t.co/D2qhnpokAJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Medium chain triglycerides - physiological effects. Beneficial for health and performance? #coconuts http://t.co/tBoLblYCnM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting study examining efficacy of virgin #coconut oil in reducing visceral fat http://t.co/kBdHTLqSAN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Antimicrobial effects of lauric acid derivatives. I'm wondering about benefits relating to URTI in athletes #coconuts http://t.co/CAGt6OFvFc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting effects of #coconut oil in Alzheimers. How about recovery from concussion? http://t.co/AvdXZftnTC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More research required on the "Tropical Diet" - Lauric acid. #coconuts http://t.co/j1soGxE1VJ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>