<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@donlothario It's like a kommunalka, except the kommunalkas were really cheap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you find yourself on the same side of the political fence as Michael McDowell, it's a sure sign that things are very fucked indeed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@allyofreason @AcademicsSay misunderstanding what "socially constructed" means. I'd give him a D; did not read or understand the supporting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@allyofreason @AcademicsSay but back to Pinker. That paragraph shows a woeful understanding of basic social science terms, most egregiously]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@allyofreason @AcademicsSay where her "arguments" hinge primarily on stating facts in a mocking tone, and using the same word to describe...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@allyofreason @AcademicsSay CHS's analyses of pretty much everything are terrible. You might know her from her "Factual Feminist" videos...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@allyofreason @AcademicsSay plus here, also p341 he says "many women" and only cites Christina Hoff Somers. https://t.co/T1nxNXNvF7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@allyofreason @AcademicsSay All 3 of those claims are nonsense; Pinker's just setting up a straw feminist to knock down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@allyofreason @AcademicsSay it's hard to do in a tweet, but here's a excerpt from p341 of The Blank Slate... https://t.co/w9s8lkWuDC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ccourtne also, same page. TOP FUCKING NOTCH UNDERSTANDING, STEVEN. https://t.co/uNeP6lDiCh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ccourtne sorry that's upside down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ccourtne p341 The Blank Slate OH CHRISTINA HOFF SOMMERS. NICE CITATION STEVEN. https://t.co/eQcXEG5Rgw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ccourtne Pinker showing, once again, that social science is definitely not his field.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onetruecathal I wonder if Paddy Power is taking bets on a bona fide coup happening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onetruecathal When I saw that my first thought was "Fuck off, like you already know all that."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikamckinnon I'm more worried about @EndaKennyTD's gleeful toadying than the shamrock itself, tbh. Maybe we can send @PresidentIRL instead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikamckinnon But I hope Ireland will be brave and stand on the right side of history, even knowing that there may be repercussions for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikamckinnon Morally and symbolically it's the correct thing to do, but I'm not sure we have the clout to tell the US to do anything...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[fence-sitting neutrality. Not sending the poxy shamrock would be a good start.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While I understand that it's an iffy move, diplomatically, I really would rather we exercised a little more equilibrium in our...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ronanlyons That's beside the point. It is fucking unconscionable regardless of what tech company any of these people may or may not found.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dj_mckeown It's been yonks since I read that book, but I think it has some relevant medical examples.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dj_mckeown Couple of other bits that might be of use:
https://t.co/bRgGOv8VDw
and
https://t.co/XXBsyk29Ge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dj_mckeown the word "androcentrism" will be your best bet for google-fu.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dj_mckeown there's good stuff written @roseveleth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SexSiopa You're not a foreigner - you're certified Irish!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlynneStark you don't liberate women by telling them what they can or cannot wear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@froodie Check thermostats, boilers, and electric heaters and storage heaters. You've got yerself a bimetallic strip on the loose.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stay frosty, kids. https://t.co/Qks4hxwMkC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MargaretEWard Also, I've been doing a lot of hammer-related DIY, so it's worked out nicely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HELlCOPTERS @Colmogorman Good christ, man, how much do you think wool costs? You may as well ask how people funded cardboard protest signs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didn't write 'em. https://t.co/Ow1lcm9jt5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From https://t.co/nmvHAU0l3j

He ran and dropped out. https://t.co/Yk7jJsVeWs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CivMaint you know, I don't believe Marx ever wrote anything on sexy boy-on-boy action.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CivMaint Him and The Green Knight, I mean.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CivMaint Pretty homoerotic story with all the kissin'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CivMaint Tom Hardy is way more craic than Thomas, though. Have you read him? Jaysus, he's a drag.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CivMaint An admittedly cute answer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CivMaint Bitch, I know my Tom Hardy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CivMaint I guess the people don't like limos. ¯\_(ツ)_/¯]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CivMaint Well, DJT said "we are transferring power from Washington, D.C. and giving it back to you, the American People."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CivMaint Low energy shitpost. Sad!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NeilBudgie @SexSiopa Piers Morgan is *for* a male of the human species? One male in particular? That seems terribly objectifying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Piers Morgan even for? https://t.co/ObtrguiwF0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garethstack @SMRepairCafe ...or was(?)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garethstack There is one! @SMRepairCafe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ccourtne
Drizzly is red,
Glitter is pretty,
Time for the sparklebear's https://t.co/3K6cvd1bcE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Despite what William Reville thinks, people coming to this country are not "replacing" us; they *are* us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shepard Fairey's poster reminds me of when I saw a woman in a tricolour hijab at the Easter Rising centenary. https://t.co/MNyxg2Iva2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oldmalley Try the video with sound.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Italian" is not a species.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll not be buying the @IrishTimes for the foreseeable. 

Not even for the crosswords.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ccourtne both unpleasant, both delirious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a watermark in my bathroom I've been trying to paint over for 3 days. I swear to every saint in every hagiography that it's haunted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dublinbusnews big thanks to the drivers on the 38 and 4. They were massively nice as I got lost all over north Dublin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GerryMcBride Fukkin' worth it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WTF is this shit?
https://t.co/mLyOlY85WD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free speech relates to government censorship. Not whether or not a private publications refuses to publish your bullshit or not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Following editorial line is not a contradiction of "free speech".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@roryhtreanor "News outlet" is probably stretching it when it's just one guy and some of his imaginary friends posting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ellenmcoyne I'm very angry, but have quite a deep voice. I could try rubbing bits styrofoam together while glaring, if that helps.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone know of any late bars (bar the Greyhound), opium dens, underground raves, illegal karaoke bars, or *anything* in Blanchardstown?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WIRED interrupted, is having it interrupted twice. Punishing someone for doing what you want them to is really bad UX.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WIRED Could you please stop bringing up the "Thank you" overlay when I turn off my adblocker. The only thing worse than having my reading..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not to miss the bigger picture here, but half of the phrases in Pell's bullshit piece in the IT weren't even correctly defined.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raven_cooke Nothing says "unambiguous disapproval" like uncritically publishing gleefully neo-fascist diatribe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenLynnRuane @IrishTimesOpEd The piece is awful. The comment I linked points out exactly the linguistic game that Pell is trying to pull.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenLynnRuane Sometimes they're useful, though. Like this comment on Pell's obnoxious piece in the IT: https://t.co/Wn9TYDlBqI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CivMaint @JesterNrx also UAE isn't Qatar. Different country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CivMaint @JesterNrx with an 85% expat population, hardly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ireland I wouldn't exactly put embassies into the "waste of money" category. Plus Ireland spends €23m per day on education now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CivMaint @JesterNrx I was in Doha recently. Looks a bit like the right picture.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Doha atm. A particular thing I've noticed is the complete lack of hostile architecture in public spaces.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emptying my handbag before flying tomorrow. I swear I could play bingo with its contents and the airport "banned items" poster.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danobrien20 I wonder if it could have anything to do with where @simoncoveney's home constituency is. Hmm...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rubberbandits Well, they started off being part owned by Orbit Communications Company, which is Saudi. So take what you will from that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't find if they have a policy of ensuring artists get a fee for their work, too, but I really hope so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[will work together to devise a mechanism to assist selfemployed artists who have applied for Jobseekers Allowance. 

Great!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just spotted this in @creativeirl plan:  The Departments of Arts, Heritage, Regional, Rural and Gaeltacht Affairs and Social Protection...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ccourtne On a side note, despite prepper tendencies, this will most likely be my reaction to the apocalypse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ccourtne I'll gently press single-serving nutella packets into your hand and whisper "God speed."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ccourtne I will hopefully be hiding in a bunker by then. That naked dude in the Wicklow mountains most assuredly had the right idea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ccourtne I also bought 20 individual serving packets of emergency jam in Dealz.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ccourtne Wait. Other way around.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ccourtne In col. A, Mr Price has emergency blankets for €1.49. 
In col. B, hmu on DM, if you want. x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ccourtne In personal or global terms, or both?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ccourtne I find buying pocket-sized apocalypse supplies very soothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, what would have been a really good idea to do, in hindsight, in Weimar Germany? Asking for no particular or pertinent reason at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My fucking drill battery just fucking exploded. https://t.co/tQCYMSNjbq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plus another good handful of poxes on all my loft floor panels for each being 20mm too long.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A thousand poxes on my attic joists for being neither exactly square nor evenly spaced.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@janeruffino Her website hasn't been updated in quite a while, but Sharon White's stuff is really great. https://t.co/pyopIDcojC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PunkinOnWheels Can it be used to describe taking your wheelchair off a ramp for a sweet jump? https://t.co/ZsGjnpXCxG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ccourtne Are we still hailing The Morrígan? I'm into it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Glinner No fish in ten did?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonorafferty @SandraVelthuis I heard an story about a report years ago in the welfare dept. in Ireland I must also tell you about.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SandraVelthuis Where is it all coming from? I really think the Irish were much less begrudging of social supports a couple of years ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SandraVelthuis Hope all's good with you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SandraVelthuis Not too bad at the moment. Just reaching the winding down point of a hectic and stressful couple of months.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SandraVelthuis the last year or so. I really have to wonder where it's coming from.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>