<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["You never grow in good times" - thank you Myles Monroe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I live for my legacy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make every moment count...life is short!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cannot sleep? Use your imagination to create your next big thing....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cannot sleep? Work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cannot sleep? Read]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cannot sleep? Pray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Work when your energy is the highest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm preparing for marriage as I wait.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am grateful for a change in my perspective.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goal is to read 55 books this year..about 1 per week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm too busy focusing on my legacy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Father help me to wait well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be honest and you can be free....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slow down, reflect and revise whenever necessary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge yourself and you will never judge others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always balance fun into all you do...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happiness to me: living the life of my dreams - as I please.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make everything humorous....thank you Chris Tucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch and listen you will learn a lot - thank you Jennifer Lawrence....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jennifer Lawrence thank you, "I give no thought to fear - I keep going until I get it"....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business will never end when you do what others won't - be vulnerable - be trustworthy - be honest  - have integrity - always.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love education - because education is the foundation of all we achieve and all we are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't need to move fast - you just need to MOVE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are willing to learn anything - you can do anything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn all you can - you will grow at an intensified rate....
Thank you John Maxwell....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Real Estate: never stop following up - thank you Epic Real Estate Podcast.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Working - while listening to some great podcasts - life is good. Thank you for wisdom, knowledge and understanding.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At this point in my life...age 40...If I don't love it, I don't do it! 
If I don't want to do it, I don't !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I created my business model in my own unique way - be authentic, be you and have fun!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kill your distractions and you will advance in LIFE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd rather live fearless versus fearful....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Worry is a complete waste of time"  - thank you Joyce Meyer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Changing your diet (eating well) - more than mere exercise can help you lose weight - thank you TD Jakes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love yourself - forgive yourself daily if necessary. Then get moving towards your legendary life!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you have any idea how important self-love is??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sacrifice is never easy - but very worth it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The more money I save - the more we can save, invest and allow our money to grow....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Write what you know and people will forever love you"  - thank you Quincy Jones....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the world and the world will love you back - guaranteed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do what you love - follow your heart - don't chase money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Authenticity is my brand - be real always - people love and respect - real-ness. Just be real, not fake - be real!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Authenticity is valuable to your audience. Show your weaknesses and your strengths.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see myself as a pioneer - I don't want to follow - I want to lead - I want to make all things new...my own way. - that's magic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must push past our fears - but not allowing the emotion to control us....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fear nothing and you can do anything...
Do anything have no fears....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waste your time - and you waste your life...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You were created to influence your world - thank you Myles Monroe (this man is brilliant to me)....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you make a mistake - forgive yourself quickly and move on with your life - thank you Myles Monroe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine it in your mind - take action on that idea - and you will see results. Thank you for legacy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Use your mistakes - to maximize your potential in the future - thank you Evan Carmichael]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have all power - you decide to give it away!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's next for me: book # 3, new house, 2 dogs.....#smiling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to the Dave Ramsey podcast - best way to start my day - the way I always start my day 🤣- next Chris Brown "True Stewardship".....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love being a woman - I love our power, our love, our strength. And how we change the world.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know how many books I will write in my life time - but I have so many stories to tell - #49]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Knowing your distractions is good - you know what to ignore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must pray for Donald Trump not condemn him. Support him, stand beside him, hate doesn't bring the best healing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will know I am here - because I will make my mark!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Work Hard + Be Diligent + Accomplish Goals + Have Fun + Implement Balance = Good LIFE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My visions are the dreams that keep coming back - that is why I am here - thank you Myles Monroe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am grateful for simplicity....thank you Myles Monroe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have a narrow focus - focus on your call, your assignment, your purpose - thank you Myles Monroe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vision controls your choices - I am grateful for good choices - thank you Myles Monroe....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vision simplifies life - thank you Myles Monroe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you focus on vision - you will overcome distractions - thank you Myles Monroe....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am grateful for every follower -- I'm living to inspire and empower you and those you know!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have crossed over to the other side....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am learning to kill my impulsiveness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am learning to be silent is good....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Preparing for marriage little by little...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A new "me" is unfolding...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am here to change my world....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live free so you can fly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love others deeply]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the ability to empower and inspire...,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very excited about my 5 minute video platform....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Practice creates perfection]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am thankful for a legendary legacy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading: "Emotionally Healthy Spirituality" by: Peter Scazzero]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do what you think you cannot...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What I think of me...matters most...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe in the power of diligence....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pray for our president daily! As a nation we must unite!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't have or need to be perfect to love me...😎]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You were born to be great]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You were born to overcome your enemies....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe in my legacy....do you believe in yours??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do your best with what you have....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women get inside a mans mind before you let him in your body #celibatelife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will be on the radio one day...talking to billions of people....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I set the bar high...so I will reach high...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My income goal is: $250K yearly by 2021.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Respect yourself and others will too..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love yourself and others will too...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am grateful for self-love...it's beautiful....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The less I talk..the more I do...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The less I talk the more I hear...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am here to soar...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always remember: people treat you the way you allow...]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>