<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[177 years ago today #Wellington settlers arrived. The original plans differ from the landscape today due to land re… https://t.co/QHUIxdEde5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlagFacts I think my screen needs calibrating...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlagFacts I think you'll find it's red, not orange... https://t.co/ex8jE93vzJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On what date do I stop starting every conversation with "Happy New Year"? @SoVeryBritish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adam Savage meets a Weebo animatronic robot! https://t.co/6GPsmCh2Qz #flubber]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZAA thanks! I did a bank transfer so should be all good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't call out Isreal on anything without being labelled anti-semitic. https://t.co/im4BsUpk8T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@NZAA - FYI your online form to renew membership doesn't work on mobile. I wasn't able to enter my membership number in the fields provided]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finished watching #RogueOne Solid stand-alone film. I'm ready to watch it again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This has shocked me to my core #highlyupsetting https://t.co/oemXgHI6Dz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzpost the prezzy - I always like a good surprise!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JulieAnneGenter I don't use it but my decisions shouldn't affect anyone else's right to choose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I haven't had the McGriddle on like forever - time to being it back, @MaccasNZ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pockethaiku Talk about motivating! I'll have some words with the elves...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pockethaiku Housing is threadbare :-(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the second flight with @FlyAirNZ where the pilot has been a woman. Very cool!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So @NetflixANZ now has offline viewing. Quite advantageous with my flight home tonight!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My photo of Christchurch from my recent @FlyAirNZ flight from Wellington #AirNZShareMe https://t.co/sNNTTZCUzK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isn't the whole point of insurance to, among other things, cover you for lost business? https://t.co/kn3TW83Wz4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They don't write newspapers like they used to! #journalism #eqnz https://t.co/w6OAGWEYrI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking good! Apparently it'll be hour long episodes and three seasons long, each covering 3-5 books (13 books tota… https://t.co/tda6baunNJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@empiremagazine I was going to say I should get into movie reviews for this but then I'd have to watch the terrible movies you let me avoid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The next 72 hours trying to get the car seat back in just the right position following the WOF guys changing it #horror #myliferightnow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After far too many click-bait headlines, viral videos and non-news I have quit @NZStuff and @nzherald. Help me @radionz, you're my only hope]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty sure Obama had black skin as well as hair... https://t.co/9eYvkebR0d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watched the trailer for #Trainspotting2. Not enough trains 2/10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does what it says on the tin https://t.co/EZhETVzoBa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KiwibankNZ that page could not be found...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoops, i accidentially binge-watched the entire first season of @NetflixANZ's @Stranger_Things in one sitting. 5/5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This graph from the @NZOFLC baffles me - why shouldn't parents be able to show their children an age-restricted fil… https://t.co/jw3WIYXeGP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MyFoodBagNZ couldn't send a DM from the app but account name is Gabriel Pollard in Wellington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well that's weird - @MyFoodBagNZ just tried to give me a second My Own Bag just three hours after delivering the first...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You uh sure you got enough there... ;) https://t.co/qQ61tIjw1T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well just finished watching the third and final season of The Newsroom on @NeonNZ.
 Simply brilliant as is the writer, Aaron Sorkin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally, a good poster! The rest looked like badly Photoshopped fanfare #RogueOne https://t.co/4AS9Mpi9Yp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The moonwalk has nothing to do with the moon, nor is it an efficient way to walk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzpost remember: lefty loosey, righty tighty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeterDunneMP you approved them, only makes sense to formally welcome them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashens I think you lost in the end...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a number of good reasons to live in Switzerland - for starters the flag is a big plus https://t.co/CtPcOo97sH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to flush away moral outrage over Smith https://t.co/ee9fWnSDnJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewisHoldenNZ @NZDefenceForce @DeptDefence @NZArmy Some American uniforms have the bald eagle underneath the flag...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's really the first thing you want people to know about the property: that it leaks? https://t.co/dz4mMup0fb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Wellington Commonwealth Walkway looks nice. Could be a good walk for a good day #cantbeatwellingtononagoodday https://t.co/u1uFSfSmqO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MightyApeMovies What We Do In The Shadows! Looking forward to the spinoff TV show. #bluray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@2degreesmobile - help my credit card has expired and I can't find the way to update the expiry date (auto payment method) online... help!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People tell me I'm hearing things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Riddle: How do you assault two men and two women and get away with it? Have a rugby-mad judge #LosiFilipo #Criminal https://t.co/9dLJC954Ov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the worst map of New Zealand I have ever seen! #Samsung #GalaxyS7 https://t.co/KCqiGlVtxc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzpost at least the memes aren't suffering! https://t.co/YE18ODrS05]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate @Metrochch web presence. Only homepage is mobile optimised, and it doesn't use reloadable URLs so info has to be reentered everytime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@FlyAirNZ flght delayed 20 minutes - app notification, text message, email and Google all tell me. Airport? No.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, and it's named after the fruit. Bonus fact: it used to be called a norange which evolved into an orange. #fun https://t.co/20L1YBdfC2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the lead up to my 26th birthday, I'm reliving my childhood by watching Pokemon and Yu-Gi-Oh on @NetflixANZ #NostalgiaTrip #September19]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a cloud! #solvedit https://t.co/eV3qVABDDE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's alarmingly fast https://t.co/sT2efBQBoW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Arrests after massive Auckland KFC brawl" - it's because it was the last day for the double down! https://t.co/FiTk0YK9Qy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm disappointed that the trending #railsgirlswgtn hashtag does not feature trains.1/10 would not recommend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FFS, @TV3nz I just wanted to leave full-screen mode on 3 Now, not stop the whole show and return me to the main page! Every. Single. Time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought it was bad to be a hoarder, but it's that time of year when all the hoardings go on display #badjoke #Election2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The results are in, and I'm hated by the Daily Mail! How about you? https://t.co/HwtqGvXFqJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finished @UnRealLifetime on @LightboxNZ. Everyone - why haven't you watched it yet?! #onemoreyear #season3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do you get when an unstoppable force meets an immovable object? Your mum's face #burn #burnunit #savage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two ferries, one harbour #Wellington https://t.co/DHXaVwqJWU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was at the Wellington #PokemonGo event and was captured in Stuff's photo. Circled in red for convenience #famous https://t.co/QEnlRopX60]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new Rogue One Star Wars poster looks like it was fan-made and badly Photoshopped: 
https://t.co/ZCtwAY4SU7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really enjoyed last night's (vegetarian) pizza from @MyFoodBagNZ #yummy https://t.co/KFSN5vHZNx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flour made from ground up crickets?! I think I'll stick with regular ground up seed flour #ThanksButNoThanks https://t.co/ONdVe5vFcF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just watched "End of Watch" on @NetflixANZ. Good movie! 4/5  
https://t.co/LQ1IjhlbgR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rosehoare in that vein, here's Bo Burnham's great inspirational advice: https://t.co/4PnIFjPIkf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another one to add to the collection! Thanks #mightyape! https://t.co/hG28huG2TM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got 10/20 in Empire's expert Disney quiz. How well can you do? https://t.co/QsErwKMq9v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanNerdCubed Is this a FACT?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome aboard @TransdevW. Good first day! #dadjokes #winning https://t.co/ZSrn88wI2Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BCAnderton Empire gave the new Independence Day movie 4/5... https://t.co/tDv68YeJBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016 is one-hell of a show - can't wait for the season finale! #brexit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watched this last night on @NetflixANZ - 5/5 from me! https://t.co/QWDmwWlh9D https://t.co/2VcN8XwwMa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Car ads should show me not how fast they can go, but how well they fare in Wellington's crawling traffic at the Mt Vic tunnel #whywellington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MightyApeMovies Gladiator is a great film. Watched that a lot!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Available on @LightboxNZ - I would definitely recommend! https://t.co/XtxovlkFGw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@will_harvie same with Fatso. Have to ring so they can offer a discounted service. I'm inclined to keep ringing to for perpetual discount]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first season was amazing! Hoping the second season delivers the sane greatness https://t.co/c5lSwWPM58]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanNerdCubed your Cities Skylines city came to life! https://t.co/kFmEkVhLpJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning Wellington! #whywellington https://t.co/CVWAQLXEgE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What kind of person throws things at people because they can't get KFC? Disgusting people! https://t.co/3RIApe6K1W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just binge watched the *entire* 1st season of Bosch, based on the Connelly books, it was that good! I'd like series 2 now, @NeonNZ #hint]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like traveling back to the 90s! https://t.co/FCD2rf5DuB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@empiremagazine is this like a pre-prequel to The Fifth Wave...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanNerdCubed completes series then?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @LightboxNZ - I would like to watch The Expanse, and 11.22.63... ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a good flag - 5 stars... https://t.co/Z8AqmvSlXl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr Robot was an amazing TV show! It was funny that violence was fine to show but US had to censor swear words. Watch now on @LightboxNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm tired of walking! #exercise https://t.co/s6wdsevpzx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Armageddonexpo I'm watching Yes Minister. Very droll.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blatantly false marketing! I'm outraged! Disappointed even! https://t.co/FRA8tvPLTi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @2degreesmobile for the free @NeonNZ! https://t.co/zBlbwtZwF8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do we wait until a pig is dead before we start to cure it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But it feels like it only just started! Well, I guess I'm binge watching the last two episodes tonight #ragingnight https://t.co/CQE6i6bdNj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watched Chappie this evening. I couldn't help but compare it to Ex Machina but it held its own and was a very nice movie #robotsarecool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessiJboon It says at the start that it's based on real events! Why wouldn't I believe that!?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>