<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@a2_4am oooo ok I can see this been very convenient for future use]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@apple2europlus I made labels for my uni folders in that font. Great to see am update]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FozzTexx gee that's great!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stand-up desk? Health Experts Recommend Standing Up At Desk, Leaving Office, Never Coming Back!
(inspired by The Onion headline)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yesterbits thanks for sharing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CuteEmergency Our new puppy,just on 9 weeks old. Name: Möet like the champagne https://t.co/sLUDAfs26E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ausretrogamer um yes it'd called Pinheads. Can't get better than that one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@libretro can I ask - both latest versions of SNES 9x and genesis .rpx files crash my wiiu on loading, requiring a hard reset. Any guesses?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@a2_4am I thought that name looked familiar, shown here in 1983, Picture Writer https://t.co/iMockaZpk1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Righting the wrongs of my childhood: I've finally completed Super Mario Brothers (SNES All Stars) https://t.co/mIGRCpEedg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@a2_4am There could be a new Twitter icon here for you. https://t.co/PipyW8PUv8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@a2_4am for female vocal try Sarah Jarosz
For jam sessions try Telluride]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I did it! Nintendo GameCube game Super Mario Sunshine running from SD card, loaded by Nintendont on WiiU at 1080p60… https://t.co/GDyn45t0WQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gumball on the AppleColour Composite //e monitor vs Virtual ][ https://t.co/hucGSFM5GY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Label scans of Apple II and IIGS Software disks https://t.co/2RhjE6BSSz https://t.co/55GVQpL74t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More Apple II software preserved https://t.co/qHzjaK5yLa https://t.co/e1Rt8riwrN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@a2_4am Reminds me of components in IQ testing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Librarian’ s Apprentice, Australian Apple II software https://t.co/32tl10cSDL https://t.co/rujqU5jwsK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@the_jongleur (In the folder titled Sandys Word Processor)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@the_jongleur Dear Michael - here are the files: https://t.co/GvoxIqVpjT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@the_jongleur Yes! Scanned both manual and reference cards at 600dpi, not haven't uploaded yet as my disks are unreadable, do you have .dsk?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Foone well.... I know they were sold at Kmart Australia because I actually remember my mum buying a pack for us to share]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We all need a good nurse every now and then https://t.co/fO1h1ARoZp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have to clean my drive head so many times that I keep a zip lock baggie with cotton tips stuck right on the bottl… https://t.co/HGcah7O6Cj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VCR anyone? I spotted this suitcase sized player at a recycle shop https://t.co/hvVMPOEQ6h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading my scans for a change https://t.co/7YjF4diCjD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Testing NTSC composite color stability on the Samsung 940MG. Nice vertical zoom feature to effectively 14:9 IIGS https://t.co/pB5sbBvij4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who knew Bernie featured vertical line smoothing to emulate AppleColor tricks https://t.co/xf1ECSknzj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Testing Bernie to the rescue IIgs emulator with a floppy drive on a  iMac for fun https://t.co/RyShraufYH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well guys I've learned something today https://t.co/gR80V5yV36]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No polite adjectives for this! #RespectDrop3inches https://t.co/tWJAcmmmRa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@6502lane @cosmoza I have a few of these, all unreadable due to degraded disk surface. I've scanned the labels though as a consolation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cosmoza and 2) inability to be written to in a copy program. Eg want to mount a blank image and use disk dup to copy an original 3.5? Can't]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cosmoza um not shown there is two major incompatibilities for Macintosh 1) can only mount disc copy 4.2 (not the resource forked 6.3)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cosmoza hmmm screenshot and I'll confirm why - likely excessive glue in the margin that stuck pages together]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cosmoza a keen eye! I drove interstate to PU A][ magazines for scanning and spotted this box out of the corner of my eye. Made an offer 💯]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@huibert @cosmoza @a2_4am @lifepillar well I did this methodically to the same result - crashes on sierra and about a day lost so 😨]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shrineofapple any indication why this perspex was made? Or what page number it's on?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stroughtonsmith wow that is really beautiful, especially the bat mobile exhaust]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rubyfromdulla @clientliaison @fallsofficial @CanonAustralia Macintosh spotted in pic 2!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@a2_4am I scanned the manual for this one x do you need it ? Hq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple Cider Spider by #SierraOn-Line for the #AppleII https://t.co/ljIcPeHqW1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TurnkeySoftware presents Ceiling Zero for the #AppleII https://t.co/YVXtpc9J3H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nightmare Gallery for the #appleii by #SynergisticSoftware https://t.co/wVvlmYgg5d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quadrant 6112 for the #AppleII https://t.co/uJ1lqV6MdP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Avant-Garde presents Dead Race 82 for the #appleii https://t.co/7BfWpHO7eS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flack back with us to ancient Crete #SiriusSoftware #AppleII https://t.co/eJNn0hERu8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exciting and Fun - Sirius Software #AppleII
Scanned here for the first time, from my 3000+ full page print ads rela… https://t.co/rHouxSyYOF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the earliest #Broderbund full-page ad I have in my collection. Scanned for the first time. Nice old logo th… https://t.co/0nNDSp8CVS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidSchPT My original Dino Eggs full page ad, scanned especially for this tweet. https://t.co/AJCFuWLaQN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#LearningwithLeaper #SierraOn-Line https://t.co/0oXLYXXMv6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me? Oh I'm just preparing a hundred apple ii magazines for scanning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@a2_4am And don't forget full scans too: https://t.co/wuidzFVS9f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think’s Lightspeed Pascal for the Macintosh, Book https://t.co/Mv7JwmsS9v https://t.co/Q0TU3Sqiuu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Knights of Legend, Apple II boxed set of software https://t.co/IoUNdVOEAE https://t.co/uTbyvngCMW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Golden Book Video Classic – Three Sesame Street Stories VHS https://t.co/tQoZ6LTyN1 https://t.co/GxD9ojpw0N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alternative Captain Planet theme/introduction, exclusive https://t.co/WrLjLWOyoY https://t.co/fnwo2ur1SG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Fb3qWgAG3I
I found and uploaded a never before seen introduction to the Captain Planet cartoon @CaptainPlanet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarbaraPyle1 Here is the rare Captain Planet introduction I'd like to share https://t.co/Fb3qWgAG3I feel free to comment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarbaraPyle1 Dear Barbara, I've just archived an never before seen introduction sequence to Captain Planet - can I share it for ur comment?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My HDMI VCR Has given itself a befitting name, 1337 https://t.co/7Uizobn5lb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Create a Calender, Epyx, Apple II Software https://t.co/L54nc1tyB2 https://t.co/qaYQftYjTK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thomas sing along: https://t.co/t9NeJvLMnq via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dink The Little Dinosaur, VHS details https://t.co/MoPUztom06 https://t.co/GTIvW6XjFa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blinky Bill – The Red Car and Blinky The Teacher, Australian 2 episode VHS transfer https://t.co/KOAg9N44WS https://t.co/Wr3pG5YghI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Upcoming disk image - DLM Presents The Writing Adventure, unpreserved https://t.co/r1TkN33eJ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovely Lady Locks and the Pixietails ‘To Take a Castle’, 6 episode VHS transfer https://t.co/XaUFxvNoZ6 https://t.co/hWv9wrUxXF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A2 Central and Open Apple Magazine as scanned by Jeremy Barr-Hyde https://t.co/q5xM8jCfBp https://t.co/OsteEy6VLT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Applecations – The Publication of the Apple Users Group – Sydney Australia as scanned by… https://t.co/FKnbeKzpFT https://t.co/YA7VwGxa9V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helix_nrg Well the good thing about New Mexico landfill is things appreciate down there.  And with perseverance good things will come😎]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helix_nrg I had no idea you needed scans for knights of legend. My guillotine is being repaired but when it's back… https://t.co/Kl4e7lBD7T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@a2_4am thanks for the clear photo,I can read every title! I've done summer games ii, clean cracks in passport but no edd, im sure you'll do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discovering Apple Logo by David Thornburg https://t.co/fMKAbFuxMX https://t.co/3ey9n9yZL7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft Home Creative Writer – McZee font for Mac https://t.co/ZaIdQ0aqXQ https://t.co/baE9PElGfr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@a2_4am fascinating and thank you for printing the comments here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blahjedi @ausretrogamer if you need help,I bought a fuji scan snap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Word Radar, Apple II educational software with manual https://t.co/zQVe4XWttH https://t.co/vmx3H7Uo63]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Verb Viper, Apple II educational software https://t.co/MutpjJSmDF https://t.co/CnlS5z8Zw2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kermit’s Electronic Story Maker, Apple II software with manual https://t.co/G6OjBTzJHl https://t.co/VqSrg8VPm3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@a2_4am very exciting for me - I have many more disks I'm working on so even further compatibility is great]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@apple2europlus And thanks to Hans sourcing the original, the new version should be all good. Nothing worse than crashes mid mission]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@apple2europlus plays fine as I generated the screenshots from the passport crack version]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dancer desk accessory: https://t.co/i4rxPIZBJt via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrating 12,846 views and $1.03 revenue for seven years. 😆 or 😨? https://t.co/oY6z1EnXp3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@viticci next thing is they'll ask you to install a plugin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dinosaur Discovery, Australian Apple II educational software with manual https://t.co/c0mnbLFVMG https://t.co/uiwbvZpxuY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Create with Garfield, Apple II software with manual https://t.co/LJbaT1PiYA https://t.co/L7yDu6uVwF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raft Away River, Australian Apple II software with manual https://t.co/x6B6Whh6cv https://t.co/iffqVji8Am]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quick-cartage Company, Australian Apple II software with manuals https://t.co/n0QqOM4Ize https://t.co/nNoCuhg9cJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Piece Of Cake Maths, Apple II educational software https://t.co/ICozLZ9ZAW https://t.co/9xELjCtUf8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mini Pix by Beagle Bros, Apple II software with manual https://t.co/EHElAG7WCg https://t.co/4kP501bXei]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picture Writer, Apple II educational software with manual https://t.co/ycUqJ0fsnx https://t.co/SCxa4NDIRG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keyboarding, Australian Apple II educational software https://t.co/pjmh1oFJFP https://t.co/7EbAQWp4hk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dinosaur Dig by Neosoft and CBS, Apple II educational software with manual https://t.co/G1COlLuWNe https://t.co/2n0zY49gxt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CARE What’s The Time Mr. Wolf?, Australian Apple II educational software with manual https://t.co/PjdK75cQXS https://t.co/5uPIH2J4BJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CARE Decide Your Destiny 4,  Australian Apple II educational software with manual https://t.co/1MxBwvTxpX https://t.co/aFj6laKmH8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CARE Decide Your Destiny 2,  Australian Apple II educational software with manual https://t.co/T2MDVZAirc https://t.co/alWrdAERa0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Al's Logo WIZ-KIT, Australian Apple II software https://t.co/coo4yO5VZ4 https://t.co/E435Rht0Ln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cunning Running, Australian Apple II educational software https://t.co/4iCH1g73Uq https://t.co/plcV0E7XVe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crimfile, Australian Apple II educational software https://t.co/MRbskWv21q https://t.co/J94ifbh8Kp]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>