<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@mfriedman_63 salt in the wound!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@radiolemans T.E.A.M Together Everyone Achieves More! !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just insanely dramatic! #B12hr #Bathurst12H @Bathurst12hour @radiolemans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From this view the porsche was racing a ghost Lamborghini that came out of nowhere! #B12hr #Bathurst12H https://t.co/cf0SjlaOT2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How fast do fire trucks go in Australia? @radiolemans @Bathurst12hour #B12hr #Bathurst12H https://t.co/qCMzzFVswg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new #ironman take a much needed rest!! @radiolemans @Bathurst12hour #B12hr #Bathurst12H https://t.co/26tT9ugGwb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you have a Ferrari you don't need a pit stop! #B12hr @radiolemans @Bathurst12hour https://t.co/O68HMGFRv6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8:20pm on a Saturday night in Vancouver and i am live streaming a Sunday race? #iseethefuture #B12hr @radiolemans @Bathurst12hour thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For sale #NissanGTR used. Needs new fenders and road safety test! @radiolemans #Bathurst12H #B12hr https://t.co/CQJNZT0MJT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving the international stream here in Vancouver! #Bathurst12H #B12hr @radiolemans @Bathurst12hour https://t.co/m2ZPlMALPJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@feliceherrig wishing you much success tonight from Vancouver, Canada!! #UFC #FS1 @ufc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whole Foods predicts these foods will be all the rage in 2017 https://t.co/iBcGjxlFCN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every Single Food Trend That's Been Predicted for 2017 https://t.co/p5FEtUDZur via @Eater]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@analogsoundcrew yeah man doing the West coast! !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump welcome to your little billionaires party. Way to stay in touch with the little guys! #fail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The__Advantage @JMWmotorsport @lemansseries love the Vantage but the livery looks to similar to the 2009-10 #corvetteracing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ufc @KoreanZombieMMA yep it was a sad day as I'm from Toronto and was there to see Mark get KOed. Same night big Nog's arm snapped!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think we already knew this.
https://t.co/FVAlUyqs76]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Working on my #racing #racetrack #tattoo #spa #nurburgring #twinning #suzuka #TopGear test track sleave https://t.co/W1JdDTDQdH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CTMPOfficial #mosport #tattoo is it racing season yet? I'm ready! https://t.co/HkfVPBuEQY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WeTheNorth watching #raptors game from #Vancouver #nailbiter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AutoSportsArt it looks like a science project involving a Bricklin, Delorean and an old 300zx lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BryanSellers @Wolf_Henzler just a few weeks till Mosport!!! Can't wait to have you guys back in Canada! @FalkenTire #17Porsche]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calamari two ways.  Lemon herb grilled and crispy fried served with pickled beets and tapanade.… http://t.co/xFZw5l6GX4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surf N Turf mini Tacos share plate. With fried fish and braised beef topped with avocado creme and… http://t.co/urbWCjsnDJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See what happens when no woman are on the morning news!! @CP24Breakfast @SteveAnthony Pillows flying, next the set? #BringTheHouseDown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got up here and look who's on my morning news!! Good ol @JRsBBQ #WWE #Toronto http://t.co/gwf9V6PTav]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im not sure what is worse. Having to change the channel as a kid with the remote on a wire or trying to stream a race off @UnitedSportsCar ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NASCAR + @UnitedSportsCar + @FOXSports1 = complete sham for international (Canadian) race fans! Complete BS!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UnitedSportsCar I understand the server gets overwhelmed its just so frustrating when the feed comes I'm and out on the website!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FalkenTire @BryanSellers looking good no matter the position!! http://t.co/q1vjuEE31U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I give up on you!! @UnitedSportsCar thanks to all the #ALMS years of great racing. Not sure how u will keep all your fans in the future!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@atflorio its just annoying as I streamed the first 30 mins of the race off http://t.co/VA0ihseYT5 now its saying live feed not available]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UnitedSportsCar I have been streaming the first 30 mins of the race. Now its no more!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No live feed in Canada? Just in car?? @UnitedSportsCar http://t.co/gF52boMGfk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess we don't want an international audience to Watch?? http://t.co/81FrzpwdLR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UnitedSportsCar imsa feed not working only in car. This is really annoying. How do you expect to keep long time fans???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do I only get in car views now?? Ffs @UnitedSportsCar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good luck to all your boys!! @K2theBru but my heart is with the #17Porsche lets see a safe clean race!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok TEAM @FalkenTire  good luck to my boys @Wolf_Henzler @BryanSellers and the whole team!! #LetsDoThis #FalkenFans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr. Cameo @JEdwardsRacing #brucrew getting read for the big race!!! http://t.co/HXR9K6Cykj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@atflorio @Wolf_Henzler @FalkenTire that is such a great shot!Do you mind if I save this pic for my wallpaper?I would rather ask then steal!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was a shame, sooo close. Great job @FlyingLizard_MS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BryanSellers @Wolf_Henzler @FalkenTire ok Team qualifying time!!! Good luck!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great job and overall winner at Mazda Raceway!! #brucrew @JEdwardsRacing http://t.co/zr5KCmzbS2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#brucrew @JEdwardsRacing is ready for the green and keeping the tire temps up! http://t.co/9Lm1SvIn7T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JEdwardsRacing using all that #BMW power to make passes up the hill!! http://t.co/22HmztkAXZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Busy in the Corkscrew! @JEdwardsRacing http://t.co/v51MWkx8iP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JEdwardsRacing getting ready to do his stint!! Bring the heat!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok Boy's @BryanSellers @Wolf_Henzler and the all the @FalkenTire team. Good luck this weekend!! #falkenfans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AutoSportsArt Smurf edition?? Not a fan of the colour scheme!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WCRacing that was as good as racing gets!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WCRacing this is some crazy good action!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@K2theBru @KPAXracing that's what I was saying! LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @KPAXracing boys are working together and working the field!! @K2theBru @WCRacing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bergh223 new car lots of gremlins still!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WCRacing YouTube link working excellent!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome back to the @ufc Champ @AndreiArlovski this pic was from my first live fight back at #UFC68 March 07 http://t.co/bexrJ3YL7L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrendanSchaub not gonna lie, @AndreiArlovski has been one of my fav fighters for years but I do have mad props for you too! Gonna b good!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey guys, thanks for the sick event! @redbullTO  #RaceThePlace how do i find the pics from the circuit? Says the dude on the DH rider 100!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@__PIFFington I ask myself the same damn thing daily!! Oh yeah what up girl!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did I need 8 inches of travel for #RaceThePlace ?? Nah, but it was fun! #redbull #redbullgivesyouwings… http://t.co/wVavRAocVE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did my lap 100th starting position and had just enough juice left in the tank on my 39lb DH @redbullTO #racetheplace http://t.co/GbFXo11IYD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @Redbull @redbullto #RaceThePlace http://t.co/o6REppEwfz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redbullTO or my tank! Open class! http://t.co/phPM7otr56]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CrazyLeoNet like I said. I clicked Like then retweeted this!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redbullTO @Joyride150 you mean one of the Whoops for me to catch some air off of! #GotWingsNow #RaceThePlace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephan_kremer was there any doubt? Time to move forward, DR is having a strong season!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redbullTO @GiantCAN @OakleyCanada can't wait!!! #racetheplace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New 200mm disks and now we are ready for #RaceThePlace Open class! Gonna be epic times! @redbullTO http://t.co/ACQ10NwvaM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@K2theBru hope this is not race foreshadowing!!! Good luck to all your boys today and my falken crew!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@K2theBru what?LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good luck today boys and have a safe race!! @BryanSellers @Wolf_Henzler @FalkenTire #LBGP #17Porsche]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One week to go!!! @redbullTO #RaceThePlace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best mail  waiting at my door today! @RedBullCanada @redbull http://t.co/U21Ff1h07S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just over a week to go till #RedbullRaceThePlace @RedBullCanada here in Toronto! #EpicTimesAhead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey buddy @CrazyLeoNet been checking out your vids on Facebook. Great job in the #WRC #TrueCanadian #CrazyLeo lots of support from Toronto!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Super hype as I just signed up for @RedBullCanada #RaceAtThePlace April 19th. #wings4life #RedbullGivesYouWings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrunMunk I shall give it a go! Also almost backyard bbq time!! #keepUinformed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EBraeden I always seem to read your posts in the Victor Newman voice. Now im doing it again as I type this back!! #keepUpTheGreatWork]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sjdForbes @WCRacing @dysonfan I decided to paint some numbers on the sides of my dogs and let them run out back instead!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sjdForbes @WCRacing @dysonfan lol even my computer is tired of waiting! http://t.co/B5OS6ogTKg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sjdForbes @dysonfan feels like loading a page from 1990!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WCRacing thats nice to read on twitter, it would be better if we could stream the race!!! #firstworldproblems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dysonfan r u going to mosport in may to see them? Its on my birthday it may be an option pour Moi!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@K2theBru @GPSTPETE @WCRacing @alexfigge @ThorneRacing enjoy and good luck. Livestream not working! :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome race today! @WCRacing http://t.co/djbl4Up8uv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johndagys very frustrating!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dysonfan yeah dude pretty bad. I habe been loading the page for 12 mins now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sjdForbes race should be ending by the time the page loads! @WCRacing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WCRacing your livestream is not working!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sjdForbes is the stream working for you?? I can't get sh_t right now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sjdForbes @WCRacing yep, Grrrr i was so hype to see it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sjdForbes @WCRacing I was. Thinking the same. Sadly I just read the race is cancelled today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sebringraceway did we make a new caution record yesterday?? I know the old one was 5:55:00 in '93]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UnitedSportsCar @FOXSports1 3 hours of caution?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MuscleMilkRace keep watching online till we see you at my local Mosport!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MuscleMilkRace damn shame. You guys work so hard. Thanks team, till next race!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter how it all ends @MuscleMilkRace #Sebring12 "we your fans" super proud of all the work the team has done!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaellgoodwin auto correct grr thanks not tix!!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>