<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[West Abbotsford at 30cm already! https://t.co/xYBZeRocnL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#snowdrift #bcstorm #snowpocalypse @RamTrucks @RamTrucksCanada @AbbotsfordDodge https://t.co/DcYzidvedw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@mperfectwarrior wait, did you say Walmart, or prison?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kbolan When would the full story be posted "soon" ? Thx Kim!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No need for a cooler when ice fishing! #bc @oldyalebrewing #icefishing @ Grace Lake https://t.co/FCQfv39ohm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well holy shit there it is. President Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@TheSpecialist4 @Frag_IDMA @Xtra_TO Could you imagine if #BLM asked to ban all LGBT people from something?! Geez. #hypocritical #wtf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Frag_IDMA @Xtra_TO oh but hey we must be all inclusive of the LGBT community else it's discrimination. #wtf #gopoundsand #hypocritical]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shawhelp enabled the hotmail server (https://t.co/zEu8P9VelB) sends it from there fine. #microsoftwins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shawhelp have anything to do with 'remote access' on the webmail? Then why can I rec and just not send?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shawhelp we wanted POP because we wanted a copy left on server at all times, even after deleting them from our device.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shawhelp it did send at one time. Not sure what changed all of a sudden.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shawhelp nope. Same thing. Receives email fine. Cannot send. It did work a week ago, intermittently.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shawhelp this happens on both our mobile devices. Can login to webmail fine. Can access it from Outlook on a desktop PC fine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shawhelp That is my only shaw email account that I use]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spyglass Kitty #babystag #crownginger hiway74 cowboyj1974 rfalk50 https://t.co/VESTGdoIOw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Seahawks #wingsgranville #babystag #winterale #cheers rmacbeth rfalk50 hiway74 @granvillebeer @… https://t.co/fVYGP6kivc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSpecialist4 @CityofVancouver Oh god I hope so #LOL #budgetcuts  #timesaretough #IPERT #nicemags]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@johnstreit1130 @NEWS1130 the Ice Patrol Emergency Response Vehicle! 🚨 #amazing #IPERT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KGordonGlobalBC @dustymaple444 @YvonneSchalle or just wear a green shirt! Ha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mbna Really? To see transactions and view balances etc ? Apparently I missed it. Will look again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mbna how do you guys possibly NOT have an app to access your accounts?! Esp in this day and age?? #goingbacktoAMEX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlobalBC @YvonneSchalle @michaelkusswx @KGordonGlobalBC unfortunately not :( Rain in #Abbotsford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @LetterkennyProb while f*cking an ostrich in Canada is probably indictable, it's not a 'felony' #USterm #notUSA #keepitcanadian #eh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#communitypolicing #welldone https://t.co/40bzMQKEt3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shawhelp well that's easy! Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shawhelp hey guys, if one of our arris gateway remotes is starting to not work (down volume) what are our options?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@instagram hey haven't been able to share to twitter in a week. What gives?? https://t.co/BB9YIwPXPy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisgailus @VancouverSun no kidding, like holy crap. #graphic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@VancouverSun Holy crap.. "graphic image" much?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's to a new year! Exciting times, friends. Cheers! #2017 #mimosas https://t.co/PkHM1EuNTk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I guess my friends aren't making it home from Calgary tonight for New Years #yyc #yxx @WestJet #bcstorm… https://t.co/FRR6IR2I4I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shawhelp the thing with IMAP is we want 2people access the same acct &amp; when you delete from either phone, to still have a copy on server.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shawhelp well they must be because it works 60% of the time. Only does this intermittently, I thought maybe server issues?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shawhelp I do, Just tried it again and now it sent (of course). Something about "cannot reach server" I think, but hotmail works fine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shawhelp hey what gives? Email (pop) send/receive only works part time on my Shaw acct on our iPhones .... then randomly will work...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got home, black ice everywhere, INSANE on the side roads in a RWD pickup. SLOW DOWN. Can't believe how slick it is. #abbotsford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSpecialist4 what about "C R I M" on one hand's knuckles and "I N A L" on the other #branded #committed #lifer #dontrobabank]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe if the #Canucks could get their heads out of asses we could have a hockey team..... #nicepic… https://t.co/vXEqSdbrS6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chicago_Police Honors K-9 Rachel with 'Last Call' https://t.co/24KwUQ6YCY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you for your loyal service. #RIP #K9 https://t.co/gjPB8iNwyS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#thisguy #hero #shittersfull #merrychristmas https://t.co/qiaxFKShlb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#haha this EXACT thing happened to me recently #usps #justshowedup https://t.co/8irL2w6Zeu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SandmanHotels It was Vancouver City Centre, beside BC Place Stadium. Just thought it was humorous #lol..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stormbrewingvan #hotdickenscider #what https://t.co/IVWUbUaWJH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#confused #nowwhat #vancouver @SandmanHotels https://t.co/phnRtrz7lP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems a day doesn't go by recently where I don't say "Drugs are bad, mmkay?" #justsayno #naturalselection]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heartbreaking, evil exists everywhere. "The story of the Ottawa officer who arrested the child-torturing Mountie" https://t.co/3wV99Y86Ou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prisoner killed at Saskatchewan Federal Penitentiary https://t.co/RSztbXI3yx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mperfectwarrior Came w/ the sunglasses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ERAvaCole You'll nail it. Make that exam your bitch. #nailedit #kickasstakenames]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ERAvaCole in the movie (2016) the woman portrayed that was filming in the room was Poitras, her documentary came out in '14. #citizenfour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ERAvaCole @Snowden @hitRECordJoe I also watched @laurapoitras 's #citizenfour the documentary behind the movie. #wakeupcall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually after posting that last tweet should I expect government officials knocking at my door? @snowden @hitRECordJoe #xkeyscore @NSAGov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saw " @Snowden " last night. SO well done, but so frightening at same time confirming what we all (should) know @hitRECordJoe #bigbrother]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So instead of trying to fix the PROBLEM, we ACCEPT it and spend a shit ton of money to setup a mobile triage centre for the inevitable ODs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WTF is a CONSUMPTION site? Seriously you're calling them THAT now? Like for people to INJECT illegal drugs?!… https://t.co/Jla6jtlucB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, I could be wrong, but I believe diversity is an old, old wooden ship that was used during the Civil War era.… https://t.co/hejVJwQOb2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How is this even NEWS? I've never been to the UK however, so fair enough, I'm not familiar with their culture. But.… https://t.co/42yJoYqR4v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well played! https://t.co/KLqXBL299U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SNOWWWWW! Fantastic getting this years tree &amp; decorating the house while snowing outside.. something we rarely experience on the westcoast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@NEWS1130 a "light" blizzard? Isn't that somewhat of a contradiction in terms?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Out of all the ornaments we pulled out today, travelling down memory lane of all the places and… https://t.co/NpD64innji]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@cbcnewsbc @globalbc @NEWS1130 Doesn't help all the "meteorologists" &amp; media jacking everyone up with all DIFFERENT forecasts.#NOmageddon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the plus side I did get to use 4x4 this morning to get out of my street. So, there's that, I guess. #bcstorm #NOmageddon #WeatherBorecast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ERAvaCole @KamilKaramali @cbcnewsbc However, still coming down in force around McCallum/King, soooo, maybe still a chance? #snowmageddon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@KamilKaramali @ERAvaCole @cbcnewsbc not as much as predicted?? #shocking #NOmageddon #typicalWeatherBorecast #bcstorm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thankful for remote start and pre-heated seat and steering this AM! @RamTrucksCanada @AbbotsfordDodge #bcsnow https://t.co/QzTuXL0xJY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disappointed yet again with so-called #bcstorm #snowmageddon. Barely a dusting thus far in W. Abbotsford at  0520.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ann_luu @CTVVancouver How are you ALL different?? In your forecasts?? Totally takes all the legitimacy out of it w… https://t.co/4S3naWSddU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying not to be excited about the snow (I love it) so I'm not disappointed whn it doesn't happen. Hopefully the predictions are accurate...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No sooner said than I looked out the window #snowmaggedon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WTF snowing everywhere EXCEPT the fraser valley?? There's a first #snow #whatsnow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Sunday #britishcolumbia @ Campbell Valley Regional Park https://t.co/Qf3gjugwx2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ERAvaCole Would have been like "Go pound sand. Have a nice walk."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fog_ducker7 @mihajloween Zoey's 3 mos. in the one pic and 5 yrs old in the other.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mihajloween @fog_ducker7 mylab had the same thing, born w black nose but turned pink by about 18 mos https://t.co/rCv5IE2O0E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome back! #tistheseason https://t.co/mh0It2ndHx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ERAvaCole Arena's been built for a year. Already has been hosting concerts. (@TMobileArena )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ERAvaCole @hockeynight @GoldenKnights what would've been wrong with the "Las Vegas Knights" ? (Maybe too similar to Los Angeles Kings?)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like the logo. Would have preferred just "Knights". Golden is too much. https://t.co/XnR80fqGW1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ERAvaCole @mperfectwarrior   1. Open Google    2. Type "anal sex" in the search box......   wait, that might not work 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mperfectwarrior @ERAvaCole #nowyouknow #knowingishalfthebattle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@granvillebeer @JJBeanCoffee When and where will this be avail? Not on any websites (BCLDB, etc.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Oil_THEdynasty @HorrorFanEdge @TanisS_14 @kenparkin77 was wondering what happened to ol' Dynasty... been FAR too quiet! #lol #welcomeback]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@mperfectwarrior @LawBlahLaw @EhJKay I knew it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go @BCLions ! Sorry for how it ended, but, she's always a fan :) https://t.co/QBkiJn1nkO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ERAvaCole geez what was on your mind lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you shitting me??? GO HOME! This doesn't concern you, not your country, you don't even get to vote. https://t.co/9tU41AsVBk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[R U KIDDING ME? What would u like us 2 do? Offer them a hug when they're feeling down &amp; attack us? Check it, OC fal… https://t.co/Kv3xTb7jjc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reports of multiple-shooting incident in Seattle at anti-trump protest?! This solves nothing. Smarten the fuck up. #tragic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alright so I'm done with my movie. How's the night? What's new?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Appropriate I'm watching an end-of-world film, Independence Day: Resurgence. Aliens vs. Trump. Meh #Trumpocalypse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drinking in an elementary school gym as a fundraiser and it's pirate night. #whatev #bestuncleever #arr #pirate… https://t.co/S43IOtOEzc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How about instead of HOPING for 'bounces' we actually use some SKILL to SCORE GOALS. https://t.co/B1ISskvWyG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Canuckula are you shittin' me?? 10 kids. Maybe 11.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#hopesanddreams #nopants https://t.co/XYb71Znir4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future is now! #coolshit https://t.co/jMkeWImzcp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@NEWS1130Traffic emergency vehicles on scene at 5:10. Three car pile. Truck/camper sandwiched a Honda between the car in front.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSpecialist4 @ctv_jon @wordpressdotcom oh good! Finally in the media! Here ya go!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>