<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@unitedMongrels @suilee crazy. I walked by studio every day. Never saw a soul. But it was quiet back in the 80s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lilsister7 better question: do THEY? I'm going with a NO on that. Haaaa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@unitedMongrels @suilee the first place I lived in London was while I was going to school there...on Abbey Road!  Not kidding! Miss it so]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm with you. Been paralyzed with illness since...💖💔💖💔💖 https://t.co/CP0y4y3u5v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@unitedMongrels @suilee can't even go to Canada anymore, without one. FFS. At least they're NICE in #Canada.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@unitedMongrels @suilee that would be a "hell, yes!". I need a new one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#RESIST #RESISTANCE #DumpTrump #WorstPOTUSinHistory  #banTrumpFromUK #BanTrumpStateVisit #PutinPuppet @POTUS… https://t.co/WXFCB7QjAw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actual lone wolves issue rare joint statement: "Stop comparing us to white terrorists" | CBC Comedy https://t.co/RNa25aatSG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#kushner #followthemoney https://t.co/UyGlZmhiSl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@POTUS @realDonaldTrump @Trump @IvankaTrump @DonaldJTrumpJr @EricTrump @TeamTrump @VP @PressSec #WorstPOTUSinHistory https://t.co/b1jq5pabUd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not gonna lie, I've been a little obsessed with acquiring canned goods and clean, safe water recently. https://t.co/sKsTm06JO4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BraddJaffy this is giving me a major  déjà vu. And not in a good way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lilsister7 @realDonaldTrump those tiny hand gestures drive me nuts. He looks like a #dumbPOTUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lilsister7 do i really want people to see me all hours of the day and night?? Hahaa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BraddJaffy that's kind of his job??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@unitedMongrels @BraddJaffy exactly!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mskristinawong trump/james smack down regarding constitutional law! Who's in?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mskristinawong and people actually like LeBron James!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swamiMAGS @PrellyLooralia @PaulBukta @RepAdamSchiff she's using her parent's computer...time for bed, young lady!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_vsvpdee @WIxFL make it known to your community]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GuntCrusha @WIxFL @BraddJaffy it's spelled M-O-R-O-N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#shameful #TrumpLiesMatter https://t.co/LQvCYofDOM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@unitedMongrels are you following @JohnFugelsang ? It's a must.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone have a video of Melissa as Spicer? I need to see it. Have no cable assess here. Please?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@unitedMongrels even my long-dead hardcore, very involved in catholic church grandparents would never vote for this monster.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@unitedMongrels @ChillACE_ this is a family show....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChillACE_ @unitedMongrels well, then...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is your president, USA! How are you not ashamed? https://t.co/do5B1f76Q2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@unitedMongrels even my 72 yr old former catechism teacher mother has taken to calling trump a #motherfucker.. haaa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@unitedMongrels you should hear me in real life!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@unitedMongrels sad that we are at this point. I'm ashamed of Americans for letting this happen. Ashamed and disgusted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VABVOX I'm missing it! I don't have cable here! Damnit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Call cheetolini at Mar a Lago 561.832.2600. He's lonely and feels like a loser. Please call and tell him he's final… https://t.co/NQBJ4Zpeho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#traitor #ImpeachTrump #BanBannon #banTrumpFromUK #BanTrumpStateVisit #banTrump #worstPOTUSinhistory @POTUS… https://t.co/0dVKMlWT24]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@goptraci @SenCortezMasto you need to read more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AsieduEdmund @vknowltonmarcus @kmusheno @guardian this is criminal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Khanoisseur I'm plugging your page on Facebook as much as possible, without trying to overdo it. Haa. Thanks for all your work!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marklatelle8 @himmiemom @POTUS attention whore troll.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiaJadeRoberto @marklatelle8 what kind of moron are you, then?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@imthesongbirdy @Khanoisseur @POTUS @realDonaldTrump thank you. He's working hard to give us a comprehensive way to follow what's happening]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Bannon’s influence on Trump https://t.co/sLVxxNW1ZS via @msnbc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the love of all that is decent in the world, would you all PLEASE follow @Khanoisseur here, on twitter. #focus @POTUS @realDonaldTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Khanoisseur, thank you!  Can we concentrate on the matter at hand, people? #trump #bannon #russia #kushner #mattis. #CORRUPTION....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gdebenedetti she incorrectly thought she'd be able to compromise with republicans. Don't give them an inch!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gdebenedetti that was a very bad move. @SenWarren #disappointed  #Massachusetts #Mapoli #MAvoter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is who he is. Even worse: people actually voted FOR this. #shameful #WorstPOTUSinHistory https://t.co/Ir9yb0R8Tb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mlcalderone @washingtonpost @POTUS @realDonaldTrump is  insulated, ignorant, delusional, and deranged. #WorstPOTUSinHistory]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PoliticalSphinx @joshgondelman of course it is! I don't know why or how people are just realizing this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been saying this for months. Keep picking at @realDonaldTrump and his inadequacies, failures, easily manipulat… https://t.co/2mO0rIAlDS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breitbart is your state-sponsored propaganda feed. @POTUS @realDonaldTrump @Trump @jaredkushner @VP #Bannon #Flynn… https://t.co/2AqpIMLls0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes! And thank you for pointing that out. I guess we need to send evidence to all those who try to create and infla… https://t.co/k4PJZOSN5T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are we 'great' yet? Sad. https://t.co/bhl5zzWhm0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PoliticalSphinx @joshgondelman There's no such thing as 'just politics' anymore. Everything in life is affected by what's happening]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PoliticalSphinx @caliwaterman they absolutely don't. And they are stubbornly and wilfully ignorant, and proud of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tipton exactly  @Rob162816 @joshrogin @washingtonpost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PoliticalSphinx @joshgondelman @Patriots good question. I only know they showed Kraft at trump fundraiser and inaugural party]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PoliticalSphinx until we get documentation, we can only assume that trump held the power over her to obtain visa.She worked before that tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PoliticalSphinx @joshgondelman @Patriots i am aware of that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshgondelman @PoliticalSphinx @Patriots what has brady done w trump lately? I think it's been a while since yhey played golf. Idk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PoliticalSphinx @joshgondelman @Patriots I agree he should not be singled out, because it's kraft and the organization that gave trump $$$]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PoliticalSphinx @joshgondelman @Patriots making brady the poster boy for this is probably not the way to go. It's the organization]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PoliticalSphinx @joshgondelman @Patriots #Kraft is a big trump donor. I will not support that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshgondelman I'll also be selling memorabilia and donating proceeds  to ACLU.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshgondelman I am  FORMER life-long @Patriots fan. As of last year, I am done. Great idea. #AGoodGame]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PoliticalSphinx he's groomed her since she was 28 yrs old to be blind to his misogyny and narcissism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NYTNational @nytimes #trump gave his doctor permission to disclose health info. No #HIPPA violation. Jesus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chiananti @Jtstdenis @NYTNational @nytimes for fuck's sake, people! Trump gave him permission!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottsongs @NYTNational @nytimes trump gave him permission. Where have you been?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carolctuck @NYTNational @nytimes short memory?  He gave him permission]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DiorIzzy @NYTNational @Fahrenthold @nytimes trump gave his doctor permission. Miss that part from before?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tbur2 @VillageIdiot136 @NYTNational @Fahrenthold @nytimes he sounds like he might me trump's illegitimate half brother.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanteRandwulf @lisarn317 @NYTNational @Fahrenthold @nytimes because having knowledge is a negative thing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump's doctor sounds as nutty as he is: delusional, excessive  reaction to criticism, self-importance..… https://t.co/TofB6kH9Cq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mike01027 Listening to the audio of trump saying "don't worry about it", his speech was slower than usual, as if tranquilized @Reuters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeNBC Where were your words against #trumpmonster when you were kissing his ass??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#RESIST #RESISTANCE #BanTrump #StopBannon #ImpeachTrump https://t.co/HnWsJzMOhz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Artistlike @suzgar1306 @amazon @JeffBezos @kramerbooks These people are evil, sick, and dangerous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amazon @JeffBezos YOU are part of the problem. #RESIST #BoycottAmazon #BoycottWhiteSupremecy #BoycottTrump https://t.co/5ycQWdr1kM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Artistlike @suzgar1306 @amazon @JeffBezos @amazon has far too many 'new sellers' also, but shipped by amazon. I don't trust them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's the way it SHOULD be, but NEVER actually has been. We still had a long way to go for equality, now it's bein… https://t.co/4eSixTInXa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suzgar1306 @Artistlike @amazon @JeffBezos the last 3 things I bought from @amazon were total junk, anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Freeyourmindkid or is it Twatsi?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Freeyourmindkid they are rotten on the inside and out, including little, young, &amp; dumb Tammy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anti-Trump backlash rapidly outpacing tea party in its prime https://t.co/g70uXpBvDa via @msnbc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VABVOX @ArtTillery1980 @aprivera05 @ShamelessWhit He's nobody. Just a  desperate attention-seeker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outrageous. Let Arkansas lawmakers know what disgusting, vile creatures they are! #RESIST https://t.co/bjALupXXpB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump: Iran playing with fire https://t.co/NDIptHYoHK via @msnbc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rewrite: Why Donald Trump is wrong about Harley-Davidson https://t.co/5ipfQWsiEn via @msnbc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What if Obama did what Trump is doing? https://t.co/jKDvmVGryF via @msnbc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me, too! - a FORMER @Patriots fan. I'm done with the #NewEnglandPatriots https://t.co/Z3icSYjopl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobynElyse He's an ignorant attention-whore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kgar_Horrible It will be going back and forth until it ends up in the Supreme Court]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NationalStrikeDay #NationalStrike  February 17 #BoycottTrump #RESIST #TheResistance https://t.co/ktzqy7bMv5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NationalStrikeDay Feb.17 #RESIST #BoycottTrump #TheResistance   https://t.co/h3gESMciSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NationalStrikeDay February 17 #RESIST #BoycottTrump #TheResistance @POTUS @realDonaldTrump @Trump   https://t.co/1MLVQPU6SA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Decisions...decisions...@realDonaldTrump @POTUS #WomensMarch #BanTrump  #BoycottTrump #NationalStrikeDay #RESIST… https://t.co/ZKuMGoprxY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YES to THIS     https://t.co/XnUvEMiedu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@unitedMongrels I will never relax with cheetonlini in the White House.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, FFS https://t.co/W6tw3s2GA4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fdell3 so much for trump's claim that he wants 'everyone' to have internet access. Access is the new word for 'only if you can afford it']]></document>
	</documents>
</author>