<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Sonya is annoying.. #neighbours]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessicamauboy I wish you wouldn't sing the anthem for the boxing match such a stupid sport.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boxing a stupid sport two people hitting each other]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanedelia Hi Shane, on Food channel they showed you making cheese toastie.. you have the same sandwich press what I have.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any chance of a follow back? https://t.co/y8la7gI3Gx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LynneMcGranger Hi Lynne just waiting for MKR you look so different from the early episodes still looking great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StGeorgeBank Hi.. I received an email to answer a survey. Do you normally send these emails? Linda.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was a large one..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi Dami, loved the song you sang with @GuySebastian please can you follow me back? https://t.co/J49cXy1kPd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GuySebastian Great duet with Dami Im.. just saw it now... your voices blend so well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EBraeden Have a lovely weekend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First world problem.. shock horror. https://t.co/byA4xqjpVR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning all except Fat Troll.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi David, please join my 2ue face book page?

https://t.co/oRJzbtIFFO https://t.co/MebLyrW8gz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hated this song. got too much over played https://t.co/Jd8lDErf82]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@woolworths Thank you for working today and delivering..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning all except fat Troll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealBradGarrett In the credits of Raymond why are only 2 of the childrens name is mentioned?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BensMenu Ben's Menu is a cooking show not a travel show... tired of that Scott person.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yuck Donald Trump on The Nanny..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its raining]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very overcast here in Bondi Beach.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate outages..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching EastEnders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could sleep now after dealing with @Telstra all day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does she always look dirty?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As ususal I was told a bunch of lies and waited till now to get back online only to find out the outage was fixed b… https://t.co/My4X7iTUPY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Telstra thank you for the 5 hour outage today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thexfactorau Its such a relief to watch XfactorUK without the audience screaming as soon as the contestant sings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its so nice not to see the Trolls tweets..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't stand Frida... Love Agnetha though https://t.co/H1QKk336ez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BensMenu Why does that Scott McCabe person always has to come on..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poor Shannon NOll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching X Factor UK now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That commercial with Richard Marx is annoying..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I pause all the gifs that I see on my time line]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you :) https://t.co/NuItZs31TJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[good morning... think I will faint if someone responded lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching X Factor UK..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop showing off Bronwyn... amateur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rageABC Please fix the play lists on the web site.. thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wish Ivy would stick to her natural Aussie accent.. #BoldandBeautiful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SBS_Food Man v Food sorry but I think this is a stupid show.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't stand Anthony Bourdaine.. he's so up himself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Channel7 Why is there no more old episodes of Home and Away in the morning?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She has to comment on each one... sheesh..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[boxing is stupid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grant Denyer is carrying on a bit too much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are there kids in the pubs in EastEnders?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steffie is so up herself.. #BoldandBeautiful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile tattoo remover.. how posh #BoldandBeautiful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's happened to the acting on Days..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is The Morning Show still on Summer series..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have my own Trolls too :) https://t.co/fX5LwWQ77b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gthomas1621 You're the only one who is arguing with me. End of discussion.. I gave you a second chance you have ruined it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No need to leave a post where the problem has been fixed. Enjoy . https://t.co/YNW2qBJskX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I REPEAT THE PROBLEM WAS FIXED NOW LEAVE ME ALONE. https://t.co/wFLyW6iJNs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because the problem was fixed and I said one foot out of place you would be out of the group. Yet you argue with me. https://t.co/YNW2qBrRtp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[G.I. Blues on now with Elvis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GuySebastian Set In Stone is being played on Smooth video channel right now on Foxtel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LyndeyMilan its very annoying not to say the amount of flour,sugar etc.. not everyone might have the internet who is watching.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saturday Kitchen stupid show on how fast you can make scrambled eggs lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No its not, its a pain... thank you xx https://t.co/Q4HGYonn1E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On here they had me going round in circles didn't they. Thanks re health. I have Lymphodeama which is not good at t… https://t.co/GhskRTL14k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heya.. could be better health wise.. but yes finally sorted out the phone and I got a refund not from the dim wits… https://t.co/NWeyeBOYXg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one chats with me here on Twitter sigh..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man v food stupid show]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rick_Stein Happy belated Birthday from Sydney, Australia. Love your shows.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its gotta be the 70's when I grew up as teenager. https://t.co/v46P9zQcVL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's so wrong should be given to the boys to keep https://t.co/EJjtZYhwIg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sound of Music, Annie(original), Grease, https://t.co/vu9YjxB7R8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#DrOz I pay my credit card in full on the 1st of every month I don't pay the minimum will take forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love how I get no responses in Twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too spicy for me https://t.co/eK2CE9bGOX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is i with chorizo!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KJC135 Because of the lock on your accoung I can quote your tweets..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning Happy New Year!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@therealroseanne Happy New Year from Australia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will anyone else be on their own tonight like me?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VodafoneAU_Help See.. you didn't reply back to me when I said I phoned up vodafone and they gave me my $15 credit right away!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11.11 + a couple of mins last for the year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Julia Morris is already annoying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To text to 1900 numbers. Thanks for nothing... why couldn't you do that in the first place without the run around..… https://t.co/FaV06mdrD7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You were no help to me - so tired of waiting with broken promises - I rang direct and I was straight away given a r… https://t.co/DwGDW9cxoG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi.. I don't talk as much on here as I do on Facebook https://t.co/awd4DBwbjC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There really is nothing on Foxtel at the moment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching Good Chef/Bad Chef.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As I have said I already sent email but you can't find it https://t.co/UeaQjIHSrJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VodafoneAU_Help Oh and don't suggest me sending an email because I already have and you said you can't find it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VodafoneAU_Help I just got a reminder to recharge to get extra data how about refunding me my $15!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was a low flying plane over Bondi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlackheathWx Here in Bondi Beach a couple of years ago it reached 46!!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>