<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[International Holocaust Remembrance Day #ResistanceBookClub https://t.co/IomtfzSbHJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Use your Park as a "third space" to play, walk, read, eat and meet with friends #sustainability #healthy https://t.co/nclQB02wcr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ResistanceBookClub https://t.co/rXOGAHhTat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our government is too cowardly to stand up to fascism https://t.co/7vZ7yGpwmH via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Malcolm Turnbull, stop the mealy-mouthed platitudes and stand up for our values | Kristina Keneally https://t.co/zjLLBq4URx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can still keep global warming below 2℃ – but the hard work is about to start https://t.co/Q8oyiupXZa via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is really easy if you are Australian to email your elected MPs and Senators. Find them and email https://t.co/SEvNWfcpO3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope I'm wrong: Shorten stands by 'barking mad' Trump comments https://t.co/x2y5jBg2D1 via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what leadership looks like @TurnbullMalcolm https://t.co/C9eRYbZGfz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrMel_T Ones that particularly upset me as an educator are ones where protagonist has diminished vocab which limits their abstract thinking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrMel_T Margaret Atwood's Year of the Flood.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ehekkala Like the hashtag #resistencebookclub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrMel_T However living near Canberra is convenient for going to protests]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrMel_T wondering whether living near Canberra is a good idea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrMel_T Have read 1984 and Brave New World over past few days but planning to move onto Handmaid's Tale and Fahrenheit 451 next]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PlanetDr a steam ship]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be fierce, furious, and fight! Join the Raccoons of the Resistance! | First Dog on the Moon https://t.co/wkPbu4rgAn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COMMENT: The real threat to Freedom of Expression in Australia is not the Racial Discrimination Act | NITV https://t.co/jbpYOzGe1V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is Up Helly Aa https://t.co/3RFvybSzT0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is Independence Day of Nauru https://t.co/2vKNNoZofU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to composer Franz Schubert https://t.co/ID0b0cNxTk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ideas for Australian Activism https://t.co/IRY7kG3QJa via @wordpressdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suddenly, Muslims are America’s pariahs | Nesrine Malik https://t.co/LBtLpNYs9o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to run a Resistance twitter account https://t.co/pEoDaUNeF3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ningaloo Reef captured from sky in drone-driven health check https://t.co/xnilur4WZO via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using bubble wrap on your windows to keep your house cool https://t.co/moCM0QIYbt via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When It Comes To Chores, You Can't Reap What You Don't Sew https://t.co/NPPH16YBWt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canberra weather: Total fire ban in the ACT declared, with severe fire danger warning https://t.co/5ZNdXrNLat via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump's ban will have lasting and damaging impacts on the world's refugees https://t.co/UgEwpxmw6I via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's order barring refugees flies in the face of logic and humanity https://t.co/WovD64noWt via @ConversationUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow this thread to find out which US Governors have spoken out against #MuslimBan https://t.co/QEoe9UiKc4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2017 isn't '1984' – it's stranger than Orwell imagined https://t.co/MTwxeHGuJN via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow this thread to find out which senators have condemned Trump's #MuslimBan and which haven't. https://t.co/GfLXhvyOCH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No president cares more about size – so let’s show Trump how many of us oppose him https://t.co/6R0fwwfu4n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cattle rot on the streets as Dalits revolt against discrimination https://t.co/myORfWRDbs via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump's Muslim ban excludes countries in which he has business ties https://t.co/IrTnJ4Qbsi via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trudeau says Canada will take refugees banned by U.S. https://t.co/txwchn0Efb via @NewsHour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What you need to know about Trump's immigration ban https://t.co/97Z7Eg1l4y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to author Allan Baillie https://t.co/7GLYsBsbu4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to inventor Lawrence Hargrave https://t.co/TYAPXf69N1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posters celebrate Indigenous languages, 'the origins of Australia's multiculturalism' – video https://t.co/JhsMMWH4NI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OED please put #teachmeet in the dictionary https://t.co/MqFcsl5qop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['I was murdered in Auschwitz': victims of Holocaust remembered on Twitter https://t.co/U56UEQVgFV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backyard chooks eat food scraps, turn leaves and shredded paper to soil and lay eggs #sustainability https://t.co/04JJJyNxoD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After Trump's #refugeeban, Aussie politicians need a plan to evacuate #Manus &amp; #Nauru immediately https://t.co/qFE84btmTv via @GetUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My fortune cookie : "No person is your friend who demands your silence or denies your right to grow" seems to have nailed 2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the time of fake news, we cannot be silent about the truth https://t.co/vK9kLaiB0J via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RayPNorris maybe if we all help them https://t.co/8UCTWyEqz9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Website That Tracked Fake Science Journals Has Suddenly Vanished via @IFLScience: https://t.co/VTfilT6ibP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Compost garden clippings, autumn leaves, floor sweepings , human and pet hair #sustainability https://t.co/HE5LsHP7mA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dry clothes and bed linen on clothes line not dryer #sustainability https://t.co/I9GOeWocph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fireworks and feasts as Asia welcomes Lunar New Year https://t.co/2h5fTAH8J0 via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is Tet- Vietnamese New Year https://t.co/WTKYEgahkG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please share with all pro-science groups https://t.co/sCqaMQ7I10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is Chinese New Year - The Year of the Rooster https://t.co/uMlCeigQKE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese new year: millions head home for festivities – in pictures https://t.co/0eF1kefMlR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia leads push to save far eastern curlew from extinction https://t.co/m8fdVKuw1F via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to artist Jackson Pollack https://t.co/8lBCYVStpc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our democracy is broken, debased and distrusted – but there are ways to fix it | George Monbiot https://t.co/f5hlM6RthN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Don't wear long jewellery': Shelter releases guide for women ready to flee abuse https://t.co/MMrTNlhi71 via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['You must be fun at parties'? Why I couldn't care less if men think I lack a sense of humour https://t.co/zAB3dsB0cz via @DailyLifeAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coles and Woolworths' soft drink sales slump amid health fears - Isn't this a good thing? https://t.co/hsVbHoey6h via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you care about science please follow this account and go to the marches #ScienceMarchAu https://t.co/sCqaMQ7I10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deadly wildfire razes entire town in Chile: 'Literally like Dante's Inferno' https://t.co/Pi4FuqWqQQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who’s taking the fight to Trump? It’s Dictionary Guy | Emma Brockes https://t.co/pD7QhK4ne0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can Raccoons of the Resistance save Science from the Tantrumocracy? | First Dog on the Moon https://t.co/ZC6PbvQX0A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['What are you actually celebrating?' Indigenous elder says Australia Day debate must continue https://t.co/pbw1AeISWU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The US refugee deal grows shakier by the day. Turnbull must find a humane way forward | Daniel Webb https://t.co/ksMt0LCBZr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five Pacific islands lost to rising seas as #climatechange hits https://t.co/syjB5Z2kYq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is the Doomsday Clock and why should we keep track of the time? https://t.co/ktziy2fzGP via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to tell if your child's educational needs are being met at school https://t.co/AtACK6Ch90 via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Australia, land of the 'fair go', not everyone gets an equal slice of the pie https://t.co/6rWhgGYUFq via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Queanbeyan Uniting Church Community Garden Fundraising Dinner 4th March https://t.co/OzRuS65eJq … #iamqbn #Queanbeyan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you following #CelebratingWomen project yet on https://t.co/a3itDwquIM ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How breeding fish in the classroom could fix a big problem in our schools. #Enviroed  https://t.co/Lgau69xCIC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stan Grant on the search for ancestor Frank Foster https://t.co/FHUsJUed2X via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Burst your bubble: five conservative articles to read during Trump's first week https://t.co/IQlTr1DfSI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forget Nineteen Eighty-Four. These five dystopias better reflect Trump’s US | Alex Hern https://t.co/x7TSuZxp4y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is Multicultural Children's Book Day https://t.co/agk4sOEg4q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is International Holocaust Remembrance Day https://t.co/aInyRGzCKb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to author and poet Lewis Carroll https://t.co/MKUIkp4pET]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to composer Wolfgang Amadeus Mozart https://t.co/zaHjlVaiol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scientists may have proven women are better at multitasking than men https://t.co/w9b8zOL1oe via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parrot pie and possum curry – how colonial Australians embraced native food https://t.co/Fa1yqaO6s4 via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia Day, Invasion Day, Survival Day: a long history of celebration and contestation https://t.co/gvtCt9WaNQ via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The twin blessings of universal health and education have shaped who I am | Ranjana Srivastava https://t.co/9xRB8UgM0N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perth youth group's rethink Australia Day video goes viral  https://t.co/rJxXYUPE3k via @watoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For Aboriginal and Torres Strait Islander people today is Survival Day or Invasion Day or Mourning Day https://t.co/GcT8KQhCFF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is Australia Day https://t.co/TeTEg3TOkV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy birthday to dancer and author Li Cunxin https://t.co/1FOc37sIen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump, climate vandal, springs to action on the environment https://t.co/4riLwSrCCX via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for a great #Enviroed chat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KateKeary1 @ChrisVella2 Guess that could be a problem since we are not all from same countries Yes/No?  #Enviroed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A6. Have we done teaching #enviroed in all different KLAs?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Second that . Even I have done it. you just follow the instructions #enviroed https://t.co/yvmC3q8yAs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevenbody I would like to hear from @Joe_Teft in Singapore #Enviroed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ecostew007 @tonialgray Hi Sue lovely to see you #Enviroed (What is WSU?)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisVella2 Major benefit of this PLN is not feeling isolated and continuously being inspired #Enviroed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My work is up in the air at the moment but a friend and I are planning to do a Climate for Change dinner #enviroed https://t.co/DC0WXFgYcM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi @MichaelBoller2 good to have you with us #Enviroed]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>