<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@lenoretaylor Sweden's Deputy PM is a Green. So proud of her stand on climate and her feminist perspective.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did Aust talk to Fiji about what action to take re granting asylum or sending refugee back to PNG? Need to clarify @JulieBishopMP #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's an idea @BCA support Publish What You Pay  so we can see how much your members pay to grease wheels for miners overseas #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BCA is face of corporate greed and climate irresponsibility. Neoliberal cheerleaders'bid for lower corporate taxes should be ignored.#auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jaraparilla @TurnbullMalcolm All who voted to repeal the carbon price committed a crime against the environment. No more back slapping.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good on @SenatorSiewert, doing the hard yards in Senate for Aboriginal and Torres Strait Islander people. https://t.co/pHTWyad0eA #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vicsaranmoore Then we need a strong show of support for @GreensMPs War Powers Bill. Lib/Lab/Nat don't support Parlt deciding. #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Knitting Nannas have made yellow and black #LockTheGate caps symbol of anti #csg. Time to add https://t.co/n79o61RuGn  for winter. #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any conversations between Aust and Fiji @JulieBishopMP pre snatching? Would have been embarrassing if Fiji had granted asylum.#auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#GrabYourWallet campaign starts in USA. Don't buy anything from Trump businesses. Plus women's solidarity. https://t.co/n79o61RuGn #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greensinspa @cunningham_cch Greens brought forward legislation to give Parlt war power but Lib Lab Nats opposed. This must change. #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perhaps now community sees need for Parlt to decide on sending Aust troops to war and not be left to PM. Appeasing Trump is pathway to war.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is great idea for old fur coats and stoles, inherited but unwanted: Give them back to wildlife. https://t.co/PIaSFzDCMr #animalrescue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republicans have overturned ban on people with severe mental illness owning guns. Gun culture gone mad. #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 1997 Howard and state premiers exempted forestry from Env Law for 20 yrs. Now Tas/Vic/Turnbull want to extend 20 more yrs. #EndRFA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This young man's life is in your hands @TurnbullMalcolm. Whatever happens to him on streets of PNG is down to you. https://t.co/Sj92oJJRZc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is FIRB doing? Housing Affordability undermined by thousands of empty investment properties. Tax empty homes. https://t.co/YDnWve61oS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@guardianeco @readfearn As Treasurer Hockey organised a session at G20 in Aust for Peabody to present. Also invited Lomborg. #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aust distinguishes between facilitation fee and a bribe. Former legal, latter illegal. Mining, oil and gas pay "facilitation fees". #corrupt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia still does not require "publish what you pay"to grease palms of corrupt Governments. Blind eye for mates. https://t.co/wxGTjd7vpB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tourism pressure one of drivers of degradation in World Heritage areas @WillHodgman https://t.co/E7BBVXRita #politas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ABC could have reversed decision to axe Catalyst but it didn't. Don't let management get away with not delivering on 17 docs. #Science]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember ABC Catalyst? Remember the promise of 17 docs /1 hr to replace it? Pack of lies.  It is Feb, when is Doc 1 Michelle Guthrie?#auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opened Tas artist Di Masters exhibition, Undercurrents. 50% Earth's oxygen comes from plankton. Saving forests imp but so too oceans.#auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does the U.S. Refugee deal require special forces to Iraq and Aust involvement in exercises in South China Sea? @TurnbullMalcolm #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Ministerial Responsibility still applied in Aust politics, Scott Morrison would have to resign. He has cost taxpayers $1m + #Auspol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmbBleich Thank You for calling out moral cowardice of those who go along with the perpetrators of injustice. Aust now a Trump appeaser.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greens from around world stand in solidarity with people of Canada who will not allow hate to overcome love and generosity. @ElizabethMay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia discriminates against people based on their mode of arrival, (boats) locks them up and bans them for life. @billshortenmp #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brandis must not be given os posting. The whole WA, Bell, ATO, Gleeson episode must be investigated seriously. #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man who bugged East Timor to be replaced by man who authorised seizure of documents and prevented witness from travelling to Hague. #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can Aust help green card holders stranded at airports? Is there a website/NGO getting organised? #auspol @GuardianAus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lukemartin83 "outdated" is neoliberal code for "unavailable for private profit". How many focus groups to come up with that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's ban is illegal and appalling but also revealing that Saudi Arabia which finances terrorism is excluded. https://t.co/zksqwQwfJX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are appalled by Trump's ban, take action and condemn @TurnbullMalcolm lifetime ban on people who arrive by boat. Defeat it in Senate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Given Aust dual nationals are banned, Turnbull cannot weasel out of raising issue with Trump in his call today. #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jeff_Sparrow It must be condemned. Aust on same trajectory leading to Trump.Howard,Rudd,Gillard,Abbott, Morrison, Turnbull, Dutton.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Presumably many Australians affected by Trump dual national ban. https://t.co/d3FMu9vjOA What say you @TurnbullMalcolm ? #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. invades Iraq, bombs Syria displaces millions then bans refugees. Media focus on "homeland security" and not on chain of responsibility.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@43a6f0ce5dac4ea They don't have a "Wilderness" World Heritage Area. Commercial development should be outside boundaries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dig it up, cut it down and if you can't do that build a road into it or put a  commercial cabin on it. Welcome to Hodgman's Tas Nat Parks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Outdated" used as excuse for undermining protection of Nat Parks in favour of commercial development. Culture yes; resorts no. #politas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian Labor and Liberal Govts have done this to a 17 year old.PMs /Mins move on without a worry. https://t.co/b677t7crLp #SeeYouInHague]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations Mavis. Thank you for everything you have done for the community and our environment. #politas https://t.co/aJ42CsNTyY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@GuardianAus: Australia's coal power plan twice as costly as renewables route, report finds https://t.co/nlLYfn9wcV” Abbott power bills??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People pursue capital gain, not rent. Buy off plan, leave empty @TurnbullMalcolm How about taxing empty homes? https://t.co/tIU7D8V5Qb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TurnbullMalcolm it is not a supply problem in Melb either. https://t.co/1g63UN32at #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TurnbullMalcolm It is not supply that is problem. https://t.co/Gs6sqCEW7g #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone who knows Macquarie knows it's a bad idea to hand over @GreenInvBank to them. https://t.co/AyEK92dmj6 https://t.co/DxRbdNoPSE #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How many apartments/ dwellings are empty in  Syd /Melb? It is not about supply. Tax empty investment apartments. https://t.co/Weai4MlANa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Makes mockery of Direct Action, pay farmers not to clear and wipe out gains by encouraging others to clear more. https://t.co/b3LBC6GmaF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Problem is method Corps use to make sure it's not theirs that is left in ground.Political donations fund climate denial+attack on RE.#auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great move forward, Karratha Council has unanimously agreed in principle to World Heritage listing of #Burrup Aboriginal Rock Art #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When is the global community going to call out Australia as rogue party to #ParisAgreement? https://t.co/8J1upO3PkM @UNFCCC  @UNEP @SE4All]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So sad for people in Melb and victims' families.Hits home because random nature of killing means could've been any one of us. #solidarity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you stand for Green liveable cities and against #WestConnex #EastWestLink, then stand with people protecting Beeliar #NoRoe8 in  WA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So proud of all the people fighting to protect the Beeliar wetlands from destruction to make way for another road. Thank you. #NoRoe8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesEltonPym Threats to people or property should be referred to police. Billboard company appears to be hosting RACV ad.What's RACV view?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama's $1b to Green Climate Fund is good but falls short of $3b pledged. #ParisAgreement https://t.co/egd5XxF1Pi #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@QMS Make Australia Day for everyone. Reject racism. #PutItBackUp #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putting every cent of fuel excise increase into new roads has delivered cash for #WestConnex It was always bad idea. Lib/Lab voted for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QMS Media took down advert after being threatened. Why? Giving in to racists is cowardice. Profits more imp than principles? Put it back up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mohamad_sowaid @AustralisTerry @QMS should not have caved in to racism by removing Advert. Give your kids a hug.Tell them to stand tall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lenoretaylor It is time Clive Palmer's "feeding the chooks" was called out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrogsGamut You forgot to add re this year's polo trip, dressed by Hugo Boss as guest of Alpha Romeo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Justpeachijo Good Question. Currently not there at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When are we going to have "dressed by" added to "guest of" in list of  Parliamentary pecuniary interest disclosure? #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@broomstick33 That is the problem. We need to take back democracy from corporates and not give in to them by filling Parlt with celebs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As democracies have become plutocracies, elected MPs chase celebrity and become faces of their bosses, not the people who elected them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Two main uses of celebrity culture, corporate personification and mass distraction." Monbiot No wonder Aust politics morphing to celebrity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aust political expenses scandal. Celebrity as smiling face of corporate power. https://t.co/sB6YQBiMlU #auspol @GrogsGamut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla offers lower home battery prices than AEMO predicted for 2040. Time for 100% RE analysis with realistic not conservative assumptions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hard to believe that Aust Chief Scientist wants to slow roll out of renewables and not speed it up. @UNFCCC @Davos @billmckibben]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell Chief Scientist Alan Finkel to stick with science and stop playing politics. We totally reject a cap on Renewable Energy. We want 100%.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotRorsta Opposing Australia going back into Iraq. @GreensMPs only ones to oppose Abbott's folly. Called for Parlt to decide on war, not PM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vale Lord Snowden. His best work was Snowden Tasmania Essay 1981 which upset Robin Gray so much, he had it withdrawn and shredded. #politas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keating is right. Aust needs to tell Trump that we will not be part of US adventurism. We should have done it #Iraq 2003, we must do it now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[30% of all vehicles sold in Norway in 2016 were electric. Australia is so far behind. https://t.co/sZV4Oj5ayj #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[National #ICAC and political donations reform go together.Set strict rules and enable transparent compliance/enforcement. #auspol #democracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing less than National #ICAC will do. Increase pressure on @billshortenmp @TurnbullMalcolm to agree. @GreensMPs fully support. #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@virginsnowbunny Non violent direct action is appropriate response when all else has failed in face of Govt facilitated Env destruction.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Art as Activism. Excellent response to another Aboriginal death in custody. Ms Dhu's death must not be in vain. https://t.co/0UQ1hiS1yd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This, https://t.co/MFtpIzALsu and this, https://t.co/sB6YQBiMlU Politicians as celebrities and corporate "friends". #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Macquarie's record scrutinised in H of Commons debate. Max pressure on Govt to stop sale of @GreenInvBank https://t.co/osJO4eV8mu #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarolineLucas led House of Commons debate on sale of @GreenInvBank to Macquarie. All parties now opposed. #auspol @MichaelWestBiz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See Bishop at Polo and Cormann at AFL as more than travel expenses, invitation by Jeep/NAB. Face of corporate power. https://t.co/JLd7o38Z0k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aust doesn't accurately measure #CSG methane.Just approved Qld 6100 new wells When will @UNFCCC seriously scrutinise?https://t.co/M7MfJb1IrL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@GuardianAus: 'Clean coal' advocacy group says businesses crippled by power bills https://t.co/isxHkKi3jA” Fossil fuel front. #Astroturfing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarolineLucas Has Macquarie given any assurance @GreenInvBank will continue to fund green projects in UK? #auspol https://t.co/MB50OYCnrA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No amount of talking about expenses reform will change anything. A National ICAC will drive behavioural change. #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JanAssink @UNEP Ice shelf floating but acts as brake on glaciers. Once brake removed, glaciers move faster, more ice to ocean and sea rise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK media all over @GreenInvBank sale to Macquarie. The Guardian, Financial Times and now https://t.co/yY8uiG4ezm #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Libs in Aust always copy Tories. If @GreenInvBank sold to Macquarie for asset strip, watch LNP do same @CEFCAus. Govt gets $, kills RE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 new companies registered  in UK pre Xmas with same names as @GreenInvBank assets signals Macquarie's asset strip plans. Fin Times #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C'mon #auspol, when are you going to cover growing concern in UK about sale of @GreenInvBank to "vampire kangaroo" Macquarie? FT latest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aust worried by Macquarie's acquisition of UK @GreenInvBank. If Tories can't abolish they sell and let predators destroy @CarolineLucas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow Macquarie under intense scrutiny as opposition to it acquiring/asset stripping @GreenInvBank grows. https://t.co/NYFXHfP4Jp #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Downer and Brandis, Howard and Abbott chickens have come home to roost #EastTimor. When will they be held to account? #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swoods210 No, every time @GreensMPs have tried for Federal #ICAC, it has been opposed by Lib, Lab and Nats. #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["the cure." E.F.Schumacher This idea sustained me through awful debates in Aust Senate on climate and refugees as majority voted against.3/3]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>