<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@AGhostler *if]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AGhostler I would not recommend the songs in fallout 4 of your getting over a breakup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@addamschloe I found the Russian spy lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kayyybearxo I'm glad I found this account lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OneyNG favourite 40k army?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LilyFoxMechanic happpy birthday :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AGhostler humans because space marines and god emperor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GamingAndPandas I must have missed that when did that happen?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AGhostler I cry every time. :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_icze4r I see absolutely nothing that can go wrong here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AGhostler If there was ever "good guys" in 40k...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GMShivers lol I'll cheer for you if they do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GMShivers they should hire you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PoliticalKathy I agree but the top left is Obamas inauguration crowed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@omyc_blog @LisaBrenner2 lol there is nothing hypocritical in my posts. And nothing is wrong just saying "little human inside mums tummy."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@omyc_blog @LisaBrenner2 @Toddkron I like funny posts but I'm not a troll lady. Lol and anybody should have a say on the sanctity of life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LisaBrenner2 @Toddkron helping refugees is all well and good and so is realising there's a little human growing inside mums tummy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LisaBrenner2 @Toddkron Lisa that tweet is both hypocritical and heartless. Be thankful your mum didn't decide to abort you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VimHomeless @kay_landd happy Australia Day lol ðŸ‡¦ðŸ‡º]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tashwil06 lol we will be ok just as long as the Star Trek scenario happens instead of the Terminator Skynet one. Haha. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tashwil06 *the good aspect she.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tashwil06 neither just enjoy to good aspects and look around the world and realise how nice a place Australia is to live.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mombot I don't know who the dev is but yeah that crowd is responsible for trying to censor games for no reason.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@omgorf @_icze4r the struggle is real.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@4NIKKOLAS @realDonaldTrump Hope that gets fixed soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FishyPlays @FeihcsiimNot @georgieonthego There are legitimate things wrong with the switch. Lack of voice chat for example.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Umbra_Luna @Camillaesque I love this exchange lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wokieleaks1 just when you think you've seen it all....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@psychicpebble it's a winner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheCartoonLoon I think the sonic one got hate more likely because it was unfinished.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MakaylaMashelle @MON1QUEPOUR wait what's the age difference in the photos? Lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheCartoonLoon god damn. Yeah stuff like that can be all sorts of trouble.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheCartoonLoon has he done somthing recently?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This controversy with the Health minister is stupid. She did her job while she was in Queensland and bought an apartment with her own money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neontaster nuked from orbit holy shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrisonPlanet I'm trying to keep my nose out of politics but the double standards are astronomical.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GamingAndPandas I'm blocked and the only interaction I have had with him was liking one of his funny gg tweets years ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DreaChu they are good resolutions to have I just need to stick to them lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DreaChu to work hard and exercise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#noblesenpai Is there any recent science fiction anime that's good?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Miya_ism has science gone to far?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoopieDoOver Best revenge is doing well in life. You've gone through some serious shit. Also doesn't help if they aren't sorry. Merry Xmas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Hammerhawk23 @Broelman ACL is both.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Broelman I find it hard to believe filling a van with gas tanks and driving it to a political headquarters was not politically motivated...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GMShivers that's too much for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JenPlaysGames it's pretty sweet! Except I want the fire physics to burn down those crude moblin watch towers lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JenPlaysGames you seen all the gameplay footage coming from Nintendo?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MisterMetokur we always said it would happen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ahruon the graphics for the ps2 were pretty damn good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NeruNox I had to double check the picture to make sure it wasn't the aftermath of an ancient disaster. :/ The image is creepy as hell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Djoats420 @HopeStillFlies globalism means giantesses? Sign me up lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrueIslamUSA @Ryan33812647 I got to give you guys credit for respond to a lot of people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GamingAndPandas for his sake I hope he is different IRL and doesn't act like his twitter account.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@norespawns I'm just happy it's more Star Trek.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NayrmanBSC Reck it Ralph seemed to do video games right. But it probably really had to considering the whole movie was about games.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gyohdon @Kite_Tales and Owlboy streams lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kite_Tales @Gyohdon why do I love the idea of evil Kite tales? Help me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ahruon is that Halo in the background?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@30SECONDFlGHTS  Kid in the black shirt starts it. 
Nobody breaks it up. 
Kid in the red shirt comes back swinging. 
Then they break it up..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DreaChu @kyleehenke I can feel the love â¤ï¸lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DreaChu @kyleehenke lol I'm fam now. ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DreaChu @kyleehenke wow you both are kawaii masters! ;) never stop doing art the both of you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DreaChu god damn that profile pic. â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Attenboroughs_D @RitaPanahi you really do have to watch out for the barbs on stingray I'm surprised she let them get that close.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gameiversary my most cherished game in the whole world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiteralSalt he is a lucky man. Lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seinfeld2000 4th me: Yes :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@X_Aeon_X @DSVoight if it was a white guy saying this about any minority...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ahruon youtube with a link on the twitter feed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump if you and the Military generals can stop the terror groups without collateral damage that be fantastic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Tsunami everyone in Japan please stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kite_Tales I was just looking combo up yesterday lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahCAndersen I have the same birthday as Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrittPettibone @IBeBibby Jesus is it any wonder most women I know don't care about this crap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With Trump working out a peace plan with Russia I hope that the U.S and Russian space programs can come together in the name of science.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@3QUlN0X @EmilAaslund @YouTube lol I got creeped out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RitaPanahi lol u know about Sonichu And all of that mess Rita?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sitcom idea have characters who resemble Trump and Burnie be room mates in a New York apartment complex.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Soo the most important question this election. When is Anime becoming real? #trump #ElectionDay #ElectionNight https://t.co/Grbs9z5J0R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stillgray He was close though to being the democratic nominee not many people can say that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stillgray I liked Burnie. From what I know of him he does seem to have a good heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GMShivers store your rupee stash with me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ahruon @DPadStudio @0nepixel you might like this Kite :) @Kite_Tales]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chaffXgrenade These 2 were the best detectives. And who ever wrote the Law and order theme was a genius.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GMShivers one day you will be a real girl and not a necklace. You just have to believe. :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kite_Tales My favourite evil kite moment was when you said you love watching small creatures burn. Lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kite_Tales @YouTube this is going to be great lol. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kite_Tales if this game had voice acting you'd be perfect for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@8bitfiction noticed your last few posts. Someone is on my mind like that as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RetrospectivePC https://t.co/gv7g4kSPfU

This looks very cool &amp; Fallout like.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@call_me_senpai god damn. Some people. Best to ignore them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@call_me_senpai does she say stuff like this often?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@call_me_senpai I'm confused to how this is even possible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@call_me_senpai Nearly 50k followers? And she says stuff like this without joking about it? What the hell?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@call_me_senpai Dear God, why would anyone seriously think this way?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GamingAndPandas hahaha. Thank you for that panda.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@call_me_senpai I hope that's a troll and not how someone really thinks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaptHat211 Have not read the comic but it looks like it has the potential to be a lot of fun. But the fun is sapped away by that rhetoric.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CrankyConstruct @SpewingMews love the style.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ninichimusic @DadaiStudios this guy lol https://t.co/rpyNELpije]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>