<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Plz help me meet my #birth #family https://t.co/EeNhxvnQN5 #reunite #adoption #brother #aunt #mom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#SNL were they ALL high tonight? LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sound familiar? Need help? Contact me. Harmony Coaching, specializing in #narcopath #recovery https://t.co/j0HXE3jDAR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#lifecoach #abuse #healing #loveyourself https://t.co/FyDwmIlcNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Harmony #Life #Coach for #traumatic #relationships and those encountering #lifes little #speed #bumps https://t.co/I7o5NZbWjq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found my #birth #family, now I'd like to #meet them Can you help #donate to my #grehound #fund #please? https://t.co/yiNgIilX0R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimHortons im celebrating by practicing rolling my R's. Oh and drinking a Timmies :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#narcopath #abuse #coach Recognize, leave, survive and avoid it. $30 will get you started on the #path to #wellness https://t.co/0WFKMuHc61]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help me travel to meet my #birth #family #RT #share #adoption #canada  https://t.co/avP1DouwNW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#RT the shit out of this. #trumpsucks #fucktrump #youkilledcanadians #notmypresident #ImpeachTrump https://t.co/6OqexCUqvP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephenKing I hope he takes the record for fastest impeachment ever!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With so much going on in the world, it has everyones attention. It doesn't always need yours. https://t.co/qljlL1W5tP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MinhLu27 Don't compare you to others; you are the best thing about you; love and like yourself first; Every morn upon waking say I like me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#impeach the bastard already. https://t.co/kPU0pFmixR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My sorrow and tears run for #Quebec tonight. My absolute outrage for trump and his policies steep in condemnation. #trumpsfault]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reunite with my #Birth #Family https://t.co/xIptlnoxcA #love #travel #adoption #share #greyhound #ViaRail #canada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Trevornoah I'm a narcopath recovery coach. My heart breaks at what he's doing  :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell @HealthCanada: Ban the bee-killing pesticide imidacloprid and save Canadian #bees for good https://t.co/b22KNQgIom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So when is #trump going to take down the Statue of Liberty?  #trumpedfreedom https://t.co/SHxvU9u2Mw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Canucks @BoHorvat SNOOOOOOP Hey Bo can I have a Dogg too please? lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help me Meet My Birth Family Fund https://t.co/XvuLvBx6pn Plz RT #love #adoption #birthfamily #vancouver #sudbury #northbay #happiness #live]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NEWS1130 link goes to surrey shooting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PTSDchat_org I am a narcopath recovery coach...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VancouverSun thry need to do better job of 180. Short bus replaced 40' and people are being left stranded, missing appts and charged for it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems like a good segue https://t.co/yqcBZ1srV5 @TheEllenShow @VancityBuzz #adoption #FamilyFirst https://t.co/ReEsQjQFHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love-bombing. Typical trait of a narcopath. If you are in a/just out of a relationship with one, talk to someone.… https://t.co/fHo3QMDF8v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parents, listen to your children. They aren't lying when they say somethings wrong #bellletstalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Canucks Go my children. Decimate the enemy. I mean GO NUCKS lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Help me Meet My Birth Family https://t.co/bkf4SLABHZ #adopted #rt #birthfamily #love #support #family #donate #money #mom #dad #brother]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unfollowed potus several days ago...found myself following him again today. WTF twitter? Unfollowed again. Documented by this tweet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ALTERNATIVEFACT: Is a non-truth to enforce own version. To be better quality than yours. Therefore, more believable. TRUE NARCOPATHIC FACT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm raising $$ to Meet My Birth #Family I'm #adopted and recently found them.   #Donate:  https://t.co/1MfoLj1pQy via @gofundme Plz RT LUV U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MELANIATRUMP narcopath. Please google it sister. Please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrankieJGrande happy birthday Frankie, you beautiful human you :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Know someone who's been #abused by a #narcopath? https://t.co/11tmds1u7i #healing is possible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because more people showed up 4 years ago ROFL #narcopath https://t.co/Ti2zWLH0gI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richardbranson that is your most important legacy. Congratulations to your family :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Narcopath #Recovery #Coach.
Lets #talk 
$30 will get you started.
Start #healing today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BT_Vancouver @NEWS1130 I may now stop buying my books online!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Patriots YAYYY GO PATS boy is my family mad at me LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joodlesnoodles this is will LOL (and me LOL) https://t.co/qQBcOQ26NZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday double checked to make sure wasn't following flotus yet today I find myself following her. WTF?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@trevor_linden Today on "did you know"...we are cousins. We share an aunt/uncle in red deer :D  Was a Van Fan before I even knew that!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephenKing If you've dated/worked for/lived w/a narcopath, get ready cause he's the grandaddy of all narcopaths leading an entire nation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And for those who've suffered at hands of a #narcopath, do not watch it. Dm me for help. https://t.co/kexIAmapWR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AllyDub @omaze yes but my sister akready has this in the bag lol hehe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VancityBuzz how about falling, breaking a rib on city property, and they keep pushing it as the adjacent landowner fault. They the owner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DerrickL That would have been awesome. Can't wait till this shows in canada. Can't avoid spoilers but all good. Just building my excitement]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zombieraptorz Posted the pic in FB thread :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lesdoggg True. Lived with a narcopath/abuser. Got out. Now I help others survive the aftermath. We need to go back to basics of dating.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SturgillSimpson Holy hell, welcome to my life!!! Great performance!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaveWeasel Hate overtime. Heart can't take it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next Mon &amp; Tue is gonna be shorts and t-shirt weather https://t.co/WrP9XTlhJm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fraserhealth @quitnowbc Nine months smoke free thanks to your program. I owe you my life. Am so grateful for the help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No words. I'm crying too :) https://t.co/Z8iTLqpQCQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisgailus I've been telling people for 2 years it was coming back. Even metro ford didn't believe me LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndyHerren I'll get drunk w/u and talk about how fucked you all are... Canadian sympathy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eddielack Van Fan here just wanting to say wutup and we miss you. One of my 3 fav goalies in the NHL universe. (Don't worry, all equal) lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bwecht No crisp 10 for you lol thats awesome. She's so adorable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Canucks Go get'em boys. I am so proud of you guys. Never wavered last 28 years. #luvmycanucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaraJeanFM @GreenDay crazy canuck can drive, you AND I will be in the back seat with the baileys LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaraJeanFM @BaileysOriginal Ok I'm in. Gotta be a small car tho or I can't reach the gas pedal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaraJeanFM @969JACK If you're driving, I'm in. I'll split gas and hotel. Jack can buy the booze.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VancouverSun So he went on vacation. Who the cares? He's allowed. Being PM doesn't absolve him of family obligations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the big world of narcopath abuse, Trump is its leader. Do not engage with followers, you can't argue with narcissistic sociopaths.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hgbaker Just read faclc's page. Not even worth wasting time. Trump supporter. And as we've all learned, you can't argue with stupid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FACLC @hgbaker Stay out of YOUR way? So the rest of canada isn't allowed an opinion? Just  yours counts? You alone make canadian policy? FU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@metroottawa No place in my Canada for Trump style politics. She can exit stage left now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He lies and manipulates. He puts on a mask. You are lured into web of lies. Soon the love bomb stops. Devaluation begins. #narcopath]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do you know you've hooked up with a #narcopath? You don't. They learn about you to become your perfect mate. Constantly evolving.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NEWS1130 No thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And a happy birthday to one of my most influential recording artists, #davidbowie You are so incredibly missed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to what I consider the greatest mind of this generation, #stephenhawking May you discover something new and grand today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VancouverXplore @HarbourAirLtd Dang we live in a beautiful piece of Canada, don't we.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait till they see the damage they're doing to their own sidewalks and driveways. https://t.co/7G9Yn5JvjF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning #narcopath #abuse #survivors. Get on the road to #recovery today. https://t.co/DTG6l9nMNo No more guilt. You did nothing wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sbarnesglobal @KGordonGlobalBC I have packets of cleansing salts  to remove neg. energy from homes. $5 and you can have cleansed sidewalks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emotional wellness #coach focusing on repairing damage caused by a #narcopath. A narcissistic sociopath. The damage is real. DM for details.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lesdoggg My God woman, do you ever sleep? We need you bright eyed and bushy tailed for our Saturday evening viewing!! lol ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NEWS1130 thats why I created my own job. Narcissistic sociopath abuse recovery coach.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TransLink i have horrible social anxiety and after waiting for an hour in freezing cold to be treated like that. I feel absolutely nauseas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TransLink 2/2 prev driver if he might know where 180 was. Kept saying oh you wanna drive the bus several times embarrassing me to the crowd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TransLink re 180 @ burq stn missing 3 times. Make matters worse driver taking over 157 was making smartassed remarks when asking the ...1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey #vancouver #coquitlam Want some #lifecoaching? Willing to #trade your car for a years worth of coaching? https://t.co/SCI0aplG0v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The kid deserves his #weinerdog https://t.co/GCUSfBNejN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#thuggyD come back LOL https://t.co/rpwjT9L4of]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bwecht Sounds like beginning of a great mob story. "Beware The Lights of Albany"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lesdoggg And hamsters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DerrickL Your show is gonna be on Discovery ID? I can't wait. My daughter and I pretty much only watch that channel. Unless BB is on lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lesdoggg I got your back. I'm only 4'9 but I'd stand beside you. Well, maybe a little behind, and over to the left a little...But I got you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi @prattprattpratt can you tell my daughter @zombieraptorz to get to bed please? Thx.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DON'T DRINK AND DRIVE. JUST DON'T DO IT.  778-866-6673 for my Tri-City Peeps. https://t.co/ne3qJyjmwh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Canucks @RyanMiller3039 Holy crap that was an awesome game!!! Good job guys!!!! Thoroughly enjoyed watching.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteveMartinToGo You are the kindest person in show biz. Just wanted you to know that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VanguardAdrift Tell it if it gets in your way it'll find out what happened to object A.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cshupe2 @HWYThruHell  :( I miss truck rides. I'm like a kid in a candy store when it comes to big rigs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. Everyone please be careful out there #Coquitlam https://t.co/qemwEf7FgL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas everyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Heyyy, wondering...can you explain what we're taxing when they say carbon tax? What exactly are we freakin paying for?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VanguardAdrift I'm waving. Can you see me? Lol]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>