<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Point1golfcoach I'm too young to remember Sir Bobby 😀 Rooney may be burned out now but he's had an amazing career from an early age]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Point1golfcoach having none of that nico ! Record goal scorer for both England and Man U. He has won everything too. #winner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rory_Dowd 😂 I'd say they would be happy to keep us out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Point1golfcoach A Genius in more ways that one Nico!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@golfingmind @EskerHills @Stewyy69 looks tight down that hole!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fine example of how NOT to train anyone. 

https://t.co/fnlJTjC7oH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coachgambetta nice job. Have yet to meet a wise person who didn't read a lot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@podgedooley great article Dools]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MolloyJoe @wardides I will have to produce a little video for the listeners I think Joe!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlanMurrayUW Looking forward to visiting Seattle at some stage! #thereverand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winter training camp for @IrishLadiesGolf 
https://t.co/7x908CoZhp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alanharty Valencia outstanding at right back so Coleman no.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starting to look like a proper @ManUtd team again. Just a pity they didn't hire Jose right after Sir Alex #mufc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Blog Post feat @aocallaghan86. A MUST READ for anyone considering a golf scholarship the United States. https://t.co/KPUDG72MsN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was some finish. Even if he was offside ! https://t.co/WwfP1bIUJm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spikesonly it's sad how coaches are forgetting about power development. What's happened to the front squat and clean ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mckee400 possibly the best ever celebration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A question I often get off parents is should teenagers be partaking in resistance training. The benefits speak for… https://t.co/KJfZw3f6P6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rory_Dowd @Joe_The_Duck needs a lot to drop out though 🙈]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone looking for a last ditch Xmas gift , vouchers are available for assessments and sessions. Email info@cannonperformance.ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RuairiKearney78 any word from your pal Kanye ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fit_For_Golf correlation. We performed a few other tests that we may use down the road for a PhD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fit_For_Golf vertical jump metrics (with correct jump protocols) and clubhead speed in tour professionals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could not have been more welcoming! Looks like a great track @ThurlesGolfClub https://t.co/VNUms2Tywb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amanachos acceleration testing with 10,20,30 metre speed gates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Super days testing @Oliver_Wilson @GaryHurley93 @MovementExcel. Looking forward to testing more European tour playe… https://t.co/6ZWll90rVV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishGolfDesk you know it's finally off season when you're watching things like that BK!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're definitely a shark 💪 https://t.co/LlHH8dcLqL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you a fucking shark ? https://t.co/aiGd7gfnWA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishGolfDesk @NiallGorey_ @DanHolland_ have to agree with all statements there lads. Happy Christmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Amagee33 he's some gobshite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Carla_Reynolds he's from the brig !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@secrettourpro Anterior Tilt position at address is never good for any golfers back. Yet to see one without a sore back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MolloyJoe you found her so !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kingratom don't forget the dubs!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoachKevinCarr what you reading bud?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonward65 hungry and humble 💪💪]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen once and then listen again. Smart comments from @ShaneLowryGolf https://t.co/E7tDXFjGtP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dunners11 @IrishGolfDesk what about the black cloud tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhillyMcMahon  just what we were talking about earlier 😂 good article for you 
https://t.co/NZfghtMerN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cawley_nathan go on the lads]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Magician that man https://t.co/JLAVBxQHN4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awful news. Unreal performances the last two years at Cheltenham https://t.co/65JKjraGzi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cgkeogh @spikesonly @SimpliFaster which is why we take so many of these vertical metric studies with a pinch of salt Ciaran!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spikesonly @SimpliFaster You not like these https://t.co/4uXwa8eCzG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spikesonly @SimpliFaster Nice CMJ in video 2! This is why force decks should be used for any reliable squat jump test.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkBroadie thanks mark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thegreatgolfers great thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkBroadie @PGATOUR @patgossnugolf Hi Mark, Do you have any data regarding club head speed/ driving distance of t… https://t.co/4EyRXrdNN9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FeidhlimKelly Well done pal. What happened with the colour co ordination? You used to have that down to a tee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can last seasons Bundesliga player of the year not get a game with a very average Man Utd team. 🤔]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisPaisley86 nice playing pal. Best looking swing on the European tour 👌]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alanharty no cutting edge. But blind has been a liability since he stepped foot in Manchester]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Super job @padraig_h @FloodRonanflood @petecowengolf @golfchiro @SetantaCollege. #winner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wouldn't have Daley Blind in my local pub team. Useless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get yourself a new trainer / Physio if they have you doing speed / power work at the end of your workout when you're absolutely busted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kingratom @leinsterlions @GUIGolf it's ok. John gives it to his charity the lantern foundation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice touch indeed https://t.co/yPhHNF9jdm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fit_For_Golf @MyTPI How good were the PGA pros? I know pros who can't break 85! That study has a few holes in it. But most do!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fit_For_Golf @MyTPI people respond differently due to their physical make up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZachsTraining @Fit_For_Golf @MyTPI You will have to send that one on to me zachary!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fit_For_Golf @MyTPI Yeah seen that one. very questionable research methods .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MyTPI @Fit_For_Golf would like to have a look at that and question it's validity. Not many perform squat jump with correct test protocols]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulKimmage as discussed in Augusta! https://t.co/A0RU7euz64]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kingratom Ronaldo. He's not a player Bill.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Training day with @go_exxentric . Eccentric phase of the movement has the ability to create more force. https://t.co/yg0eyY6F8N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RuairiKearney78 that was some heist your mate @kanyewest staged]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattmcalpin1  not good enough for @ManUtd sadly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishGolfDesk @NiallGorey_ @kingratom at least wait till the end of the round Brian.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishGolfDesk @kingratom @NiallGorey_ the black cloud strikes again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spurs look the real deal this season. @MAYBSTER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great seats. Thanks to the boss @ShaneLowryGolf #upthedubs https://t.co/nA63jJPSQW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomRyan295 the graphs are readings from the jumps.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomRyan295 it's the software with the dual force decks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redtricky41 #UpTheDubs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomRyan295 hi Tom. They are various metrics from counter movement jump and a squat jump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Point1golfcoach what about the force and pressure of stensons swing nico   Golf porn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Point1golfcoach go to the fridge during adverts for a fresh John smiths @MAYBSTER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Productive day of prep for my masters thesis with the doc in @SetantaCollege. Very exciting study coming up https://t.co/QmtdWFo960]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant 68 to finish. Much deserved for all your hard work and great work done by @foxgolf60 https://t.co/9EEzGVgjtY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevstack @kingratom if he performs in the morning he would have to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevstack @kingratom pieters put on a stripe show in practice apparently #frozenropes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GYM_Ferris upgrading to the 4 I'd say !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davy2708 go on my son. Think I'm good too. Not like last time getting them late !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dpugh54 how's the coffee Denis?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@18STRONG_ @MyTPI watch this space #masters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gerryhussey I thought you were a Galway man 😀]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ducks_11 don't agree with that. Their skills were off. I think you had your chance !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The great still seem to get results despite performing way below their normal levels. I expect a different Dublin performance sat week #GAA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3rd place in the world for our girls. Huge achievement by all. Delighted for coach Dave Kearney. A man of vision ! https://t.co/TDChnh2hVh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickMarshgolf @Point1golfcoach Mark Roe doesn't know his arse from his elbow ! Chris is one of the best swingers out there.Poetry in motion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pipergolfer you can't help me so John!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im a big fan of using the bosco tests for my athletes. Here is a great video how to perform them correctly.  
https://t.co/RTWJgXxa6f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulMcBride0 nice playing last week boss 💪]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ducks_11 Sure every newspaper and radio station in the country is doing competitions for two tickets! So thats most of them gone!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ducks_11 if i get any ticket at all ill swap with you ha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@petermorgan7 Keep an eye out for your old mate kidddd!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Safe to say that tickets for Sunday are like gold dust. 🙈 #gaa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely brilliant @padraig_h  https://t.co/3AyMjebjKN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6am Monday morning workouts for the Louisville Women's golf team https://t.co/RT5M4IH1tV]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>