<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdwardYuen88 @NEWS1130 @postelsia @domoiscraving "Thunder Snow"!!! It's a real thing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cqrcmp @LesliBoldt @VancouverPD @PortMoodyPD  would you wear flip flops in a blizzard or hiking boots at the beach! Need the right tires!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattlee980 @CKNW @TransLink probably be a shorter list to say what IS working!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NEWS1130 @NEWS1130Traffic thanks to you there too!! Along with the maintenance crews and the private snowplow operators]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@120Sports he looks a little deflated]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@icbc @BCRCMP @VancouverPD PASS on driving drunk and just RUN instead!!!! #seahawks  #Superbowl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VancouverPD please tell me he goes code 3 for the delivery!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jillreports Jerry Dobrovolnycant even look people in the eye!!!! He's looking down and to the left, even he cant believe this BS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jesstrukker @DriveBC @TranBC @LMDRCMP SERIOUSLY! drivers need a warning not to do this!!! Also dont stick a fork i… https://t.co/HmtvoUoj8i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nationalpost meanwhile in Canada......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NEWS1130Traffic live look at the rest of Canada looking at Vancouver https://t.co/YrIe940jIE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NEWS1130Traffic has anyone counted but I think you've sent a record number of teeets between 6-10am today!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnHua @CityofVancouver @GlobalBC yup that look like the work of a unionized muni worker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnHua @CityofVancouver @GlobalBC COV just threw CMBC under the Bus!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cbcnewsbc Yes! Living in a metropolis gives you greater and faster access to everything. Therefore ...... rural = slower and fewer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NFLCanada why do the Patriots cheat? #askthepats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZVandeguchte also in BC residents pay about $800/year in premiums to government.  Also money generated from lotto sales goes to healthcare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZVandeguchte the massive benefit being everyone in Canada is covered for a massive injury or condition or disease]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZVandeguchte I remember a report a while back suggesting it cost Canadians  $800/month while decent cover2in USA is under $600/month.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZVandeguchte there is nothing free about health care in Canada. The fees are just hidden in the taxes people pay. #biggovsucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@winsthatcher @NEWS1130 @Southsiders no one seems to be protesting that point either!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@winsthatcher @NEWS1130 @Southsiders not if they have Jewish members. Jews are banned from several countries too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Breaking911 what's next, they get sent to their room with no dessert!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CstKelly this Yankees fan had to chime in with a winning cup!!!! And police food to boot!!!! https://t.co/fFOWqjdVlF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benwilson1130 @NEWS1130 @UBC could be the new @CAH (cards against humanity)!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheWeirdWorld And "lol" looks like someone with their arms up!!! #cantunsee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BCRCMPTraffic @VPDTrafficUnit pretty sure it's a scam/virus. Have you heard/seen this one before? https://t.co/iPBnVsFIN6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CCallaghanNews @yvrairport I can actually see my house from there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SomeonesAnIdiot @zkeefer player " well we always give 110%, we're just happy to be here and play against this talented team"!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michellesplant again, who gets to decide who is allowed to stay and who isn't? Free speech is free speech and should not be silenced]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michellesplant well then, in your opinion who/what determines who/what can and cannot be on social media?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michellesplant no company, corporation or government should silence anyone! Free speech is free speech. If something illegal notify police]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michellesplant slippery slope when you suggest "silence" these people! are you will to give up your right to free speech???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScanBC damn socialists!!! They think we should share everything!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder if there is ever a security scare and the secret service need to get Trump out of the way, try yell "Donald Duck"!!!! #justsaying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardMadan @CTVNews words without actions are meaningless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScanBC can we say "black" magic these days!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NavRav28 how can you blame Trump for what happens in a foreign country? Also how do you know it's an islamaphobe?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CTVNews sources say 5 fatalities! So much for gun control]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlobalBC @globalnews this hipster thing has gone too far]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@futureyes70 @TBejaGlobal @GlobalBC so people are actually killed by terrorist! We better protect ourselves by any means necessary!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TBejaGlobal @GlobalBC I wonder how many of these people would actually open there home and/or financial sponsor refugees??!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You invite them you pay for it! Let's see how many people actually open up their own homes and wallets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@earthriseset you said tax the wealthy! I guess almost the refugees can have jobs building the pipelines!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@earthriseset typical socialist open door policy but send the bill elsewhere! It's a slippery slope when u invite the world. Look at Europe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ABCPolitics @ABC no such thing as FREE!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@earthriseset @CNN prefer a realistic view! Housing costs are already out of control. Jobs are scarce medical system stretched no room no $$]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@earthriseset @CNN are your wallets open too? Housing, educating, feeding and clothing people with nothing comes at a price. Might raise tax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bonniezmom2 @CNN typical Democrat you pick and choose what you read and watch for your own self fulfilling prophecy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@globalnews well if there's one country that knows how to protect it's borders, I'd say Israel is spot on!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NHL @Gatorade Is the smithe division winning?? I sure hope the Campbell conference wins tomorrow!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jillianyuen especially that Ferrari theme park]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jillianyuen probably not! That place looks awesome!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jillianyuen I'd love to visit Dubai]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jillianyuen @macdaley360 @MMorton980 @CKNW @DuranCKNW980 thankfully not. A ban is a ban.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jillianyuen @macdaley360 @MMorton980 @CKNW @DuranCKNW980 will you protest for the countries I've been banned from too, because I'm a Jew?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@macdaley360 @MMorton980 @CKNW @DuranCKNW980 that's fear mongering! How about real issues like affordable daycare, rising $$ food gas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@macdaley360 @MMorton980 @CKNW @DuranCKNW980 what's "right" about protesting something that isn't your own government?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterlouwe @MMorton980 @CKNW @DuranCKNW980 then take action on Canadian issues such as First Nations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MMorton980 @CKNW  @DuranCKNW980 are these people on "protest stand by"!!!!??? Don't people have better things to do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@K_Woodhouse @NEWS1130 which pipeline are they against # buildthepipeline #jobsjobsjobs https://t.co/okHG7Vutil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@globalnews he's only doing what he said he would! There was plenty of opportunities not to vote for him!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NBCSports properly inflated footballs and trying to play without spying on the other teams play book]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlobalBC I'm banned from Iraq Iran UAE Lebanon because I'm a Jew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NEWS1130 how come those PETA people never protest these events]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nationalpost just call it Tino Hortinez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NEWS1130Traffic SB traffic crazy slow from 8th. Big trucks are just squeezing by. https://t.co/LWom78X5wo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NEWS1130 my heart absolutely aches for the parents. I'm 39 and the father of a 2.5yo boy. I cried my eyes out when I heard this letter read]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewWestPD hope it's resolved peacefully. Any ETA of opening]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jiteng02 you blocked me. So I'm not able to view or respond to what you are saying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jiteng02 your freedom is to ignore and walk away! It's freedom of expression and freedom from expression. Works both ways]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jiteng02 just because you're offended doesn't mean you're right! Stop crying and stop being soft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jiteng02 not illegal at all. Falls under freedom of expression!!!! You can flip the bird to whomever and wherever you want!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CityofSurrey @DanBurritt @cbcnewsbc @CBCVancouver the question was to raise dialogue as to why people are OK with fares but complain tolls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NBCNewYork barely a week in and Americans are reading more! Obama couldn't do that in 8 years!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanBurritt @cbcnewsbc @CityofSurrey @CBCVancouver agreed! I just don't understand the double standard. People hate tolls but ok with fares]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanBurritt @cbcnewsbc @CityofSurrey @CBCVancouver will it be free or tolled (fare)?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScanBC McShitty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CTVVancouver @molkoreports how can you blame weather (Mother Nature) for something caused by a human? More like, not driving for conditions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch this on your mobile device and tilt the screen

https://t.co/JGweR2LOVA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BurnabyRCMP what can be done RE nuisance squeegee people SW corner Lougheed HWY  North Road. All drug activity along Rochester Cul-de-sac]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsMaleHumor how do people makes these?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JillSlattery why did you tweet the # in the first place without verifying it? Weakens your credibility]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JillSlattery @GlobalBC typical media: quoting numbers without any fact checking or proper research]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CTVSarah @CTVVancouver why are you promoting the mockery of someone's physical abnormality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NEWS1130 I'm sure the weather was a major factor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HPSupport where can I find the product key so I can install MS office. No hologram sticker on bottom of laptop or… https://t.co/C9v3T5ofm1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScanBC sucks when you can't afford the $4 a week]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barbi_desantis @ABC7NY pretty sure all on board survived!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CTVVancouver @CTVScottHurst WOW!!! Did you know that in some parts of the world they line up an hour for food!!  #firstworldproblems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NEWS1130 absolutely 100%!!! They are such an influential couple that it make BC get noticed and people will visit and then spend $$$]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jgpfeifer that means you have to pay BC union wages! That would translate to higher fares! Are you ok with paying even more?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NEWS1130 which pipeline don't they want? https://t.co/s1mQaBIoaS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProHulaHooper actually it's the opposite. People invest, get greater ROI. Rather than stale wages and investing just above inflation rates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProHulaHooper def 1000s of jobs which is fantastic for the Econ. Cheaper oil = cheaper transportation. High rates: great for investments]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NEWS1130 Yay, she finally did something right!! Jobs jobs jobs #buildthepipeline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CKNW Yay, she finally did something right!! Jobs jobs jobs #buildthepipeline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Yahoo when is Meryl Streep going to apologize for hers???!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SInow @richarddeitsch I'm sure he'll be back back back back someday somewhere!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarDown @TSN_Sports @NHLBlackhawks @JonathanToews @88PKane @SDarling_33 @brispe79 he'll never be a soccer player!!!!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>