<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelTankardReist Carrots for kindy teachers this Easter then!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recommended reading for Donald J #Trump: First 90 days-hacks in the corner (oval) office https://t.co/N6rXmBTSuR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Australia Day to the Aussie contingent at @ULMWarhawks ðŸ‡¦ðŸ‡ºðŸ‡¦ðŸ‡ºðŸ‡¦ðŸ‡º]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Brisbane needs a #hospitality service revolution. How hard is it to smile and give a damn?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a time for cute headlines. This is not one of them. https://t.co/63JDQtfwXm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ULM_BSB @ULMWarhawks Will you ship the lawn mower to Australia if I win? ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brava @QIMRBerghofer on supporting your working mums #Australiawide #WomeninScience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is @Dreamworld_AU turning its re-opening into a PR spectacle? Misguided yet again!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thnx @merlocoffee Will send an email. Don't worry - still a Merlo fan ðŸ˜Š]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually just had a bad @merlocoffee How is this possible?? ðŸ˜±]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StGeorgeBank Internet banking not restored for me. Worked perfectly yesterday. Yr help desk is closed. Help required.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Thanksgiving to our new @ULMWarhawks family, especially @ULM_VB, @ULM_BeachVB &amp; @WiredAcesVball ðŸ‡¦ðŸ‡ºðŸ‡ºðŸ‡¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Completely agree with @pruemacsween @sunriseon7 Bali is no place to celebrate Schoolies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear @Qantas Next time I travel on QLink can I pls have a mag, working tablet &amp; wine after 5pm? Or at least let me buy a glass with my card]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@USQVC farewell message: tell at least one person how important universities are for our democracy and future. Thank you Jan Thomas!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need to learn to celebrate failure says PwC's Ben Sorenson #IMBrisbane]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When it comes to innovation, we're all encumbered by life experiences - Ben Sorenson, PWC #IMBrisbane]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to hear about the international future of #Brisbane at @AmChamAU Bring it on! @rowland_au]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come on down #MattDamon ðŸ‡¦ðŸ‡ºðŸ‘   #TrumpFreeZone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prophecy... #USElection2016 https://t.co/NMsqzaq1qV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another plus... we get to see more of @AlecBaldwin on @nbcsnl #USElection2016 #wtfisgoingon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there a big enough paper bag for worldwide hyperventilation!? #USElection2016 #wtfisgoingon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tremendous comeback! Congrats @ULM_VB @ULMWarhawks You sure do give us our money's worth! ðŸ’ªðŸ‘ðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's heating up here in Brissy. Hurry up &amp; win @ULM_VB so we can hit the beach! â˜€ï¸ðŸŒŠ #TalonsOut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just a game? What an insight into the human spirit #SurvivorAU @Survivor_AU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm waiting for @Sacha_B_Cohen to unzip himself from the Donald Trump suit #USElections2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like @woolworths Rewards revival has prompted @Coles to up the ante with @VirginAustralia https://t.co/Xqk9VaLKe3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not shaved your legs for 3 weeks? Welcome to success as a business woman, according to QLD #TelstraBizWomen winner Pixie Weyand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing like the unbridled joy of a proud mother. Congrats @Pntwemlow (and mum) on #TelstraBizWomen QLD award. Oh crap!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best wishes to @USQVC Prof Jan Thomas at tonight's QLD #TelstraBizWomen @rowland_au]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do something joyful today. Buy a BIG ISSUE! @BigIssue #dogood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there any form of public transport more detestable than a Brisbane bus? #whiplash]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If a child is sick how often does the working mum take the day off vs working dad? #genderequality #workplace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great effort @ULM_VB Intense game. Next one is yours!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just another Sunday morning watching @ULM_VB Loving the live streams. C'mon Warhawks! https://t.co/MEohujdTiL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like the way @AlanTudgeMP is handling himself re #welfarecard Alan 1, Eva 0 @sunriseon7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Livin' on a prayer. C'mon on Sharkies! @Cronulla_Sharks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Volleyball is the biggest participation sport in the world &amp; the most gender equal. Well done @ausvolley &amp; VQ on a great #AJVC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ULM_VB Well that's just bloody huge!!! Woohoo #Warhawks @ULMWarhawks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ULM_VB woohoo! One more!!! #TalonsOut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheer, cheer the red and the white!!! @sydneyswans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving this week's @GruenHQ pitch. That @qantaswallabies ad was priceless - and perhaps just a little bit true ðŸ˜¬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome to the new QLD Warhawks cheer squad! #TalonsOut #DaggyDads @ULM_VB https://t.co/iag9aV6nPt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stay in the fight Warhawks! You can do it! Come out believing and come out strong @ULM_VB #TalonsOut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's go @ULM_VB In for the kill! #TalonsOut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do you do when it's 4am in Brisbane, hubby is snoring &amp; you can't sleep? Follow @ULM_VB match updates! Woohoo Warhawks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spectacularly creative reffing tonight. Call over-turned mid scrum, malicious kick in the back overlooked. What next? #NRLFinals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@parisonthecoast I'll be sure to check that out! My hubby does all of his own ironing - thank heavens!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snaps to @woolworths for having a dad cooking in their chook TVC. Now we just need some blokes in cleaning product ads! #genderequality]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ULM_VB That's my girl! Nice work @GLConvey Great job #Warhawks! Tim Tams coming your way!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only mum in #Brisbane with this sticker I bet @ULMWarhawks #TakeFlight https://t.co/p69Dqm9tfy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey #Brasil - what's with the booing? We don't boo in #beachvolleyball - ever! #uncool #Rio2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Westpac I need someone to contact me ASAP please. Travelling overseas and suddenly can't use card. Had no issues until today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do they do at JFK when they only have one barista &amp; they're swamped? Charge double for a cappuccino so you don't buy one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am I still watching the #Olympics opening ceremony? #climatechange #Rio2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With a child competing at an elite level in sport for AUS, I'm in awe of Kenya's runners @DatelineSBS #AgainstTheOdds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #GoldCoast will become even more politically powerful says The Hon John Mickel. Parties can't win without GC votes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovely to connect with so many friends of @rowland_au at our Gold Coast launch @LArdern https://t.co/3Pg5XhBKQD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Room for both social &amp; traditional media when it comes to news?  @ABCmediawatch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@4corners story makes me wonder if media receive counselling for horrors they witness. We didn't 30 yrs ago as young cadets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Re-inventing your brand in a digital age  https://t.co/QwiH80SCoG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for the #U19FIVB live stream @bet365_aus Watching my baby @GLConvey play in Cyprus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @BrisbaneJane for shouting out to us sporting parents in this week's @BrisbaneNewsMag The sacrifice is worth it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poignant to be reminded today of how we stood with France at #Fromelles 100 years ago. We continue to #standwithfrance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Final home court training today before heading to Volleyball Australia team camp in Adelai... https://t.co/bvceOxQGjO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice to see Alan Jones channeling his inner Matt Preston on #QandA tonight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tanya, you won't have a whopping surplus to help people buy big screen TVs if Brexit creates another GFC #QandA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What?!! @BBC is calling leave vote victory. That's a win for xenophobia #Brexit #SadDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We Gen Xs paid astro interest rates on first homes AND suffered hideous 80s hair! @triplejHack #WarOnYoungPeople]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We never use the c word - client or customer - only the f word, friend" - @OSLaundryAU on homeless people @triplej]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Might get a few more guys wearing head gear in school rugby  https://t.co/uTLXLcnodx #NoBrainNoGame @QldBrainInst]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putin says he considers Trump to be a bright man. Cretins unite. #USElection2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Donald, I'm with her." Let's hope @Oprah can incite some common sense #USElection2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conjured this up from my local Carina bakery. #Brissy burbs coming to life at last https://t.co/B0XgsXXi5I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think my mate @tonyparkauthor would be chuffed to see #Botswana named best country to visit by @lonelyplanet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LendLeaseGroup CEO Steve McCann is passionate about keeping his people safe. His emotion on the topic is very real #qutblf @QUTBusiness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didn't we all aspire to be someone from #LALaw ? LendLease CEO Steve McCann says he wanted to be Harry Hamlin #qutblf @QUTBusiness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teams that think differently but can work together create best outcomes - @LendLeaseGroup CEO Steve McCann #qutblf @QUTBusiness @rowland_au]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#PTSD affects more than 1 million Aussies. @rowland_au helped launch #Bolt convoy today to spread the word https://t.co/Sv4GNme7bS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm raising money for Let's get Grace to Cyprus!. Click to Donate: https://t.co/EObdNiYn4o via @gofundme]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just watched #MoneyMonster Has me wondering what I would do in Diane Lester's shoes. #CrisisManagement]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No judgement - just respect &amp; compassion - for the mums on @insightSBS tonight #insight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lights, camera, action! Fab media turn out to help spread the word to get active #JoinTheMovement @rowland_au https://t.co/uOtu9wP0x2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids navigating 80s gadgets with @lehmo23 Thanks @theprojecttv - I suddenly feel very smart and tech savvy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I agree the term "guys" is a bit sexist. From now on I'll be sure to greet all the guys at work with "hey girls" - just to even things up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@4corners asking the Qs many have over #IVF - are profits being put before people? And do shareholders &amp; private equity care?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can someone please share a vision for our nation? You'll be more likely to get my vote if you do #Vote2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RezaMahammad Always inspired to pull out the wok after watching your shows #sumptuous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People don't respond like they once did to science-based information says @TimLangmead #TheCAS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CrisisRoom - will get the skinny from you on said Africa solution over lunch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FacingChina says he's an "information concierge" for @Huawei - that's going straight to my #LinkedIn profile #TheCAS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helping @FacingChina share the @Huawei story with my 153 followers #ToInfinityAndBeyond #TheCAS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nswtaxi Yes he heard and yes he eventually turned on GPS. We got there in the end!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jumped in cab to go from Sydney CBD to restaurant in Chippendale. Cabbie says: "Know where that is?" - there's your problem @nswtaxi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More populism than policy in politics today - a challenge for those navigating government relations #TheCAS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't think I've ever heard a comms manager say they're not a fan of key messages. I'm all ears Josh Murray #TheCAS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to hear corporate affairs "generalists" are making a comeback! #TheCAS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure @nswtaxi "level playing field" message is the one that will resonate with No 1 influencer, the consumer #TheCAS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a lifetime Doggies fan, delighted to hear CEO @raelenecastle speak proudly on reputation #TheCAS @NRL_Bulldogs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing better than the @sydneyswans gliding past those Hawks!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>