<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Which non-winning #Eurovision country (not counting JESC, EYD &amp; EYM) would you like to see their first win? Odds on now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can Melbourne midwives Karen &amp; Ros beat the first two teams' scores? #MKR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Eurovision fans, which country that has always qualified will likely fail to qualify to the grand final for the 1st time? Odds on now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natalieet What do you think of Red Velvet's new song Rookie? #SBSPopAsia #HashtagHits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can I request Flashback by After School please? It's Back to School season #HASHTAGHITS #SBSPopAsia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JJCC_PrinceMak What is your favourite Chinese Zodiac animal? #sbspopasiaprincemak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will David and Betty do better than Damo and Caz in #MKR?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey followers, if you're interested, you can check out my website Cindayz45. Link below https://t.co/h21nhhCm29]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@staticsan It's been nearly a year since I started playing Neko Atsume]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natalieet What do you think of Gallant Tablo &amp; Eric Nam's collaboration song Cave Me In? #SBSPopAsia #HashtagHits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarbear_Oz @staticsan At nighttime, it's full of American TV shows]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarbear_Oz What years did you watch Eurovision? And why you didn't watch the 2016 one? @damiandmusic participated in it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarbear_Oz Why? Do you know anything about European music or just Europe in general?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarbear_Oz What's wrong with reality TV shows? Do you want to watch this year's Eurovision in May on SBS?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarbear_Oz You can try other TV shows such as MKR. There's plenty of choices!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Favourite slogan from the most recent years of ESC including 2017? #Eurovision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And there's no "Stay in PopAsia" or "K-pop only" option.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I talked to SBS PopAsia on Messenger about "SBS PopEuro", what do you all want when it's created? #SBSPopAsia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natalieet What do you think of miss A's Suzy's debut song Yes No Maybe? #SBSPopAsia #HashtagHits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who's excited for the 2017 season of My Kitchen Rules? #MKR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZeroArmour Wonder Girls was the first JYP group I discovered. The other first K-pop groups I discovered are Super Junior and BIGBANG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can I request 12 Zodiacs by Leehom Wang for Chinese New Year? #SBSPopAsia #HashtagHits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PopAsians, which group that disbanded this year so far do you miss the most? #SBSPopAsia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wiwibloggs Yle Areena let me watch the Finnish national final unlike UK's one which won't let]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PopAsians, which artist premiere is the best? #sbspopasia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SBSPopAsia You said you were going to premiere a new Kyary Pamyu Pamyu song on TV, but you chose more K-pop instead #SBSPopAsia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you PopAsians discovered other K-pop groups before them, just vote no!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Following the Wonder Girls' disbandment, did PopAsians discovered them first? #sbspopasia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelbourneIdol @SBSPopAsia don't have the rights for their MVs to be played, only the labels PopAsia has rights with can be played]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wiwibloggs There's only the performances and the winner announcement on YouTube and not the entire show]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wiwibloggs BBC iPlayer won't let me catch up on #EurovisionYouDecide because they think I'm outside of UK #Eurovision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where are the PopAsians! This poll can't be left without any votes, vote now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natalieet What do you think of NCT 127's new song Baby Don't Like It? #SBSPopAsia #HashtagHits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natalieet What do you think of Luhan's new song Skin to Skin? #SBSPopAsia #HashtagHits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can I request Shanghai Romance by Orange Caramel for Lunar New Year? #SBSPopAsia #HashtagHits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natalieet I can't even hear your voice at 6pm last night and I thought Hashtag Hits didn't occur on Australia Day #SBSPopAsia #HashtagHits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SBSPopAsia Where's #HashtagHits today? #SBSpopAsia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZeroArmour But triple j are more interested in English-language songs and are doesn't play K-pop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZeroArmour But there are 66 Aussie songs in the countdown!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who's listening to #Hottest100 from @triplej?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SBSPopAsia Did you put the @mychonny show on earlier than 8pm? #SBSPopAsia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natalieet What do you think of NCT 127's new song Limitless? #SBSPopAsia #HASHTAGHITS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natalieet Thank you for playing my request! #SBSPopAsia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natalieet What do you think of Hello Venus' new song Mysterious? #HashtagHits #SBSPopAsia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can I please request Limitless by NCT 127? #HashtagHits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natalieet Rate Seventeen's song Highlight #SBSPopAsia #Hashtaghits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yo!  I made a rap song in #AutoRap by #Smule, and it's awesome.  Listen to it here: https://t.co/wKdgYJuFNs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JJCC_PrinceMak Did you spend your early childhood watching Play School or The Wiggles? #SBSPopAsiaPrinceMak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[KPP stands for Kyary Pamyu Pamyu since the whole name can't fit to the tweet due to the word limit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natalieet What do you think of the collaboration song from Yasutaka Nakata + Charli XCX &amp; KPP Crazy Crazy Crazy? #SBSpopAsia #HashtagHits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can I request April's new song April Story please? #HashtagHits #SBSPopAsia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PopAsiaMegaMatt Who's going to host Beats &amp; Bars after @DrJ_SBSPopAsia left the PopAsia team? #SBSPopAsia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is @eatyourkimchi not airing tonight on #SBSPopAsia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natalieet What do you think of SNSD member Seohyun's debut song Don't Say No? #SBSPopAsia #HashtagHits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natalieet What do you think of VIXX member Ravi's debut song Bomb? #SBSPopAsia #HashtagHits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natalieet What do you think of 2NE1's last song Goodbye? #SBSPopAsia #HashtagHits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natalieet New song poll is back for 2017! What do you think of AOA's new song Excuse Me? #SBSPopAsia #HashtagHits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natalieet Can I request Hello by Da-iCE because it's the first 2017 episode for Hashtag Hits #SBSPopAsia #HashtagHits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SBSPopAsia Is top 30 on today or return next week?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PopAsians, what's your opinion for today's episode that aired on 22/01/2017? #SBSPopAsia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PopAsians, which artist premiere in today's episode is better? #SBSPopAsia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZeroArmour There's no Hashtag Hits tonight, @SBSPopAsia told me Hashtag Hits is back next week]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JJCC_PrinceMak Which K-pop albums did you listen to in full? #SBSPopAsiaPrinceMak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SBSPopAsia Will there be anything new for Hashtag Hits for 2017?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SBSPopAsia When is Hashtag Hits returning for 2017? #SBSpopAsia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out what I made! #SBSPopAsiaMemeMaker https://t.co/AAyyJKd52r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PopAsians, what is your opinion for today's episode that aired on 15/01/2017? #sbspopasia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#sbspopasia If PopAsians are interested in other non-Asian pop stuff, why not take the poll? No BTS there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quiz time! Which country is most peaceful according to the 2016 Global Peace Index? Answer revealed at the end of the day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NguyenCinday If anyone presses "don't know" more, I'm sending another poll related to European music]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PopAsians, would you like a digital radio station called SBS PopEuro (non stop European pop) to happen? #SBSPopAsia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrJ_SBSPopAsia Then who's going to host Beats &amp; Bars next week?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please give this poll some votes, do anyone want the two idols' birthdays be ruined for no votes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where's everyone? They're meant to vote not ignore it, get voting!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two K-pop idols' birthdays is on 11th January and we have a birthday poll, which one of these do you like the best? #SBSPopAsia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anymore PopAsians voting for their opinions? One vote so far.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZeroArmour There is, did you check the TV guide properly?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sunnycomesout And they just being played in today's episode]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PopAsians, which artist frequency would you want to have on PopAsia TV? #SBSPopAsia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JJCC_PrinceMak How much money do you earn a day when you go to your music career? #SBSPopAsiaPrinceMak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two votes so far, this poll needs more PopAsians to vote before the two idols' birthdays ends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey PopAsians! Because two K-pop stars have their birthdays today, which one of the idols do you like the best? #SBSPopAsia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you for playing my request most suited for summer! #SBSPopAsia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JJCC_PrinceMak Which 2017 songs would you like to listen to? #sbspopasiaprincemak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One person voted and all other PopAsians haven't, get voting!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erinangel16 You can only vote for one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PopAsians, which January 1st episode is better? #SBSPopAsia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three BTS songs and not a single Perfume song played on the New Years special, looks like PopAsia is slowly adding more K-pop #SBSpopAsia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrate #happynewyear by welcoming 2017! Who's staying up to watch the #SBSpopAsia New Year's special?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sugamins_ Gosh, five songs released in 2016 in a row and two non-2016 songs in a row so far, you want old songs to play.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sugamins_ But what we get so far is mostly songs released in 2016.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sugamins_ We better wait and see. I hope there's more than just K-pop's Big 3 labels and BTS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So far, the New Year special played nothing but BTS and artists from the Big 3 K-pop labels #SBSPopAsia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy New Year! A farewell goodbye to 2016 and a huge hello to 2017! 🎇🎆]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chimchamsies @SBSVICELAND it is. This is where it also air episodes of SBS PopAsia TV.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy #NewYearsEve! It's time to say goodbye to 2016 and welcome 2017 in a few hours time! 🎇🎆🎊🎉]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yo!  I made a rap song in #AutoRap by #Smule, and it's awesome.  Listen to it here: https://t.co/2fb0WVmou1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SBSPopAsia But you forgot to put up a top 10 playlist at 10am!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yo!  I made a rap song in #AutoRap by #Smule, and it's awesome.  Listen to it here: https://t.co/23RyUDPT9s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yo!  I made a rap song in #AutoRap by #Smule, and it's awesome.  Listen to it here: https://t.co/x778mdA5ce]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>