<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[An interesting 2-1 decision about potholes of potential relevance to cyclists. https://t.co/vcSZUxOj3k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smaryka @Strava Depressing but sadly familiar.  My view is we do need to keep complaining.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@velobetty Really don't understand why the euro is demonised.  I am glad of every last one I have stuffed away somewhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TweetBails It's the cycling proficiency ones that believe we should be in the gutter!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beztweets @ErnieMarples Yes quite or &gt;c10 years notwithstanding the credit for a guilty plea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ErnieMarples @beztweets 
Because the CPS approach is this.  Amounts to confidence that jury would convict of mans… https://t.co/nmOqZ2P3oW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is very interesting and remember that if bikeability were part of Nat Curriculum then all drivers would have i… https://t.co/F0Ey857Csj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@f0rmat @beztweets @SurreyRoadCops @rjdekanter I agree with you but even catching and disqualifying them presents 'political' challenges.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Including the A315.  Splendid. https://t.co/W7BtGwcCKk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beztweets @SurreyRoadCops @rjdekanter Also, many drive to a much higher standard when they are being tested.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beztweets @SurreyRoadCops @rjdekanter No real shortcuts to deterring bad driving.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beztweets @SurreyRoadCops @rjdekanter Nice idea but you just won't get compulsory retesting of faultless drivers in a democracy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Laura_Weislo @Doctor_Hutch He may be North American. When I hired a bike there they were v keen to set my saddle too low.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CHAIRRDRF @Doctor_Hutch Bit coincidental that Scott Lomas was also under a suspended sentence for unlawful wounding though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@geckobike Risky tweeting in those terms before her sentence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@citycyclists @CityWestminster Mildly depressing that there is any such parliamentary group]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MartinPorter6 @theJeremyVine 
It is worth reflecting on the real sea change in attitudes over the past 5 years
https://t.co/RFXYPEpUdA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[..and many of us are v grateful to @theJeremyVine in addition https://t.co/xe4ei4i9uO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday's @allpartycycling session may be viewed here
https://t.co/xcJqtJYF0J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is why I told @allpartycycling that the Met response to bad driving co plants was much improved https://t.co/WfKfpJ4ooT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increase in small claims limits, that is. https://t.co/e8vBhKIrOb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They really have their act together at @MPSCamden https://t.co/uJD791iff3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonproven @beztweets @WeAreCyclingUK Thanks!  Agree cars do not (yet) make decisions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beztweets @WeAreCyclingUK Isn't it an illustration of what not to do?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's close pass https://t.co/k0DQI4H6XT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AsEasyAsRiding OK.  I told him I would report him, he responded 'all those millions spent on cycle lanes']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AsEasyAsRiding Yes.  Sent conversation to police too.  Indistinct but intent q clear https://t.co/c2dAWeBiK8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here is that Seymour lorry clip resulting in 'words of advice', no course, no prosecution https://t.co/nZ8h5HEJiL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will be there giving evidence tomorrow https://t.co/tZS63CZdTa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, so true, though I would add that we need to make a start with those who endanger the most vulnerable https://t.co/by1kE7rXGK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @SurreyRoadCops Have invited Surrey TPU to read @Trafficwmp 's excellent blog https://t.co/7N2xnDRU0v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AsEasyAsRiding @Al__S @beztweets 
Blimey!  Forget the gimmicks and adopt better road positioning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Characteristically powerful words from @sarahwollaston https://t.co/Qm7cDyzmJG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And we thought we had problems with the Head of State's prerogative powers https://t.co/x7VrIS3lKJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must be ever vigilant against this. https://t.co/MsMSBA3ILl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Appalling driving in Cambridge City Centre.  I do hope he loses his licence over this. https://t.co/x5cJFiij5K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is where government reforms should be concentrated, on keeping bad drivers parted from their licences.  No loo… https://t.co/3SlUlLv0J9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is such an improvement on what went before.  Since Oct I've made 3 close pass reports.  NIPs in all 3.  Action… https://t.co/ZkieOkmnFQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ShoestringCycle @SurreyRoadCops 
My view changed a lot once I gave my teenage daughters bikes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShoestringCycle @SurreyRoadCops 
..or at the very least a day long training course as alternative to prosecution IMHO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Trafficwmp @SurreyRoadCops @CHAIRRDRF Great.  Got to avoid plums like this: https://t.co/BKl9o0Tet2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Trafficwmp @SurreyRoadCops @CHAIRRDRF 
..and presumably educating them is an important part of the scheme?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Trafficwmp ?
Either way, reinforces the desirability of RPU going out on bikes as you are not dependent on TPU for action]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ShoestringCycle @SurreyRoadCops @DC_Police 
Thing is I had already given words of advice https://t.co/3Zfl8DHazR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SurreyRoadCops @CHAIRRDRF 
Think @Trafficwmp were saying they got to deal with submitted videos themselves.  Am I right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CHAIRRDRF @SurreyRoadCops @Trafficwmp 
I will keep you posted on the latest one Bob.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SurreyRoadCops @CHAIRRDRF @Trafficwmp 
Which is, I think, the problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just learnt this one was dealt with by 'words of advice'
@SurreyRoadCops https://t.co/ccjUok0KAn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SurreyRoadCops I have now sent it off and asked for an update on the last close pass I reported to Surrey TPU on 4th October 2016.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SurreyRoadCops @BCCletts Thx.  I have emailed TPU to ask whether it is worth sending in the video of a close pass.… https://t.co/QMXQCUoTRX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SurreyRoadCops @BCCletts 
To be clear it is the 'must not rely solely on a perception of distance such as a close pass' to which I refer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SurreyRoadCops @BCCletts @SurreyPolice 
Given the content of this form, it does seem a report is still a waste of… https://t.co/AFfH4S5id4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can it be coincidence that the politicians of whatever party which get cycling make the best sense generally? https://t.co/eaHmMAfsPQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plus @SurreyRoadCops have said 'watch this space' https://t.co/8lpDoMQQjK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marko_richo @London_MTB @grantincles @aduffillphoto @UKCycleChat 
I wrote up my 2009 ride in my earliest blog post.
https://t.co/McquaEmXYZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MPSCamdenTnSgt @Lakerlikes @BBC Very well said.  Good policing has always involved discretion.  Potential to harm is key relevance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@peterwalker99 
Parliament may of course amend any proposed legislation.  Entirely up to them.  #sovereignty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wish it were otherwise but he is clearly wrong https://t.co/AA6FCvhk1O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shame controlling the activity of the victims appears to come before controlling activities of polluters. https://t.co/47iMESG2NA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['We believe you didn't know what speed limit was' does not imply not guilty.  Prosecution appeal?
https://t.co/5csB9dFg7V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Close pass op to be rolled out to 16 forces? Is yours one? #cycling https://t.co/pSS24NhHEn via @roadcc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@russellcharlton @mragilligan Really?  Zero?  Are you sure?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Impressive winners and runners up https://t.co/njh99RMpxK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happily the cabbies right to protest is balanced by my right never to use a black cab again.  With apologies to the… https://t.co/IHpTQAncxg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Better advice than 'do not breathe' https://t.co/exH6mUi8a6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SurreyRoadCops @BCCletts @SurreyPolice 
And here is yesterday's.  A30 would be a good spot for an #opclosepass https://t.co/zs4rsLgIJJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grantincles @OliverJeffcott I love pothole chat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OliverJeffcott @thetimes @grantincles Thanks for coming']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BCCletts @SurreyRoadCops @SurreyPolice Thanks but no collision (hospital was location).  Surrey TPU would not be interested.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great my commute is from the southwest.  Red all the way. https://t.co/0IxiABBlmH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ashford Hosp 1830 last night.  Would be super if @SurreyRoadCops @SurreyPolice could start #opclosepass and deal with these drivers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MPSCamdenTnSgt @GruffLewis Cripes.  Did he stop?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulSBurke I would prefer to see him indicate (and look) https://t.co/X8yvaKMjwF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulSBurke Yes that is true (and so am I!!).  Left turn lane comes right at end of bus lane and buses (and cycles) often go straight on....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MetCC It is that refuse driver's lucky day as I find I have deleted the film.  He got into the wrong lane it seems.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MetCC The refuse driver you mean?  Didn't get regs of the red light offenders.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not at all clever driving by the refuse driver either!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not a bad idea for @metpoliceuk to do some enforcement at Clockhouse Rdbt, Feltham.  So many jump lights.  That sha… https://t.co/YNM42JJQ3W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Particularly unfortunate language he uses given our Transport Secretary's views on cyclists as road users. https://t.co/eNoP6SSnfs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Newsflash for the transport secretary: cyclists are road users too | Chris Boardman https://t.co/6IvP9dmofn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How flippin' close is this!! https://t.co/jeVYcU1nZK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whatever is he talking about?? https://t.co/1snKZYdocs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This really is v v good from our heroes @Trafficwmp  https://t.co/SgK3oyBbhX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MPSCamdenTnSgt that's what I write on those forms!  For a surprisingly long time ACPO wouldn't accept that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely no reason to require Independant witness if sufficiently evidenced eg by camera. https://t.co/R6b9bgJFp2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems dangerous but expect plea to careless was offered.
https://t.co/HCI1i1wLUN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One for the @allpartycycling inquiry perhaps? https://t.co/D7jDP0Qt7j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gmorganshu @martinkeyBC What?  A lane in UK that is so wide that you are comfortable being overtaken by a vehicle in the same lane!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewjlockley Think you must be missing the point.  Do read it again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The logic of this s irrefutable https://t.co/tHLCB5stQl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@velobetty He's like a guy I used to cycle with who would keep shouting 'keep in' from the back of the group.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was already massively impressed with Lyon @RachelAldred https://t.co/RuVlmBtu1Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great example of this today from @danofchester on cycling techniques. https://t.co/arP7dA1goH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Entry applications to @ThamesVelo Spring Road Race on 30th April now open
https://t.co/HDmAjfHPTa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisgerhard No, I was stopped when I tried it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, tax wealth in the hands of the recipient and encourage legacies to impoverished grandchildren https://t.co/eX3jWDvApE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Better war on all our children than 'war on the motorist'/polluter https://t.co/A2dnE4cc0v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carltonreid @TyneTom 
Rather more cars than bikes in these images:
https://t.co/oW8Ujn8wRW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to reverse the rather questionable decision that a bicycle is a 'carriage'??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is hopelessly muddled to pass a law and then tell the police when to enforce it.  There are alternative laws aga… https://t.co/D8WjOd1kGU]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>