<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@EliasHinckley Serving a lifetime appointment from which he can't be fired or have his salary cut? One of THOSE judges?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This so-called judge..." https://t.co/xdZYacrPL8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Words some never expected from Trump's UN ambassador: "“Crimea is a part of Ukraine. Our ... sanctions will remain" https://t.co/XAHFaSYVle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Eric_Jotkoff  Looks like it be more benign than that, believe it or not: https://t.co/OOMbf8OCmB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mystery wrapped in a riddle wrapped in an enigma: Trump's Treasury exempts some IT products from Russia sanctions https://t.co/eb6OYYNBHl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know, I have been feeling oddly unsettled lately but couldn't figure out why. https://t.co/YY1uFsjFfu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federal workers turn to Signal and burner phones to thwart Trump https://t.co/uMHgY6YW4G #encryption https://t.co/2Pt8kEsYS7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump team building a wall inside National Security Council. And staffers consider bolting. https://t.co/QGceHY5H1E https://t.co/M8rQ55gY0J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solzhenitsyn: "One man suffered from insomnia &amp; he had trained the whole of Moscow’s officialdom to watch with him" https://t.co/iHFvz4TBN0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billkuchman Many Catholics have trouble with that definition too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The AP story didn't say "invade," though. https://t.co/4PqIEvieEq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia and Mexico, you're on notice too. https://t.co/mQqvSeJAwm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ndrichardson The Clinton building and Trump hotel staring at each other is still kind of perfect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EPA is actually in the William Jefferson Clinton building. https://t.co/vKXxCtiTXX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OH in the newsroom: "Where are the swords?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Rosslyn news: DC region's tallest building, vacant since being built in 2013, finally gets a tenant https://t.co/4XvDmgIDwv #soullesssuburb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["February might be Black History Month, but every month is Trump History Month." https://t.co/vU3XMESILc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Frederick Douglass is an example of somebody who’s done an amazing job and is getting recognized more and more" https://t.co/vU3XMESILc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump will never stop complaining about that one pool report on the Martin Luther King bust. https://t.co/iPiJXunPdf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had an editor who used to cut stories by deleting every other paragraph. He said it was amazing how often you'd l… https://t.co/TgBSzm6dIE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Especially the "stay in" aspect. Reporting and editing jobs at local newspapers have vanished by the 1000s in the p… https://t.co/5QxhPB4OOh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mentored by the mob? Trump labor secretary lawyer Andrew Puzder got his start working for a notorious mob lawyer https://t.co/eXp6SgjXAr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@POLITICOPro is looking for a reporter to cover transportation security, a topic much in the news these days: https://t.co/IGzqQT1fuF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Democrats erupted in frustration at the GOP 'obstructionism' and vowed to find a way to push Gina McCarthy’s nomin… https://t.co/eInyzdKO1w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Historical Parallel Police are out in force in the Yates firing, insisting you can't liken events to each other unless they're identical]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Butt-tweetgate update: Spicer did it again! https://t.co/IBbe0i1G3b by @patrick_c_reis, the David Halberstam of but… https://t.co/L2CplR00GB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does that mean people are saying that Dana Boente is playing the role of Dolores Umbridge? https://t.co/w4AnT3oTxr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OK, this is seeming a bit more substantial than a subtweet... https://t.co/cbvGSXMZyv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm guessing Sally Yates didn't sign an NDA, though. https://t.co/ENFmjmaISo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But did Sally Yates at least get a positive reference letter from the White House?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are people calling this the Monday Night Massacre yet? Too soon?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It’s extremely rare for administration officials to circumvent Republican leadership &amp; work directly with... aides" https://t.co/0ERazlhMds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior House Judiciary staffers secretly worked on Trump's immigration order WITHOUT telling Republican leaders https://t.co/0ERazlhMds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“I do believe that if we win back the House of Representatives, impeachment proceedings will be started.” https://t.co/4FAzSs5eJv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's Trump doing in the White House? Exactly what he said he would, to Republicans' and Democrats' dismay https://t.co/4FAzSs5eJv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robo-signing affair dogs Mnuchin before committee vote https://t.co/WPXB6LQ7fg by the great @Woellert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s regulatory clampdown called more flash than substance https://t.co/vzE7XXMuCb @AndrewRestuccia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump "will definitely pull out of Paris climate change deal," says former Christie adviser who never met Trump https://t.co/NIc22XJQ6S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WH: No mention of Jews on Holocaust Remembrance Day because others were killed too https://t.co/bobdLTHB5R Couldn't… https://t.co/1Eo725Fldo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And yes, I know that's a parody account, although it's hard to tell what it's parodying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The media reacted with horror to the bombings, but also did their jobs. Including journalists from my newsroom who… https://t.co/ErxMiw5vx6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Hotels' question from October about people's "favorite travel memories" is getting some unexpected reactions… https://t.co/RZgth0keSM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the thousands of protesters were also part of Trump's elaborate plot? Sometimes multiple "big stories" actually… https://t.co/BSRXyFiyhI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DHS actually started asking for the social media information late last year from visitors on the visa waiver progra… https://t.co/CsbAjfaIin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually, DHS started doing it in December: https://t.co/wjZxhFVCuC https://t.co/QAn7GMCFra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Obama administration had already begun asking about foreign visitors' social media info: https://t.co/wjZxhFVCuC https://t.co/gmNTnN9gMe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@CNN doubles down on second straight hour of 80s documentaries as protests continue at airports nationwide. MSNBC sticks with Lockup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breitbart: "Terror-Tied Group CAIR Causing Chaos, Promoting Protests &amp; Lawsuits as Trump Protects Nation" https://t.co/uOshGTmhce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Countries where Trump does business are not hit by new travel restrictions https://t.co/GGJUpuUdlB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ianbremmer: US citizens who traveled to Iraq, Syria to kill locals for ISIS: 250

Iraqis, Syrians carrying out ISIS attacks in US: 0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everybody has a right to protect their country," man in halal restaurant says on phone. Can't tell if he's defending or criticizing Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I always thought those socks were up to no good... https://t.co/2ASBmRIC5H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are the Catholic bishops subtweeting Trump now? https://t.co/zFYcZK9QW8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Only Americans suffer from the delusion that Muslims are not already being extensively racially profiled" https://t.co/yTvj4pfJMO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the New York Times responds to @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/wc1l6BusOY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rhinovirus has a well-known liberal bias. https://t.co/Jmh7fYid5d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hacker impersonates Sunrun CEO, nabs employee W-2 tax forms https://t.co/Olcl2sqR5G https://t.co/15LPPvMbb5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump talks tough on China’s hacking. Why not Russia’s? https://t.co/NoUtCCYuGj by @cory_bennett https://t.co/sah3eEDzBM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best wishes and congratulations, @PattiHartranft, from a @DailyCollegian alum https://t.co/dNxH6xzhdL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because of course the @nytimes throws a Plato's cave reference into the middle of a Russian hacking story… https://t.co/HwUTjTP8Qg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FF our great @POLITICOPro transportation team: @kathrynwolfe, @JAscholtes, @Gardner_LM, @TSnyderDC, @brigurciullo and @dailym1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump White House abruptly halts Obamacare ads https://t.co/dWQgq9x0k2 Great scoop by @pauldemko https://t.co/ySeu8NEihd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#!/usr/bin/perl
use warnings;
use strict;
use Moose;
use Memoize;
use Tie::Handle::CSV;
use WWW::Mechanize;
use Data::Dumper;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@nytimes says Trump is using his "old, unsecured Android phone." Cybersecurity threat? https://t.co/ua2IAS4C4k by @ericgeller @POLITICOPro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the other hand, maybe he rooted it and installed a custom ROM.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's "Android phone is more than likely a Samsung Galaxy S3...which last received a software update in mid-2015" https://t.co/537v7vnppa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But wait, hasn't Trump also called Obama a weak leader? https://t.co/AqDf0r7VMu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By comparison, the still-unfinished Everglades restoration project that Congress approved in 2000 was supposed to c… https://t.co/2fvcohQuK1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats launch scorched-earth strategy against Trump https://t.co/13hUkTy07l "They were entitled to a grace period and they blew it"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Media Split on Approach to Trump Coverage https://t.co/RhsA9QqHgO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@realDonaldTrump has the White House, a GOP Congress, a Supreme Court seat. His critics have rogue Twitter account… https://t.co/ibF4AK4SWw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federal workers' Twitter brushfire burns Trump https://t.co/tTZZozH6sR by @nancyscola with @andrewrestuccia https://t.co/TJT8iOcaRv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frustrated House Republicans press McConnell to kill the filibuster https://t.co/kn5zvobmfZ https://t.co/9BuaaO6rSq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What are the bad things that can happen if a hacker gets control of your phone number? https://t.co/5SnVQFpQ9A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flashback: "Executive Order tyranny -- Obama plans to rule America with pen, phone" https://t.co/0Q7FqoT6C8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By Palm Beach standards, that's still the equivalent of operating a Target. https://t.co/zFmmPK5fWt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Restaurant sound system playing Christopher Cross, "Ride Like the Wind." Least convincing badass-outlaw-on-the-run song ever?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And now the parody accounts step in... https://t.co/EJlUl0f33Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As of Tuesday night, this tweet from Jan. 19 is the last one from EPA's main account. https://t.co/lWFTvwQoXB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["But what if the Trump presidency is actually off to a surprisingly effective start?" https://t.co/6zK4LhdlNj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At first I read this as "WordStar," proving that I'm both a dork and kind of old. https://t.co/LwsajHdxPh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Definition of the day: The Streisand effect https://t.co/GZpNm1zZUO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[National Park Service employees are often super hard-core about their agency's mission. More people seem to be getting a glimpse of that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's gonna be yuge now. https://t.co/aJcdDFYKvB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In other words, this too shall pass. https://t.co/VpkGpl35yb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“From what we can tell, the cloud of Mordor is descending across the federal service." https://t.co/5yARtoPcWJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't tweet. Don't send out press releases. Don't post to Facebook. Don't update websites. https://t.co/5yARtoPcWJ https://t.co/ACVYO9TH6F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greens won when Obama killed Keystone pipeline &amp; delayed Dakota Access. But Trump just revived both: https://t.co/p30ZWqKXrF #KXL #DAPL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's always been more of a GPG fan. https://t.co/qL29EWzRBb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WriterChickNJ Yes -- will never forget that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WriterChickNJ After that, charming folks would occasionally mail us white powder to express displeasure w/ a story &amp; we'd go into lockdown.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WriterChickNJ Yes, Bob Stevens in Lantana was the first to die in the 2001 anthrax attacks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the next four years, the synonym for "waving the bloody shirt" will be "waving the relocated MLK bust."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know who else has gotten "white substances" mailed to them, and in some cases died from them? They're called jo… https://t.co/bdHGn2rAln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starting to see a pattern... RT @kylegriffin1: EPA Freezes Grants, Tells Employees Not To Talk About It, Sources Say https://t.co/5d9x5K17JG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time Traveler: Everyone In The Future Eats Dippin' Dots https://t.co/vdtQdYdSEN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Florida judge resigns after being accused of comparing female lawyers to "cheerleaders" and saying blacks should "g… https://t.co/RnMnfRzSNl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate it when mom and dad fight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or: "I've got a Jolla tablet to sell you." https://t.co/BOh8r0iLgp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America, You Look Like an Arab Country Right Now https://t.co/H7tkZchawg https://t.co/RaxEFMvtIA]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>