<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@NiallOK I'm only up the road in Cabra. I never remember to rub an ice cube on skin when I get a burn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NiallOK Where do you live? I have a huge aloe vera plant (this is not a euphanism).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DebraMessing Every yr the Irish prime minister visits the White House on 17 March. Calls for him not to this yr https://t.co/lCjBu2ytqi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever thought about pet fostering? https://t.co/8xsdu7Xnb0 is always on the look-out for new fosterers. The joy of a cat without commitment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishRail Taking a journey from Broombridge. How do I pay? Have you installed Leap readers since my last visit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBClamacqshow Up the Hill Backwards by David Bowie. Cheers from Dublin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look what arrived on Australia day! #grantandi #go-betweens @RobertForster3 https://t.co/rk4aotKJkm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IanDempsey Love the Cult! This girl has class. More Cult daily please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this. From Montreal, Come by She-Devils https://t.co/F3EnUhkXwt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@8RadioIreland Flipping fantastic to hear Auto Da Fe on the radio!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OldeEire I learned about disc damage on a first aid course.  Can't imagine the pain. No disco dancing for you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OldeEire It surely is. I've had a cold since September]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've spent the day contemplating something positive. Here's a pic of my fab new leopard print socks https://t.co/vmnopSG7DR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PMcLoone Definitely time for Ant Music by Adam and the Ants]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dublinbusnews I got a 38A in Phibsborough that wasn't listed on any Real Time. #surrealtime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dublinbusnews Thanks. Stop no.80 says 43 mins for 122. Real Time Info is seriously screwed. #scifi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dublinbusnews At stop no.77 and it's 54  mins for a 122. What's going on? This is Cabra, not Navan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boo, new foster kitten. This super friendly purr machine will be up for adoption soon… https://t.co/EuXaCu5zkk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fobraonain Fantastic start to the show! Stars of Heaven are my favourite Irish band. Eat your orange or your cake...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PMcLoone Sadly my fave song of all time was used in a car ad, Wide Open Road by the Triffids]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm selling a futon. Open to offers. https://t.co/XTs1udI4pC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UlsterBank_Help I'm not remotely patient, I'm very annoyed, so no need to thank me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UlsterBank_Help So this is what I pay a tenner a month for? Thanks lads #massivefail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fobraonain It's QUITE SOME TIME since Iast heard Decadent Days! Loving it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PMcLoone You probably have playlist for tonight complete, hope this is on it, love it. https://t.co/UOPARnKVQG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlisonTodayFM Try stemless glasses. I use some tumblers from tesco. Cheap and long-lasting and Spanish stylee!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonBarry_ I took that photo! Nice to see it again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NadineORegan Loving the choices of @davidmcw so far! #disco #partyinmykitchen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be on @8RadioIreland at 2.30 this afternoon. Give me a shout if you'd like to hear anything in particular]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sjfanning Grass is it exactly. But I'd reached a point where I was prepared to try anything to make my immune system stronger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking to adopt kittens? I'm fostering these 2 dotes, they have become fab little chaps since I got them https://t.co/3uOClO5Dv8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Christmas habit of a daily Irish coffee has been replaced by matcha tea. It's VILE. But I've been ill and read i… https://t.co/vrmjcbuj4p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlisonTodayFM My fella Grizzley Adams chops up the Christmas tree every yr. Great burning! Just make sure to use a fireguard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Send help: what's there to do of a Thurs night in Achill sound? It's as dead as heaven on a Saturday night]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm looking for a pub quiz during the first week of January. If you know of one please let me know. Dublin area.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaraghBroph RECOVERY! Ireland is in recovery! (Not for me anyway)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wham! ticket, my 1st ever gig. RDS. https://t.co/HKAprpT89H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wham! In the RDS was my 1st ever gig. RIP George Michael]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cerysmatthews Here's the phonetic pronunciation : Nullig Shunna Dit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmerTheScreamer I feel your pain, I got my festive dose. But it won't stop me hitting Hogans later!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCRadMac Beat this: we have a Barak Obama service station https://t.co/2wNN7xlc1U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Old Toy Trains https://t.co/cjocFyNpBG @martylyricfm Any chance of this? Never gets played at Chr...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@todayfm Lads, so much auto-tune in the mornings.  My ears hurt! #toooldfortodayfm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mistereatgalway @FSAIinfo I spoke to them at a food fair. It's packed in Belgium,  made here. No equipment in this country for shape]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be on @8RadioIreland at 2pm today. 94.3fm in Dublin,  or online at https://t.co/6INhq92WuH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ben_watt Thanks!  Will do. Really enjoyed gg in @whelanslive recently]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ben_watt Any sign of your website coming back?  Bought Hendra on vinyl and want digital version. New record player not  coming until Jan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be on @8RadioIreland tomorrow at 2pm, 94.3fm in Dublin. There will be Blue Nile for sure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blue Nile fans take note! Great radio doc by @KenSweeney  #insearchofthebluenile https://t.co/xXGEFqTEeZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SaturdayKitchen I love an Irish accent on the show!  #paddytakeover]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A new one to me, Christmas in February by Lou Reed. Thank you @8RadioIreland ! #feelingfestive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@martylyricfm It's not Ch*** until I've heard Dan Fogleberg. Pls hurry! In work at 8.30]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inspectors on the 38 leaving city for Blanch. 3 of them. #ticketalert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@makeupmonster_ @mufeireland I'd love to win. I nominate my friend Louise K.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2pm today I'll be on the fab @8RadioIreland. Shout now for a request]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to playing great tunes on @8RadioIreland tomorrow  (Sun) at 2pm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Funny how the studio audience of the #LateLateShow is mostly female but guests are mostly male #wherearethewomen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@8RadioIreland Omigod it's amazing how a song can take you back! Love Engine Alley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MissusVee That's one of the funniest things I've seen on twitter in ages!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Selling a lampshade, genuine #NormannCopenhagan Bought in Brown Thomas https://t.co/0Lzk03woVR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@urchinette I know you love cats *and* magazines. Are you subscribing to Puss Puss? https://t.co/Q6NEr1lmyA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tempted to go to the pub. #powercut #dublin7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Power cut in Cabra. Anywhere else?  #powerout]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCRadMac What, no Guns n Roses in Slane news?! #missingascoop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York at end of Dec for a short break. Will I freeze my ass off? Anything open?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@antodarcy1 Thanks a million!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daveGildedALM @thedraysmusic @8RadioIreland One of my favourite Irish bands, going back a long time!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to playing tunes on 94.3fm https://t.co/6INhq92WuH, 2pm. Hit me with your requests.  @8RadioIreland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@8RadioIreland Any Teenage Fanclub for everyone going to the gig later?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CineramaGav You might enjoy it! I'm not a huge fan, but Hairspray was great a few years back in the West End.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/sThrJCJoaf is on the FM this w/end! Tune in now for your drive-time commute. 94.3fm in Dublin. I'll be on tomorrow at 2pm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCRadMac "Laois" is pronounced Leesh. Cheers from Dublin!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PMcLoone Any Ivor Cutler?  Can email. And Aztec Camera. And Camera Obscura]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBClamacqshow Thanks for being such a great supporter of Irish music ! #powerofdreams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/tb3p0xfBGB Looking forward to seeing @hindsband tonight in the Academy #dublingigs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NiallCrumlish I'm with your daughter!  #timedoesntstandstill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aircoach I guess the 3 hrs from Dub to Cork as listed on your site is subject to change?  Another 40 mins according to Google maps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlisonTodayFM I had never heard of it until recently. Think I'm a bit past appreciating it at this stage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barbarascully Of course!  Up to 48 hrs is fine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@salihughes Welcome to Dublin!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I made this for @last tv which was a great show on RTE 2. Finally got it transferred from VHS tape to dvd. https://t.co/nvNw4hF0eh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AntonSavageShow Pls tell Kim I will be spending exactly zero getting Chr** party ready #nojob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johncreedon Heading to Cork city for the w/end. Any top tips? Is the Hi Be still there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBClamacqshow It's only now I appreciate that song by the Saw Doctors. Great to hear it again. Hi from Dublin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelenORahilly I've heard that song a million times this year and still not sick of it #tilted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@8RadioIreland Pink Frost by the Chills. Hi to Garret and Pablo in D7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heartbreaking to hear neighbour's dog barking on a night this cold. I'd bark too if it was me! #AnimalCruelty #dublin7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's freezing. @wigwamdublin https://t.co/aXu4L7xttJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PMcLoone ABC were fantastic in the @olympiatheatre #datestamp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ABC,  Olympia Theatre, #dublingigs #80snostalgia #poisonarrow #lookoflove https://t.co/gryTQ89vjl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@martylyricfm I LOVE Convoy!  It was all we had before the Internet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@muloc2016 Hope you caught Cattle and Cane]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@graywaster I am! Today at 4pm for 2 hrs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catch me on @8RadioIreland from 4 till 6 today.  Only ever great songs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fobraonain I had Dessert Boots on single!  Great to hear it again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SexSiopa @car_ireland A real life woman on the #LateLateShow ?!? About bleeding time. You and Bruce-I'll be watching!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last Christmas is playing in @TKMaxx_IE  This is HELL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh look. More men on the @RTELateLateShow springsteen-late-late-3061453 #wherearethewomen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCRadMac For real, Irish dancing on the radio was a thing here in Ireland.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ben Watt and Bernard Butler,  Fantastic gig tonight in @whelanslive ben_watt https://t.co/iobwkvnetc]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>