<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@EurotekIreland @Avtek Would love to have a chat see if we can get you involved? Can I email or call? Thanks Bernice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephenMangan he knows it's not the apprentice..  Right?  Right?  @realDonaldTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bowandpearl well she's definitely stylish enough to be there.. Gorgeous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just heard that this is @EurotekIreland @Avtek work ..love it. be amazing for childrens hospital in Crumlin. https://t.co/wxop7KV8RG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CMRF_Crumlin interesting article.. https://t.co/qB6GUiAeSR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hotpatooties I really wonder what his ex wife Ivana thinks considering she fled communist czechslovakia.. Most his children half Czech.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great speech @RealBrentPope at @IGFAie dinner.. Funny stories &amp; tall tales. Fantastic fundraiser for @CMRF_Crumlin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At @IGFAie dinner supporting @CMRF_Crumlin.. Loving the moving floor effect in @crownplaza Northwood Santry https://t.co/cu6lZhpAvi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daraobriain @joshwiddicombe watching mock the week..all jokes about The Wall &amp; trump..flick to @guardian all facts The wall &amp; trump #grim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I #ScrumTogether with @DoveMen to win #IREvFRA RBS 6 Nations tickets. Pick your match by 8pm &amp; you could too https://t.co/3AXcVJnVTU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[or maybe this one? @PSupica https://t.co/1V0qrUodcG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We have to win one day @PSupica https://t.co/KHmikRhRvD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[brillant prize . fingers crossed.. #brasserie66
#giveaway #Dublin #TuesdayMotivation #win . https://t.co/KM8Mzf2vCf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnpurcell21 @wowburgerdublin they were pretty busy &amp; said 30 mins max but seemed to be staff chats alot so took a lot longer. Beside Mak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlisonTodayFM Ikea glasses are self breaking...then you go and buy more cause they're cheap..false economy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LoveYourGarden2 can you nominate from ireland? Parents would love it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wowburgerdublin that's good as here since 1948 and order still not ready... Bored]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davemcginn_ie @wowburgerdublin what time is ranelagh open till this evening?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilCawley just heard you speaking to navy guy.. Did you see the Le eithne #christmasjumperday video...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could do with this... need to treat @PSupica after spending Christmas with my family and unwell parents..… https://t.co/8FCAEUm7Tx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LoveYourGarden2 @wordpressdotcom wish he'd do one in Ireland.. Parents would love it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016 for me..brought my favourite person , lost a lot of idols and made me get to know myself at lot more .. Happy New year heres to 2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Commitments.... 25 yrs old... Dublin so changed but @Glen_Hansard the same just a beard these days..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gutted. George Michael]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@foggynotions @owensiemusic unreal. What a year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dunners11 Lovely to meet you &amp; Sophie in the Kitchen ! Great to have you coming in to see the children. @OLCHCrumlin @CMRF_Crumlin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlisonTodayFM great to hear you talking about @CMRF_Crumlin today..check out our new sign... https://t.co/l1eIzSCOvP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MonicaVinader is it too late to order to get delivered to ireland?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NiamhieNiamh this is link..:-)  https://t.co/DLuNXpRveG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AMcGill1978 @NiamhieNiamh any interest girls? https://t.co/IFxqYqnHIi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KennedyLucy nice. My breakfast definitely wasn't like that in there!!  Congrats on the new arrival]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cmcmdmcg @debbieddub @PSupica this is all of us now !! Wont have it any other way.. #littledarlings https://t.co/M83i79BlOx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@debbieddub @cmcmdmcg Katie would love this ... https://t.co/7mSipHzeUC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DublinCocktails @angelinasdublin would have to disagree.. Average food all round..flat prosecco and very slow staff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing footage.. But makes me feel so much better to read this teeet https://t.co/B2uUPJoBfX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CiCashen so T is doing really well !! good to chat . keep in touch ,. bx https://t.co/T5BgSCDKhp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to the pictures later... #christmasjumperday https://t.co/T5BgSCDKhp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@louisemcsharry @andotherstories love their stuff.. Hope they have good prices...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mandsireland Nice jumpers ..be good for #christmasjumperday for @CMRF_Crumlin check these out @PSupica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to win Neven Maguire's MacNean House Experience #TheTaste #WinMacNeanHouseExperience @TheTaste_ie @nevenmaguire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CiCashen is this the type of work day you have now? https://t.co/CeD1lrMgXt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AskMandP thanks for trying...if anyone finds a lone zebra please think of us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AskMandP with regard to this..wondering if possible to check any of your shops storerooms for spare ones as product no longer sold..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sweetpmac or local builders suppliers may have recommendations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sweetpmac ah think guy works from bray so probably a bit far. They did refrub my bathroom .tiling etc. Try local woodies/homebase for one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sweetpmac where you living? I know a good plumber who may do it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AskMandP thanks for letting me know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AskMandP ok thanks. Guess i hoped warehouse would have some unused from damaged mats or something.. he loved it and really notices its gone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sgormo @debbieddub @cmcmdmcg @JOEdotie @ElChiefMoore apply...go on... get Debbie onto your couch too...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PSupica maybe ill win these and get to go... @AMcGill1978 if i win ..you around to babysit!!! #irevaus https://t.co/1LTSSiQpdE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@debbieddub @cmcmdmcg @sgormo .....did you see these..gogglebox cast members needed..get your sofas ready!! https://t.co/Ij7QOoBzOu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AskMandP ah I'm so disappointed.. is there anything can be done? I dont see them for sale so hoped you would have some spares!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PSupica this is what i mentioned https://t.co/akfKVTuGiX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AskMandP Hi,,wondering any possibility getting duplicate set of little animals that come with jungle gym.. zebra gone missing.. #sadbaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AMcGill1978 you'd be great at this  https://t.co/fjZJgjmkrt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@debbieddub hey you should check out this lady blog..its brilliant especially after a long night.. https://t.co/z8f43j0ijq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AMcGill1978 interesting article.. I know guy who wrote it if want more advice..  https://t.co/mIqqHSCbsd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Deliveroo_IE hi you'll need to follow me so I can send a DM. im in D12 near kimmage road west though if that helps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PukekoPastures hey...you should follow @ultimaterugby on this...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@quirkyglamping @thelatelateshow ah would definitely have turned on for David McGowan but cant with them letting someone so vile on as her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Deliveroo_IE thanks for replying ..we got the flyer in July !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DillingersD @Deliveroo_IE hi, wondering why we got notification of delivery in our area into our letterbox but you still dont? #badservice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've voted for #Heaslip in the IRPA Try of the Year award 2016
https://t.co/TqlzZ4Yl5K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daraobriain yes but unreal filming and narration #wayoflife #planetearth2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cooper_m least you probably have coverage...nothing on the national channels..not even highlights!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sgormo @debbieddub..  How come this isn't one if you.....  https://t.co/f7PyPa9k6o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thewhitmore sorry to hear you're injured...saw this in a shop and thought make you laugh.. #ladygarden https://t.co/rOtVOFohUs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cooper_m @marionmckeone it's a bit emperors new clothes isn't it....everyone around him not going to mention he's losing...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AMcGill1978 check these out  https://t.co/WxrZGWwPfp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SharonHorgan fab interview fab dress..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stolensleep do they mean by 'routine' you put them to bed, they get up,shout, cry, chat &amp; then you just let them sleep on you ? #babysleep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daraobriain so Jam then...or orange jam.. Great episode.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bowandpearl ah dont be tellling me that!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StokkeBaby Hi thanks. the link it just shows one type @mothercareirl seems to have 2 versions at different prices  https://t.co/plNigE7sMx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StokkeBaby hi, looking at the baby carrier.. saw online front carrier ..can this also be used as back carrier and is there a price diff?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NMIreland hi..do you have a customer service email please...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DublinZoo great thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Deliveroo_DUB got voucher in postbox..deliveroo in your area..go online to get @DillingersD message we dont deliver comes up! #poorservice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DublinZoo do you have any method for customers with limited mobility to get around]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@debbieddub.... Have a look  https://t.co/noBVER0tjj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@imccinemas @savoy Hi, My dad ex army ( congo ) was interested in Seige of jadotville on monday but not sure if he needs to prebook. thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aldi_Ireland thanks.  I'm away Nd so much I wanted to get... Sigh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PSupica if we win the @image_magazine competition for @cliffhousehotel this could be our view... #fingerscrossed  https://t.co/113Ev0iOGG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@debbieddub @DaniCullen ...put it in the diaries.. Baby stuff aldi https://t.co/WTd3TZTxMZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fearnecotton yep and he hasn't gone back to sleep yet.. #chats #tiredmum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aldi_Ireland Hi saw that baby #specialbuys are due in rathmines store on 22nd..will this be the same for all stores?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ask the government to cut the red tape for thousands of people trapped in homelessness. https://t.co/KPWA6xr9Eg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NiamhieNiamh hey didn't your sister meet Rory there  https://t.co/9vVF80BqBu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCSport @psupica what's with the #SLOENG???  Surely someone can check a simple thing.. Slovakia - #SVK   #Masterminds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ODMgmt same.. Avoiding all tweets about it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@louisemcsharry great article..you should look up @stolensleep really great blog and person to follow ..she makes me laugh on the rough days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leinsterrugby HI, Can you please let me know if I can bring 7month old in carrier in ? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LobFest2014 thats disappointing to hear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leinsterrugby hi is it possible to bring baby in carrier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jduggantodayfm @IrishTimes greed and corruption]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leinsterrugby hi for match in Donnnybrook on Friday..is it possible to bring baby in carrier..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PSupica ...you should recommend your favourite place in ireland .. https://t.co/7iPZ6HEYqJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PSupica keep an eye out for this competition.... https://t.co/Sdzx2FKhkI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stolensleep the best is when they say..oh i had to wake them this morning....!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@debbieddub did you see these road closures for Sunday  https://t.co/1DmOwp4nma]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>