<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@CGreen63 @mitchellvii there will be no illegals voting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspiritcan @BlackburnRuth @biker_bowen83 @EMcCra2 @vetek45 listen people irresponsible vaccine practices are killing humans not infections]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls @realDonaldTrump @POTUS Kellyanne you are an amazing role models for new women to follow,don't let anyone put you down]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sammacaw74 OMG this is just priceless, how about they are wasting tax payers dollars and stretching voters patience, we need our government]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Blakes30s @ups2death @Heritage @sensessions the law and order shall be enforced]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Blakes30s @noble_milford @Heritage @sensessions California doesn't get it, there more than one state in USA #MAGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@USPatriot06 @DineshDSouza @realDonaldTrump I think he is done turning come out and chase those dems back to do what they were elected for]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucmpaquin @DineshDSouza @realDonaldTrump not to mention free health care too and not what they offered to the voters as Obamacare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sheilascarp @LilaGraceRose @ericmetaxas @PPact I feel the same way. It kills me to think how heartless this all is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Project_Veritas I admire you and your crew, thank you for standing for true nature of journalism and keeping us informed,fear nothing w God]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is There an Anti-Vaccine Shadow Network? https://t.co/yLD7OgDegc via @mercola]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stormnatcup4u @Pamela_Moore13 it can be New York too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaliVaxChoice @NVICLoeDown they are out of their minds, vaccines are dangerous weapons of mass destruction]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@giannajessen anyone is a value all lives are precious disability in one eyes is greater abilities in God's view, blessings are from him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BusyDrT Trump hit ground running very encouraging should change a lot of resistance to get our questions answered, praying for deliverance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BusyDrT great read, thank you my favorite doctor,shared on FB too, hopefully more parents awake to true and present danger of vaccines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaliVaxChoice @USATODAY CDC is out of control,time to audit and installation of law and order,deliberate endanger of Americans is a crime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VickieSpringer @sammacaw74 @az_valentine @FoxNews @CNN @MSNBC they are disgusting and the fact that they had kids at this orgy made me sick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RWSlater I had a good laugh imagining it, and what a great way to go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OnlineMagazin Restoring law and order the only folks scared of the blue is criminals, support our police and armed forces, be patriot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@az_valentine @corockymtns beautiful state is getting destroyed so sad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@giannajessen @Casey_Nicole5 kindness is what us humans should give one another every day, simple acts of kindness, it's easy, smile]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichardTBurnett I read testimonials from people who worked for him that he never makes these acts of kindness public]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brithume @washingtonpost Project Veritas is what investigative journalism must be, grateful for all your work and sacrifice,God bless all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@az_valentine please don't tell them,they won't figure this out on their own,just sit back and enjoy these crazy old bats protesting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ToscaAusten so much agree with you, they are running out of crazy ideas and old fools to be committed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bob_0713 @IngrahamAngle @DailyCaller one can only pray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@njtrainlady @IngrahamAngle @DailyCaller hopefully soon,their time has passed and gone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BOlson63475131 @IngrahamAngle @DailyCaller it's a mental relations, both belong in the crazy house]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @DailyCaller old girl completely lost her mind, faith is not something you register for, old fool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IngrahamAngle @SFGate Lol,science is bought and paid for,watch out for sponsors and follow the money,sell their soul to anyone,no trust]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump all Obama ever did was weird and dishonest,he committed the biggest consumer fraud in history,Obamacare,no surprise on exit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BusyDrT this world of profits over future of humanity is completely out of control, our movement has work to do and urgent it is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@giannajessen well they had lied to us for a while, not any more,truth has a way to come out eventually,sad for all lost souls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCBreaking @greta @BBCNews I recall they said Trump will not be our president and he is Mexico is going to pay for the wall and more, no??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RenaSummersLtd @Maximus_Paulus @WhiteHouse @POTUS I am so happy with Mr. President's 1st days in office just the beginning.Bless him and us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrAlanDeng @aspiritcan are we starting to see the truth on real and present danger? Thank you God and Heaven.Humanity may survive vaccines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JulieFormo @aspiritcan @REALTheRealDEAL @thereal_truther it amazes me that vaccine defenders don't want to hear about danger of ingredients]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaliVaxChoice @AsburyParkPress It is refreshing to know how many are awake in search for the truth in vaccine impact on our kid's health]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“HuffPo removes vaccine safety article (again) in record time!” by @jb_handley https://t.co/WBIQoqXRpc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@az_valentine praying for return of humanity and family values to our nation. It starts with amazing first family. Love and respect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gqforbes4 @RichardTBurnett @johnrobertsFox @FoxNews This is time to investigate and prevent such practices from ever happening again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cwtkns @gqforbes4 @johnrobertsFox @FoxNews that's why Clintons and left were so sure of their win, they were wrong, Americans one this time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LockThemUp2016 @LouDobbs @POTUS I switch to CNN when #SheppardSmith comes on, he belongs there not on #FoxNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joatchley52 @LouDobbs @POTUS there are many of us in America that feel just like you. We respect and love and we are united in patriotism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigStick2013 @RichardTBurnett it's about time we get our country back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrisonPlanet It looks like it was not Russians after our democracy but Germans. How did this happen?Wow,thank the Lord we have a new CIA!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RdblancoDavid @foxandfriends @DineshDSouza she deserved it truth hurt her]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls @AaronBlake wow looks like desperation drives the mind crazy, just ignore them Kellyanne,they are sad crowd w no hope at all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @FoxNews @CNN Fox so far is the only outlet that doesn't distort the news, unless you watching Sheppard he belongs on CNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LilaGraceRose @LiveActionNews and democrats were concerned with country's budget, that's how we address it, cut the useless spending]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls @markknoller one only hopes that democrats and left wing agitators will find decency within to stop attacking 10 year old]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii it was offensive to me as a woman and all I stand for, these women are not reflection of feminist nature and nurture,love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@livingrace @mitchellvii me too, I would never be accepted among the ones that marched there, it was a disgrace for women mothers and wives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DineshDSouza left and eugenics don't want love and families they want control and power over one's body and mind, Trump family defies it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mitchellvii well my opinion Obama was smart Hillary toast he played nice with Trump, it pays to be nice we shall see]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheDiBlogNews @DineshDSouza @nbc if we stop wasting our hard earned money on garbage they produce , they will collapse , economics simple]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SandySmartass @DineshDSouza @nbc LoVE it, and crap they are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@giannajessen you are an inspiration for many, your story is tragic yes, it should never happen to no one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls @jeffzeleny @PressSec I thought liberals asked for diversity? Oh no, what about their propaganda machine?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CranSimpson7 @PeteNicholls2 @chicaguerrera @KellyannePolls get over your"facts" millions watched cried from happiness, you cried too, lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamieObama @KellyannePolls I do and I like her , she is smart and beautiful and successful, you eat your heart out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rolandscahill @teriberi_teri it's a long list sparky, and looks like you eat it up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rolandscahill @teriberi_teri since Pravda used to be controlled by communist party in USSR, CNN is controlled by democrats and pharma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@giannajessen you better of if they don't block you they start to insult you, libs can be nasty crowd and love to fight dirty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steele_rosanne @RichardTBurnett me too, so many hopes and aspirations blessings on our great country and her people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oreillyfactor because women that marched are pro murder, not pro life, simple explanation,don't reflect what women in US represent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LilaGraceRose @PPact @LiveActionNews Victory!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SheriffClarke what she said there on the podium was treason, can't undo must face consequences and under the law not above it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@concernedrep well many of us don't have the same privilege so we elected Trump to shake the status you got, don't like it do you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@concernedrep @aspiritcan good luck with that, I was like you ignorant and trusted my kids doctor, I was wrong, you will learn hard way,sad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@concernedrep I don't believe we lived thru Trump plan yet, it only has been a few days, and 8 years with Obama taught me not to trust]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nybybirth @aspiritcan @debnantz @ThisMomHCN they poison us with many times replicated cancer inducing crap they cooked up in labs, eugenics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow @politico let's wait a bit it must be fake news again considering the source,they will apologize it it's not true,as usual]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theRealMleh you must be taking meds by a handful that's what you push I understand, may God forgive you,me and my damaged kids won't]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theRealMleh @aspiritcan @savitrisun @UNICEF that's another BS from you, we got plenty of unvaccinated data to do study, you scared of truth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theRealMleh you know the sad part even if it is true you will always defend the dark side for vaccines, must be a good pay for you from it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theRealMleh your medical school books are written by pharma. Open your eyes and search dipper. Look at what Gates did in India. Criminal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DiligentJoshT We are big Trump supporters we are true Americans and patriots, we don't need to see his taxes, just do his job as president]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls I don't need to see his taxes. I want him to improve mine and lower the tax rates for working Americans and US businesses]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theRealMleh if you want to look at the big picture look at profits pharma making and sick generation of kids on our hands, that's the truth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theRealMleh and you should know why autism is more prevalent in boys,polio??check history books it was going away before vaccine mandate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JudgeJeanine Judge don't waste your precious time on this old fossil. He is a preacher from the past,and he has no ability to see future]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@concernedrep he is the sane one, you liberals are mentally brainwashed to bash anyone who speaks the truth,just like you doing now with me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theRealMleh okay so at least you admit vaccines cause autism, just stop saying a lie that vaccines prevent infectious diseases, that's BS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@craigwidga @EuripidesMaui @mitchellvii don't be sorry, there are many broke Americans after Obama devastation of our land]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@2Twitte39301335 @Thomas1774Paine @MatthewHrenak old fossil Brennan is history, who cares about his opinion? No one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@concernedrep @Thomas1774Paine you are the only one who is into crowds dude, we watched on tv millions of us, give up he is Mr. President]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@babblingagain @Thomas1774Paine and they don't respresent us, but themselves, ugly and nasty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PPPTCE @Thomas1774Paine don't insult onions, CNN is worthless , onions good for your health, lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sammacaw74 @CBSDFW well I believe these felons deserve what they rioted for, law and order, enough with lawlessness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theRealMleh shame on you for promoting known neurotoxins injected in kids, unless you know shit about science,degree don't mean intelligent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theRealMleh Huge BS you just said, research real science. I can't help stupid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nybybirth @aspiritcan @theRealMleh @savitrisun @UNICEF extremely valid point,Feds stop protecting vaccine manufacturers license to kill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nybybirth @aspiritcan @theRealMleh @savitrisun @UNICEF these marching women should have opposed the vaccine schedule, nope they want killin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greta @MSNBC @BigGeorgeSATX @RMSwartz2 @tlynnleggie Greta I watched you on Fox but not any more, you crossed to the dark side, sorry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ACLJ Clashed with a few abortion defenders, they sincerely believe that killing babies is better for humanity,saving resources,me horrified]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Franklin_Graham absolutely correct and what is so astonishing all these people who witness and approve this senseless murder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kellyanne Conway Meet The Press FULL HEATED Interview "Alternative Facts... https://t.co/oUon9JCTM9 via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DidinChaKnow @7marinesa @patrici61580698 @DanaWinters93 @LilaGraceRose so that's somehow justification for abortion "naturally"?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>