<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@jk_rowling the 1690s by the look of it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TorgHacker showing a disturbing lack of basic principles of governance, he's CinC of armed forces and the Senate doesn't declare war alone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AxelGrindington this is the potential straw that will break the camel's back and force a change. He shouldn't go though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProfBrianCox how do these people not understand that science is all around? That we live by those laws first and man's second?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AxelGrindington and to meet chicks, left that bit out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing feels better than watching your child smile in their sleep #dadlife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan technically that honour goes to the Mexican president who cancelled, she's 2nd to be invited]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeithpBarry all of them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I #ScrumTogether with @DoveMen to win #IREvFRA RBS 6 Nations tickets. Pick your match by 8pm &amp; you could too https://t.co/eD3qzxuxje]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, could he look any more disinterested? https://t.co/X6BXu1DCke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolute joke of a country that requires baptism to access basic human rights to education https://t.co/VPcUFfDDZZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AxelGrindington Trump just screwed the Standing Rock protest with 5 more EOs today to deregulate environmental protection]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AxelGrindington also, we need to organise XWing at some point]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AxelGrindington Trump is dangerous precisely because he doesn't believe the rules apply to him, and they never should. That is scary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AxelGrindington a free pass just to see what he can do. He is ignoring all international conventions. Obama at least played by the rules]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AxelGrindington Neville Chamberlain waving a piece of paper springs to mind. I'm no fan of the guy, but I also don't think he should get]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AxelGrindington also, if history is any guide, the fact of allowing people like Hitler time to screw up made it worse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AxelGrindington he hasn't got a majority mandate to act as he is. He's using ExecOrders like hammers instead of legislation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AxelGrindington yes it is all parsing words and grasping straws but here's one point - he lost the popular vote by over 3million.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AxelGrindington or his breeches of the Constitution's emoluments clause and his breaking at least one federal law by deleting tweets?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AxelGrindington how about his dismantling of the ACA, his federal hiring freeze or his banning NGOs the advise abortion from funding?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan @JSB_TV not yet he hasn't which is kind of the point to protesting now. Once rights are removed protest becomes revolt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#humblebrag was left off the end of this one. Dick. https://t.co/RTzpTotG2q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waaa!! Waaaahhh!!! Waaaaahhhh!! - literally all I can hear in my head whilst reading this. What a fucking manchild. https://t.co/ybeVWQt7bJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mguggenheim @realDonaldTrump @lisadraws they were all at work, building his wall. Bigly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrahamMcNeill more like 'writing Putie Pie a little love note']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe the GOP is just full of fucking criminals? https://t.co/y1tHRoErEX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan @ItsShols 'free and fair' - as paid for by Russia Inc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone who doesn't believe in love at first sight has never had kids]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unintended consequence of a baby no 46, my hands smell of lavender Johnson's baby wash all the time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piersmorgan @realDonaldTrump he's too much of an ego maniac, craves celebrity endorsement of his presidency]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump though it takes the piss out of the whole Alpha male, marking your territory thing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So @realDonaldTrump allegedly likes golden showers. What a shock. He likes golden everything, look at his horrible tan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AxelGrindington I have a chubby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AxelGrindington feel you. I've had a dose of man flu the last two weeks. It's a bastard to shift]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ghook because that's what the attitude to an election in Germany in the 1930s was]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AxelGrindington everyone exists in their own alternate reality and we only briefly share fleeting moments in others]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone's ready to scrum down for the new year @leinsterrugby https://t.co/WXyUQec2mw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AxelGrindington also, we really need to play XWing. I've gotten loads of new ships. Have a Scum list I want to try]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AxelGrindington yeah, trust me. Once it gets into the Dominion War arc you'll be glad you did. Worf comes over as a regular]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AxelGrindington @CatriciaParr there are websites for that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AxelGrindington DS9 is epic. First 2 seasons are so so but S3 onwards is some of the best Trek ever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AxelGrindington no, I constantly expected Al to turn up at one point]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AxelGrindington fuck the French]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two months old and my daughter can smile at me. She's plotting something, I can tell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TorgHacker the irony of guys waving a CSA flag telling people to 'get over it' is astounding]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TorgHacker or dual candidate tickets. Under the older system we would have had Trump with Clinton as VP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TorgHacker just shows how crazy that system is. Targeting certain states is worth more, which is what the EC is supposed to prevent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AxelGrindington @Gojiranotron @NetflixUK I've heard good things about it. Busy watching the Crown. Interesting look at 1950s England]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder if, in a hundred years, 2016 will be marked as the year that WW3 started? Or will it just be noted as preamble.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hmm. Next up, Hugo Boss will be asked to design the transition team's uniform https://t.co/Z3Pm5lf3EI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoever said diamonds are the hardest material known to man has obviously never been scratched by a newborn's nails]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TorgHacker did you see this? https://t.co/NXZGraQWSq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He is not wrong. Trump was inevitable. His ability to do damage is not https://t.co/mTglIxm8qL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TorgHacker is there no catch up tv service? It is well worth the watch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, shit, that's a scary thought. https://t.co/IAll38Ydst]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TorgHacker or be forced to more likely. Especially if he runs to the middle and pisses off the congressional GOP leadership]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@muskrat_john best case is actually that he comes out, says 'Psych!' and quits straight away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three weeks old, already has her grumpy face down pat. Definitely my daughter https://t.co/NQOfaNegjV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three weeks into fatherhood. Forget water boarding Trump, just give terrorists a newborn. They'll spill soon enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never thought I'd see the day that I would be concerned if a pair of tights match the dress #daddaughterproblems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neiltyson that's called Canada I believe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TorgHacker holy hell that's scary reading. I agree that could blow up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AxelGrindington @thejournal_ie well, it was fleshy coloured after that cream the doctor gave you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AxelGrindington Mormon guy. Goddamn typos. And this is definitely one of the worst elections ever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AxelGrindington Gary Johnson has a better chance than her. Or the moron guy who might win Utah and lock the Electoral College in a draw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grahamdbailey cause TDs won't take a pay cut and most of them are double jobbing as TDs?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grahamdbailey yes sick! Stupid typos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My baby girl got suck on me for the first time. Can't wait til I'm 90 and pay that one back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daughter is now a week old. Still no fine motor skills. Guess I'll have to keep basecoating all my stuff myself...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My daughter will be one week old tomorrow. What's the appropriate age to begin self defence classes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carrieffisher or he's just an obese lunatic with a perma-tan addiction and his head up his arse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now that I'm a father to a 3 day old daughter I must face my first existential crisis - what to dress her as for Hallowe'en]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Marina_Sirtis doing more to help complete strangers in the last half hour than most politicians in a lifetime. Real life Counsellor Troi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lord_Sugar if Trump won a Trump Appreciation Contest he'd claim it was rigged. The guy is a weirdo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TorgHacker it wouldn't surprise me to see a spate of mass shootings at polling stations on election day in 'blue' districts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...other counties with 10x the population. Yes. Because it was random you gomp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The guy who wrote this is an idiot. Actual quote 'the supposedly random process managed to choose four from Leitrim… https://t.co/O62WYjQaSm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#wipwednesday still working on my Space Hulk. This one pretty much finished https://t.co/IL3QN9GAPb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Work progresses on my Space Hulk set https://t.co/Koy8VcX0Gf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Explosm the only ad I need to promote Joking Hazard to my friends https://t.co/ztao4a4reP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TorgHacker a giant Lego Star Destroyer is reason enough to release that kit. Rogue One is more of an excuse 😀]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@muskrat_john can someone also buy that lad a dictionary and point out what 'dictator' and 'president' mean?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CatriciaParr @ukfathers @AxelGrindington he also fails to understand the basics of infection]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrissyteigen but how will you live a complete life now without his touch?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haven't painted any GW stuff in ages. Finally getting around to some Space Hulk #wipwednesday https://t.co/ZEmiy4YGwj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great weekend gaming. Dreadball Xtreme, Fluxx, Joking Hazard, Gloom, XWing and Blood Rage. Also tried to play Relic but abandoned that one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All food *was* organic? Allow me to fix that. All food *is* organic. Unless you're eating non-carbon based substanc… https://t.co/qLSWqcyaus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really? Doesn't he know that's all that religion does? https://t.co/fU6XpZFFad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@starwars Never. Tell. Me. The. Odds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enda Kenny? Really Twitter? Why would I follow him? https://t.co/4kjntop9Ek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finished my Dreadball Xtreme set https://t.co/JHewSbpeUQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surprised that Trump hasn't hammered Hilary on her illness. Maybe he knows something we don't? #conspiracy #tinfoilhat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlanTudyk and if it doesn't expand your consciousness then it ain't worth it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TorgHacker oh definitely. They're appalling. The Enterprise (TOS) is a shocker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TorgHacker I've a big collection. Bought myself Slave I and the Most Wanted pack last week]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TorgHacker I rarely play to be honest but like the look of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TorgHacker how's the Ghost? Thinking of getting one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sinistersnowmen no, it was doubling as a fashion blog. Yeah, stupid autocorrect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sinistersnowmen do restaurant reviews too and call it 'It's a wrap']]></document>
	</documents>
</author>