<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzgameshop only console versions? no steam keys?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redknightnz81 and now the notification they have updated and too try them out. Weeeeeee! Excite!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Downloading all those important windows 10 updates... for calculator and alarm / clock. How did I ever manage before?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I now have a new game to give the title of Worst Racing game I have ever played....  Motorcycle Club (PC)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotham taking the creep factor up to 11.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzBrowncoat no problem dude. thought I had more than that tbh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hot cross buns out for sale already....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well I timed that walk in between the gale force winds and downpour spectacularly badly..... Soaking wet and beard almost blown off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... or if anyone has a cheap windows phone (520/620) for sale, could be interested.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone got a nokia 520 backplate (with plastic buttons still on)?. Will take broken phone for the part if necessary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yummmm golden syrup pudding. Just hot enough to not burn tastebuds / throat / stomach when eating quickly too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And that Alan Wake boxset must be worth millions now too... MILLLLLLIONS.... right... right.... right? Oh and the DJ Hero 1 turntable too?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So now that Tekken 6 is on BC for XB1, that means that limited edition (unopened) with hoodie I have is worth mega money now, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sooooo excited  - and everyone has a beard - it means they are serious guys https://t.co/fNUeHIcONB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SparkyNZ hopefully customs don't notice - as long as it is under $400 NZD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redknightnz81 well that hammering didn't last long (#thatswhatshesaid)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really hammering down with rain now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzBrowncoat if you are happy for me to just send in normal stamped envelope can do it tomorrow as going past postshop. Need address tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzBrowncoat have an Xbox360 logo sticker 5x5cm in size. Really old so not sure on sticky worthiness. Also X360 lanyard if he wants it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Member when international motorsport (#F1, #VASC) used to be on free to air tv in NZ? https://t.co/YxrWRnwiZ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And then there is the fact that #VASC is only available here on (rip-off) pay tv.  Sooooo many others are available free to watch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honestly, #VASC doesn't really hold my interest anymore.  Too many others offering better racing, competitive fields and awesome cars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So with GRM going back to Holden in #VASC, I am wondering how long Nissan will bother &amp; wondering if any manufacturers are looking to join?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 2016, I was 1st in the New Zealand TrueSteamAchievement Leaderboard #truesteamachievements https://t.co/ANM865tvVn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Dubai24HR race live on youtube (just started). Provided by @nismo https://t.co/qRhq3eFsuH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/xPkAtomMn6 is giving away DiRT Showdown (PC) https://t.co/QrROmxlbN5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oooooo Agents of SHIELD getting really gooooood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nightwlf @nzBrowncoat at least they don't expire.... well not that I have noticed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was a good one #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DiRT Rally (PC steam key) for $15USD on @indiegala. F1 2016 for the same price too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@indiegala recent post on the steam group and wondering if sale prices are working or they have expired? https://t.co/theIUpCOeU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[decent little shake just then #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got some new cheap &amp; comfortable shoes, then discount donuts at supermarket bakery. Everything coming up Milhou..... Bradley. Wooooo wooo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I completed the game Cranks and Goggles https://t.co/8SAu16ddew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Traffic at standstill just north of Plimmerton heading north on highway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wellington airport turbulence is like "Enjoying the flight? Well I'll fix that.    hahahaha fuck you" No fuck you turbulence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bought bottled drink at airport. Big mistake. Overpriced and almost flat when opened it. Thanks Nelson. Glad to be leaving anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had a family Xmas breakfast (so much bacon!) then family lunch (so much trifle!) now time for nap. Happy Xmas everyone!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redknightnz81 Saw it at State in Nelson in one of their fancy arthouse cinemas.  Comfy leather seats and everything. Would recommend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redknightnz81 and the last thing I need when I'm trying to get all the M&amp;Ms in my mouth is to focus on the movie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just seen the movie Arrival. Really good. Requires a bit of thinking tho or it'll be a mindfuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzBrowncoat @Spintires @OoveeGames @PlayStationEU its prob a lot cheaper on steam too. Always able to find it on sale somewhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzBrowncoat @Spintires @OoveeGames @PlayStationEU haven't tried with controller. Just keyboard. Will check when home on 28th]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzBrowncoat @Spintires @OoveeGames @PlayStationEU I have the PC version. Very very technical]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Porirua station coffee shop do an awesome (sugary lol) hot chocolate and their banana choc chip muffins are yummm too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bonus: Getting emergency exit row seat I flight (extra leg room) free. Bummer: Announced 30 min delay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like steam is being crushed with people looking for xmas deals..... like me :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Warped_Sanddog sheesh -15.5 is cold. Cool picture too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GRID is free for a limited time on https://t.co/2ss1OEQPeT https://t.co/bcdSoTJqvL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[little wibble woblle there #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That sugary caramel frosty shake sure kickstarts the heart after skipping a beat with the burger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just started a new magic act with Baconators. Put one in front of me and it magically disappears.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Warped_Sanddog getting a white christmas over there?  It is damned hot &amp; humid summer Xmas here.  Happy Xmas &amp; New Year to you and family.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RadishNation Cheers to you bro. Wishing you and family a happy Xmas and New Year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to have a haircut before visiting the relatives at xmas time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well the last TDU was decent enough. Hopefully they pass it onto worthwhile dev house. But against Forza Horizon wh… https://t.co/vvYyH5UahH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. It's been 5 years since Jason Richards passed away due to cancer. #cancersucks https://t.co/lhlGC1SuVD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome news for #WRC being on #redbulltv free to watch (hopefully everywhere) some of it even live woooooo https://t.co/QRyrxdKwWw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.... quakes started again #eqnz.  Decent rumble then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching first episode of 3 percent at the moment. Seems ok so far.  Reading subs is hard tho :( waaaaa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[most of the tv shows I like are on a mid-season break :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlancpainGT do you know why the #Sepang12hr youtube videos are geo-blocked in New Zealand (and guessing other countries)?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I completed the game DUCATI - 90th Anniversary https://t.co/ibiST1I2Qp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Morgadeth @Steam_Support I get that sometimes when can't connect &amp; Retry. It just hangs on making connection dialog, so I just kill it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So they are rebooting "The Mummy" franchise.... with Tom Cruise in the lead role.  As if the originals weren't bad enough......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Third time completing this game after X360 and GfWL versions...... https://t.co/pvlWo1BNlk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I completed the game DiRT 3 Complete Edition https://t.co/hQoU9t6xeM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mirinda (orange &amp; raspberry flavours) is back on sale here in NZ - I'm prob late in noticing lol - wooooo more sugary drinks for summer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzBrowncoat youtube stream here https://t.co/nQEaTs8UsZ starts at 2.30 fri afternoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone used powerline internet adaptors? Keen to get rid of wireless and since renting not allowed to cable in the walls lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone else up for the #F1 finale?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was a violent jolt right then #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TheGrandTour is a great show.  Recommend watching it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@windowsstore All it looks to do is pull videos from @youtube as well. Such a dodgy developer. Should be removed off the store ASAP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems legit for $325.00 .... some people are real ****s.  Has an NFS one for $1000+ too. Reported to @windowsstore https://t.co/XEMX7l2i9c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In case anyone that follows me is interested.. PS4 version of Battleborn for under 4GBP (7NZD) excl shipping. https://t.co/QMiPYJldH3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I completed the game Motorama https://t.co/1U0a9AljjH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Decent little rumble a few mins ago.  It had been a while since felt an aftershock.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzBrowncoat @NetflixANZ you may be getting older, but the women stay the same age #yeahbaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I reached a new #TrueSteamAchievement Milestone: Completion Percentage of 55% https://t.co/n3SdV6SQX5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cars 3 teaser trailer is pretty dark.... https://t.co/wnrfqwKhZG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well hello friendly cat which isn't mine (or any of flatmates) https://t.co/IxOb6cxoYN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sheeeezus that was a huge crash at Macau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I have to evac due to the quakes this summer, you all better be able to handle my pasty white man titties.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SparkyNZ I swear I sometimes feel phantom shakes..... everytime I hear a creak I brace myself in case it is that start of "the big one"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done to @HaydenPaddon and @JKCoDriver doing NZ proud on the global motorsport scene. Onwards &amp; upwards for '17 WRC with @HMSGOfficial]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Multi monitor setup in windows? use winkey+shift and arrow keys to move active program between screens. Sooooo happy I know this now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rain has started again. Wooooo! Just what we need more of.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those breakaway controller cables too. Soo many accidents avoided #15YearsOfXbox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I preferred the original controller too #15YearsOfXbox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Playing RalliSport Challenge for the first time with custom soundtrack playing #15YearsOfXbox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still rolling a little.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was a pretty decent rolling quake aftershock #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I reached a new #TrueSteamAchievement Milestone: 1,250 Achievements Won https://t.co/n3SdV7arOD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think I'm starting to get motion sickness from all these aftershocks....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could the SimMayor of New Zealand please stop mashing the Earthquake Natural Disaster button. Please! #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was a pretty decent aftershock #eqnz..... still rolling a little too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Original quake revised from 7.6 down to 6.6 now back to 7.5 #eqnz https://t.co/a4aHCoH5k5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[tsunami warning from civil defense for all southern coasts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bloody hell... all these damned aftershocks]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>