<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@cerysmees is this instagram??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went to go get cat food earlier, came back with Â£80 worth of clothes and no cat food]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuming when u put a tv show on and it's just starting the adverts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why doesn't my cat listen to me?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do u become skinny in a day? Asking for a friend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does anyone want to do my shift or my life for me? #notakebacksies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zoe_curry what happened?x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I rather be shiny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need food and compliments]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to live in a world where sleep earns you money and dominos makes you skinny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally got my new phone! ðŸ‘ŠðŸ»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I THINK I BROKE MY FOOT AGAIN ASDFFHJDKDBS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When @cerysmees gets ID'd for a can of Pepsi Max ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*whispers* come over and sing Your Man by Josh Turner to me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boys are rly starting to piss me off now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's so hard to sit still when gasolina starts playing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My friend who is terrified of clowns is dressing up as a clown for Halloween hoping the other clowns won't get her]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unlucky update no. 182638: I LOST MY BANK CARD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's October 3rd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I managed to singe my eyebrows and superglue my sock to my foot both in the same week. Please don't ask how as I'm not quite sure myself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder how a modern version of the cha cha slide would go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Funny that some women can get grossed out by the smallest things yet don't think twice about leaving their jam rags on pub toilet floors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phresh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm finding it hard to get used to iOS 10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Autumn body it is then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder what it's like to be financially stable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The more famous you are the bigger your sunglasses??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The train conductor just caught me taking a selfie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm bored and can't stop eating Doritos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can u retweet yourself now?Â¿]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like I look better without my glasses on but then I can't see as well without them so maybe that's the problem #hmmm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you ever feel like you chew too loudly?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onmybay My reply would've been faster but I really struggled to spell sophisticated]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onmybay normally a meatball one but I can't eat that in a sophisticated manner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is everyone going on holiday/doing something different and I'm here just going to work and subway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a customer in work who keeps grinding his teeth very loudly and I'm so close to handing in my notice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When someone orders you some chicken but doesn't actually pay for it. Can't trust anyone these days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is there always one sock missing????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday in work a customer called me his 'favourite pair of tits.' Yh Nicole would've worked too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone do my washing for me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tinder should have video so I can see mans sick vape tricks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a large forehead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Your favourite past time of watching netflix and drinking half a bottle of wine goes from really lonely and sad to quality time with bae"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can I have a try again option pls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ezria tho #pll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know I can trust my new phone case because I can't seem to get the fucker off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too fat for shorts, too warm to leave the house and get some exercise - struggle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excuse me while I go step off a cliff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm already sick of this Pokemon game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're born with a face like this you kinda have to be really into makeup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy 19th and a half birthday to meðŸŽ‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Benefit did my eyes and eyebrows and I've never felt more flawless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me on my 19th and a half birthday  https://t.co/APrjIBvdAb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best out of 3?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blue wine???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MY NEW PHONE IS HERE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't even think I can pronounce my last name properly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone on the bus has farted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder how I'm going to lose this one lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fast internet, good quality selfies, nice looking layout #blessed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just ordered a new phone!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do people catfish when they can play sims]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ChubRoll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['I'm a breathing expert']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It ain't even hot tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People keep using my head to 'warm up their hands']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wasting 10 minutes trying to take a selfie for such a simple snapchat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walking around Cardiff with my top inside out like the marvellous pleb I was born to be]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like such a dick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This illness has brought my mood so down these past couple of days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been so clumsy lately, my legs are almost covered in bruises]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just had the strangest phone call in work
Random number: Hello how are you? 
Me: I'm good thanks
Random number: that's great, okay bye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm tweeting so it looks like I'm talking to someone instead of standing on my own like a muppet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm wasting my phone battery]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opening a can on the bus is not as discreet as you think when you have headphones in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just said something in a really weird and high pitched way, now it keeps repeating in my head and I hate who I am as a person]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any more bad luck heading my way??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like McDonalds are really trying to prove that their food is real lately]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zoe_curry this is legit what I was thinking the other day when on the bus https://t.co/XQfBcvG778]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And I'm back to square one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is it so hard to wash a bloody sieve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is a big no from me :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cerysmees This look though :'(( https://t.co/XDIHgGZyRJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was not ready for that latest episode of @OnceABC, Legit blubbering like a baby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do I keep eating Chinese food]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abigailsuch is that what I think it is?ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want a hug and a winge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah this ain't fun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abigailsuch being on top]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think that guinea pigs are the only animals that can poo on me and I'll still find them cute ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only in my ear though, I'm not that mental]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eye Candy is good but some of the acting is awful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Lady Boys of Bangkok were amazing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onmybay I'm on a budget!ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onmybay I can probably afford lots of cheese burgers tho, then you'll be jealous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Less than Â£10 in my account and it's monday #someonehireme]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't decide if I want to do something productive today or just lay in bed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onmybay um where's my follow back???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone put me down]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>