<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[It's hard to leave a job when next person changes everything &amp; makes mess.Obama's a much better person than me.Must be so hard to step away]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was just a little bit looking forward to a cuppa and some @BLACKCAPS action during toddler naptime...#rainraingoaway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guess school's back. My FB feed is full of photos of school children #bless #thisold]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzpost unfortunately not what I was told late last year. Seems there may be some confusion....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzpost so this means only within same city? 'You can change your delivery address to another location, while your parcel is on its way']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seekjobsnz thank you youre helping with my feelings of despondency!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seekjobsnz wow what a cool job...think I could invent wine and beer experience...!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seekjobsnz marketing role in Queenstown. Pref Mktg Mgr #hensteeth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seekjobsnz I wish you had 'tell us how amazing you are in Twitter characters &amp; we'll find a job for you' #queenstowndreaming]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lost to today's wind sanity, humour and my toddlers hat....the hat could be in Auckland by now I'm sure my sanity and humour will return]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a day ending in day and it's windy...must be summer. That's how low expectations are!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rawsoncj @Geekpulp I agree. What were you thinking seriously...!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone out there looking for a great NZ experience w ample fresh air do the #otagorailtrail Hurts the bottom but so worth it #nearlyhalfway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow now 7 working days 13 days and still no update on my 'courier'. Thanks @nzpost your service is quite special even at this time of year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to all the patient, courteous drivers between Feilding &amp; Alexandra since Weds. Restored my faith in driving #windyroads #allsafe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm trying to be calm and xmassie but seriously 6 days for a courier within N Island. 2 days for 20kms &amp; still no sign #busytimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KalistaCampbell wow that is so cool #yayyou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was too excited about throwing my new nerf during dinner to photograph sorry tweeps. Thank you #nzsecretsanta &amp; the choccies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KylieBrooks81 it's all about the giving at this time of year....hee hee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are still many many good people in this world and esp NZ. #nzsecretsanta is proof]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish the #nzaa were on Twitter then I could implore them to be Christmasy and grant me a new member wish #goodcheer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The suspense of waiting for receiver to get their #nzsecretsanta while waiting to not be home alone to open mine https://t.co/L0Uav3RD7Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amateur mistake hubby. Didn't log out of @TradeMe so now I can see what auctions he's been watching #pressies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This high school yearbook blackmail is disgusting. Son finished school,no exams,signed out early to start fulltime job no yearbook for you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KalistaCampbell I hear you last time I tried the wheels were quicker than I remember and I broke my elbow #ouch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good turn done for the day. Found a discarded wallet under some bushes on way to Santa cave. Handed in to the @nzpolice to reunite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How am I supposed to pay for using the tauranga toll road when the online system to pay it is down....@NZTA? #timesticking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh I can't wait to get my gift wrapping done all saucy like by the Loins #badtypo #PNPlaza https://t.co/bCfvlHucxu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go the @BLACKCAPS sadly I favour sleep right now but I'm hoping to wake to a lovely win #summersport #ausvnz #chappellhadlee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eloquentsonia @KylieBrooks81 28 pages for a Saturday paper is tragic #whybother]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How hard is it to work out we get a @DomPost not a @ManawatuNZ Oh well it'll only take 5 minutes to read the whole paper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Better stop procrastinating and get movin on my @nzsecretsanta #goodelf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope you've had a terrific day today @KalistaCampbell #HB2U #hiphiphurray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right off I go for a peaceful shake and rattle free night...and a little Miss who again sleeps until 8am #fingerscrossed #tiredhouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's the 1st one I've felt today. It's really not fun when you're home alone with a sleeping bubba #eqnz #nervesshot #noisydoors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Geekpulp @KalistaCampbell I just hope those near the centre are okay. Josh and I still I see the doors!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KalistaCampbell @Geekpulp awake too the Young family!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KalistaCampbell nice to see someone else freaking out...we're all awake except for Sienna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would the earth please stop moving now. Starting to feel like vertigo #eqnz #shaky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[15 mins of stand up instead of 7 days @JeremyCorbett He's doing ok there's laughter in the room #nailingpalmy https://t.co/j86Gd4SEof]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rocking the #manawatubusinessawards tonight. Adding some colour to proceedings of I may say so https://t.co/FywoNpAKuT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’ve just signed up for awesomeness at #nzsecretsanta. Love it!! https://t.co/m2Ywr4RUat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is very frightening....#electionnight Surely it's only the early counts favouring Trump...Surely...please no]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here you go @rawsoncj 😊 https://t.co/gim74buTjC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rawsoncj I trust you voted then...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How are you feeling @sarjanehughes? #nervous #excited It's a big day!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Checked with fam whether I'm too precious but apparently not...no need for @skysportnz to advertise UFC during ABs game #enoughviolence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rachoconnor probably when you move somewhere more tropical....lovely in feilding!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's only when travelling on other unnamed airlines that you realise it's the little things that make @FlyAirNZ so good #nexttime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#1stworld #mummaproblems what to do when another child not only blatantly pushes your child over in a pool but also her friend? #youngbully]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AllBlacks wish we'd been able to watch last ABvAUS game online....Oh well never mind #overitnow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've voted for #Perenara in the IRPA Try of the Year award 2016
https://t.co/71t2iPtwTu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been hanging out for dessert all week in KL so thought a milo roti would do the trick #whenindoas #localfood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HamishMacaulay they look horrendous!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LydiaKo crazy hot here as a tourist let alone playing sport! Good luck out there!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If they say they're genuine Gucci baby shoes who I am to disbelieve #kualalumpur #markets #shopping]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing beats the giggles from Miss 19months as we fed ostriches in ridiculous heat today at #kualalumpurs bird park #heartsmelting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KylieBrooks81 on no. That sounds grotty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gutted having to 'watch' @allblacks via twitter from Malaysia Cant find an online watch to save myself  #loyal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow @ANZ_NZ you could have not been more unhelpful. 5 days to get foreign currency 200km up the road. You underwhelm me #poor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do I really have to wait up until 10pm tonight to watch the @SilverFernsNZ in action!? #bedtime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MAS is it possible to take our hopefully sleeping toddler in her buggy all the way to the gate? Travelling AKL to KL #thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyanLSimpson @OtagoRugbyTeam  @sumostevenson I assumed they were trialling the new concussion testing technology....?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's also a shame that schools are driven by credits not getting kids into the right option for them #biggerpicture @NigelLatta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving the thought provoking programme tonight @NigelLatta Plenty for young people to think about, shame they wont be watching... #apathy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AirNZFairy @WetaWorkshop oh man am I too late?! My husband is a major fan I would be upgraded to amazing side status of I took him to this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vodafoneNZ how much are the Fuji prints in the app featured in today's email? #thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Safe to say we'll have crackling tonight after little Missy turned the oven to 260 fan grill #whatsthesmell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So if @juliansavea7 is on 43 tries now who is ahead of him? Any chance the commentators can tell us @skysportnz @AllBlacks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlyBuysNZ I'd love to but I'm not getting that option...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sounds a bit sap but I loved your #cue top tonight @ToniStreet Could I rock it around home with Miss Toddler tho #grubbyhands]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day old tiramisu cake.  Come to me!! #yummygoodness #healthkick #domesticgoddess https://t.co/U7fBnJxe7q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good 1 @FlyBuysNZ. I travel 20km to pick up my reward to be told it's out of stock. Great experience...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Much much better post match @skysportnz  Entertaining &amp; actually funny. Thanks @JamesMcOnie @sumostevenson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring it on!! Let's go @AllBlacks #gametime #wine #snacks https://t.co/s4Gj87q9cO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's many who think they're seriously under-funded but I suspect @jono_naylor you're missing a 'm' #typo #funny https://t.co/SuLanJAUl7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sewing the perfect pastime in which to be strong while willing my toddler to nap #mammamamma #notgoingsowell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TwoPaddocks trying to find your blog &amp; getting an error 'your connection is not private attackers might be trying to steal your info' #bad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I'm fairly sure they mean the book not the person...@dancarter https://t.co/hFgUFKj1LM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CasBMCarter the amusement is those who proclaim to be action oriented. It's council so very unlikely!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's past my bedtime so I really hope staying up to yell at the tv is worth it tonight #sleepy #AUSvNZL #allblacks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TwoPaddocks such a great episode. Love Saturday night CC. Can't wait to partake of some product at Xmas after doing the mighty Rail Trail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ecstatic joy from watching the new @SparkNZ twinkle twinkle tv ad #lovesit #simplethings https://t.co/BMczMbGaIF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going to watch the triumphant @BlackSticks quarter final. So much easier when I know the result #victorious #Rio2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And again today @NZStuffEditors trying to read Olympics news and getting access denied. I'm off to @nzherald you're rubbish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I give up on the news for tonight. Every link I click takes me to a 404 page @NZStuff @NZStuffEditors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So gutted for the men's @BlackSticks Did us proud though @Rio2016 #robbed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow it makes you proud of all the kiwi Olympic athletes but seriously how amazing are the @kiwipair Years of hard work, such legends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel all warm and fuzzy about Fiji winning the #7s #Rio2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Council candidates, stop humouring us by using words like action and energy...you're running for council #noaction]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seekjobsnz do you think some advertisers ignore appns using the apply button if there's wording to say contact blah by email?#noreply]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pushing the buggy walking the dog drinking coffee trying to catch updates of the #Rio2016 #7s final]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I swear Aussie sportsgirls get lessons in making their hair pretty and the use of ribbons #Rio2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brgibson11 @MorePho you'll need to in tonight definitely #5degrees]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eloquentsonia it's disgusting and totally disrespectful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eloquentsonia totally agree. Elder abuse is akin to child abuse in my book]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love it when they say how long your overseas delivery will be then you hear the box hitting front door step over a week early #wearingthem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats on a great 1st season with the @Highlanders @greg_pleasants You haven't converted your uncle yet...who knows for next season!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Highlanders so exciting. Not so exciting to make me lose sleep but that's why we have #mysky #getup #loyal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And for today, thank you my timing was impeccable #watchingrain #torrential https://t.co/lRnBAc0na2]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>