<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@mohraqeeb Sure seems that way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OOrpington The industry blamed the over-parity impossibly high aussie dollar. (Lower wages couldn't save auto, unless below min wage)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheMurdochTimes I am sure there was personal coaching on how to tell so many untruths that truth no longer has currency. Abbott then Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HomeOfGastro I'm all for healthy food but this is a worthy breach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CenterForBioDiv @barbvee Of course he would because Christians think animals have no soul so therefore are disposable. So cut funding.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RoosterRoss I wondered who that slimy airhead was on the drum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sydney rents have gone ballistic. Hmm wasn't that only meant to happen with negative gearing reform? We've been tricked by #LNP again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RorNotRed Good idea Dutton, Turnbull, Morrison to start with]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Multiple severe domestic attacks and lawyers think he's harmless! Need to get head out of books into the real world]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump ban based on nationality, even if they can prove no terror connections. But he'll accept 1250 from Turnbull as a buddy. #hypocritical]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Trump’s Rode vs Wade rhetoric wasn't rhetoric. Now women will lose authority over their own bodies. Don't let it happen in Australia!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smh Land Titles Registy shouldn't be a profit making machine! It's milking taxpayers and should be streamlined, not sold!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull: "continue their mindless rush into renewables". As if that's not a virtuous pursuit! Turnbulls head needs rewiring! #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LarryShort777 @Alex_Medley13 @TeaPainUSA And Trump will be influenced by family business, read this, from December: https://t.co/2HMbvQM5LK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WilliamsCodex I remember Kenny Everett video show but not the kit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tedlieu @politico Trump promised to pull out of Korea. Everyone thought it was rhetoric but when he does,there begins the nuclear arms race]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamiaw @motherboard Goodness me! It's obvious with this at his disposal it was impossible for Trump to lose. Explains his confidence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulineHansonOz Like Turnbull’s non existent jobs and growth: she'll wish for it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@susanamet Someone explain to George what a human is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billshortenmp Turnbull doesn't act, he procrastinates. He'll ask Gladys to release land in SYD but nothing except more debt will be written]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkDiStef Paulf Handjob deliberately disrespected these entire countries with deliberate misspellings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelhallida4 Only $100B of carnage #NBN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelhallida4 Can't compete with grumpy cat https://t.co/0fTf8csYav]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bishop64 @michaelhallida4 But that's actually useful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@james00000001 Hey Trump, you're not making the place safer, mate!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our regime of making life difficult for women is actually brutal bullying, forced religious views 

https://t.co/xPBynJNaUa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrimeVideoAU I'm doing a long flight next week, will report back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrigidMullane @guardian I hope she converted it to Mansplain so Trump could understand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrigidMullane @amagickeagle999 For anyone thinking that Julie Bishop is a moderate, potential leader for LNP, be warned!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mavsmum @AAAopinion @elliemail @virgotweet @Telstra Our LNP Gov't has demonstrated over and over that our privacy is worthless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If terrorism on USA soil is almost zero, isn't it possible that Trump’s disrespect of 7 nationalities could actually make the risk higher?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkHarrisNYC We learn lessons from history. Erasing that memory would mean having another holocaust in the future!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[/2 is to bring some supply of housing on the market by greedy negative gearers losing their low tax status]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Alexander revealed LNP'S nasty secret on housing affordability: it will force those with many properties to sell a few... WHAT'S NEEDED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@guytaur @afneil And many other innovators. Like Nikola Tesla, who invented the modern electricity system, turbines, fluorescent lights etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's 90 day ban of 7 countries will have lasting effect: his disrespect of their nationality will be always remembered and reciprocated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@harbinger Any publicity good publicity?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomKingTK @DonnieTheCon Most of the ME whistle blowers are now locked out of the USA. Trump not too smart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday I bought business shirts and ties from David Jones. Worth giving a plug as the 2 staff were amazingly helpful, more than expected]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kon__K @timpoliti I want to know what Trump is gaining from this deal. If nothing, then he'll expect a favour back, big time!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyNewsAust @terrimbutler Finally ALP is reforming policy! Please tell Shorten]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshrogin @elizgw @benjaminwittes Now I see who the jobs Trump will create are for: Law school graduates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wombat_wood @FoxNews @KellyannePolls @realDonaldTrump Play that video to the 100 people who couldn't board flights due to their nationality]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jess4_RK @wombat_wood That’s a desperate way for Trump to use his personal money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Refugee: "Where shall we go now USA closed?". Answer: USA via Australia; Turnbull's sending them there soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshButler Cool, will check out Lyft. Any other Uber replacements?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NTarnopolsky What others? The deaf people that Hitler used when developing the gas chambers? RIP to all affected but don't deny Jews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone PLEASE EXPLAIN to me how Pauline banning immigration helps primary producers and regional Australia. It's not jobs so what benefit?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZipZapPS4 Ha ha jokes aside, asylum seekers would love to move to the USA. Even with Trump it is destination number one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dazza50 @MeckeringBoy @digthatjive I'd love to know what's in it for Trump!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MeckeringBoy @digthatjive OK so settling them in the USA won't encourage people smugglers but in AU it will? This is flawed LNP logic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GhostOfPJK @madbb2015 Fake or not, I bet you won't see it on Fox! (although it is actually on https://t.co/vlPBuR3JXs)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcialangton @theage God only knows why white sauce and salad dressing require nano particles! Don't want any supermarket food!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nettythe1st I'm surprised Trump knows Austria is next to Germany. Being landlocked and small, it's pretty similar to Australia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Miridunn they couldn't find the like button]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@broomstick33 @colleenhm @darlingcat @billshortenmp Bringing existing doesn't help people smugglers - new arrivals are still turned back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mercola @rupafitz I don't want Glyphosate in my cell membranes. But I want it even less in the kid's cell membranes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OrBVIOUS66 @GayCarBoys Ha ha hopefully not too long for us. I'm not yet able to detach from city-based job, but working on making portable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NanaWithSoul @fuertecorazon @GOP @CBS Trump will spend up big, increase debt, but the amount of jobs probably following Obama’s trajectory.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fuertecorazon Anti-west focus will move from Israel to the USA. Risky business]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealMuckmaker @WSJ Trump abandoned allies, vets, shows his true colors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GayCarBoys Yeah would be great to setup a community with actual values. "Value Migration" may become a thing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darlingcat @billshortenmp +There is no v argument against resettling the existing ones here. I'm sick of the mental torture and money waste]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GayCarBoys @leftocentre That’s my long term plan, move way north of SYD, get solar panels etc. May have to bring forward!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrimeVideoAU I downloaded it to my phone to watch on the plane. So far I like the content, hope you add more over next 6 months while cheap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billshortenmp Bill I like the positive message. Last election you hinted maybe down the track we'll bring existing detainees here. It's now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GaryFallon2 Fossil fuel subsidies I don't think will ever go because is used by primary producers. I prefer to focus on renewable energy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're genuinely, I mean really truly, concerned about AU national debt, then you will strongly advocate to remove negative gearing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnWren1950 @kyotojoe1 @ScottMorrisonMP @theage The LNP politicians know stopping neggearing solves housing affordability. They ignore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@voltscommissar Absolutely! Strategy 1: reduce x so even x supporters lose interest; defund x. 2: defund by 80%, refund by 20%, take credit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yashar @kBHZUDGUZ63wQPM @JoyAnnReid Brilliant explanation. If only we could somehow convince the Trump voters to watch this video!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MGliksmanMDPhD @fos57 @POTUS Yes I'm terrified because I can imagine the consequences and can see it is obvious that many others don't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProfBrianCox There goes any near term hope for nuclear fusion power. #brexit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenSanders @MrDenmore Trump has sown the seed and turned the faucet of disrespect to full, for massive numbers of home grown terrorists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRealNews @auntytrue Two egos against the entire world]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BillBillshaw @kcarruthers @adrianctate @Onision @jimwaterson nah not with American way - it's illogical. It's when listing lots of dates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@craigthomler @engadget Will probably cause problems for cloud computing systems. Trump, President Reckless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeterPyke Housing affordability is easier to fix by curbing negative gearing than by massive supply in outer suburbs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GuardianAus @guardian So the USA doesn't need the 5% of their doctors because they are Muslim? What a ugly world we're shaping]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BillBillshaw @kcarruthers @adrianctate @Onision @jimwaterson I prefer years first so it sorts properly. I think we'd get used to it quickly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CFMEU @theheraldsun TPP without the USA and Japan isn't TPP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realgolden1 @guardian And yet conservatives think their backwards mentality saves money! #LNP creating debt while achieving nothing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History will not be kind to Donald Trump when his biggest achievement was to build a wall. Boat factories will be the beneficiaries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicholaskitchel As if the USA needs more Christians! More intolerance, more division more disrespect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kcarruthers @adrianctate @Onision @jimwaterson Yes I'd love that. For one thing it sorts logically in a spreadsheet or text editor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@treboreuk @jimwaterson @johnmerro1 The Yanks think they invented aluminium because they have produced most of it, thanks to cheap power]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimwaterson Why not use the format 28-Jan-2017? Even non-English speakers can figure it out!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suelynne12 @brucerossbrc Surely there was a better qualified candidate like a wine maker in the wonderful Margaret River district!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump drained the swamp and Mike Pence emerged. Yet another career politician. Back to square one!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Malarndirri19 ABC emergency services is a core responsibility. The Gov't is being irresponsible allowing Guthrie to destroy it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bhojanio @AzureMedia @washingtonpost Very powerful story]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Honeputu I haven't heard of it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wef Wise advice!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, those giant roosters!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elliemail @nanna68 @guardian The ABC must maintain emergency broadcast services. It's a core responsibility!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has it occurred to anyone that Trump’s risky policies could actually REDUCE jobs? He plans to raise debt so this is #debtfornothing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hellbrat @UnitedAussies @KikAlario @iamakrean @australianpeop Hey Turnbull we're still waiting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's #TwitterDiplomacy with Mexico is a fucking joke #fuckingwall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LawyerRogelio @RogueNASA @ActualEPAFacts @AltForestServ @AltNatParkSer Thank you for the genuine links]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McnairMira @JulianRoepcke I'd prefer building bridges over walls]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>