<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gingerheaddad that was a fantastic sketch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChloeMugg that's how I start my mornings.  She's the Booger queen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChloeMugg that's hard. Hope his breaks soon and the baby doesn't suffer too poorly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChloeMugg holy crap! B had fevers that high with roseola]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChloeMugg my uncle is a newf so I'm partially fluent ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChloeMugg oh is he related to my husband?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChloeMugg advil and tylenol.....stay hydrated]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How quiet would my feed be if I muted everyone who mentions or RT something about Trump?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@tdsb I emailed the school 3 weeks ago and still no response.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can someone tell me if there are open house days BEFORE registering for JK 2017? @tdsb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChloeMugg he sounds perfect for the long haul. I'm glad you can count on hi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I power cleaned the bathroom floor. Porous tile grout is horrible for a bathroom. Vinegar &amp; baking soda makes a satisfying fizz.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lizbeth_City mine give me a few hours at most. Though I get wicked nightmares if they hit in the night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lizbeth_City @Sher_Khan I woke up with one in the night through to this morning but I think it was dehydration more than anything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pregnantwhiner I give a lecture that it wasn't made easily. I worked hard!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are proudly one of this number!  Baby Z was born in the Cedar Room! https://t.co/aPieDngvc5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kainin shut up.  That means I'm *that* much closer to 35.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChloeMugg oh that's horrible poor bub.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChloeMugg saline drops don't help? I have to clear Z daily]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow is Groundhog Day. It's my favourite holiday!  #seriously]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kainin you mean a car out Baci?

I'll see myself out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shawnmicallef "cholera flaps" is my new favourite phrase.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In non political news: Baby Z gave her first laugh out loud. Full belly baby giggle!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My beautiful blue teapot has a fatal crack. #teadrinker 
Guess I can repurpose it as flowerpot and still enjoy it.… https://t.co/F1fsSUia0i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@filmcraft_ check Craigslist for some? Maybe they can be cheaply replaced?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That satisfying feeling when the kitchen is clean and the coffee is hot. #domesticbliss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's 3 months old. Growing like a weed. She's pushing 17 pounds! #hipdysplasia #pavlikharness https://t.co/jvKsKBP6SE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lizbeth_City booooo switch pharmacy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Halfway through Baby Z's #pavlikharness! Six more weeks to go! #hipdysplasia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChloeMugg and my husband reminds me of this fact when I get down on myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChloeMugg this was me for sure last time. And the first shrink wanted me to supplement and start solids at 4m When I said no she berated me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lizbeth_City past 2 days have had low pressure so we've felt sluggish. Maybe that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emiiilyt she's almost half way through. Doing amazing should be out in 6 weeks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PialiRoy meds. Therapy and supportive family and friends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheresaPolyakov we are still deciding between the tcdsb Ukrainian extended day or tdsb french immersion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the second time I've had postpartum depression.  This is the second time I'll fight it and win. #BellLetsTalk #endthestigma #ppd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know what's amazing? OHIP covered therapy &amp; health insurance for the meds I need to beat postpartum depression. #BellLetsTalk #ppd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well baby Z has passed the weight limit on the bassinet....probably over a week ago. So off it goes. Now just the baby jail.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LanieLou57 what's on your rocking chairs?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Cloudy with a Chance of Meatballs 2" is essentially "Jurassic Park 2".... I clearly watch too much Netflix. #breastfeeding]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChloeMugg meds and therapy. #PPD 2nd time. Hit harder and faster this time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChloeMugg this was me exactly this time too. Felt I ruined big brother's life.... hugs #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Postpartum Depression can hit hard and fast. Don't suffer in silence. #ppd  #BellLetsTalk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My tea devotion started early.... this tea set had plates and cutlery too. #teadrinker https://t.co/quYPAI5ayF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If James Earl Jones does voices for both Mufasa and Darth Vader... does that make Simba a Jedi? #StarWars #Disney #NerdParent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kainin @L0Litsmonica and then you're stuck forever with me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@goldsounder @renbostelaar I think this is the case. Verified accounts have an option the rest of us don't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My husband irrationally hates my current snapchat filter obsession. No sense of the ha ha.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChloeMugg if it means we get to hear your accent....then Yes By!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChloeMugg now that's a big mess. ...but aren't you frozen solid now in your area? ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChloeMugg it's a dry mess. He didn't fall off the counter....the baby didn't get a taste.... #brightside]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IanConway last time I encountered her she made not so subtle racist comments of the "help our own first" variety.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone said my daughter's name is "unique" through pursed lips and scrunched nose... I know what that's code for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lizbeth_City found it! On the app it's under settings &gt; display &amp;sound &gt; accessibility]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lizbeth_City thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lizbeth_City where would we find that function?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kainin and diabetes. That heart is full of diabetes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Used it a few too many times.... https://t.co/STFvse9X4m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tried a smoked butterscotch latte from s'bucks and was disappointed especially when I reached the bottom where all the syrup settled.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hip Clinic Day! Baby Z isprogressing amazingly; gets an hour out a day now. Yay bathing! #hipdysplasia… https://t.co/Rh27sR54Lp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kainin if you survive it you're doing better than him? Most historic year?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kainin it's your "Jesus Year"!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went through my Amazon wishlist and found shows I was going to buy my mom. Grief pops up from the most innocent endeavors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dude from the @CCSGTA knocked on our door. Said not interested, he said wasn't asking for anything. Just sharing info. THEN asked for $$]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight was the first time in 12 weeks I had an hour completely to myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emiiilyt time to change the password?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lizbeth_City darn. Today is a take out kinda day. Or soup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three separate EB subway delays on my way to an appt this morning. I'm so glad I don't take the subway regularly. Super crowded too. #ttc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lizbeth_City it was super icy this morning. Put makeup on and order takeout....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is great news for ON. It helped us so much to have unlimited time with my mother in the end at the hospital in… https://t.co/qArCYcEjYz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a thin, slippery glaze of ice on everything. Commute safely!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That moment when you read a "5 signs" list and realize you're surrounded....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish sellers on Craigslist would learn the meaning of "mint condition". You can't call it both mint AND gently used.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lizbeth_City I've learned "to code" is a far cry from "useful".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no teapot emoji!?!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In #GameOfThrones where is the Red Waste filmed? #GoT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baby Z has started showing teething signs. Only Elvis and rubbing her gums make her happy. #sendcaffeine #andsnacks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may stop buying dystopian novels to focus on the daily news.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daisyJD that's adorable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Antivax dude gets the job.... we may need to delay any trips south of the 49th until after Baby Z is done her full vax schedule.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kainin triple threat!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baby Z settles down for music. She likes Elvis! #BurningLove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kainin but you have never bragged about an umbrella!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kainin bets on how long it takes for you to forget it on transit?

I'm guessing 3 months.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lizbeth_City I'm just starting out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lizbeth_City actually more than one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lizbeth_City which one? I just started watching and I've seen problematic one already]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eating cake and drinking coffee for breakfast.  This is how you adult right?!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kainin drive safe. It's snowing pretty steady here too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrtimlong @annetdonahue @BrentButt and like a good kid in tried to give back the money because I thought it was accidentally in there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrtimlong @annetdonahue @BrentButt I almost choked on a dime covered in wax paper....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmilyBat it was pretty decent until the boat slammed into the port. Then it jumped the shark.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adamed both.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annetdonahue my friend did but they were Persian.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChloeMugg it's not a wastebif it makes you feel better for the rest of the day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmilyBat I'll rewatch it and let you know...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmilyBat I remember seeing it in theatre because it was super hot out and my friends and I wanted ac....I don't remember despising it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vandamir she looks like the torti we had when I was a teen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vachon's Billot Log cakes are so much more magical than I remember. #fatkid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emiiilyt @Outpost_Coffee both!!!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>