<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Just in case the mayor needs to use his bike. https://t.co/35zRM83DbO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CTVVancouver @CityofVancouver What has changed since last snowfall? Nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@globaltvsports @globalnews Why not move Super Bowl to Saturday?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's next? All-day dinner? https://t.co/dJrguKJymh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Richmond_BC Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That is one giant blanket disclaimer. Don't sue. Told you already. https://t.co/1Y57YwTykf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not bad. I am as rich as a very small part of a billionaire. #PositiveThoughts https://t.co/5zAj7QH4Qh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think it is a typo. The study meant to suggest "Safer for ME to yield, not stop." https://t.co/TMbHPocuVF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ban first class on planes. Make room for more spacious seats for everyone else. https://t.co/qJUv38FsFs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A culture believing there is a recreational purpose for drugs pushes these people to death. https://t.co/iAijXbZJ5M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kudos to good neighbor. Safe and dry wide sidewalk . No ice. @Richmond_BC @TheRichmondNews Cannot say the same for… https://t.co/J15puUQFuI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We should ban comparable aesthetic procedures on human too. Those are such a waste of medical resource. https://t.co/OzvVkfCoUI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bonus time. Extra minute free of charge. https://t.co/J2zqsl64Jk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes. It is at least more important than fb-like notification. https://t.co/lrvmu8wJag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Skipping floor number 4, 13 etc in condo is confusing, too. https://t.co/ReCTqDbJu9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When in doubt, throw it out. https://t.co/PVSNoRmrRc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you. https://t.co/JABIUkdcKz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not the tracking cookies kind of cookies. https://t.co/9IlLcTW0G5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's the Canadian way. https://t.co/fAzpfmkZd3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They seems so out of place. Do not understand the allure of conflict tourism.  https://t.co/OEC2cJrbn0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wise judge. Compelling reason of judgement. Judge rules dogs should not be treated like kids https://t.co/lFkFPSPbZI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is whst happen when we surrender in the war on drug. Who are bringing the poison to the street? #bcpoli… https://t.co/AaDLp8XZ7l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shall we put horsepower restriction on #novicelicense? Or create new license class for race car? . #bcpoli https://t.co/IbLQKakImv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A healthy dose of fake news to start off the day. https://t.co/se6ZiMAcxl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We do this to improve the average wait time figure. There are still same number of grandparents waiting. #cdnpoli https://t.co/FaBT3nmPIU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More #energysaving  tips for #Christmas. Lock up the house and go visit your friends or sit in the mall. https://t.co/i6JhXrc0FY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is this happening now? There were no snow since #ALEXFRASERBRIDGE opened? https://t.co/jE8FGNReS6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...And the media is so biased. https://t.co/m22Ymk7bCt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Growing dollar by dollar. https://t.co/cfCqRzrtjY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now, see who cannot drive in snow. Montreal or Vancouver. https://t.co/XLMRfHQzSp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She is indeed one inspirational woman. She should be heard. https://t.co/C4HmBG4Nac]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CTVNews You have no photo of TD Tower? The photo shown here is not even downtown #Vancouver.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope it does not take as long as #BobDylan  response to his #Nobel win. https://t.co/BNDGrJ2beg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ubyssey Healthier than this Germany option. https://t.co/kkaDyEE47N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBCNews Just keep the ads. I don't mind the ads at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cannot argue with that. https://t.co/iZysxKC1te]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CTVVancouver @CTVNews Is it made in China?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is really an English only pronoun problem. Wait, we can just use the word 'it' instead. https://t.co/4sixU4oiuL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And taste very good too. https://t.co/9Up4872sV7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sheila_Scott What are you saying? The armed suspect was a victim of...? For a moment I thought you are referring t… https://t.co/AUriB3dmdP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insane effect of our insane scheme. https://t.co/oq8aYwWAWO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CTVNews What? They want a cruiser that looks like Fisher Price ice cream truck?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here come the 3am tweets. https://t.co/aQHFr1qOyn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CTVNews Just wait for the 3am ranting tweet from new @POTUS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best news so far tonight. https://t.co/nupSyMtgdB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lady placing large order @thaiexpress at #foodcourt. Causing long queue. Too cheap to order catering. #selfishness https://t.co/ju19qJKFDk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Age old debate. Nurses or doctors better at giving shots? And now we have pharmacists, too. https://t.co/FAK6xW1gqZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He really likes the backup camera optional feature. https://t.co/CfIDGIuIsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[W10th bike lane bad choice. #Vancouver #vanpoli https://t.co/R48qV04VLl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations! We deserve it. https://t.co/kZ2PiqOhkG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are they asylum seekers running from #TRUMP 's party? https://t.co/PC60w4sXC0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dread that this might appear in Vancouver one day. #vanre #vanpoli #bcpoli https://t.co/GSLZH93tUY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NEWS1130 My fridge's light works perfectly  when it was new, three days old and even now after 8 yrs. They tested it before delivery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Adweek @annieleibovitz The wods #Lincoln and shot in the same sentence of the tweet caught my attention.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why using a cookie photo in the article. Are those fortune cookies? https://t.co/pk3CsIMckV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@22_Minutes To #DonaldTrump supporters: It's rigged. Don't bother to come out to vote.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cbcnewsbc Why this was not covered in @VCHhealthcare initial news release? The victim has just passed away over the weekend?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bchydro Kudos to your crews working round the clock to restore power for us. Good job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interested to know what to look for when I examine purchased eggs. https://t.co/UWFwTF4Nbl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This time,  everybody knows the name. https://t.co/nK1DNlBzEP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CKNW @FionaForbes It was sort of  fine with me leaving 5pm on Sunday. Took only 8 minutes to get on 52nd Ave. Not hours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy doctors and nurses, better care to patients. https://t.co/ItCxCNNDvE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lightened up people.  Dad is new to this video editing software. https://t.co/ngH2EPw90S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me too. I wonder who did focus group research for the team. https://t.co/KPO8UScbnp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something my wife refuses to believe. https://t.co/ESwDZVJvLC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Already late Friday night in #London..@inspireleaders on #Periscope: Alex Popa busking Oxford Circus London https://t.co/4yOJ75PRxW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bchydro My dryer is unable to dry a full wash load in one cycle.. #Dilemma of stacked washer/dryer combo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Uber drivers, you are making money for them to replace you.
https://t.co/srbvJP3CuS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes. And who says all covered-up men tuxdo is not fashionable. https://t.co/na4O48IceR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's cold here. https://t.co/xZsGaVumRj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isn't that #cheesecake? https://t.co/hzDZ5MQZ34]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make sure Canada got the refund, not the MP constituency office. https://t.co/WS93ZtZtUV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thebuzzer @TransLink . Yes. Thank you. The more room the better. https://t.co/0rlvj7gCq3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CTVNews Donald cannot distinguish between a political rally and a #SNL sketch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NEWS1130Traffic @vancity_kini  From another angle. https://t.co/I9EOiiiigO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bchydro Richmond outage north of Elmbridge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CTVVancouver The rest of the body has been censored out for security reason.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sheila_Scott @CTVVancouver Good observation. The Fancy shoes are indeed a telltale sign.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fancy dress shoes set the mayor apart. https://t.co/WzgNNxfDAd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not  drug trafficking or a public health problem. It is a mass poisoning attempted murder case. https://t.co/twqtgDiFM9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ManyPeopleAreSaying the words in his foolish remarks were carefully chosen to woe foolish voters. https://t.co/qtKMrV5SZf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lot of interesting insights can come from search matrix. https://t.co/uePrlTkcmF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So the  tax is working. How many local families can afford to send children to UBC and buy a $700K condo at the same time?.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good that Ottawa has no vacancy tax. #VanRE https://t.co/6BPasSSxFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How many kids would challenge their parents tonight on #flossing. https://t.co/aCRyiYegMc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you all. So we can have good photos. https://t.co/QDSDn0WZEs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CTVNews We often laugh at NRA's logic in US gun debate. But we think in similar way when it comes to pet dogs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBCNews They shouldn't have to ask for emergency cheques. The gov't should have sent them long time ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See if Govnt allows us not paying  tax for 6 month? No pay. Public servant quits job in disgust https://t.co/Jd1VAEgqTj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But it is fun nonetheless. https://t.co/b4BPXoUqYq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmilyLazatin980 @CKNW @TransLink  When all gates are closed, we won't "forget".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could it be that democracy does not produce the best result all the time? Or is it only as good as the voters? https://t.co/lAwOLxQ9Fr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unlike in the movies, reality is not action packed 24/7. Lots of wait time in field reporting. https://t.co/HD1wVOfMcS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isn't it illegal NOT paying wages to workers on time?  And for months? https://t.co/I7cxiq8ZXm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CTVVancouver @CTVAndrew Would a supervised suicide site help, too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good that they've found common ground. https://t.co/4sWLqtbW9S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good for her. She has made this artwork comes alive. https://t.co/Q74DeekSOI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CTVNews A ban will not work as intended. Look at how well it goes with banning distracted driving, banning narcotics etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He was just marching along, not dancing, maybe? https://t.co/EQbP6IYOSs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parliament can change the lyrics of #OCanada  once more to adopt this version. https://t.co/UpnnYPqdDh]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>