<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@DebRobson3 @CrazieKatWoman @SkipLicker @exiledenglander Fuck off racist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, America. What have you done? https://t.co/zrzvXzhuwG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Divorced. Finally.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm out of here for a while. People* are shit.

*some]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CidLives1 Choices made against *all* Muslims? Like Hitler blamed all Jews?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously, some of you are fucking deranged. Fuck you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CidLives1 Fuck off, this isn't the time to blame the 'left' for violent cunts' actions. If Bush ('right') hadn't fucked up Middle East…!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_zeiram_ Fuck off you thick cunt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a fucked-up world. What utter cunts there are that would do this. Killing anyone is bad, killing those you don't know for bigotry? WTF!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've ignored news all day since I heard it this morning, concentrated on enjoying time with my kids. Now I'm sat in tears looking at story.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShakeyStephens I disagree. That's bigotry. I don't like the cunt, but that's because I know what the cunt is like.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoktorJeep Good. But I think the west and east coastlines of US tend to be more civilised. Not so much Florida, Texas, etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShakeyStephens You know enough about him. It's when you don't know someone's name but you hate them for religion, belief, colour, sexuality]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The gun-toting American 'Christian' 'right' must be confused. A Muslim killing US gays. Their heads will explode trying to find a position.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a stupid fucking world that we live in where people 'hate' people they don't even know. https://t.co/JNnZf3Tu6z https://t.co/IkzPpbH0pY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boys taken home, vodka at hand, sat writing a sales strategy presentation for work, listening to Division Bell: a normal Sunday evening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@B_4_Brad It was! Better than usual, even if I do say so myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And on the plate! https://t.co/0B1FWUoXro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And don't fall asleep at the wheel? https://t.co/kA7obxDJa4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@omotforest I was very cautious opening those!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@julieteresah Until you tread on a snail. Or worse, dog poo. :-(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sir Philip Green 'Should Lose His Knighthood' &gt;&gt; Says the man who supported the IRA? #twat https://t.co/ZMPABswOyk https://t.co/1Oe3s2ZGFp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[:-O https://t.co/NAARQF5Z6G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LapGongLeong @wallaceme Because they're making them up?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keonne I hold a libertarian summer drinks in Clerkenwell - not many are voluntaryist - but some are. July 1st, if you're interested.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I ought to get up and have a shower, but now Just A Minute has started I may just wait a while…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pmitch69 I'm 50 and still feel as stupid as I was as a teenager.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@obotheclown #foodporn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*tin-foil hat* https://t.co/JrZAzdqZsX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomhagen_ @WillMcHoebag @AuntyMartin Sometimes I do. #guiltypleasure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MortuusBestia @WillMcHoebag I do, but those are relatively minor in comparison, and most due to my choices in life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heartbreaking listening to Warwick Davis talking about his two children that died. Lying here in tears. #BBCRadio4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The hatred for 'others' prevalent on here is but the tip of the iceberg. Today people are killed for who they are or are not. And tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WillMcHoebag This is why I take the term 'check your privilege' seriously. I'm white, straight, well-paid: I don't face other's struggles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, we can always learn from Hitler: we can learn 'never trust the state' and politicians are parasitical lunatics. https://t.co/sSHC8r8CaO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WillMcHoebag @AuntyMartin I've cut him adrift, I waste too much time trying to convince bigots to open their minds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twat! How are your IRA murdering pals? https://t.co/snpLFdBXp2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@julieteresah *sniggers* I've got a great anecdote about that, but I'm not telling it on here!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol! First track is the Star Wars theme!! :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ricardo_Bald @EnglishEmma @bricklanecoffee @TripAdvisor I think you're vastly underestimating their value.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WARWICK DAVIS IS ON DESERT ISLAND DISCS! #BBCRadio4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That dog-whistle worked well. Another racist identified and kicked off my timeline.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Maxipsycho I have no problems with people criticising all religions. There's a huge correlation of islamophobes and racist cunts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Maxipsycho Mary was 13 when Joseph knocked her up, if you believe these fairy tales. Why are you following me, you racist twat?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Maxipsycho It's not: that's your interpretation, assuming you've read it (or more likely you've read and believed racist rantings).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Maxipsycho Really? So all those Imams and Koranic experts who say islamism is apostasy are lying? And those Muslims killed by Islamists?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Maxipsycho The clue is in the words "not all". I'll explain the word "all" if you need me to?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Maxipsycho How many Muslims do you know personally? Any of them show Islamist tendencies? Cut anyone's head off, have they?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Maxipsycho Is that what you're claiming? 40% of 1.3bn Muslims are Islamists? 520m Islamists?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Says @Nigel_Farage, MEP for 17 years, and the man who's stood for Westminster five times. https://t.co/bYxBHDfPhd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Emma_L_R I could feel his disappointment from here!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Maxipsycho So which statement are you challenging?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I must admit that dancing video is cool! Almost hypnotic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@almurray You'll have to narrow it down a bit if it's a politician…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juliegirling @HouseofTwits @StrongerIn Maybe @Nigel_Farage is planning to be a currency trader once UKIP has met its goal. #vestedinterest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LisaMuggeridge He's brilliant. :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PurrplePawz You like a bit of Rod, do you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Not all fans are hooligans"

"Not all Muslims are Islamists"

You cannot believe one without the other; not unless you're a hypocrite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShakeyStephens @cbascaran 50,000 *angry* people. :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*waits for all the usual accusations* https://t.co/uKfPKvz7yE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Political_fun @jameschappers Does it mention 'don't let your husband leave the kids in the pub after an afternoon boozing'?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@julieteresah a) what's wwf? b) it's not *her* again, is it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShakeyStephens @cbascaran Don't ask me, I hate soccer. I do remember it happening though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mike_Fabricant Have you voted in my #EUreferendum poll? https://t.co/FC7pv0BdS5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Lesions"? How nasty is the campaign getting?! https://t.co/ly8G74UIyy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShakeyStephens @cbascaran They've done it before!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@campbellclaret Have you voted in my #EUreferendum poll? https://t.co/FC7pv0BdS5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The second question is the killer one for me… that's how I ended up engaged in 1996… :-( https://t.co/LKzRD6TlNi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Edwina_Currie @ConservativesIN @StrongerIn @qeensdale Have you voted in my #EUreferendum online poll? https://t.co/FC7pv0BdS5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@julieteresah Don't waste it on the birds!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alternyaaphro My favourite Christmas film!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@julieteresah It's lovely! Tried it with chutney and crackers?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jedigirl33 Too late, sorry! https://t.co/jdcevqcpqh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pissing down here. Better get up and make tea &amp; coffee…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More lies and rhetoric.  https://t.co/8zMC1to43m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KarenDanczuk It's a shame that all separated parents can't get on for the sake of their kids. You're a good example.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done, lads. This stupid soccer contest could be called off… https://t.co/WWrlc4y7M7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remind me the percentage of the Brussels and Paris attackers that were non-French or non-Belgian? https://t.co/A4ZTTpGui1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching series 1 of Waking The Dead and I'm reminded just what a fantastic actor Trevor Eve is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My poor boy. He's converted to soccer in the last two years and has just learned the perpetual disappointment faced by England fans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching Grand Designs and the poor wife is being interviewed at the start of the programme with a huge bogey hanging out her nose. *boak*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pasparakis I think the arsehole is trying to make the point you think he's missing. He can fuck off, if he is. @SimonDanczuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The irony of 1066 votes isn't lost on me: the year we were really taken over from 'Europe' unlike now. #EUreferendum https://t.co/pRHtnvlE2y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And if I see that fucking annoying Deezer advert again I'm cancelling my subscription.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bloody Lloyds Bank advert. *dries tears*. Bastards. #wuss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live music at #cheshamcarnival @ Lowndes Park♡ https://t.co/gcAtJADDwj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #flypast at #cheshamcarnival @ Lowndes Park♡ https://t.co/QKWVHpgg3i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The view of the carnival in the park. #cheshamcarnival @ Lowndes Park♡ https://t.co/GCTUkLOc6Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think this lady is from Hemel Hempstead. #cheshamcarnival @… https://t.co/WXmB9xn0Z3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great sentiment from Roald Dahl. It applies to homeopathy too. @… https://t.co/NK4iaGAeD4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eldest boy in the #cheshamcarnival parade! @ Chesham High Street https://t.co/646A7ABAqi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know you're old when the police start to look younger than you!… https://t.co/zXcqlVdKan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waves to @alexhern and @MarkShaw43! #cheshamcarnival https://t.co/DKvJmdyEsg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pre-procession #selfie at #cheshamcarnival @ Chesham High Street https://t.co/plgjQYKlQr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our very own flypast for Chesham carnival. https://t.co/QaNXhPgUFw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We've had the flypast while we've been in the park, now queuing for burgers and hotdogs!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're anywhere near Chesham you should be in the park for the… https://t.co/tzrLcmxXp8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The schools of Chesham carnival parade approaches! https://t.co/Xo0AzoaZy3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just had to explain to my son that he's not on an "orange parade"… https://t.co/He1NOJaljm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matkinsj My tackle is low enough thanks!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>