<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[In case anyone wants an early idea for my Christmas present this year. https://t.co/SR20hSrllo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JezCorden no need. we all have our share of WHAAAAT! moments. I work in IT at a hospital and still balk when i see million $ projects!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JezCorden good question. I do appreciate the reasoned exchange my friend!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JezCorden what if there is that savings over time in gov expense and crime related to having the wall?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JezCorden humbly you realize that your calling the majority of the US crazy https://t.co/jBcnxZ0wQV and many other countries that do this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Casino's aren't the answer and neither is government control of the funds. Another reason for Trump-ism people are… https://t.co/CPWJ40WSzQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@waywardstrategy now I want to go fire this up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vitorgrs @GoodThings2Life yeah but that power and volume button placement makes me crazy on the xl.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[15014 launched today. Nothing to lose i guess! Here we go... https://t.co/TbfLzZTwOz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @lenovo thanks for the goody box and entertaining video. #ifixedit https://t.co/kMUAaq0cjI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gotham is back. Nice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@travpope yep, that's my plan also. Lets talk again at the next update. Hopefully about a better outcome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@travpope it seemed counter intuitive to "like" your comment. They need to have a feel your pain indicator.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoodThings2Life hard reset!? Don't have that in me today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[upgraded #950xl to 15007 and now having it reboot every 15 minutes. Any of the 10 people in the world using this device have this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @bccasteel has Jake insisted a preference yet? https://t.co/xmRGceA8rK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will get StarCraft just to load this up! https://t.co/gfT7gLqblq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You ALMOST make me want to play #RTS! https://t.co/KXto5dgfcJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The latest #WalkingDead by @telltalegames https://t.co/qZfKhAxXQQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @anitacasteel chewy needs a baby to play with! https://t.co/q2D8TsVibB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheCheekyTaurus yep I think your right. I've said "I'll wait for #Microsoft s widget" I'm done with that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @bccasteel You can now customize Cortana on Android https://t.co/18LTS5MkkC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer Submission: AAA Medical Free now used in more than 50 hospitals https://t.co/XQpRXlaoDA #EHR #Azure @mspoweruser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoodThings2Life @JezCorden whatcha playin during this marathon? I recently finished up @Titanfallgame 2 single player which was fantastic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just realizing today is a big @NFL day today! 😃 #earlychristmaspresent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas - Wayward Strategy Deserts of Kharak Giveaway. https://t.co/pHufrtujok via @bccasteel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jcollison 55 now predicted dropping to 21 tonight in #maryland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recently finished @Titanfallgame 2 single player. Any chance of more sp action?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @waywardstrategy check this out... https://t.co/SQEJW69KCe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes believe it should be an option to donate OR for sig others to benefit. https://t.co/18Sh0m9CwZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheCheekyTaurus oh sorry delayed response to loosing your contacts on outlook]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Startup Turns Video Cameras into Health Monitors https://t.co/0xJdcnCwTh via @ I'm telling you THIS is the future of monitoring! @oxehealth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheCheekyTaurus wha? Any idea what occurred?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait I got it is managing ammo resource management!? 😆]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But I want my rts to be more fps with no resource management! Well maybe I just want a fps 🤔 https://t.co/YOtgvDebNB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoodThings2Life @CarmenCrincoli criticism often says as much about the critic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finshed the single player game and enjoyed the entire experience. Great game! https://t.co/wkzW3J90TY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoodThings2Life let me guess🤔, your wife isn't on twitter!? 😆]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still get quizical looks when saying "I was listening to this book the other day..." https://t.co/gBxpguCZsl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I listen more than I read and believe it's the modern way to ingest content but no, not the same thing. https://t.co/EIklqcUx1H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Healthtechtalkn any new episodes coming soon?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's with pushing all the #rts stuff dude? I tried to raise you on #shooters ! 😄  https://t.co/lSED7bauEH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not what was said padre... https://t.co/1JvuELnWf0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Downloaded on @audible_com today! https://t.co/JQCQ8BcBsz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok this gives me a chill... https://t.co/XGCyKnh9iP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Skype Been using the new  #skypepreview on my pc/phone. have a few ui issues BUT am hooked on managing text messages on my PC!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsmichaelwest I work in health care and when I hear users say this non sense I want to suggest another career!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really enjoy #TheWalkingDead but the commercial to show ratio is getting out of hand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good read on a Saturday morning https://t.co/hN0MV7nDw8 #HacksawRidge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JezCorden would you not be libertarian?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoodThings2Life @kylealden this discussion reminds me of something, wait, wait don't tell me...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Skype Several times a month. we have a 5, 3 and newborn in another state and enjoy how Skype helps us stay connected.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoodThings2Life @Daniel_Rubino oh your one of those....😄]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoodThings2Life @Daniel_Rubino hey you millennials, get off my lawn!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading the grandkids a book over @Skype using the @Xbox https://t.co/1KfblIWaFt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really enjoying the single player game in @Titanfallgame 2 and this writer agrees https://t.co/MSfNchY7wd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cuff_S @THWACK now I'm wondering if this is REALLY you!? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cuff_S @THWACK enjoyed the article. I wonder if eventually w will have personal bots to handle growing communications we r all managing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Xbox my friend! https://t.co/N7h1zXnO7y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Daniel_Rubino hey I'll vote dog over cat any day but I'll follow you anyway. I just ignore the cat stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatriciaHeaton @WalkingDead_AMC so what's your guess on who gets taken out? I'm going with #Daryl.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsmichaelwest I had the same issue I kept a onenote page and made a pro con list I filled in over time. After 6 months I'm using winphone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WinObs or like I hear often at work, "tech is not my job" while they are handing over the laptop they can function without.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft’s Channel 9 to get a new design, preview now available https://t.co/SpacIpePX4 @ch9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's my grandson! 😃  https://t.co/u0R9og9a7o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not that I see... https://t.co/N5CmqT90uZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couldn't make #Ignite, me either! 570 sessions already on line! https://t.co/57wvUWR7jv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[using #continuum more lately on win10 mobile but missing some apps. Hope to see @DocHaloApp join the #UWP family! Ready to help test!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to @SurfaceSmiths podcast today. If your a #Microsoft pro or enthusiast you need to follow these guys. Thanks for the call out!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottisafool I had this just happen this week. Plugged a USB keyboard then snapped on the surface keyboard and all has been fine since]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very best #windows10mobile apps https://t.co/ClA5d7FUuX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've just entered to win a Lenovo Yoga Book from @WindowsCentral! #win #contest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoodThings2Life yep we moved from xen to VMware a few years back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoodThings2Life well for average end users we've had good experiences. Have remote users working 7x24 on the platform. So #Windows10 plans?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IEhrgeizI @GoodThings2Life @itsmichaelwest ive had some frustration being on insider but that's part of being on pre release]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IEhrgeizI @GoodThings2Life @itsmichaelwest I'm sitting tight and watching. my 950xl fits my needs just fine and the platform is in flux]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoodThings2Life @VMware @citrix interesting. we use a bit of both at work. have more history with C. what's the background?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read on @mspoweruser about @VMware solution for #continuum for #windows10 i want to know where the heck is @citrix with their plans?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big thanks to @JamesFalconer for his help today! https://t.co/LCeZlpmtVb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Daniel_Rubino @windowscentral thanks for responding on your day off hope we can resolve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ALASKANJACKSON well I am something of a gangster! No really, totally confused 😖.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I've been banned from @windowscentral no notice no reason no response from site or @Daniel_Rubino what could I have done?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DellHealth @kylematthews @beatnb @TGen fix link please!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoodThings2Life use my LG bt collar every day. That and #Cortana make me hands free anywhere. Also listen to @VernonEL podcast empire!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GaborFari @GoodThings2Life @gcaughey @bitdisaster @waltritscher @csharpfritz too much fluff, banter and snarkiness from the male hosts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @windowscentral can't get emails answered regarding my account login to your site. Little help please?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IEhrgeizI Happy labor day. I recently switched back to the #950xl from my iPhone. Missed so many things on the platform]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh the gift of being the early riser is making that first pot of coffee and getting that first sip of the first cup. #firstsip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always like to understand the origin of holidays. Like many this one has truly veared from it's intent https://t.co/63eVkyHSEU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great clip and share feature in the @audible_com app on my #Windows10 phone. Very useful!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bccasteel yep mom got here and she's excited about new emoji's! I'm on insider where #Cortana is currently broken making this me 😬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ryan's Costume 5K Run and Family Walk https://t.co/7FO5WStFlt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[way to go @PNCBank for supporting  #Microsoftwallet payments! Got mine set and ready to go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoodThings2Life @JezCorden @mattjbrown thanks for the shout out! Hope to find a few to try.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[USA’s 5th largest bank adds support for Contactless Payments via Microsoft Wallet https://t.co/cjXl0IfM15 apps may go but apps may come!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rodtrent @NexDock is now shipping, writing this post on it this morning. Fascinating potential still in alpha stage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@twindadjoe celebrating the 31st birthday of our twins this week. Happy Birthday @bccasteel and #justincasteel! Love you guys!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey #windows10 fans. I'm looking for some good #wup games to try using with my #lumia950xl with the @NexDock suggestions?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wjxt4 hey @bccasteel you have 2 days to celebrate this week!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Armstrong cable and internet out tonight in #risingsun Md. for several hours. I guess I'll retire to the library with a brandy]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>