<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@bogdanoviclab is a terrific mid career scientist starting his new lab @GarvanInstitute   If you are into Epigeneti… https://t.co/22CPvGewrz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interested in the role of the immune system in metabolic disease &amp; cancer? Join us in Fiji in August. #imcd https://t.co/pzOKU6xW1Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No....Dr Noakes doesn't ignore the evidence...he just presents 'alternative facts'😳 https://t.co/PGvwt4V46c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Without doubt. https://t.co/VM9dIVTOje]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How many of the 10 million Democrats that voted for Obama in 2008 but didn't for Clinton in 2016 wish they did now? https://t.co/EEH5o5mOC5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Given that hardly anyone will be able to get a visa without being interrogated this seems like a great idea. https://t.co/TQqrkVdqJI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Plea to Trump Fans: This Man is Dangerous | The Resistance with Keith ... https://t.co/VmcLzLBrO1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Syrian boy drowning fake, Port Arthur fake (Rogers), NASA climate dates fake (Roberts). Guess One Nation deals in '… https://t.co/0aXZRxc56z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Precisely why everyone should stop hoping Trump gets impeached. This guy will be the President!!! https://t.co/14hXk3PZuS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Richly deserved @CSHeartResearch   Congratulations https://t.co/CVtYnn04S1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonderful AoY. Being a scientist is a privilege but biomedical research is expensive relying on Govt funding &amp; phil… https://t.co/SHh2RxGFzN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is very encouraging that the twitter sphere is seemingly unanimously positive. A great night for medical researc… https://t.co/azrYeU3rFR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am so happy that a medical researcher has been recognised. There are many, many more anonymous great ones in this… https://t.co/RDs4t4xqE7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whereisdaz Anyone who insists that NASA fabricated their climate data is not worthy of debate.  Akin to anti vaxxe… https://t.co/YpoB6RenXs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When someone presents data at a meeting which are dubious, the presenter can now justify the data as 'alternative fact' 😳 #kellyanneconway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jan 20th 2017. Take a deep breath world.... https://t.co/EWQnrtGEWz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whereisdaz I don't advocate this. I do however do science everyday. I can't call it 'work'. Science is my passion… https://t.co/95IuBtEZA3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A little rich coming from the only player to be disqualified from #AusOpen. Jan 21 1990 was definitely "a black eye… https://t.co/tnHP7435LN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2/2 we don't know what goes through the head of  @NickKyrgios or others under pressure? Ask a psychiatrist or neuro… https://t.co/XUhjahiXNh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think all should stop the negativity towards @NickKyrgios   We don't vilify other young men who display erratic m… https://t.co/C2gw8euBl0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I suspect he is too right wing for Donald Trimp https://t.co/GDu7PJcrkm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GregHuntMP was a Fulbright Fellow at Yale. Hopefully, he is pro-medical research and we see a badly needed injection of $$$ into the @nhmrc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Memo to Americans. You voted a person who pays this level of care in his communication as your next President who a… https://t.co/0JUu9usMtC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To all the racists out there. I just love this photo. Every one I know does too. Islamaphobes are in the minority.… https://t.co/SANR1wAxlT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mohamad_sowaid @JakeQRyan @MikeCarlton01 Most of us don't hate you. We care about people not religion. Racist trolls hide behind twitter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will try for Sunday week (Jan 28th). https://t.co/GdEqWHggb7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi knackers. Anything that doesn't put load through the joins. Swimming, cycling and some weights. See a physio and… https://t.co/MUX1J7KuiS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IanWoolf the patent has now expired which means you can get generic brands such as Asmol. Hence it is over the counter rather than PBS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LouiseMBurke What has he got to do with the quoted article? Because the author is not even famous in his own lunch… https://t.co/CKB0VWuicH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oops @Qantas that  is  a pink Pinot Gris don't you thin? Looks like a fine Rose though.... https://t.co/CEmvEDJwjm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lot of people must be into exercise science because the author is definitely not that influential #humbled https://t.co/ENAoiEcDXJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I shed a tear when I heard  Obama's classy outgoing speech, then I skipped a beat when I heard the disgusting alleg… https://t.co/8Ifkazec3m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very interesting statistic.... https://t.co/u8Y1iZIOsn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomnoon89 @NatureRevEndo easy to find @GarvanInstitute website. Cheers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomnoon89 @NatureRevEndo Tom,please email me and I will send you a PDF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MickLynch_Age I live in Lower Plenty and Foxtel signal is absolutely fine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am really lucky to work in an organisation where the cleaner and the director are equally respected by all includ… https://t.co/CTmBrNIgan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlueSpotScience @andyphilp_lab so many important myokines yet to be discovered. The field will grow exponentially.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mwkeenan I usually ask them why they are in such a hurry to get to their crappy job that they hate. Usually goes down a treat😜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interested in immunometabolism and chronic disease? Join us in Fiji in August!!!  https://t.co/BrPQ8BvCpC.   RT ple… https://t.co/SylQPMfzwf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dr_krystal Max Planck just appointed 5 new directors. All had to be women. My friend Erica Pearce moved to Freiburg.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dr_krystal @DuttonChemistry @AlexWHewitt Nothing makes me prouder than a former post doc excelling in independence. Old men aren't all evil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dr_krystal @DuttonChemistry @AlexWHewitt However, not funding 'old profs' simply because they are 'old profs' is reverse discrimination 2/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dr_krystal @DuttonChemistry @AlexWHewitt No problem not funding based on lack of productivity or innovation is fine 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jgryall @nhmrc @GordonSLynch @petecurr cheers to all. As an old, male I am made to feel guilty about my success. Akin to a Democrat Elite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can never understand why Aus crowds boo opposition athletes. It is so uncouth and disrespectful. Why not more humility???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whereisdaz If this translates to humans I am doomed. Travel plus alcohol consumption at meetings = trouble!!! https://t.co/04DWOdAEjz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haha @Barnaby_Joyce is now the oracle on how to cure obesity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophiescott2 @ConversationEDU perhaps the govt could also inject $ into obesity/T2D research for novel treatments/cures?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Frankfurt airport and bumped into Former Vice President @algore. You just can tell when a person oozes goodness and kindness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[don't know what made me feel worse-Trump presidency or Leonard Cohen's passing. Surely if Dylan got a Nobel, Cohen… https://t.co/OEGDPZUsPI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone who thinks yesterday was doom and gloom for us in Aus should listen to  our former PM @leighsales https://t.co/DszYmagF68]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gianina_Natoli congratulations to you too. For me there were no celebrations, just relief. At 51 it was going to difficult to retrain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gianina_Natoli @DrAsh_Smith @DrScienceLover agree, but older scientists who have served the taxpayer well for 20 years are falling off!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gianina_Natoli @DrAsh_Smith @DrScienceLover don't focus on age. I am older and have never had less #nhmrc $ Problem is shrinking pot of $$$]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kon__K isn't @corybernardi part of the existing Govt? Such a ringing endorsement for both his peers and his PM. #ausalreadygreat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bridie_OD @DavidWalshST @SaintFrankly Froome?? Watts per kilo are ridiculously stratospheric (and that's with an overestimated body mass).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bridie_OD @DavidWalshST @SaintFrankly so wish I was there. A true ambassador for clean sport. What about Wiggins?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@corybernardi Aren't you part of the current Government?  Ringing endorsement for your peers and your PM! https://t.co/5UxBmCUgZT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DocmartyAus ummmm, can we have a chat about this tomorrow????😜😜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Journalist on PBS Newshour "the closest thing we have to compare with is Berlusconi". Look what he did to Italy!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whereisdaz my youngest daughter is 11 - she fully recognised those two elements comprised the cornerstone of the Trump election platform]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AustralianStory the most heart warming story on the rural town of Mingoola. Good people working together. The foundation of our nation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bridie_OD @ozdale makes me proud to be Australian. The foundation of our country. Pity Right wingers are probably watching reality tv.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rohan_connolly @rustyjacko I was shocked to see that David Warner loves watching cardoonz. Had him picked for a reader of Shakespeare.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andyphilp_lab presenting @GarvanInstitute on why exercise is vital for healthy ageing. https://t.co/JgFQRPho8u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whereisdaz @dr_krystal this article related to appointments not grants. One constant- past behaviour predicts future behaviour.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pleased to finally join the 21st Century with the purchase of my stand up desk. https://t.co/SSq3Wy6LTF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could there be a more iconic Australian image? Kookaburra sitting on a Hills hoist! #loveAustralia https://t.co/Apb4S8eCvF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very sad to read this news. A wonderful scientist who led the stress protein field taken way too early. Vale Susan… https://t.co/qX9bvnbNai]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AJMurph5 For now.....Statistically the data are probably 2 years old. We know what has happened in the interim. 😜 https://t.co/n0LLDhLLkQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whereisdaz @SciBry the system is tough for old guys too. Don't blame us, lobby the govt for more funds. I could have zero grants in 24h.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whereisdaz @SciBry Over 50 mate I'm old. Ask the young scientists I mentor, encouraging, promote -see if they perceive me as a "challenge"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SciBry @whereisdaz this attitude is both a generalisation and ageist. We were young scientists too once. Good young scientists....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jgryall you are too kind! Very humbling. Hope that I get some project grant money to justify NHMRC investment in m… https://t.co/SK7gk9rIUw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sammostyn @Peter_Fitz Every time a see a photo of Bomber I feel good. Best poli never to be PM. Had too much integ… https://t.co/MrrC2xU643]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love my Southern European heritage..... https://t.co/PO05wkARF6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vanbadham The rise in housing supply is linear, the increasing in pricing is exponential.  How can negative gearing be irrelevant? #ScoMo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@proferikrichter @ANZOS_Society You know the answer to that one Erik!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three generations of Exercise Metabolism in Oz. Drs Watt, Hargreaves, Febbraio @ANZOS_Society 2016 meeting. https://t.co/ZEwmMPVBdV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ANZOS_Society proud to be presenting today. Prouder to see my former fellows Drs Watt, Bruce, Carey are now leaders in the field #feelold]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnAHawley great quote but you missed the best part of the speech....."COME ON MAN!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rohan_connolly Round 1 2017 Melbourne Darby at the MCG. 80-90 thousand???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice work @LykkeSylow @proferikrichter good to see this published! https://t.co/EfluVdBeEt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whereisdaz @monsoon0 @BBCNews it isn't either/or. Both happily coexist and learn from each other...at least in my research bubble....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a scientist I now have a genuine reason to covet the Nobel Prize. You get to call Bob Dylan a peer! #NobelPrizeLiterature]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This month marks 18 months since I joined @GarvanInstitute Feel both humbled and privileged to work in such a great MRI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whereisdaz You can relax this week Darren. RGMS is down for maintenance until Oct 16.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kon__K  well I guess 'Kon' would be very difficult to pronounce with someone with the IQ of JC. Keep up the good work Kon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whereisdaz you forgot to tweet that this is the case if you're Dutch. What type of behaviour is selectively reporting the data? 😜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProfPCDoherty making a great deal of sense (yet again)  https://t.co/45gwg3TxNs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a scientist you know you are old when...you suggest to the lab you do an experiment and the response is unanimous laughter 😳😳😳]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cameron Smith...humility in defeat. All class.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Luke Beverage. The epitome of emotional intelligence. He just gets people. #AFLGF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At last @afl get's pre match entertainment spot on. Sting still rocks!!! #AFLGF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vanbadham Agree, but have you checked out the US voting blogs on who won ?...VERY SCARY #debatenight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exploring  molecular links between exercise and disease prevention https://t.co/IU5DjMtiKd https://t.co/pZbGKJabBP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robbo_heraldsun  feel sorry for Wood and Monteith whose reputation will be unfortunately sullied. The others will be forgotten.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Robbo_heraldsun @RalphyHeraldSun can't help thinking Luke Breust had a Herschelle moment tonight. Feel for him. https://t.co/sjzkkpb9ld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dj_keating no results yet. Can't tell anyone anyway because if strict embargo]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>