<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Open to bribes, ehem--"campaign contributions". - The Independent https://t.co/E8Rp7eOO9k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this sustainable for 4 weeks, let alone 4 years? Trump's 'terrible' phone call with Australian PM - ITV News https://t.co/MfYyCpiOKf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unless 2020 elections are cancelled (Trump keeps talking about "8 years"; does he know something we don't?). - CNN https://t.co/2tmzkdT48W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh boy. Trump &amp; Team will be rich beyond the wildest dreams of avarice at the end of his stint. - The Atlantic https://t.co/PwVaFnmUi2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Trump supporters sneer at protests, what are they scared of? - the guardian https://t.co/DFK6D7Frdh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No surprises there. Donald Trump 'taking steps to abolish Environmental Protection Agency' - the guardian https://t.co/id3i2K8cGG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once a narcissistic slime bag, always a narcissistic slime bag. Reporter: Trump bragged to Australian PM - CNN https://t.co/gVR6fKpLoc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More Americans were shot &amp; killed by toddlers last year than immigrants. Build a wall against toddlers, #USA! Wouldn't have to be very tall!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is now a Stop Trump Coalition! Hooray, I say! - the guardian https://t.co/vCxS3bhn9f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Resistance with Keith Olbermann https://t.co/byUH0k1Wvn via @youtube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Political clothing labels. Love it! https://t.co/n2NVgTBEkA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, PLEASE. Donald Trump 'could be impeached' over immigration ban, says Texas congressman - The Independent https://t.co/2YCssqU2uJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yo, Donald: if you dare set foot in Britain, we'll show you protests like you wouldn't believe. - CNN https://t.co/BVkb5PS4Qc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The US now has no State Dept, no Attorney General, and no ambassadors abroad. Congress &amp; Senate apparently AWOL. All power in tiny hands.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Petition: Make co-operation with Trump administration conditional on human rights. https://t.co/UBv884CmQv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[23 Angry, Hilarious, And Extremely British Signs Protesting Trump's Refugee Ban https://t.co/IY1oz9lLV7 via @RachaelKrishna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Bell's vision of Trump's UK state visit in today's Guardian. Petition to nix it now signed by more than 1.6 m… https://t.co/MvkLXScx7R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not just you, Your Maj. Every decent person is appalled at the idea. Trump state visit 'very difficult' for Queen https://t.co/bteEmCpVgS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a word for that kind of government. It ain't "democracy". Trump sacks defiant attorney general Sally Yates https://t.co/cyrGvFKct2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BorisJohnson: if you think that the US is still a democracy, as you claimed today, you should read this. – Medium https://t.co/yCjELyKnar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Given Melania's history, this is rich. Trump's 'vile' comments about Kate Middleton sunbathing - Mirror Online https://t.co/snlRySpiL2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpiritAnimalUS @CalebBoyington @AdamBlickstein This is a coup d'etat. Anywhere else you'd by now be watching who the army will side with.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeorgeTakei Dulles CPB ignoring federal judge's order, handcuffing people, deporting them to detention centers before lawyers can act.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is implementing intelligence service answerable only to him. Not the US. Coup is in progress. USA: what are you going to do about it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump has purged the State Dept and fired every US ambassador. But he's already accepting campaign contribs for 2020. Coup in progress.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[READ THIS, America. “Trial Balloon for a Coup?” by @yonatanzunger https://t.co/fcOHrHr0Al]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do @GOP worry about repealing Obamacare? Millions of uninsured? Naaah. Midterm elections. - The Independent https://t.co/NsBhQvB7p5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love my home town! Sadiq Khan: Londoners will not 'roll out red carpet' for Donald Trump - Evening Standard https://t.co/e2pcPzSZmN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My new favourite time waster is to watch the signatures update on this. Average: about 1000/minute. - Petitions https://t.co/lXfwrw7D9P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crackdown on man who trolled Trump went too far, free speech experts say - the guardian https://t.co/nc4h5TGNfI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Common error. Hitler too was appointed after a minority vote bc they thought they cd "handle" him. - The Independent https://t.co/6Eei6mvI5r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now we know @theresa_may 's model PM. It's not Thatcher. It's Chamberlain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring the Orange Clown on, @theresa_may . Both of you will end up with egg on your face. - The Huffington Post - UK https://t.co/knT5MVgmaW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More #alternativefacts from the dictator. Trump team says travel ban implementation a 'massive success' - Sky News https://t.co/Clzs3S4nPp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is headed for a million signatures on its first day!! Britain to Donald: Nobody wants you here. - Petitions https://t.co/lXfwrw7D9P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HouseGOP @HouseDemocrats @SenateGOP @SenateDems : any comment on @realDonaldTrump instituting religious persecution in America? Anything???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm with you on this one, Jeremy. Jeremy Corbyn: Donald Trump's UK state visit should be put on-hold - The Telegraph https://t.co/c63Ipfak4r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prevent Donald Trump from making a State Visit to the United Kingdom. - Petitions https://t.co/lXfwrw7D9P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump: "It's working out very nicely. You see it in the airports, you see it all over..." https://t.co/h8J6Q9xE7G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even conservative British MPs have Trump's number. https://t.co/ngDJ9oENxY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even conservative British papers have Trump's number. https://t.co/8yv5ZD9q9j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The wonderfully talented, incomparably expressive and impressive, wrinkled and crumpled John Hurt is gone. How we will miss you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, that sounds like a democracy to me. Bannon: Media should "keep its mouth shut" - The Independent https://t.co/bwxYHJ3iQa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any woman speaking of a mutual "attraction" involving Trump, in any sense, makes me physically ill. - the guardian https://t.co/9n7AHa1CsW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump first invites Mexico to cancel, then slams Mexico as leader cancels trip - BBC News https://t.co/re78st9mS0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations, @EPN . I wish @theresa_may had your kind of self-respect and dignity. - BBC News https://t.co/re78st9mS0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theresa_may : As a citizen of the UK, I am ashamed that you're grovelling to a dictator, sex predator &amp; torture supporter. #NotInMyName]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More evidence that the new #POTUS is nothing but a vile, despicable bully. Just beneath contempt. - The Telegraph https://t.co/xpYPU5oRFt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope Mexico does cancel. I wish May would too. Anyone who deals with the vile dictator Trump has no self-respect. https://t.co/J7s8WUaNYX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On her flight May should read Trump’s book: the other guy is always shafted - the guardian https://t.co/n94MIuMUkv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["America First" means America's relationships w others will be hostile. No matter how much May begs. - the guardian https://t.co/H8aa8RVmtc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And here's our PM cozying up to a dictator, a sex predator, a torture supporter, a climate change denier - BBC News https://t.co/cjFF7dNBNo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...but let's not forget that the human trafficking deal w Turkey was an EU brainchild. - the guardian https://t.co/PtzwMQivlH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Hotels to triple US properties in defiance of 'no new deals' pledge - the guardian https://t.co/uMFqpiAtqo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I gave this a follow! https://t.co/tZ5m8z8a9Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s lies are delusional. But the dangers they pose are now very real - the guardian https://t.co/ZmoiYuODEb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Myriachan The Donald himself keeps claiming the election was fraudulent. If he believes that he's got no business accepting that office.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing to see a nation this terrified of its own Head of State, yet unwilling to depose him. - The Independent https://t.co/F3p0Rlm6Ue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A nation tries to prevent its own dictator from starting nuclear war. - The Independent https://t.co/F3p0Rlm6Ue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump : if millions of people voted illegally, you should, as the beneficiary of a fraudulent election, resign immediately!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why we're suing Donald Trump - CNN https://t.co/v1uyB568wB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More bottom feeders in Trump's swamp. Trump economic adviser leaves Goldman with payout of over $100 million - CNN https://t.co/Vio5vhqJS1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dictatorship in action: 6 journalists arrested on felony charges after covering inauguration unrest - the guardian https://t.co/W1bxZCeszx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/4 of the US might lose health care. Trump's HHS pick: Right to Medicaid not guaranteed under block grants - CNN https://t.co/s7WGjXqqwC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump silences government scientists with gag orders https://t.co/pY6OwsHhQ7 via @Verge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is Kellyanne Conway not in jail for assault ?  - The Independent https://t.co/hvqDcPrAUO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just reward for loyalty, right, Jimmy boy?Trump plans to keep Comey as FBI director - New York Times - Reuters https://t.co/Rextye2g92]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sekoch06 And don't forget alt-elections, after which Breitbart will report that Beloved Leader got 99.9% of the popular vote.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Leader Trump talks about the next 8 years of his presidency as if the 2020 election were cancelled. Anything he knows that we don't?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Trump continues to ape Hitler, the Ermächtigungsgesetz should be next. Look it up. (Hint: forget Congress, Senate, future elections.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching Trump's USA is an object lesson to all of how quickly a flawed democracy can deteriorate into dictatorship. Wehret den Anfängen...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrs_n_cook @OwensDamien @CraigCo62 What makes you think he'll allow another election to take place? All you need is a "national emergency"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump's 'day of patriotic devotion' has echoes of North Korea - the guardian https://t.co/SHm8lhUfxa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good mourning, America. Bye bye NEA. Bye bye NEH. Bye bye NPR. Bye bye PBS. https://t.co/xWvbxU60P4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ethics lawsuit to claim Trump is in violation of Constitution - CNN https://t.co/WvJqjHpvOA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A lie told once remains a lie but a lie told 1000 times becomes the truth." (Goebbels). Right, @KellyannePolls ? https://t.co/r6Alx8IyDV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A lie told once remains a lie but a lie told 1000 times becomes the truth." (Joseph Goebbels). Right, @PressSec? https://t.co/M1xpT57mBh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PressSec : All dictatorships deny reality. All dictatorships suppress the free press. - The Telegraph https://t.co/yD5udWG661]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join the movement to stop Donald #Trump! Add your name: https://t.co/2l7Kb90UtQ via @moveon #StopHateDumpTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're one of the few women worldwide who missed a march, you can still get on board: PUSSYHAT PROJECT https://t.co/o7CzaOZ9Jo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In other words: bye bye, free press in America. - The Independent https://t.co/L3dXMaP4hi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More to come, I'm sure. Donald Trump's company violated its own rules on day one of Presidency - The Independent https://t.co/fXRumANjZw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A movement the likes of which we've never seen." But not the way you mean, Donald. - The New York Times https://t.co/YirnTD5jv3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even Trump won't be able to grab 'em all. Pictures From Women’s Marches on Every Continent - The New York Times https://t.co/pMfaEKbbb0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 times Donald Trump's team didn't tell the truth on his first full day in office - The Independent https://t.co/ym5xaAR9GQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Petty dictator Trump just "requested" a state do from Queen of England, specifying it must be more lavish than the welcome for Obama in '11.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Gets Defensive About His Turnout As Womens' Marches See Millions Take To The Streets Worldwide - UPROXX https://t.co/nHu1h0CflM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump's press secretary uses first brief to lie about inauguration attendance numbers - The Independent https://t.co/oAGzCHBYkp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anti-Trump protesters fill streets across the globe - CNN https://t.co/myXvUcy5cs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wha-a-a-t??? How can that be even remotely possible? One wonders why Americans even bother having laws. - CNN https://t.co/fNm2hPll09]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plagiarising speeches and now--cakes. Yeah, I'm sure this basket of deplorables is original enough to think of a re… https://t.co/SvgwUUC0fh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Better to live in a monarchy that behaves like a democracy than in a country that calls itself a democracy &amp; behaves like an autocracy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[200,000 at protest. Ca 10,000 at Inauguration. - BBC News https://t.co/9nq9A2rKRZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear US: I'm so happy I left--when you made W, another loser of the pop vote, #POTUS. You'll always be my favorite Russian satellite state.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['American Carnage': The Trump Era Begins - The Atlantic https://t.co/XKkBbCXciy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Climate change, healthcare and civil rights no longer On WH site. But you can buy Melania's jewelry though it. - CNN https://t.co/BOM34WCF0l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Best Protest Signs From the Inauguration of Donald Trump - https://t.co/3asVtppzpJ https://t.co/Eveyb31tKg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will Americans find the guts to do what is right? Donald Trump impeachment effort already underway - The Independent https://t.co/bJSKx1ZLVV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Guardian comparing a class- and accomplishment-free plagiarising nudie-model with Jackie Kennedy. - the guardian https://t.co/S9vmziWwny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“An open letter to the president, Donald Trump” by @SkylarJordan https://t.co/Kagqzqnyj6]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>