<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I just ... wtf is wrong with these people? Snopes says true. https://t.co/ApFL66vaOX https://t.co/S0phmXdnGB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excuse me while I go puke. https://t.co/B8otpQU4yd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or about the GOP's willingness to abandon all norms in pursuit of giving 45 total control. https://t.co/GKKdE4oVlF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Celeste_pewter Called and got immediately put on hold. Did get a person ~2 min in who said they'd pass my comments along to the committee.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And called her actions a "betrayal" https://t.co/7U5fbhGNGj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenateDems @timkaine please tell me you're no longer considering appeasement given 45's statement on @SallyQYates https://t.co/XrFU8g5Tti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WTF?! This is NOT normal. This is not how you govern. https://t.co/Vn8tezSZub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They're talking about Sessions. https://t.co/ks9c7v6Hr9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attn @timkaine @MarkWarner @RepDonBeyer Dulles CBP is still not obeying the Court Order! https://t.co/lycBOeJ0Cm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The U.S. military said it killed 14 militants in a raid... Medics... said around 30 people, including 10 women and… https://t.co/3doW9JgonT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An important thread on the Constitutional Crisis that *45 has created with this EO. https://t.co/UrE2RSXr8a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DHSgov The EO is discriminatory, unConstitutional and damaging. Stays have been issued by multiple Federal Judges and you should comply.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember that Sessions had a hand in drafting this unConstitutional EO. Stand strong against him and urge your coll… https://t.co/JVax6OILYf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Given the DHS press release ... https://t.co/gMZd1iVK88]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy Shit! This is NOT NORMAL! Thread! https://t.co/dJVy7vlBqW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're going into D.C. today to protest be aware that #wmata is messed up this weekend. https://t.co/DFkP3khs4c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a real press release from DHS -a dept led by one of the Cabinet members @SenateDems voted to confirm. https://t.co/K9QnkppnzD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timkaine @MarkWarner Please be advised that Sessions was, reportedly, involved in this unconstitutional EO.… https://t.co/Qoirxtx2y6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director of National Intelligence and Chairman of the Joint Chiefs should insist that everything NatSec pertains to… https://t.co/rro5KteSNu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of the best people I met in grad school were Iranian. https://t.co/wgjpiJirpV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this thread on how bonkers the Green Card system already is. https://t.co/aH51DPZbmB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@estherxlwang Do you have translators? It seems like English only signs might miss some people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LacyMB Well @CAIRNational and @ACLU have filed suits and @RefugeeAssist is apparently sending lawyers to JFK airport. Could start there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@T_Lyte So is Bernie. Move along.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thread! And if the Party leadership could please step up and get its ass in gear... https://t.co/pQ5NanWKIH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Costc Photo question - Why can't I print a postcard where both sides use my own template? Your back allows for no customization or images.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@womensmarch Could you maybe post the images at a decent resolution or link to an actual printer with a standing order not a random app?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@womensmarch I'm trying to print some postcards but I don't have room to dl a new app and all the print shops tell me your pg sizes are off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anybody have a script for, "Stop acting like this is just politics as usual and organize yourselves into the Resistance we need you to be"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yikes! This is not normal! https://t.co/vKbqO7v1z6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BirdG81 @owillis I can't believe nobody snatched up HRC's team she had some pretty good twitter folks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe focus on Sen @Sen_JoeManchin (D-W.VA) who has said he'll vote for Session according to the article. https://t.co/gDcDovtY6l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Note - Toomey (PA) - I know some of you are his constituents. https://t.co/sScgV20Iwl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trains were incredibly, unsafely overcrowded on Saturday  and they lost $? #Wmata is doing something very wrong. https://t.co/tQpvvyh3wd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why would anyone be reimbursing you @wmata? Isn't that what paying for the ride is supposed to cover? https://t.co/WkyDARblfo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good! Nobody who wants to destroy or profit off the institutions that make this country work should be put in charg… https://t.co/Lzj4zIhzpf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't care who you pick to lead; get your shit together and resist louder. @MarkWarner @timkaine @CoryBooker… https://t.co/ARrCa2O60P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proof that Dems and GOP aren't playing the same game. GOP is doing everything it can to ensure there will never be… https://t.co/xEoT93IhxR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AltNatParkSer Shenandoah National Park (2016) https://t.co/VjaeFIhPlZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes Please! https://t.co/M2fbLmkuK4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People who want to destroy our institutions shouldn't be put in charge of them. #whyIMarch #SwampCabinet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because obviously civil servants are the swamp not the billionaire lobbyists he's hiring into his cabinet. 🙄 https://t.co/kYMsRezhlO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is he seriously going to cry over glitter and "locker room talk"?  You have only yourselves and your President to b… https://t.co/6Nr4NtnAWl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could get behind a Tax Day protest. https://t.co/6KKT3V71fN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This abdication of our responsibility to engage in peaceful international relations would be despicable. https://t.co/tQBfBAYucX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone I know who wore a hat either made it themselves or had a friend who made it for them. #pussyhatproject https://t.co/4RojV34wRF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@monkeycomics The fact that a respected media sources is repeating a comment as a headline implies validity and give credence to  it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@monkeycomics Thus when the headline is just "(S)He said X" with no indication of the validity of the statement it is problematic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@monkeycomics I'm not sure how true that remains these days. With fb and twitter and everything else ppl seem to read headlines and move on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConnieSchultz @snarkarina Having trouble figuring out who to support. It seems for every 1 headline NYT/WasPo gets right they get 3 wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@killyourfm Yes. They seemed intent on getting out of the crowd as quickly as possible with minimal interaction so it was easy to ignore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The crowd near me wasn't even particularly rude to the people who were trying to get around wearing Tr*mp hats. https://t.co/xavDfKmoMn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A shot from before it got too crowded and we headed off to catch a train at Arlington. #WomensMarchOnWashington… https://t.co/09CzR3HFCC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over to the White House. #WomensMarchOnWashington #latergram https://t.co/XkZp6TEd7J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We walked around to the back end of the #womensmarch https://t.co/ORsTI88D1k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WomensMarch  #latergram https://t.co/xk1PYA6qnF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are finally moving!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We have made it onto a platform. Who knows when we'll get a train. #WomensMarch #wmata]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is NOT normal! https://t.co/S2cEbc5Bu4 https://t.co/r6Ll4G2YJF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well this isn't promising for anyone who's worried about voting rights. https://t.co/k9g2IOtv1M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When everything gets overwhelming... https://t.co/rOMl8FORFG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is #whyIMarch https://t.co/1ZYjcpAKXb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Selkie1970 @katelinnea many of our offices/departments are hard to turn. I'm not worried about my day to day, but i do worry abt others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Selkie1970 @katelinnea as a civil servant, most of the people I know are scared but carrying on bc there's nothing else we can do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClintSmithIII @Susannah_Nix because they think their kids are going to be the winners and they don't care about the rest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She knows exactly what she's doing; it just happens to antithetical to what most people expect Ed Sec to do. Thread… https://t.co/cZuMShbRZw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the person that the @GOP wants to force through the hearing and confirmation of before her ethics review is… https://t.co/56eHLNjDJl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes and I'm also annoyed at the infomercial producers for feeding the confusion by implying incompetence to keep th… https://t.co/6Z2iF0i4zz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessicaValenti I don't see anywhere in the article that an anti-choice group has been granted partnership or sponsorship - what'd i miss?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things to remember. https://t.co/NQphjPLpno]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is NOT normal! https://t.co/ecAXANBxTT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its the main march because the BernieBros were too busy mansplaining how their guy would've won to get their shit t… https://t.co/W3GQCmL9pB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is important. https://t.co/aNlTtNhzBg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who do you think makes the decisions under the #ACA? @SenateGOP's hypothetical replacement takes decisions away fro… https://t.co/l5Jy3VgrN2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People who think like this should be ashamed of themselves. Medical care /= furniture. https://t.co/ZKUDnyLUjI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @HiddenFigures is the type of story we should be telling when we talk about what makes America great, not just John Glenn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wearing my #RebootTheSuit tee to see #HiddenFigures bc apparently I have to learn about awesome ladies from the movies  instead of school.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thread https://t.co/cLqNspYx19]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you need some cute today... https://t.co/Y9iusItLZE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And that's going to pay the bills how? What an ass. https://t.co/tv5K3BliYn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is awful! Honestly the more I hear from official police mouthpieces in this country the less I trust them. https://t.co/4RkbNcONiM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker Why would nobody stand with the House Dems on this? https://t.co/Y1aybPihnB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenFranken But you won't stand up with your colleagues from the House and object to dubious election results being counted? #shame]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenateDems Where are you? Why have you abandoned your constituents, your colleagues, and your country? Where is yo… https://t.co/GuCaQPYBfl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenWarren @timkaine @SenSanders Where are you? https://t.co/8baElldAB4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn it #PSU! Maybe if you haven't started by digging yourself a 13 point hole. :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @GOP this is garbage. Grow up and show the morals you love to campaign on having. https://t.co/mmTlBs3GFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok, #PSU let's keep playing like the team that showed up for the 2nd quarter. #RoseBowl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok @psufootball let's do this! #RoseBowl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holiday gaming with the family. #ion @GotGeniusGames https://t.co/ei73xfamL9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UGH! Do they not realize that this kind of garbage is why people don't trust them? https://t.co/wx377cq7co]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And this is why I remain a registered Independent. https://t.co/opTfQYq8h0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is Not normal. So happy to see the @GOP's famed values platform is as strictly 'do as I say' as always. https://t.co/zTnT3IFOmP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is so gross. https://t.co/NoYF8Z1Mhy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not like his daughter's the one taking over the First Lady's office and talking about hosting events or anythi… https://t.co/QHnZ0MWuMi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So who else is watching the @PTXofficial Christmas Special?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really wish Broadway was more accessible. #Allegiance should be required viewing in high school history classes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are similar problems with drug trials. https://t.co/ji6qKezKDY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @TheDemocrats - why don't you have any representatives in this process? Why have you abandoned the electorate? https://t.co/PLMMZS3S3U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @TheDemocrats I still don't understand why Stein was the only one calling for this is the first place. Explain… https://t.co/qqPNZxUCQJ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>