<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@sez_sez @ravenous_wolves hi is this the nz version?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[photo provided from the group of Ngātiwai teens https://t.co/t9Ynq5pZAf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it also features this telling graph (red = Māori) from an OIA (further breakdown will be on the spinoff) https://t.co/ylwCZih1zU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Maria_LaFonda @eamonnmarra hey @ryoffknighton can u photoshop our flat heads on top of Maria's actual family for the fb group]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eamonnmarra @Maria_LaFonda omg is it out? maria why did u  go to auckland, what about our flat screening!! &lt;/3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lightyouonfire yeah im like teacher/ youth worker? idk i just like journalism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrancesCook @melissa_wishart @nzherald i hate this world :/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[live footage of the guy who creates the WINZ application process https://t.co/o7IFPhldWX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the online version should be on @TheSpinoffTV in some time for those that can't afford or access Mana x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For 6 months I fllwd a bunch of resilient rangatahi and cool mh workers working to prevent Māori suicide. Story in… https://t.co/uQo9vuRfd5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tinycliffe @noahmccormack just remembering that Noah is an American really :3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noahmccormack visit me and @tinycliffe imo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@featured_nz @frrcooke this the one i tell u bout]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[newtown has a charity where there is a lil block of free computers and internet next to the library. it's so great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jess_McAllen thank u kind ppl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tessairini lil john, he always tells the truth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSewphist I've been trying to find a part time job to pay rent and came so close to a great one but missed out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need happy encouraging words or pics if u have any spare please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mairesmith thank u!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bimbymay I'll be down the road if u need a hug xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sam_Carswell I swear Auckland was way easier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jess_McAllen this is my one hundredth earnest tweet for coming close to a cute job but jus not getting it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is trying to find a part time job in Wellington impossible: an investigation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this is so applicable to nz as well https://t.co/qXiwwnuuWc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jess_McAllen adding "vintage" to trademe listings https://t.co/sgDFnDDwxP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i'm selling stuff if u know anyone who might want things/ want to hate read my attempts to get $ via trademe https://t.co/487Nm0BAu4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@someofmybest why ...does a picture of crackers have so many favourites?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HungryandFrozen made me super grateful i got accepted into tory st. such a gamble. If u ever want gazpachio (sp?) i am jen's neighbour now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it's such a complicated system to understand unless you've been thru it but stories like these r important to show the reality of it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[a really good read on difficulty accessing public mental health care in NZ by talented assss @HungryandFrozen… https://t.co/DaH6iZokLM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HungryandFrozen can i share the medium post on me timeline? x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ravenous_wolves is that @worried_mind's dog??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lightyouonfire i needed this today u angel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[r u a nurse? r u a surgeon? r u a doctor? r u the 1 for me? pls contact jessicamcallennz@gmail.com
*fr a stry, not romance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weird that low income families get a discount on NCEA fees but not the remarking a paper fee ($20 per)?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaronNewZ interesting q for a psychologist to ask haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AliceCooke3 I don't thiiink so thanks x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ctlne imagine if someone bought it for u when in the throes of depression]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beingahouse @elesedowden oh my so relieved I'm not the only one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@josephmoore1 we watching movies at Henry's flat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jess_McAllen i mean it's going towards my freelance tax returns but now I don't have to sell all my soul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i'm an idiot and hadn't claimed my tax refunds from working while studying and now my life is so good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tinycliffe WELL I AM EARNEST QUEEN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tinycliffe not related to ur story but ALSO A NICE THING lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tinycliffe i put ur christmas card on my little board of good memory things coz the surprise of that gift was so touching &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@josiecampbell obama follows you??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jess_McAllen frankly i find methed up suits have more entitlement complex thn stoned beggars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dovil oh it's a woman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dovil who?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if reporters are gna ask beggars what drugs they taking can they also ask CEOs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this video is so weird, the reporter asking the guy: "do you do drugs? what sort of drugs?"

https://t.co/ZCsJwy7k6E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MavaEnoka omg thank u for reminding me i was waiting for a response from last friday from them haah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MavaEnoka yeah it took ages to try and figure it out and it seems real conflicting everywhere so I was curious if MOH had released s/t x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MavaEnoka where'd u get the 50% stat on ppl taking there lives having contact with MH services?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davejac i thought they were tking them out of service today :O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jess_McAllen did u conside they may have just meant figuratively]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this comment on the wellington live fb page regarding the upcoming ~weatherbomb~ is savage https://t.co/MEdpr1HAqI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tessairini i mean not that mad coz a friend paid for them BUT STILL the audacity imo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tessairini ok so their fake chicken nuggets were advertised in a big bucket and when i got them it was a tiny box! so mad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tessairini was it at lord of the fries]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_T0M_V_ we're having a bigggg revamp and i can't wait!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pitakakariki I think GPs sometimes can but its really hard to get. I've never been allowed on them and only got 5 coz they r addictive af]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toby_etc this is rude to labradors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jess_McAllen find u a journalist who talks about their meds on twitter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_T0M_V_ i'm normally not allowed on them so this is like hell yee self control]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my psych gave me 5 benzos while i double my meds (coz a side effect is anxiety smh) and I haven't had any which is a h u g e milestone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kellydennettnz @NZcourttweets pertinent to the discussion on KJC ha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkOneinFour @PennyRed patreon saved my butt last year as a freelancer! x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i wanted to read an article on forbes about why millennials don't get promoted but it detected my adblock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[im still just..astonished that people let u (in a journalistic capacity) ask about incredibly painful experiences and dnt throw things at u?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FreyaDalySad @bvrcoe i love this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomdionysus @NZJon i have posted in there, naturally]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Eve_K !! we never did that walk w jen either. i was tired and forgot bt should we do friday? am i organising in a tweet, wow who am i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this is my new author bio pic. u cant stop me. https://t.co/GgkZ00bAd8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lyndonhood this is not what i imagined cider to look like]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beckeleven @Donna_Chisholm i listened to this while resting my eyes and it was so nice I listened to all of @NaomiArnold spinoff ones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Eve_K can u cook for me eve pls i will provide something.  i just need to think of a talent that isnt being overly emotional xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@someofmybest hot goss from our local new world: there is an apple DEPLETION]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jess_McAllen this is me announcing I have a looong story in @ManaMagazineNZ next month :3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[can i pass off the winter i didn't write any big features as a performative art work on a real life depressive episode thx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tnichss can u write a story about it thx Jess McAllen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@guicueilleurs I thought this was a metaphor until I saw ur reply]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noahmccormack :o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonbwilson @virginiahlarson one by one my favs cave]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@meladoodle same reason i didnt retweet lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AliceCooke3 I have a story due tomorrow but trust me i am DEVASTATED x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GalletaPoco idk what is going on but lots of love x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HadleyDonaldson alerting my parents]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NicolaYoung15 i love the pencils]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RFStew i gave u my heart, what more do u NEED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ranginui WHAT where??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NicolaYoung15 well it's mainly my parents, three dogs, a cat. me and my sis will be visiting tho haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noahmccormack it doesn't bode well that the only reply to this tweet is from an American :'(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@delaneymes_ it us https://t.co/P8bGmGvUxg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[what are some cool things to do/about Whanganui? my fam just moved there - three dogs so outdoor stuff helpful. NO NEgativTYyyy plsss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Megapope @AMidnightVoyage i thought they were Arama's]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Megapope are those ur slippers?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@henrycooke this should be an advertising campaign for the media frankly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@henrycooke the burglar actually just wanted to read the latest scoops in the tron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[is she..on the waikato times website https://t.co/whKgh0ogL5]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>