<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Hmmm. Wonder if 'funkygibbon' project is being run out of UK office?  #goodies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matthewc1465 Father in law.  Which was weird because he normally calls via Skype or WhatsApp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How wrong would it be to propose #sqlsaturday session that was focused on cross-skilling a DBA to work with other platforms; mySQL, Oracle?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrissie1 @Ko_Ver there was no electricity involved. The torture device was based around suction power from the water-wheel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrissie1 @Ko_Ver for example, small doses of iocane powder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr13's laptop is graced with #WindowsInsiders #ninjacat to ensure uniqueness among classmates /cc @donasarkar https://t.co/mlfsjmFjzy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@2degreesmobile You need to update in store/kiosk software to handle current email scenarios. xxxx @ xxxxx.nz can be valid (no .co.nz)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greglow yup. included at no additional cost as part of cable internet. some services in NZ require 0x (landline) not 02x (mobible) number]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The landline just rang.  For a moment I was all "what the hell is that sound?!?!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JenniferMcCown @jdanton sounds like a dodgy area of LA...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jdanton @JenniferMcCown lower middle is the best I'll give ya.  Kansas is middle https://t.co/MJ9OJwR7rY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JenniferMcCown How is Texas classified as the middle of the country?  @jdanton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft are taking leaf out of Apple's playbook; forcing an update to application update installer before the app… https://t.co/M76lHAZMHT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MiramarMike good turnout wasn't it. Very lucky with weather.  Pity it was so hard to hear  @WellyHigh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@freitasm on a bus didn't notice a anything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamFowler_IT is it still usable?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First day at @WellyHigh https://t.co/rMBRVtiicB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MiramarMike we're on our way there too.  First day for Mr13  @WellyHigh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah @SparkNZ and their ever reliable status pages https://t.co/uvJjTH8PFG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @CountdownNZ @matteastnz @stevebiddle  wife got one of these early this morning too. Very grumpy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so, same as last year
And the year before that.
And at least the 5 years before that too. https://t.co/Eiotl5DESN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Phil_Wheeler earlier this week https://t.co/3TDi1oViDA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Petty sure all animals (&amp; most of the plants) want to kill people. It just a matter of time until they figure out h… https://t.co/V7VP3cilCZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[with hands that big, make that man a keeper... https://t.co/r4eiTPgaxe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SparkNZ The biggest problem is the handset I use doesn't like your 4G frequencies :( And Mr13's handset is locked to 2D but that's easy fix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@freitasm are you able to tell me which email I used for your Slack team?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really should consoldate mobile accounts
I'm on @vodafoneNZ
Wife is on @SparkNZ 
Mr13 is on @2degreesmobile]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#thischangeseverything?

https://t.co/tzDovC2ePJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MiramarMike Too much stuff on east side of Welly.  Weta should use Karori VUW sites for new projects...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@geofftnz I know feeling.
I'm considering sending current maintainers occasional anonymous emails; "hey, have you checked the logic for x"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah, when social media people don't read the content before acting. https://t.co/kwgxX1rEhc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dcasousa working ok now without needing login. Maybe @sqlpass are using CDN thats slow at updating @Warwick_Rudd @TheHybridDBA @sqllensman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sqllensman @Warwick_Rudd @TheHybridDBA @sqlpass can confirm the same from NZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sqllensman @Warwick_Rudd @TheHybridDBA @sqlpass or chrome, edge or firefox on PC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dammit. Almost did a @seanspicer by typing creditcard details into the wrong window.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there anywhere in #wellington that does engraving on things like mobile phones and laptops?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drsql @redgate throw @MladenPrajdic SSMSToolsPack into mix &amp; lines blur even more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thurrott three six five]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WinObs you keep away from my luggage...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jpdanner How securely fastened is it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SirSQL Just roll him into the quicklime pit under the raised floor in the datacentre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbrislen I found them too dry and very little taste of marmite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you don't have a disk/belt sander available https://t.co/amu4IIp4zW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Intelanz 7th Generation Core i5 :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeginTry real Oracle professionals are expensive. SQLServer is cheap, therefore their DBAs must be cheap too. SQL is all the same isn't it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AtomicPlayb0y The @2000AD could be complete if my mum hadn't given away chunk of collectioin when I moved out. Still working to reuild]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jethrocarr the data is there. a decision was made to not present that information.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AtomicPlayb0y I tried that once, and they changed artists 4 issues into a 12 issue series. last 8 were an artist I HATE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AtomicPlayb0y But if there is a series I missed, I balk at paying $60 for a collection of 8-12 issues collected. 

Dumb.I know,  3/3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AtomicPlayb0y I happily pay for a number of physical weekly/monthly individual comic titles.  Probably $10-20 a week. 2/x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AtomicPlayb0y of all physical media, graphic novel compilations are the ones I struggle most about paying for. 1/x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AtomicPlayb0y so the GotG reference was the soundtrack, not the move itself?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nakedgeek which linux iso are you partaking of this fine evening?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AtomicPlayb0y Book media I happily approve purchase of
But music/video/audiobook. If digital (non streaming) option is available, acquire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[been there, done that. 
Not with 2016SP1 but one of earlier SPs that introduced new syntax that bit me in demo. https://t.co/gQOg2j8KD8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AtomicPlayb0y you buy physical media?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AtomicPlayb0y so you were sans-comic?

I'll see myself out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy crap.  Bernie Ecclestone has been turfed.  #FormulaOne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CateOwen they followed you the whole block?  Our cat(s) (including past) would lose interest at the gate...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VirtualPCGuy @hypervguy What's current situation with HyperV on Win10 (fasttrack) laptop that only has WiFi re guests talking to interweb?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AaronM_NZ but it's outside. It's gardening not plumbing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AaronM_NZ Also. why the complex connector arrangement?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AaronM_NZ sometimes things go right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Migrating Mr13 from #windowsphone to Android.  He's quite upset about a number of facts (not just loss of apps/game progress)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@freitasm as long it doesn't contradict the comic where Han dies on Earth after crashing Falcon &amp; Chewie is Bigfoot...  @Coleadve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SQLintheWild I know the feeling.  I really needed to rebuild after early vNext build, but in the end my job ran out &amp; I gave laptop back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SQLintheWild but then the license is tied to that machine, and not to others (like your main box) until you deactivate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SQLintheWild custom VM for training?  I often prep too far in advance and get hit by things like that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grrl_geek take a normal teaspoon and cut it in half.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, Monday then :) https://t.co/9rriGrkktr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteffLocke noooo!  You're not allowed to be that young. I visualize #sqlfamily as 40omethings like me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought current events seemed familiar
https://t.co/H6ZVjxE4cT

Thanks @straczynski]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder what happens if you pick the wrong energy source.  @WhittakersNZ @MeridianPower https://t.co/va1AMmbrko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vivster81 Surely you mean @bing it.  @BrentfromNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vivster81 what are you using? I was using a 640 until my son killed his phone. I moved back to 1020 until I needed Android for client work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Acquired from @mitre10nz last week (really good price). Been availble since at least beginning of Dec. Why is nobod… https://t.co/4GCUrtTy5I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vivster81 @stevebiddle you're still using a Windows phone?!?!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just discovered new trailer/epic music publisher (similar to Immediate Music, 2 Steps from Hell, etc).
Soundcritters.
Thanks @SpotifyNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Maps feedback asks the weirdest questions sometimes.  Wanted to know if local fish'n'chip place was good for Tapas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SQLBek your body is subconsciously wanting to soothe the spices from the food. Like drinking milk to help with eating peppers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Phil_Wheeler saw one recently "If you are not intended recipient, you are in violation of law will be will severely prosecuted"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WestpacStadium sorry that should have been AFL; Aussie rules]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CyrisXD oh.  That thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CyrisXD what  is it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WestpacStadium when does ARL come back to Welly?
We saw it last year with FatherInLaw; want to show my dad this year (if possible).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jpdanner Ummm. @lucybols isn't looking at the laptop.
She's either sideways critiquing you, or observing the magnificent bush in the dark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CyrisXD next weekend is orcland anniversay, which means monday 30th is a sit on your arse &amp; contemplate the universe day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CyrisXD Move to Wellly.  We've got another day of day off tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanselman 2339 mean what now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SirSQL /unfollow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rabryst it's a star trek: next generation reference.  Picard is tortortured &amp; shown light. He's told 5 lights but only 4 are there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jethrocarr it doesn't actually look like the picture on the box. Not that that's going to matter apparently. ;p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SirSQL are you suggesting said photo is the new https://t.co/iLpSYchGmi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryancrawcour even in a nosql env similar concepts hold true. changing state is quicker than deleting (Yes, I know UPDATE does DEL then INS)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryancrawcour It's logical they'd just flag row in 'following' table as inactive rather than delete
They screwed up WHERE clause in migrate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZTAWgtn is anything going right tonight?  :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when did @SpotifyNZ introduce "Your Daily Mixes"?  If this is planned as a replacement for Discover, I highly approve.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This implies that @Twitter keeps track of who you have previously followed even if you've changed that state subseq… https://t.co/0LBXRtqM2h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yakmoose here you are without power and @jpdanner is drinking a "Knife Party".
Who the hell comes up with these names?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah.   Wellington in January.
/cc @WeatherWatchNZ https://t.co/sihj9yGF8a]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>