<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia criticizing Trumps immigration policy when their own is condemned by the UN
The words pot kettle black come to mind
#BringThemHere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you refuse to let them in your own country how can you have the cheek to expect USA to take them
#BringThemHere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump yeah australia refuse to take them then criticize you for not taking them.  #hypocrisy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Id love to drop 50kgs"
"Do u wanna come do some exercises?"
"Nah my back hurts"
That's why you're massive
#ImACelebrityAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take your socks off for God's sake Andrew #9Married]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emiliejay87 i wish they would give us some sort of clue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elsielou77 ah just shave it all off then you lose the extra problem of it being ginger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elsielou77 cut it how far? No matter how much he takes off its still gonna look like a perm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's not set up at all is it? #9married]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is this bitches problem.  Youre not marrying him love (fortunately for him) #9married]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow the mother in law from hell! #9married]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toniknz id have just called it off after that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nadia not going for the kiss, so wrong. #9married]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrZanaTuran wrong the countries are Iraq, Syria, Iran, Libya, Somalia, Sudan, and Yemen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrZanaTuran he wasn't from any of the countries banned either was he #stopwiththelies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrZanaTuran Bethlehem isnt in any of the countries that have been banned so not really]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When every other leader in the world speaks out...Spineless australian PM @TurnbullMalcolm refuses #notmyjob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ummm....you can't get married in this backwards country though #BrideandPrejudice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why would your ex go to your wedding in real life? Setup #9married]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're hardly miss universe yourself are you cheryl #9married]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My winner after 5 seconds of watching... betty #mkr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She really loves herself this 26 year old hate to tell you darling....youre not really all that #9married]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickmhTw @TopherField what a load of shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[😂😂👋👋👋#Tomic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jess you can't say to someone "you've not been through what I've been through" when you have no idea about a person!! #CBBUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElliB_123 ummm she's married]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#firstdatesuk
god fearing 😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nelly without the bouffant = yes 
#firstdatesuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has joe got some kind of nappy rash on his face?? What's with the eyes??!#firstdatesuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joe = COCK #firstdatesuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus christ listen to this Ghostbusting freak #firstdatesuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DO NOT invite a girl to an arsenal game!! She shouldve walked out there and then #firstdatesuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GidgitVonLaRue but it pays better than most "jobs"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh snap!!!! #FirstDatesUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did the jerkin guy get turned down by her? Oh dear! #FirstDatesuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow this must be the shittest episode there has been in all 7 seasons #FirstDatesuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Personality of a brick this geezer #firstdatesuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ouchhhhh!! #firstdatesuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#firstdatesUK did he just say a nice pair of teeth?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope his waistcoat isn't halal 
#firstdatesUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#firstdatesUKwho cares if its halal or not its meat eat it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FQ_Window but unfortunately this has happened in every country in the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't call it your law and system.  You're australian it's law to you too buddy #FirstContact]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess he's just scared of the water #FirstContact]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SpaceHurdyGurdy yeah but that's not an excuse you can hang onto forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do they drink so much #FirstContact]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seeya later twitter fam #FirstDatesUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rb_hickey wow i love your eyes😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tim has been the most entertaining of all the guys so what are people shocked about?  #FirstDatesUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tims going a bot too far. Hes going to blow it with this bird #FirstDatesUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK version is far better than AU version #FirstDatesUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doesn't drink. Just get your coat and leave #FirstDatesUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess I'm the only one who likes Tim then  #FirstDatesUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This guy is hilarious #FirstDatesUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haha she'll be asleep so if we're quiet it'll be fine#FirstDatesUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greysfan must be the king of brighton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not george langchild!!! Omfg he knows george #FirstDatesUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mrs doubtfire is back #FirstDatesUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@J0annaRuth next year?! Not enough people on the dating scene in oz??!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shit i forgot this was on #FirstDatesUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdzyPadzy after watching i thought they were innocent but now im certain theyre guilty. Let me know what you think]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdzyPadzy just put "rebutting a murderer" into iheartradio thats a good one. Goes through each episode.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdzyPadzy now check out all the evidence that was left out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do they have to warn that there are dead people in the show #ARIAS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always thought bernard fanning was a surfer.  I guess you learn something new every day #ARIAS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Equality at its finest well done Luke #FirstDatesAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're not getting a second date Luke #FirstDatesAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did he only bring $30?!! Hahahaha #FirstDatesAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I should've gone on this show instead of whoring it around on tinder #FirstDatesAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're not going for drinks you're in sydney pubs are closed already  #FirstDatesAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black eating chicken joke.  Its ok cos he's black #FirstDatesAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toby looks like a serial killer to be honest...just saying #FirstDatesAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gym talk during a dinner date 🤔 can we just order a protein shake please?
#FirstDatesAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You shouldnt reject her before the morning after #FirstDatesAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["My best feature is my boobs" 
"I dont like people looking at my boobs"
 #FirstDatesAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oops #FirstDatesAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First time ive heard a posh aussie #FirstDatesAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What would you like? "Can you chuck an apple crumble in the blender and stick an umbrella and straw in it please" #FirstDatesAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't think so love #FirstDatesAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But why travel through a whole war free Europe to get to uk? #Exodus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greysfan with gonorrhea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah Frankie your parents must be so proud #FirstDatesUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frankie trying the 5 date rule...we all know youre talking bollocks love #FirstDatesUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't touch her you'll get all sorts of diseases #FirstDatesUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[😂😂😂 deepthroating a squash ....line of the night #FirstDatesUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is she even on first dates all she needs is tinder and swipe right to everyone she comes across #FirstdatesUK #FirstDatesAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Id get up and leave pay the bill yourself rude bitch #FirstDatesUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dave_rock_star she wouldve done if it wasn't a tv show]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anniefitness she was shagging him as soon as he walked in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Berbalina yeah we've all been split up now 😔]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She cant eat chocolate but she loves the toblerone #firstdates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are.we using firstdatesau or uk?? Were all split #FirstDatesAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bookies = TAB for you aussies #FirstDatesAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had someone slapped this guy's forehead?? #FirstDatesAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sarah has no rules its just a ploy #FirstDatesAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Annalise has been on the defensive ever since he said he had a gastric band #FirstDatesAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no way you have a 10 date rule
Its probably a 10 minute rule
 #FirstDatesAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't ask if you wanna split the bill if you're not expecting the answer to be yes #equality  #FirstDatesAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bet melvin and jess see eachother again 100% gonna happen #FirstDatesAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Typical kid of today, can't leave his phone alone.  Says me on my phone😂 #FirstDatesAU]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>