<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[US launches review of North Korea policy https://t.co/uYkyK3IOLn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More here: Trump leaves WH unannounced to honor fallen Navy SEAL at Dover AFB: https://t.co/xHw80HmtRk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More info on Trump's unannounced trip to Dover for arrival of fallen SEAL. Delaware Sen. Chris Coons accompanying P… https://t.co/un411aJBqX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We now have our answer. https://t.co/NDLHSxsit5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Where's Trump going" Twitter is bad Twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Latest WH schedule said Trump has a "legislative affairs strategy session" in the Oval Office at 5:30pm. Still unclear where he's heading.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And Ivanka Trump is with him, per WH pool. https://t.co/Uazj7UFslM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@KimDozier has a great look at Bannon's influence &amp; the "alternative node of power" inside the Trump White House… https://t.co/jj6JvMBSua]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schumer says he has "very serious doubts" about Gorsuch. Also says Senate "much insist" on a 60-vote threshold https://t.co/ssxBFRNNWD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Safe to say Faith &amp; Freedom Coalition is happy with the Gorsuch pick. Here's Ralph Reed https://t.co/IbWvDl85Vq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DNC statement on Gorsuch: He "doesn’t have the utmost respect for constitutional values of liberty, equality and ju… https://t.co/MQQWvHCxhx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DHS Secretary Kelly says the department knew the executive order was coming and that it isn't a Muslim ban https://t.co/nu6UO0ZSJX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats are boycotting committee votes for Tom Price and Steve Mnuchin: https://t.co/hW5uCJES0N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New: UK Parliament will debate whether to allow Trump visit https://t.co/cOFUaISusn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is leaving Obama's executive order on LGBT workplace protections in place: https://t.co/5JoNvNSBFF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And #FF @woodruffbets, who has been on top of this story from the very start. Incredible reporting. https://t.co/MJbz7cnswC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Internal DHS numbers contradict White House's claims of how many people were affected by the exec order this weeken… https://t.co/wLwWrIvwwB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump just fired acting AG Sally Yates for refusing to enforce his executive order. Statement calls her "very weak… https://t.co/UTELjs5KE1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScottNover you clearly won]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently @ScottNover and I just made our debuts on C-SPAN https://t.co/YCPseJ3ftw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fleischer: "The press has lost too much of the trust of the public." #trumpmedia @SMPAGWU @GWmedia https://t.co/NnEywTyvvD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@jeffmason1 on Trump's sour relationship w/ media: "That tension is healthy and normal, and it's going to continue." #trumpmedia @SMPAGWU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ari Fleischer: "I love thar you all recognize how much you love and miss George W. Bush." #trumpmedia @SMPAGWU… https://t.co/qjDQLPXBFR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Acosta's first comment for panel after Spicer interview: "I think we heard some alternative facts." #trumpmedia… https://t.co/QhXLv1DIj0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@PressSec on media coverage: "The default is consistently about the bad." #trumpmedia @SMPAGWU @GWmedia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@PressSec chewing out Jim @Acosta as Acosta sits in the audience, unable to respond. Acosta just interjected, though. #trumpmedia @SMPAGWU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@PressSec on if he regrets crowd-size briefing: "I'm a forward-thinker." Says he should've taken questions. #trumpmedia @SMPAGWU @GWmedia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@PressSec says he doesn't agree with Bannon's comments, but he "understands" where he's coming from #trumpmedia… https://t.co/Vx6kfmH4qN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@PressSec: Media "always leads with the perceived negative." #trumpmedia @SMPAGWU https://t.co/8LmYV3hhMP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@PressSec Spicer on Iraqi translators now barred from entry into US: "I understand that people may be inconvenienced" #trumpmedia @SMPAGWU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@PressSec @seanspicer at @SMPAGWU: response to executive order was "blown out of proportion" https://t.co/RXGXDun0wB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front row for Sean Spicer interview at GW w/ @franksesno https://t.co/UyPueb5Qfs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama in his first post-presidency statement: "American values are at stake." https://t.co/P7V4ea5OmZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MLB punishes Cardinals for hacking Astros. 2 draft picks relinquished to Houston, plus a $2 million fine https://t.co/KMd4HQeFko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George H.W. Bush released from the hospital after being successfully treated for pneumonia: https://t.co/d93pMDUBOJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@timkmak interviewed a few of them: https://t.co/mvKSLnp7cF https://t.co/knxe7JkL0h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful story by @BLNadeau, who was at Rome's Fiumicino airport today as Syrian refugees arrived https://t.co/SuqReUQMVT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Trump executive order slashes regulations; orders that 2 be eliminated for each one added/created https://t.co/wcBpmYXs6S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@woodruffbets dispatch from Dulles, where feds apparently ignored a court order to let detainees see lawyers: https://t.co/UOVbpPmKko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In addition to Bannon's appointment to the National Security Council, @PoliticoRyan reports the Europe &amp; Russia pos… https://t.co/wjtIznVaXg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New statement from Trump: "To be clear, this is not a Muslim ban, as the media is falsely reporting." https://t.co/iHSWBWgTsI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The part of the EO that suspends the refugee program is getting much less attention as Dems focus on airport messes https://t.co/jjEo1ED1kz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In what appeared to be a reversal, Priebus said the executive order doesn't apply to green-card holders:… https://t.co/8vWp84xVlT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McConnell shrugs off Trump's executive order as Priebus sows confusion over who it applies to. Me: https://t.co/jjEo1ED1kz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McCain &amp; Graham: "Ultimately, we fear this EO will become a self-inflicted wound in the fight against terrorism." https://t.co/3qfLyNyO6T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thread: McCain criticizes Trump's executive order. Says it wasn't "properly vetted" https://t.co/yzznOyF0Na]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House releases statement after a U.S. servicemember is killed during a counterterrorism raid in Yemen… https://t.co/jAsgbctXiP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@timkmak spoke w/ Iraqi translators who worked w/U.S. military, were vetted &amp; granted visas, &amp; now can't enter U.S. https://t.co/mvKSLnp7cF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Italy's Matteo Salvini backs Trump's executive order: "An invasion is underway, it needs to be blocked." https://t.co/Q6NJttAbNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cory Booker's unusual method of contact with CBP officials at Dulles airport last night, via @woodruffbets —&gt;… https://t.co/QE1ZzrfXRD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@woodruffbets' dispatch from Dulles airport, where Trump's first major constitutional crisis unfolded: https://t.co/GCdVtMvWU7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton tweets support for protesters, say of refugee ban: "This is not who we are." https://t.co/ovuJhrUJLl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Members of Congress showing up to JFK airport with protesters https://t.co/Ojv1iqlUXU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Sunday shows will be fun tomorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ff @woodruffbets following the protests at Washington Dulles airport https://t.co/3j2ubkqAe4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oakland A's throwing some shade at Trump over crowd sizes... https://t.co/KgXwOboviB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House readout of Trump's one-hour call with Vladimir Putin. Kremlin's readout was released a few hours ago https://t.co/Qv5m90mlQX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@justinjm1 writes on the detentions at JFK airport, whose namesake was challenged for his Catholicism: https://t.co/bX4OJFj7hP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More: Senior administration official says of the executive order, "We're dealing with a relatively small universe of people."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEW: Senior administration official says green-card holders from the 7 countries "will need a case by case waiver"… https://t.co/wxqabdEZ8b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Readout of POTUS' call w/ Merkel—lots on NATO, including: "ensure all Allies are contributing their fair share to o… https://t.co/d2n5Adj1Py]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 Syrian families who arrived at Philly Int'l Airport from Doha this morning were detained &amp; then sent back: https://t.co/0zCXaXDtOn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's executive order is now having the effect of preventing Muslims who have valid visas from returning to the US https://t.co/AP7W6vTDyr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New: @VP Pence will join @POTUS Trump on phone call with Vladimir Putin https://t.co/odpjdOo8eU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump executive order says admitting Syrian refugees is "detrimental to the interests of the United States"… https://t.co/DLZB8JzmSc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More executive orders on Trump's schedule tomorrow. Topic(s) unknown. He'll also speak w/ Shinzo Abe, Merkel, Hollande, Putin, Turnbull.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It also blocks new visas to individuals coming from Iran, Iraq, Sudan, Syria, Libya, Somalia &amp; Yemen for 30 days: https://t.co/XlwzsSnZwZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEW from @KimDozier: Trump executive order suspends Syrian refugee program indefinitely https://t.co/XlwzsSnZwZ https://t.co/MMSB4RPooT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump signs executive order that temporarily suspends refugee program &amp; suspends Syrian refugee program indefinitely https://t.co/XlwzsSnZwZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It’s a day by day situation and I’m definitely scared to go to work but what else am I going to do." https://t.co/Rm2F9BBFoz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump reportedly floated the idea of scrapping the Electoral College. Mitch McConnell quickly shut that down https://t.co/ADBCMWqyZP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MLB Commissioner Manfred has met with the Indians' owner over a possible logo change: https://t.co/OTwk3sKQin https://t.co/HMFFP6p2D1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump on yielding to Mattis on torture: “He’s an expert. He’s highly respected. He’s the general’s general." https://t.co/F7xRglSqnt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From @BLNadeau: Will a Celebrity Get the Vatican Ambassador Job? https://t.co/LHetoE78IE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@POTUS Trump says Mattis can override him on torture/enhanced interrogation, even though he thinks it works]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@POTUS Trump after tough, smart question from @bbclaurak: "There goes that relationship." ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Trump is a Cowboys fan." https://t.co/IoLZc9826V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theresa May on her meeting with Trump tomorrow: "Have you never noticed that opposites attract?" https://t.co/HODKgFqmJL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Via pooler @DavidNakamura: Trump motorcade in Philly heckled by protesters booing and shouting "we hate you" &amp; "go home"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[News aboard AF1 via pooler @DavidNakamura: POTUS executive order today "likely to be further detail on the investigation into voter fraud."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Via pool, Spicer on EPN cancellation: "We will look for a date to schedule something in the future."… https://t.co/arGyq7endY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BREAKING: Mexican president cancels meeting with Trump after border wall flap https://t.co/pxRn3j55TU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Trump boards Air Force One for the first time https://t.co/MxDn29NfrK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former top Clinton staffers unload on David Brock, via @swin24 —&gt; https://t.co/iy8qPxlTry https://t.co/G5dSM8iLWy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Ryan, Mitch McConnell rebuke Trump on torture, @timkmak reports https://t.co/tLUegPY2zk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[File this one under: Because of course.

https://t.co/Fj8XU4SZTl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“[David Brock's] ability to produce wins for Democrats is nonexistent,” Sanders' former campaign chief tells @swin24 https://t.co/iy8qPxDuj6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pmaxwell @taylqrgang yep, looks like one of those automatically-generated passwords]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's the section of Trump's executive order pertaining to the border wall https://t.co/xD9jWgeiXJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mixed ruling on Italy's electoral law opens the door to early elections https://t.co/2A94h8f1Id]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And unfollow @swin24 first. #UnfollowSwin https://t.co/fPdBN3xG0Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spicer says Trump was presented with "studies and evidence" about illegal voting, but declines to elaborate. https://t.co/LvQfnxh56y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Avalanche Hotel’s Miracle Puppies Keep Hope Alive https://t.co/dcHHbFBhQl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Decision coming tomorrow on Italy's electoral law; ruling will signal when elections can reasonably be held https://t.co/A1kzbdQUwF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The date is wrong on this. Says January 21, 2017. https://t.co/EoTAFxhQE1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graham: "This is going to erode his ability to govern this country if he does not stop it." https://t.co/NoGAtHxz8z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DoJ could face lawsuits for accidentally doxxing immigration judges as part of a FOIA request, @woodruffbets reports https://t.co/vM487y3b6O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok then https://t.co/9dOZgbZbT3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow at 11am, @POTUS Trump will sign another executive order. Topic not specified by the White House.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KailiJoy Did you read the story? It quotes groups like the Congressional Progressive Caucus &amp; other Dems. Was never claiming Bernie is one]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>