<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonPHT After 51 games, same 52 points as last season. Only 3 up on 28th instead of 5, and have a worse GF/GA differential than last year]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Proto I think "Superbad" would still fit in this game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonPHT Awful idea. Trading Shinkaruk + a pick in order to keep a waiver caliber replacement level player?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pheenster01 Let me ask you this: if you trade Virtanen today for Josh Jooris, and Virtanen ends up a bust, is it still a good trade?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dbekar81 @Van_city_Nucks @Stats87 @Tmart1040 @tweetalex997 @Arpannnnn 52 points in 50 games this year. Had 51 in 50 last year lol28th place]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Van_city_Nucks @VANcanucks92 @Tmart1040 Granlund is Brandon Pirri. Same player. Pirri was recently waived.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Van_city_Nucks @VANcanucks92 @Tmart1040 With Granlund's icetime? I'm sure he could be as much of a liability. No doubt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Van_city_Nucks @Stats87 @Tmart1040 @tweetalex997 @Arpannnnn @dbekar81 Can't stand management that's destroyed this team]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stats87 @Tmart1040 @tweetalex997 @Arpannnnn @dbekar81 @Van_city_Nucks Except he's hurting the team with all the goals scored against him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stats87 @Tmart1040 @tweetalex997 @Arpannnnn @dbekar81 @Van_city_Nucks A smart GM gets baertschi for cheaper. He was done in Calgary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stats87 @Tmart1040 @tweetalex997 @Arpannnnn @dbekar81 @Van_city_Nucks Granlund is a liability who's a replacement level player.Dime a dozen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VANcanucks92 @Tmart1040 @Van_city_Nucks Granlund is an NHL veteran. Shinkaruk is still a prospect who is waiver exempt. Big difference]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tmart1040 @Van_city_Nucks Doubtful. Granlund would likely have been waived by now. Canucks could have him and Shinkaruk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tmart1040 @Van_city_Nucks Giving up a prospect who's producing at the ahl level for an NHL replacement level player is not a good deal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Van_city_Nucks @fr_aquilini Brandon Pirri could have been had for free and been equally as bad defensively and inefficient offensively]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Van_city_Nucks @fr_aquilini Good for them. You're wrong though. Baertschi sure, but Granlund is a replacement level player statistically]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnnyNuck @Van_city_Nucks Based on the stats.His GF%, GA60, and his scoring chances against.On ice for almost double the goals he produces]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Van_city_Nucks @fr_aquilini Wrong. Granlund is a big defensive liability and poor offensively given his minutes. Ditto with Sutter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fr_aquilini Not on the right track at all. Team lacks elite prospects. Almost every trade Benning has made has hurt this team]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arsmaster69 She would be the Jim Benning of the US education system.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarciaOnTheGo Bernie Sanders represented change, DNC stacked the deck against him. People didn't vote or went for trump. Now we all screwed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarciaOnTheGo Clinton's antagonization of Russia was concerning, and was a pure establishment candidate. People wanted change]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@willesonsports If Benning and Weisbrod are back I'll boycot the team completely. I can't support the mess they've created.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@botchford @taj1944 @SatiarShah @SHAP4LIFE @DavePratt1040 Team has same pts total as after 50 last year. Other teams around them got worse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sportsnetmurph Jim Benning has said he believes this is a playoff team.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshRowlands9 @BeggsTHW Pirri scored 22 and could have been had for free. Also Granlund hasn't scored 20 yet, so....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DustinDame @arsmaster69 The team's point total is roughly the same as this time last year. Others around us have just got worse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Canucks Why is our leading scorer on the 3rd line?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeggsTHW His goals against/60 is awful. Yes his PDO is low, but it's worth noting his linemates play better without him than with him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshRowlands9 @BeggsTHW Brandon Pirri scored 22 but he was traded for a 6th round pick and was on waivers this year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeggsTHW Just because you say he has a good 200 foot game doesn't make it true. Defensively he's been awful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattsekeres @BeggsTHW Granlund has been awful defensively and has been scored on at an almost 2:1 ratio as the offense he's produced.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeggsTHW @mattsekeres Granlund is a replacement level player. Good comparable is Pirri who was just on waivers. That's still an awful trade]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NicholsOnHockey @FanRagSports Benning knew every other team would struggle? Canucks with same point total as this time last year....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattsekeres Been doing it all year. We're only 3 points out of 28th. ðŸ¤ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JakeCanuck @GovindMinhas Not true re:draft. There's a drop off after the 7th or 8th pick. Plus anything that gets Benning/Linden fired = ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GovindMinhas I see it as the opposite. This hurts the Canucks long term. Finishing 9th or even 8th and being smashed won't help anything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bunktuzzi44 Of course not. Dallas is playing. They won last week. Those reports Green Bay beat Dallas were just fake news #alternatefacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JDylanBurke I posted this on a message board. Recovered at the 1 and he rolled into the end zone. Shocked no review.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoLeviMitchell I got the same prediction. Green Bay and New England. Should be an exciting Super Bowl.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SatiarShah @SFOJay Lol there's no way 19 should be up. Captain invisible during the playoffs. At least Linden meant a lot to the community]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Proto @DustinDame These are the same people who think Benning will make the Canucks great again. Seriously. SMH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@canuktraveller @TheGreatHockey uh this team improved defensively when Gudbranson went down. He's going to be grossly overpaid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@canuktraveller @TheGreatHockey LOL against a bad Nashville team. Just wait until February/March. Tougher schedule.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@botchford Maybe there was a spider on his finger and he wanted to shake it off before putting it near his mouth?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@imacVanSun Uh wrong result. That should have been a good goal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ochocinco Absolutely. Great young QB, franchise RB. That team will be a force for years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheStanchion He was sour about the Cowboys losing and wanted to take it out on the Canucks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GovindMinhas Only good game so far these playoffs, but was a classic. Wanted Dallas to win, but supporting Green Bay going forward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nuckles37 @Verviticus @HockeyDipshit @DubiousRhino It's a shame @arsmaster69 got banned yet trolls like Krutov, Grangod, and others remain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Verviticus @HockeyDipshit @DubiousRhino It's insufferable. Stat deniers who think their opinion is correct "just because" w/o any evidence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didn't realize how bad #NFL officiating is. So many missed pass interference calls. It's insane.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdlundEric I got Dallas and Pittsburgh today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ochocinco I'd probably beat you but I don't have the game. Let's settle this in Madden 2k15? ðŸ‘€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeSantagato Enjoying my chicken permission and Julius Caesar salad on a Saturday night. ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JDylanBurke Do you prefer using corsi metrics over scoring chances/high danger scoring chance metrics?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@botchford Might protect Megna instead of Horvat who's just a checker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdlundEric @BCLions @Bighill44 @Saints Would be nice to see Biggie get a Super Bowl ring to go with his Grey Cup ring. Elite club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nuckles37 @BlakePriceTSN This]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@T_cat53 Congrats on signing with the Colts! Good luck, and represent!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlakePriceTSN Or, like you said and like other teams have done, go a man down if you can't get an emergency call up in time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlakePriceTSN If Rodin is too hurt to play, why not dress Hutton if you're going to bench him anyway? At least have the D on the bench]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlakePriceTSN Huge respect for you for telling it like it is tonight and calling out the team (and Shorty) about Rodin's treatment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdlundEric Tough to go with San Antonio when they had a 1st overall pick in that span, while others like Detroit have never missed playoffs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picks for this week: Raiders, Seahawks, Steelers, Packers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulosenra @sportingintel I see no reason why the #CFL can't enter the top 5 on that list. Outside of stadium capacity in some cities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SDesai71 @AndyCole84 @botchford Lol Benning doesn't have a clue how to manage a sandwich, let alone a hockey team.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front row at #YukYuks to see @DinoArchie tonight!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zoeydeutch Canada has universal health care. I don't understand why the US is so resistant to a similar system.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TSN1040 Tkachuk. No question. Not hindsight either as I was screaming this on draft day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such a BS way to ruin what was an amazing #WorldJuniors game. Shootouts should never determine a gold medal game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ain't she a beauty? Good weight on it. Happy to win some bling playing #fantasyfootball https://t.co/Hbtx9hDn8p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DudeAb1ded Why does he deserve credit for Granlund? He's been awful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taj1944 Must be due to that winning culture they established by finishing 28th last season]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DinoArchie Happy birthday! Hope you had a great one. Planning to see your show on Friday at Yuk Yuks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlakePriceTSN probably when the Canucks get new management/coach who understands Sutter is overrated and shouldn't be getting those mins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BowelAuger @GovindMinhas @botchford Raymond, Ballard, and a second*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats @Bighill44 on signing with the Saints. Will miss you in BC, but I'll be cheering you on to get that Super Bowl ring now! Good luck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joservice @markhmasters Motivation? This is the semi finals of an international tournament. What more motivation would they need?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavePratt1040 You guaranteed they would make the playoffs and win a round last year. Please stop guaranteeing things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arsmaster69 I thought Granlund was supposed to be Bergeron? Sutter was compared to Toews. Smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@botchford Keep Tanev, trade Gudbranson who's an overpaid bottom pairing defenseman.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlakePriceTSN Ergo, Canada is better than Sweden ðŸ˜‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Proto Eh...he did some good for Germany economically, but the idea Hull was talking about was a terrifying horrific idea. SMH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patersonjeff You mean you don't frequent the Roxy too often? lol. Happy new year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy New Year!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BakesTakes84 Yup same game. One of the best hockey games I've ever seen. The Russia game in that year's SF was amazing too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@omgitsdomi @mirtle Amazing what a proper rebuild can do. #Canucks take notice?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JDylanBurke Jason Megna was on the Canucks top line....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patersonjeff Best part of getting sick over Christmas is I had absolutely no desire to leave the house today lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Proto My prediction is a Cowboys/Patriots super bowl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CamChism Happy Birthday and Merry Christmas!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas @IAmJericho and @FightOwensFight You both made the Christmas List! https://t.co/bllEb3wzaC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas @rolly_lumbala46 I hope you and your family have a great one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas @SGore85. I hope you and your family have a great one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas @T_cat53! All the best to you and your family.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas @dantemarsh! All the best to you and your family.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas @crainey3. All the best to you and your family.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas @JJ_Jennings10! All the best and congratulations on your upcoming wedding.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas @TravisLulay and to your family. All the best, and I hope you have a great one.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>