<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Draft done zzzz hopefully it looks good enough to put out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@InciseG @dephh_csgo the waterfront is really nice looking, also the court where the celtics play]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dephh_csgo if you can, catch a game at Fenway or at least go there to see it, the Public Garden, bunch of museums about history n stuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheGrech obv still draft but when it's out im sure itll be crisp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheGrech when you read it you'll feel like you're amongst the stars with them 😂😅]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheGrech :O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@omgxamanda depends on the kind of unhealthy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheGrech hello from the other side]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wizardriesx @ToastMetal cool can I play siege with u next I am a plat but dw I don't rage XDXDXD nice PC btw!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hehe

stars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait to publish this piece though, feel like it's really hit or miss but I'm hoping to the stars that it's a hit.

Slightly nervous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wizardriesx fuck the forest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yo anybody watch that show "The 100"?

any good?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinMDee @SrsEsports but ya rain is goat and has been for a while iirc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinMDee @SrsEsports also focus was kids that could have a breakout year or did last year and will continue to improve significantly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinMDee @SrsEsports he's been up there for a while and is constantly highlighted, tried to do most that aren't acknowledged as much]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[really want to mm/pug like a madman when im in the USA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noshirt_tv missed the fuck out of u no homo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tyonzz @wizardriesx @ToastMetal u should hear the dropkick nonces he's playing with right now the 24 monsters and 1 shake is needed 100%]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[kids act so differently when they play with streamers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@witmerCSGO can confirm, used it to dm when i was in the US and kids would just flank or wait at the spawn, impossible to do anything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Arsenal waking up to this news like https://t.co/ip79k53LXp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I remember when the weather was the least trusted bit of the news]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wrote about the 10 CS:GO players I think you should keep an eye on in 2017. 

https://t.co/sKHkUvOHrz

Some inclusions may surprise you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cowiiiie thnx u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SPUNJ best of luck! you'll nail it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adorbss the boriung guy fuck OFF ROMAN SHIT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinMDee LMFAOOO STOP BRO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[dear twitter

listen to rush]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ELBlackout do u get the trail mix with the chocolate in it or nah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another make or break piece incoming

For now it's in the stars 😎]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@astralisgg I want those Astralis pants man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheGrech hey thanks, some of them were wonky throughout but at least i got the big one woo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whilst I may never be able to make esports a paying career option, I still love it (CS particularly). Watching it grow everyday is amazing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[after watching a pro cs event I go into mm expecting everyone to play like the players I just watched 

huge and repeated mistakes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feel like I'd be a sick hype man for a team 🤔]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @astralisgg if you guys sold the sweatpants(?) like Dupreeh wore at the major I'd definitely buy some 

Just saying!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheMeowzar he just didnt give a fuck, we were used in a 1 off thing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheMeowzar guy bragged about spending hundreds on alcohol and drinking when he knew he had money owed, and bought steam games on the reg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheMeowzar lmfao shits a joke we got rid of him but the man still walked away with essentially free flights and accomodation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheMeowzar did u ever get anything? think u got ur last one at around august iirc?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheMeowzar LOL i purged him from everything ages ago - he stopped like a month after our big spiff - want to say around Sept?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adorbss shoved down our throats lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adorbss 30 should've been anyone else

it had to be him
when it reigns
it pours snores]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MlbsPenguin SHIT PROMOS WAS SHOVED DOWN MY THROAT HANDED EVERYTHING FUCK HIM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[could've had ANYONE ELSE but you had ROMAN REIGNS

such a waste]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[what a waste of a 30 slot

boo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessbubger @ChilledChaos nobody saw this one coming :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the rumble went from yoooo to

why]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MlbsPenguin FUCKING SICK THO LIKE WTF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[that match https://t.co/fh6qKiMpD5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I liked a @YouTube video https://t.co/U4JltZNhzR Dupreeh gets personal, opens up about his struggles and what he's fighting for at]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I liked a @YouTube video https://t.co/FRJlDu2qBY Guide to Global: Picking the Right Keyboard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TIL 8 upside down is 8

#royalrumble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THAT CHICKEN AD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Fluffy Warm Fuzzy Stunner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wizardriesx @MyNameIsMachine me at pax and afterwards

sry guys no hangout have to grind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FreakazoidA you're an awesome player my guy, I would love to see you up there and competing in a competition like that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesbardolph THE ROAD TO WRESTLEMANIA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darmuhCSGO idr to be honest, I got into CS ~late 2014]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2012 --&gt; 2017

The era of competition. https://t.co/epxDG0vrD6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not often we have the two actual best teams in the world in the finals, but we had it today and it was electrifying!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love watching it because of matches like this, I love playing because of intense, competitive games.

I love CS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two sides that deserved it and one won. It simply is fantastic. Many people don't like Counter Strike; it's hard for me to understand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These are the kinds of matches that make you want to cry for one team, cheer for another. The edge of your seat, the make you shake games.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoever said this, both strangers and people close to me 

get fucked nerds https://t.co/fEXDnEWczE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheGrech jonah was right too pls thnx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy for Astralis

Gutted for VP

Mixed emotions, emotional highs, amazing Counter Strike

This is a major! This is Counter Strike!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[nah sleeping through this too tired sry csgo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ok see u all at major in 3 hrs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hey @csgo_dev will you marry me xD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love when I can see the hard work and preparation that teams do in an actual match. I love seeing improvement.

I love Counter Strike]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ms_shadowfax was actually rly impressed w/ you guys tonight, can only go up from here. keep up the excellent work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving this T side so far from @MythixCSGO on Cache.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not a bar James. https://t.co/1DYT9qlxdI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate false reports that are built up and written as legit, the shit actually pisses me off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The writer's "sources" are incorrect. 

Cloud9's owner, Jack has also stated that the rumours are false… https://t.co/7Zn5O2aCGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[fuk major final tomorrow at 2am

gym

then royal rumble

fuk fuk fug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adorbss it'd be perfect for a number 20-30]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArticXD ur fine then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArticXD optimism and an open mind is key to fighting negativity, closemindedness and phobias of any kind

positivity is key]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when you're trying to go inner but TaZ just domed 3 of your teammates https://t.co/Kjd4mzwD9d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@XvG_Ecko ya good idea tbh thnx ill do some emailing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@XvG_Ecko mmmm ok, my flight leaves on the 6th of march so i just needed to know if i was gonna miss it/cut it close]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[does anyone know when they're shipping out pax east passes btw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paszaBiceps very well played, i hope you win tomorrow! GLHF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[fuck it im waking up for this final idgaf team lets go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheGrech one hunned percent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[what brand pants is taz wearing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheGrech im really impressed tbh, felt like they integrated him well and he was an actual team member, and not just a temp stand in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At this point SK/VP must have some sort of rivalry.  Every game between those two has been fantastic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VP ARE GOING TO THE FINALS BABY

MY PICKEMS ARE SILVER YO

WHAT UP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[look i care about my health

please no overtime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MATCH POINT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArticXD would be a godly final, and i think ppl will be happy no matter who wins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[basically what im trying to say in a nutshell https://t.co/yelSnl97zw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[need to nerf that fucking UMP tho holy shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's definitely looking more comfortable w/ the AWP on Cbble now, and tbh overall fox had a decent event @ a major for a filler. Well done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SK's run in this tournament has been sick, and I've been impressed with how they've integrated fox, but he's looking real weak on Cbble imo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ToastMetal y this not ur twitch pic smh ultimate disrespect to the artist by not showcasing their work 

sm
h
@wizardriesx]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>