<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@lbcoen ah yes, the drownings. So much more colour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@valerieloftus aw I'm jel that actually sounds lovely]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bubblenoma well luckily I got it the same time as this boy I used to get in trouble for pinching]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bubblenoma loads of people got ringworm it was like an initiation of sorts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@motlinebling I bought a vanilla one to decrease the uneasiness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FUGOSLAVIA I stole this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's was from touching a gate though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I once had ringworm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andgoseek I fucking know. It smells nice and was a euro though. But I feel like crap after it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate myself so much for buying this https://t.co/HDYRaGsux9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@luigii249 ah I didnt read that sorry. You can never be too careful these days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@luigii249 WHY WOULF YOU PUT THIS NEAR YOUR LAPTOP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's it now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big line of traffic on manor street, is there something on?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Broken glass all over Smithfield, did something happen?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I call these mom tweets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickyRyan_ yeah well it's clear where the money is going isn't it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@valerieloftus @NickyRyan_ aw I'm mortified I was very flustered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delight to meet @NickyRyan_ while getting a few bits there in Aldi. He'd a v fancy whiskey so I can only assume he does the big shop in M&amp;S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bubblenoma I don't know his second name but he used to send out the educational samples]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feel unwell. She was sussing my mood out to break the news and all. https://t.co/FlQuzMjPWC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MLSaperstein sure thing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sound guy at work is leaving but I don't know much about him &amp; just had the Halloween pics. Rip u will live on fore… https://t.co/h6AAdqzy8X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will somebody get that Wayne Rooney Whitney Heuston tweet on a mug for me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theirishfor TAIM AG CAOINEADH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greeneggs_ @rbcakn i've been hotboxing the shed of late i will admit but i wouldn't say FULL of problems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MauriceCotter @leedalyire yeah, that would be embarrassing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MauriceCotter @leedalyire do you think you were punked by some kids Maurice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leedalyire yeah it's sealed. which is even more suspicious. bc it shouldn't be suspicious. if that makes sense?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rbcakn you should come over sometime. we have 2 couches and a shed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leedalyire lee, it's definitely a trap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is absolutely a trap. I've never seen anything look more like a trap, in fact. https://t.co/r8hAiXcSml]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@storkboychoons @Bubblenoma @JurassicArse please, in these trying times, Gary and his hair were our only hope]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brilliantshane ok gonna do this next]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm watching the sketchiest of the alien conspiracy docs https://t.co/XCdGXIjetK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FUGOSLAVIA yeah obvs i am gonna go straight ahead and revoke those permissions now alri jfc the stress of my life is intolerable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@valerieloftus ew. i'd sue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FUGOSLAVIA i didn't do anything david is really cross at me now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mormonhorse @FUGOSLAVIA oh my fucking god]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[Valentine] @mormonhorse's Valentine should be @FUGOSLAVIA! Who should be yours?
via https://t.co/COuMx6vwmE https://t.co/FRGFAXO74b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greeneggs_ god damn it sam the dogs on the street know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greeneggs_ pathetic, sad, and fake news]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jiffington i hate cryptic jiffy. do you want to double date sometime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jiffington i haven't posted you anything in a while. although not worth my while if im seeing you this week i suppose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jiffington dont get smart with me, when shall we wed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brilliantshane @growth__spurt ahahahahahaaaaaaaaaaaaa. not presentable me even, but actual clinically depressed perpetually stoned me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DCotter1986 first trump, now this. what next]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@motherofnaggins oh god how did i not see this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I use my post its as a coaster. So when I have to pass somebody a note, I have to rewrite it on other post its &amp; pe… https://t.co/GgMVgS4Eqs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mooooooonassi I hoard a lot of food at work and forget about it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I turned this around https://t.co/Wmu85N0o9h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joolsd oooo sounds like i've graduated from dublin and am ready to move to london!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oldasballs do u think i am happy about this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aoiph oh god that sounds unreal. i don't have the parmesan but i have the salt and oil. i also have some tomatoes. there may still be hope]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@petes_sake that cover is unreal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alan_maguire it's all crows and popes from here on out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alan_maguire this sounds like a case for Maguire, Cussen and tannam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alan_maguire aw man sausage rolls are class. This is probably the meanest you've ever been Alan. The bad egg of Twitter, Alan Maguire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alan_maguire Alan in my head it was a fancy salad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If anyone wants to bring me lunch today I wouldn't say no, this is a new low https://t.co/IfSmUeDhCD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@saoleoin 4. wow seems like way longer. that was one of the best nights we've ever had weirdly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah yes, Australia as a barometer for racist policy, that's fine https://t.co/rDuQq6UGW6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Diary entry https://t.co/6c4JrFW1oG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beehassler sounds like an ethical minefield,   I'm out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beehassler would you do a murder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And now, to get back to Mail Order Murders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am so high so decided to get a taxi to the train station and the driver is playing Bob marleys greatest hits https://t.co/EJBxiXmFHH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greeneggs_ oh my fucking god without me you bastard I'm literally dying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope David is happy with getting books as presents for the rest of his life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clonmacart aw the a capella version is way better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is as close as I can get before it starts to burn https://t.co/dA6zju3jSd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jiffington @mormonhorse @daithihartery was it expensive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daithihartery @jiffington David I have to go my mom is ringing me ok bye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jiffington sous vide is making a comeback I read. I like surprises. I eat everything and amnt allergic to anything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jiffington get the hobs going for a frying extravaganza, I say. Basically you're not wriggling out of this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jiffington let me guess. Oh I know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jiffington bacon and cabbage. What's your favourite boiled item]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jiffington ok cool I like a good consensus. Why have you never cooked for me I think that is 1) selfish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jiffington class. I guess maybe we are probably best friends now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jiffington fair play Barry. Ok I will investigate. Does Hollie want to come too. A lil trifecta of love and honour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jiffington what was it. Is Barry on Twitter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jiffington how about Wednesday. Do you want to wear matching outfits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jiffington oh god I'm so close to vomming but I want to eat that also is it real. Yes I do. Let's hang this week &amp; do an exchange]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daithihartery oh trump is bad. Ok.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daithihartery David he's the bad guy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I fundamentally regret the kebab]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How are we at this point https://t.co/otpFk6ERM4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm delighted to announce that I will be ordering a kebab soon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worked out @joemcevoy2 is single because he has the wherewithal to keep blutack in this shiny perfect square in a d… https://t.co/OQgcksNzYx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joe: Who's this?
Me: Talib Kweli 
Joe: Who?
Me: Talib Kweli
Joe: Metallic Welly, cool, cool, yeah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jiffington ohh it was on my alt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jiffington what tweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jiffington she asks about you a lot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leedalyire thanks Lee. Obviously it was my creation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bubblenoma that's such a great jumper do you want it or what]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My mom keeps sending stuff like this to the family WhatsApp and she's really upsetting my sister, I think mom prefe… https://t.co/YGzZnw3ziQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FUGOSLAVIA never, only irl, best friend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FUGOSLAVIA oh my god I'm in cork right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tanora and waffles #fitfam https://t.co/hE2iIJaaSD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smoke weed every day. Roll strawberry laces into bales every day. https://t.co/zp1l577Hrj]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>