<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[where is @pmbillenglish comments? #whythesilence? https://t.co/Jyc3kuugv6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pmbillenglish are you REALLY taking the day off when the ban just happened? normally a supporter, but this is disgraceful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm waiting to hear @pmbillenglish make a stmt re Trump &amp; the ban. We are normally a nation proud to stand up against wrong. #whythesilence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZTAWgtn an hour to get from cnr kaiwharawhara and hutt to the car park by the station. crazy times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/M252sBtHWO ... I wish the world would do this course. (or at least all the leaders i have contact with!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dingfelder ships same day... so it's possible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dingfelder mightyape has them?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[any idea where is evacuated? i'm heading home soon... https://t.co/1m0uhcltbF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[that is by far the cutest thing i've seen today... and I'm scrolling through the cute emergency page... https://t.co/SpvsTlcKFY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[summer.. but other than that! https://t.co/57dpq9kcqB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gojkoadzic sounds intriguing. hope you share after the talk!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wow. chilling. so true too. we need to look at and listen to others more. https://t.co/ZmT6EJ71tH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dingfelder so it's "inconsiderate" rather than a particular speed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dingfelder there's rules (don't know law ref) around not going too slow. 10km under limit for more than half your practical test is a fail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David's talks are always good, haven't seen this one, but i'm sure it'll be great! good luck @DavidJCMorris!  #baot… https://t.co/USHcpeXBcW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally had to clear out my "done" column. It's amazing how many tasks we do! #baot #kanban #imorganised… https://t.co/EdKyyQRBg3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wow. humans suck. lets all be cats. https://t.co/JTEf9v0tpx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WgtnCC any word on Clifton Car park and when/if it might reopen?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dingfelder Kiss definitely the best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_jjw_ supermarkets usually have these things in the aisle with stationary etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ketogenic lunch #yummy #lchf #summeryfood #fresh https://t.co/nl1QgFDyHt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dingfelder maybe - i knew about ethopia and turkey. but my other point stands. unless its coffee butter :) its added to the coffee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dingfelder think its still m to c... 1 because theres more c, 2 because the turks/africans that had c first didnt drink milk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dingfelder a quick google search says dairy - milk is what i search 7500 years, and around 2000 for coffee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dingfelder people prob said the same about cows way back when]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twelve Days - Twelve stories for your true love | PledgeMe https://t.co/wEPGGVKBvA via @pledgeme I just pledged - you should too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[make this every week for a snack... sometimes twice a week! #lovejerky #LCHF #yummy #havetohideitfrommyhusband https://t.co/uWqhXRH2Wg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[get in there people! https://t.co/xBeLA6jaiR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[from what i've seen a beautiful book! perfect Christmas present for the love in your life! https://t.co/6lO03os0Yk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dingfelder cornetto. yes they do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_jjw_ some of the Gulls, like Hastings have staffed premises.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome #giveaway by @ketodietapp and @NuNaturals! #sugarfree #lowcarb #keto #paleo #healthy https://t.co/kkDPWl38zM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ditchthe_carbs one of our favs! so yummy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[great idea! hope it gets of the ground. check it out people! https://t.co/rP8HptYh5E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rosiedaydream you didn't pierce it first did you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emilywailes mommabear could've gone to it! real name "Shirley Patricia Joy" (No middle name)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ditchthe_carbs @NatviaSweetener yes, as you tweeted that i found... only had tpo try 7 supermarkets...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ditchthe_carbs @NatviaSweetener yeah I've been using that, it's good. wanted the powdered one though!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ditchthe_carbs was just trying to order some things (swerve and some flavored extracts) through amazon - no NZ shipping! how do you get it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProcessInColour dammit, thought that might be the case, we don't get back till sat night! Have to be Next time! 😿]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProcessInColour I'm going to see nephew for 7th b-day 2morrow night, in hawkes bay, so that might not work,unless you're free during day?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProcessInColour @RedvespaNZ are they using lego?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProcessInColour argh! fogot you were in town. would have loved to have caught up :( don't suppose you're here tomorrow???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dingfelder we head out to the place by the roundabout at... think it's plimmerton. or the one at the bottom of churton park.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nickfoard_agile I think that is the same one we bought a couple of months ago. I love it! it's a great fridge/freezer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[very interesting article. If we increase the frequency, we become used to it, and therefore there is less sugar coat…https://t.co/ShjGdTe4yO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my latest post - a carry on from the last two on customers and their needs #baot #customervsconsumer #splitfocus https://t.co/4STO3QgIDM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[good to know. https://t.co/9bTujBnaSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome cookbook #giveaway by @ketodietapp &amp; @DJ_Foodie: Taking Out The Carbage AKA the Big Book of Bacon! https://t.co/M9bb1OMpyE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[interesting article #boat #designthinking #customerneed https://t.co/aMva6jeaP3 via @stanfordbiz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ditchthe_carbs had a stevia pep-mint hot choc this am for the 1st time in ages... man! my sweet tooth has changed, WAY too sweet!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook: Facebook, alter the reporting system so it can't be used to silence dissenting opinions. - ... https://t.co/NEDr8t7L5j via @Change]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[little something i wrote #baot https://t.co/fpHl23ADPS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_jjw_ yes... just can't remember how i did it.. it was truly annoying so i disabled as soon as it started]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gojkoadzic why has no one done this???? i'd totally pay extra for no kids flights!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_jjw_  learn - just read the scrum guide. qualified, think they're all about the same price.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ditchthe_carbs  Welly is beautiful (for this 2 minutes at least...)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ditchthe_carbs love how you cater for all :) (i'm in NZ too and not thinking much about icecream)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#boat #customerexperience #somethingiwrote https://t.co/M71JSHKwIM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're the only female in a conference talk... #itx2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#solidarity #lovenothate #JeSuisBagdad https://t.co/cWQn7SlSkN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ditchthe_carbs just made the macaroons in the cookbook you sent me... Super pleased with how they turned out! #LCHF https://t.co/llOg6Wm5Tn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/1c48CCVECX @nickfoard_agile new format coming! looks like good improvements]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my brain goes "this poor fat unhealthy cat" my heart goes "naw, cute!" https://t.co/wF4UuZKdbJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dingfelder can't help you wit that one :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ditchthe_carbs these look great! and the book looks fascinating. #lchf  https://t.co/yhIuhH1B0Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dingfelder does she want one? the why wouldn't you? she's 13 not 3.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please help support Dry July, add a #Twibbon now! https://t.co/5MJb1gHv4m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[very interesting! hopefully it proves successful after further testing https://t.co/Ky3OkLzlpo via @DigitalTrends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[love it read the whole thing, and at the end, its not available in NZ. stoopid little unimportant country. https://t.co/W9FfcJyH3T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shane Ross https://t.co/5EX7LWd5IB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i don't agree, but i'm not sure who is... what is your definition of "best"  https://t.co/2Scky7XSEd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hmmm certainly "grasping" for skills there... Weirdest connect request so far. #yesimthatawesome https://t.co/uRxBzrZ0wN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New toy!!! Loving the @FiftyThree app so much I bought the pencil! #pretty #visualnotes https://t.co/YhXWVis7oB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[heart wins! :) heart ALWAYS wins!
 https://t.co/zXz9J4lvrd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so, i wrote a little something...  https://t.co/dKcPO2fn4u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#autismawareness #differentisnotbad #learnaboutit https://t.co/mjQkfq5gPE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[tried these, and love them. literally eating one right now. #yum #Ketogenic #didimentionyum https://t.co/mGLo6gIl2T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[still think @nzpolice have the best one so far. :) but good effort @nswpolice  https://t.co/1MogOQnbQv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dingfelder naw. can i be a "rando" too?????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[why yes, yes we do. 
 https://t.co/hbyQWqDrcl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[playing with pen, yanking the lid back off the top, there's a highlighter! #thepenthatkeepsongiving #stationeryfetish #stationery4lyf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dingfelder i have those days.... but then i'm not a liberal ;P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dingfelder my, that's not very liberal or democratic :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wtf?? how can these people live with themselves??? https://t.co/Pyrheooceb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[interesting - she makes some good points #equalitymatters https://t.co/uXkRIaiJQ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patchworkraven I'm re-reading all the JD Robb in death books. a bit of light smut to get me through the days :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the 30% who are not me scare me.  https://t.co/tgv8rPZyDF via @nzstuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[now we need ID to pee. #ludicrous #whenwillpeoplewakeup #thumbsdowncops #wtf #fuckthisshit https://t.co/p2BnjPq0Uc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wonder how this impacts those who settled under the old rules? https://t.co/7U5aRUGyYY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEWSFLASH readily available legislation is secret and scary if you weren't aware of it. #iwantmyignoranceback https://t.co/13MLTyrLY4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hilarious! https://t.co/H8OgSAcIg7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[weird place for it - anyone needing to go past there around then take note! https://t.co/MixhTY3HXa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[has anyone else noticed the addition of mint flavoring to lipsticks lately... its weird...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[woohoo, unexpected bene for volunteering on ANZAC day - I get a park at the venue for the dawn service.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dingfelder dom post seems to indicate its in porirua somewhere... whats going on in CBD?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_jjw_ right back at ya! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_jjw_ not could support, would support, do support.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_jjw_ its hard to condense to 140 characters!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_jjw_  heart breaking, well written and I agree. BUT in any other shape, at any other time i could support. not now in that shape.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>