<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The break. The magic.  The beauty. The Rafael Nadal!!! Vamos!!!!!!!! #NadalDimitrov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This tennis is insane #NadalDimitrov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And to  fifth we go.. #NadalDimitrov #sleepisfortheweak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But Rafa is also playing well. Always the professional. #NadalDimitrov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A year ago Dimitrov would have stumbled at this stage. Right now he's playing better. #NadalDimitrov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone get Dimitrovs coach a drink to calm his nerves. The man has been on edge all match. #NadalDimitrov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That single handed back hand though #NadalDimitrov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your player is two sets to one up and you still feel nervous. #NadalDimitrov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just realised it's Nike vs Nike. At least there will be a win for Nike in this... and in the final.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rod Laver enjoying this one. Hopefully reminding him of his hay day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Serving first in the fourth. Makes it easier.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One more set to go!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nadal has got his poor girlfriends heart racing. At least but a ring on her finger to calm her down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dimitrov vs Nadal ... the battle is on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Serena vs Venus!!!!!! This is what tennis is all about!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And it's an all Williams final!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrendanNg1 your tweets are brilliant. Stop making me laugh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blink and it's 18 17 in the fifth. Wow @ivokarlovic @HoracioZeballos @AustralianOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zeballos and Karlovic match just wow. Can they both win? @ivokarlovic @AustralianOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Puig!!!!!! What a way to win!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing. Fantastic. Unbelievable. Words can't describe. Del Porto with the win @Wimbledon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NoleSlam #nolefam! Idemo!!! @DjokerNole fabulous game to watch! #RolandGarrosFinal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rolandgarros @andy_murray @DjokerNole @BrendanNg1 the bromance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally the French Open!!! What a match Novak! (: well played by Murray too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And he's into the semi! Nice job @delpotrojuan !! What a win over Chardy. Rankings mean nothing when your a champ!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HE WON!!! Yes @delpotrojuan ! One match at a time!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He won the first set!!! One more to go! Vamos @delpotrojuan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's back! @delpotrojuan ! I could not be more excited right now for this man!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrendanNg1 can he just marry me already. So adorable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol one more plate and Andy has a whole dinner set. Taking positive vibes from the match.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sealed with an ace. Congrats on the sixth Aussie Open title Novak! Hard luck Andy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Murray being a runner up at the Australian Open. Still a better love story than twilight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SKYNZ Any update?  The aussie open final is about to start]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kerber your beaut! What a win! Great fight by Serenaa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Both Serena and Kerber fired up after each point. So intense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back on serve. What is happening?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay that first game third set... those points. Wow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kerber is like great shot Serena. .. but seriously just give me the game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the least handshake was friendly. But wow. What a way to dominate by @serenawilliams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hmm looks like Serena will serve it out from here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Serena serving up a bagel and a bread stick today. What I call lunch. What Aga calls... wait she got another game. Wow. How?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@halfadams who dobs Mike in? This won't be shown for another 6 months in New Zealand.. #behindthetimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrendanNg1 touche!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She got a game! Come on Ninja!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The warm up was longer than that set.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How is she already serving for the set? I leave my desk for 10 minutes. Now this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. Double fault. Aga needs to reset. Down a double break. And Serena is in beast mode.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AustralianOpen the kid looks the most excited about this match.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A break already! Please don't get bagled. #serenavsaga]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrendanNg1 tease me on FB and not reply. I come twitter stalk you! He looks so skinny there! Oh those two are a thing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ferrer! !! VAMOS! Deserved that set.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Muzza already with the break. Let's keep it that way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Ferrer the walking red bull! A new one but a good one! VAMOS!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiting for 5 o'clock so I can go watch the tennis.. One min to go!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone else picking @vika7 to be in the final?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AustralianOpen @milosraonic @NGVMelbourne @BrendanNg1 he has a gf?????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just to good by Nishikori atm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrendanNg1 neither. That was too much. They can't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rafa is back!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hewitt! &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AustralianOpen Oh Ferrer! What an angel!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No top swap! Come on Hewitt!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When is the top swap happening?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrendanNg1 ferrer is so sad about Hewitt going bye bye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ferrer with the traditional watch putting on!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrendanNg1 I wouldn't mind seeing them top less. .m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh Hewitt we still all love you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How is Lopez playing doubles after that epic singles match? #BeastMode]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrendanNg1 yes please. I need sleep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It mustn't be easy the thought of ending someone's career. Ferrer is handling is well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh Chardy gone too! :( his instagram is the best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrendanNg1 yes? But not with that outfit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh no. Absolute heartbreak. Bye bye Sock. Oh and to Rosol too. My puppet is sad :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a side note the popsicle is still alive. On to melt on to round 3 in the aussie open]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On to set three!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a game! Good hold by Ferrer!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Both men's tops are just now made of sweat. #hewittvsferrer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrendanNg1 no one does. That's why Petra moved on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good hold by Hewitt. Man Ferrer is a beast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hewitt is like this guy is makes me run more than my three kids.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really want Hewitts top minus one star]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One set down.. how many more to go? #hewittvsferrer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a side note. . Come on jack sock!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hewitts top reminding you that you are playing an aussie at the aussie open. Just in case you forgot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrendanNg1 hungry for Pospisil ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrendanNg1 I told you it looks like an iceblock!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's going to be a long one. #hewittvsferrer #AusOpen2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrendanNg1 @ESPNTennis @stanwawrinka he somehow looks like a really delicious iceblock though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrendanNg1 @ESPNTennis @stanwawrinka Ew. So gross]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrendanNg1 it's okay. Back on serve.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rafa out 1st round. Wow. Madness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who saw that coming?  What a match. #nadasco #NadalvsVerdasco #AusOpen2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just a feeling but Nadal has got this one. #nadasco #NadalvsVerdasco]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a point!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nadal with the break!!! Verdasco looking a little sleepy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest thing is Hewitt still has to play after this. #nadasco #NadalvsVerdasco #AusOpen2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't stop watching.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Verdasco looks tired. Nadal has this one in the bag. #NadalVsVerdasco #nadasco #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huge congrats to @BautistaAgut for winning the @ASBclassic https://t.co/CgsEV2H1Po]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantastic win by Venus and Pavic at the @ASBclassic! Let's get the aussie open title now boys!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>