<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuddApatow @AC360 @CNN Agreed. Far too much nonsense going around to muddy the waters further with crap like his. Stick to plain facts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CherryCorday @WhatsFilming I'll see if I can spot any signs if they're still there tomorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRachelFisher @MaraWilson Whoa. Back up. President Fuckwit slagged *someone else* off for looking shabby? Mr Long Tie?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhatsFilming Whole whackload of shoot trucks etc parked on Ontario by Queen E today; crew parking at Nat Bailey. Didn't catch the signs tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Keri_Adams @MinDhariwal OH MY GOD I LOVE YOU MORE THAN EVER!!! (Keri, not Min. Sorry Min.)  ;-)  #sssmokin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimrhodes4real @Mark_Sheppard ...oh boy did he!  Well said!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SabrinaSiddiqui @LindseyGrahamSC He's tone deaf too. And he hates music. And now he wants some money for band instruments. #TrumpMusicMan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PSA: If you like Nordic Noir and shows like Broadchurch, you should be watching @Cardinal.  Really rather good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chumplet Yeah, only a complete asshole would haaahhh I see it now...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ERICBALFOUR @washingtonpost He seems hell bent on turning allies into enemies.  Who does that???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the maestro said... https://t.co/5p5pRoYW1h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@quinncy Is it me or does he look like Petyr Baelish?  Never trusted that guy...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OhNoSheTwitnt I've never trusted Petyr Baelish and now he's on the Supreme Court?  Dammit!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lawrence To be fair (can't believe I'm saying that for him) it's been so long coming I think they might have done it whoever POTUS was...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JenaFriedman I agree with you, I believe you are right, but I'm fucking terrified you're wrong...  #resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chumplet LOL! And neither of them look much like Shanahan!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AP  File in the "so delicious it must be fattening" dept...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Fuckwit's Inconvenient Truth. https://t.co/InaoD8fB1L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JenaFriedman ...or remember that ep of Star Trek with the Nazi Planet?  That.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshrogin @FernRiddell Oh lord what's his twisted bullshit logic going to be on this one...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidCornDC @MotherJones FFS yes!  If this isn't the time, then when is???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I honestly thought World War III would be caused by the rise of the machines but no: Nazis again.  Those assholes are real assholes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tarastrong @facebook WHAT. THE. FUCK. FACEBOOK.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jhaletweets @missjessicalee @WSJ So: The Russian president &amp; a nazi (yes he fucking is don't look at me like that) are running the USA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bobodinkus @ChrisWarcraft  Yeah.  I guess they looked at history and went "I can see where they went wrong"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@goldengateblond Christ on a bike he thinks these things are equivalent to a fucking IMMIGRANT BAN???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smerconish Lol... Sounds like the bots turned it up a notch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PlacidiJoe @ChrisWarcraft me too, but I gave this one a pass since it's a list of facts. Saved me the effort of typing it myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theprovince Yeah, I'll bet they did...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PlacidiJoe @ChrisWarcraft History?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only President Fuckwit would be inspired by #HolocaustMemorialDay to go Full Hitler.  #MuslimBan #resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's Happening?  Yes Twitter, what indeed. What the hell is happening...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[realDonaldTrump Lying Liar Lies &amp; Lies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Deanofcomedy @PolitiFact #LyingLiarLies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN  This will bite hard: Apparently she's the Rowan of the Tennessee yarn shop community...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never used to swear on social media.  President Fuckwit has changed all that.  Fuck you, President Fuckwit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@torquilcampbell REALLY effin' weird...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@allinwithchris @chrislhayes @CoryBooker @MSNBC  Yup. It's true.  Lying Liar Lies (and Lies).  #resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GailSimone @MaraWilson If that doesn't deserve a Picard Facepalm I don't know what does... https://t.co/isIwum6bcX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theprovince So now they're just messing with us?  FFS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess some folks are happy with court jesters &amp; pretty E! puppets...  

I hope you keep on keeping on @aishatyler 'cos you rock! #resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CharissaKinney @slpng_giants Yeah, not sure if @StubHub will care.  But then again, maybe they will...?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Disney: What the hell? https://t.co/EvVkJbMpNm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TODAYshow Lying Liar's Lying Liar Lies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatyTurNBC @nytimes ...and Steve Bannon should go f*ck himself.  #resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theprovince Works for me...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Slate @Lawrence They could start by telling her to fuck off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost Everything else going on &amp; she's talking *sports*???  #smokescreen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Katzedecimal  Comrade: Party of the first part ("America") henceforth to be known as "The USSA".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeauWillimon  "Welcome to USSA; have papers ready"#resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattyglesias It's what he does best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AP Welcome to the USSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gabrielsherman Welcome to the USSA...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN Remember how the right threw a fit every time President Obama signed an executive order?  "He thinks he's an Emperor" etc? Sigh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamestaranto @chrislhayes President Fuckwit better wear his chastity belt 'cos Manatee's gonna be up there like a rat up a drainpipe...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@guardian Lying Liar Lies and Lies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cbcasithappens @CBCPolitics @CBCNews @MaximeBernier TREAT. HIM. LIKE. ANY. OTHER. CANDIDATE. NOT. A. CELEBRITY.  Deny oxygen to nonsense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cbcasithappens @CBCPolitics @CBCNews @MaximeBernier OH FFS don't use his own cool nickname FOR him. DID YOU LEARN NOTHING FROM TRUMP?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AP_NFL  Aww, bless him.  Not much of a thinker beyond calling plays and throwing the ball, I guess.  Very good at that, though...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laurenduca Talking to that woman has been pointless for about 14 months.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Deanofcomedy Lying Liar's Lying Liar Lies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndyRichter ...and yet they continue to serve him and allow him to serve.  This just gets better and better...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kalpenn Absolutely 100% agree. For Pete's sake, it's not like there aren't enough assholes &amp; idiots in that clan to legitimately go after.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kalpenn  Dear god!  He. Just. Can't. Let. Anything. Go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@guardian Lying Liar's Lying Liar Lies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimfromDa70s Awww wall of meat snowflake needs a safe space...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterwsinger @Katzedecimal  ...but didn't you hear?  We're in "alternative world" now!  The Land of Do As You Please!

#resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MBrundleF1  Agreed on both counts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These. Fuckers. Must. Be. Stopped.  #resist https://t.co/9XteTd7LW2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NARAL @aishatyler  This. Fucker. Must. Be. Stopped.  #resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nutrsavvy OH WAIT never mind!  I found them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nutrsavvy Hi!  Where can I find all the recipes you featured this morning?  (I was intrigued by the chick peas!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost Lying Liars Lie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NBCNews Too late!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatyTurNBC Lying Liar's Lying Liar Lies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBCScott I'm sure he does; what do OUR people think?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidfrum Will there be any point attending?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theprovince  Must be an election coming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KieranToTheLeft I *think* this one's bogus. Couldn't find the quote. Shame though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidCornDC Call them on their lies whenever they lie.  And call them lies.  And call them liars.  Every time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeithOlbermann Unt now ve shall all ignore ze crowds in ze street unt discuss ze size off ze crowds at Herr Trumps inauguration...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh and yes, @CNN, did you not learn? Point out his lies within the headline. What do you have to lose? He already hates you. Own it. #resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattdpearce @joanwalsh ...also, in other news, you are massively outnumbered, you lying fascist prick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@soledadobrien @billyeichner Bear in mind this is the man who thinks his hands and dick are huge and everybody loves him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN This from the guy who thinks his hands are large.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Acosta This is a joke, right?  They aren't actually going to try and convince us he had a big crowd? DON'T THEY HAVE BETTER THINGS TO DO???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TWITTER!  I NEED A "LIKE ALL" BUTTON, STAT!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@langtrychriis At least we can spell "inbred"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatyTurNBC ...is it possible for an institution to roll it's eyes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@goldengateblond Indeed. One day that dude's little sister is gonna kick him in the nuts when he tells her to "sit down and shut up" #resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I gotta hand it to you, President Fuckwit; you really have brought the people together in a common cause.  #resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeithOlbermann  Why didn't he run the spelling past his new Education czar oh wait never mind...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JenaFriedman Awww... But I really like President Fuckwit.  It shows respect for the office but distain for the idiot in it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid @Milbank It's what about 1/4 of America has come to, yes. The deplorable 1/4.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Classy move from @strombone1 on Hanks goal.  #truegent #sportsmanship]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBCNews You're really not reading the crowd here: we'd rather rub salt in our eyes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sounds about right... https://t.co/lTSpUlEpfO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN Yep, he's right there.  This is all pretty f*cking unbelievable.  Just not in the way he means.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chronicleherald  Who?  And Who Cares?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@guardian Presumably days 1-3 are "Inauguration then two days off".  Or are you counting Monday as Day 1, like President Fuckwit is?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>