<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrankMcRae I repeat - because he is reflecting the US population's total fear. That is the evidence, I was not a being normative. Jeez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kaitiakituturu We are reducing the number of economic migrants - significantly &amp; way more than the incr in refugees]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrankMcRae Garbage. The point I made  was why America is so frightened. If U can't grasp that then your prejudice is insurmountable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Trump’s immigration policies are an opportunity for NZ - https://t.co/Xe4ca6Fsqu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That sounds about right... National portrait: Gareth Morgan, reluctant politician - https://t.co/xLchDRMXR5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Privilege to give Rua Rautau speech with Dame Turiana Turia yesterday. Thx Donna Hall, Sir Eddie Durie 4 hosting https://t.co/R27nGoWJ8p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_writehanded_ Already announced in our Policy #2. No bans on religious basis plus 'yes' to double quota]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drtimwright @roddrury @TheSpinoffTV we do, just that the hurdle is very high for fast track]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kiwidwj 3 are out https://t.co/j1QMNy8Y4N. Tax reform, immigration and environment. 4th is on 7 Feb, 5th Feb 15th, last 2 in March]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@2TAPU Must admit I saw the term more as a description of one who betrays his own people rather than anything specifically racial]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@2TAPU And you care not that he's betraying the Maori struggle for the treaty to be honoured? Fine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ellis2013nz Personalised  - deliberate, offensive - your view. It's an accurate description of what he's done, communicated succinctly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JB_H14 The evidence is overwhelming if you had any doubt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kiwidwj I was talking about one specific location where swimmers have now been banned. You sound a lightweight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calling Winston Peters 'Uncle Tom' is a big call, here's the evidence behind what I said - https://t.co/Z3MDn63oKc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need more than a soundbite? Here is the unedited speech I gave at Ratana yesterday  -  https://t.co/APxsGLoqmJ via]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honoured to be able to speak at #Ratana again - Here Is my speech https://t.co/fDh2D6VLGW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While Auckland housing keeps getting more unaffordable, Establishment Parties trot out the same failed solutions.  https://t.co/nVwqa6mUMM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While Auckland housing keeps getting more unaffordable, Establishment Parties trot out the same failed solutions.  https://t.co/Y32XQf00Pe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing Housing Tax Loopholes Would Solve Demand AND Supply Problems - https://t.co/Na3fQCNc3u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You Don’t Have to be a Leftie to Care About the Environment (or Inequality) https://t.co/e8U222C1sE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TOP wants to reward forward-looking farmers &amp; penalise enviro laggards. @FedFarmers  call that “backwards thinking” https://t.co/UeNGuDaiJu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is @NZGreens shunning a win for the Environment and Economy? -  https://t.co/OMRFeJ0KQY #topnz #nzpol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garry_reymer @FishandGameNZ @PaulBMcGill did you ready the policy? https://t.co/I1pubbaORI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Opportunities Party #Environment Policy is out - Polluters pay! #NewZealand  #TOPNZ #NZPOL https://t.co/U7HLPcC83X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We just released our environment policy - Polluters must pay! https://t.co/7XL8wydRTG https://t.co/nedWp3f5hE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rhimona There's always one of them, with a bee in their bonnet about something trivial. Talk about a quibble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TOP's environment policy is out tomorrow. Watch this space.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Use_ful_idiot And if we overpay folks our firms shut down. There is a balance, I know where it is. Right now? Too many immigrants]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Immigration Challenges in the Tech Sector #nzpol #topnz https://t.co/uK28lhJMb1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do skilled migrants find it easier to get into the US than into NZ? Yet we welcome low skilled with open arms - https://t.co/H4SU2ajmJ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“House Prices Cool Off” – Yeah Right - TOP https://t.co/fMHUppFr3D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“House Prices Cool Off” – Yeah Right - https://t.co/ws7VlKySHy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the facts change, I change my mind. Wonder what climate change deniers do?(Lord Keynes paraphrased) https://t.co/mvBuh55w2G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can democracies protect citizens from the power wealth concentration confers? https://t.co/WTNnW0vrVU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top 1% of NZers own 20% of wealth - https://t.co/bKMXVh64ew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our hottest year on record, but there’s cause for hope on climate change https://t.co/jqW4TgJMaD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobJStewartNZ @NZGreens I tried to convince Greens to move to centre.  We would certainly work with you if you're part of govt. No probs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobJStewartNZ @PhilTwyford @BenRoss_AKL Have had plenty of working groups eg; McLeod &amp; Tax WG. Just need politicians who aren't Wimps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Opportunities Party to Register https://t.co/FvfvjyfcGD - #nzpol #topnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SergioGE0RGINI S is 2nd order issue. D is by far the big 40 year long issue &amp; is national.Periodic S bottlenecks occur - mainly localised.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SergioGE0RGINI Always wondered how I got a PhD in economics when there are so many geniuses out there.Why is D curve constant? Upskill time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Colin_R_Gale AS wouldn't be necessary if addressed the tax loophole]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SergioGE0RGINI Of course, that's what decades of excess demand leads to. Need to get cause and effect sequenced b4 u can conclude. Circular]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SergioGE0RGINI That's a stretch. Of the 80% over half are below median income. NIMBY's? Think again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pbgates57 No it didn't. Said BB OR OLDER - big difference. Many already retired, no cashflow effects at all. Many BBs also in the 80%]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SergioGE0RGINI closing the loophole will discourage landbanking, encourage building. Supply issues are localised, different topic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pbgates57 The enemy is denial, not the people. Read the blog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisALee_NZ @Suzyiam @Colin_R_Gale It's well past land. We're not still a medieval agrarian economy. Read the policy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TFaddy Agree totally. That policy is coming]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SergioGE0RGINI That's a second order issue. Of course if demand is permanently pumped up, supply bottlenecks will periodically occur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Enemy is Babyboomer Denial - https://t.co/m0Ui3fT8KM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@karlrohde Read the policy. Ask me a question that confirms you have. Otherwise you're just wasting my time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TOP’s policy to make New Zealand fair again; Some numbers https://t.co/64hucvTQyE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tanjainjac weird. Israel is "superficial" too if that's your point. More relevant though is the 2 state solution Netanyahu doesn't want]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mathew_parkin he's horrible, an animal. Any civilised leader knows there are limits. This twat acknowledges none. That's weak not strong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Settlements headed all way to Jericho on Dead Sea. Aim is to split Palestinian in 2. Far Right Netanyahu's goal 2 d… https://t.co/UJLyrcYLA0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netanyahu is a thug. Israelis need a civilised leader, to respect the Green line, &amp; accept 2 state solution. No exc… https://t.co/4D2uVIqBnT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Adriannone1 and about bloody time, those laggards have let Israel go 2 far. Still Trump will reverse it, symbolic only by Obama]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is wonderful. But with Trump coming, Israel will be emboldened to just destroy Palestine Congrats NZ  https://t.co/k5mXGfYZwy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump imminent so too little, too late. If UK hadn't abstained last time might have had time to call Israel to order
https://t.co/4oyI11yi2a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another river lost within our lifetime. We need to fix this - https://t.co/hwtMwtV62D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewAtkin75 No issue there - 2016 a record temperature year yet again. Surely it will come down in 2017, after all El Nino is well past]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrentDoncliff Totally - those are 2 of our TOP 7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for your help @lacticaltd. Nice to see one who "gets it" and is sufficiently eloquent to help others understand.Well done, Merry Xmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matineeidler You're a sad RW extremist, peddling the line all Muslims are evil. Your prerogative, but I dump bigots into the trash 3strikes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matineeidler Such a lovely guy, great display of compassion &amp; humanity, bet your kids really look up to you.The KKK in the US is recruiting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lancewiggs Why? There's no evidence for that at all. All research is about need for high skills if you want GDP pp to lift]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matineeidler silly xenophobia. We're talking 300 people whose lives are in danger. U need to get real. 25,000 in Canada, show some humanity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To Contemplate over your Christmas Cheer - https://t.co/UJqvTL2Wzy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lacticaltd Totally correct. It is all about raising productivity on all forms of capital - &amp;  raising all of New Zealanders' incomes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are reasons to be concerned that the sheer number of low skilled temp migrants is impacting on young Kiwis https://t.co/46QZya4mBO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Zealand and Refugees  https://t.co/N7oI3viP4M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jimbysexypants Haven't Jimby. Wa Kainga won our comp, and was out b4 heard of RP. No issues with coexistence https://t.co/rD6dusIGJi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fight for swimmable rivers continues... https://t.co/HAyH71u3gO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lord of the Rings actor says NZ tourists shocked by polluted 'sewer' Middle-earth  https://t.co/g5fawAKI85]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Paul_Kasner @MxDEJ yeah, thx - pleased to have an army of spell checkers, just awesome. Oh and some cool cats engaging on policy too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MxDEJ Yeah, prob is I can't change who I am, play it honest or don't play is my approach. I just won't stand fools, can't guild that lily]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MxDEJ I have more confidence in voters than that Max. Don't think they're all suckers 4 tabloid media Desperados]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dchwgtn1 @D3vils_Helper No David-leave your prejudice at the door and feel free to engage.But if u can't be civil you'll get short shrift.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tory_selflove @MxDEJ Thx Tory, will pass your congrats to my media guy - he's genius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MxDEJ No - 3 chances to be civil &amp; then you're dumped. More than happy to meet civil with civil. Otherwise go learn your manners. Sorry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NZ's Hard Right now needs logic when it trolls, Rodney's Rabble readily dismissed - time 4 him &amp; Jones 2 Go Dancing https://t.co/P34GvbFe9i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ILJames Sure - how's it going to be funded? That's the difference between dreaming &amp; reality &amp; what we've worked out. It will test Kiwis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@the_probot Thx probot, frustration of those ripped off by NZ's education regime is understandable, they are v vulnerable people, shameful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Zealand Migration Trends - What the data says - https://t.co/HWMeyKcAoX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brian Fallow: Tax the house? It's worth a look - Business - NZ Herald News https://t.co/vpCTrrLLFz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anagilling I say play the argument not the person if you want any respect. Otherwise - sadly - you are just online noise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need immigrants whose expertise can demonstrably enhance New Zealand’s technological progress  https://t.co/Xgw462E8mV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WeEntweet No. Separate issues. Did you read the whole policy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TOP policy two is out. This time we are hitting immigration. Let's get the talent to live here - https://t.co/MRcmzyAsgJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catch the Foreign Corporate Tax Cheats, Ignore their ‘Tax Structuring’ Advisers https://t.co/IPR5Ta63AL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZWatcher @TheSpinoffTV Wrong. Read FAQ 8 on https://t.co/KxkBG593fF. Max mortgage = val of house]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tobesters if I wanted a lecture I'd ask 4 1. Pse stay on topic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hav0cnz @Pbgates57 @TheSpinoffTV Ask me a specific then if FAQ 13 doesn't help. No question is too hard, believe it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@madinnz I realise some need spoonfeeding but reality is there are so many scenarios. See FAQs 29 &amp; 43 on https://t.co/KxkBG593fF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pbgates57 @TheSpinoffTV Well sorry no time for spoon feeding. But if there's a prob just ask again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toby_etc @normnz @TheSpinoffTV thx Toby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZWatcher @TheSpinoffTV Not quite, it's x% of the value (x being the min deemed inc). x is set low enough to make deduc of costs unnecesary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@m4rchmain @duncangreive Aahh so that was your purpose, nothing to do with the policy. C u later slater, trolls not welcome here]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>