<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[A good mentor teaches you how to think, not what to think. #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A single day is enough to make us a little larger or, another time, a little smaller. 
― Paul Klee #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a great reminder... &lt;3 https://t.co/QrY8Ra2mBk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 Simple Steps Effective Content Marketing Made Easy https://t.co/uPfRglUDML]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Streams of Traffic For Your New Website with Wonderful Webinars https://t.co/172yOvKyyg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Easily Solve Project Management Disasters with Trello
https://t.co/LsM8Ol9GC4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your life is an occasion. Rise to it. ―  Suzanne Weyn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Easy Social Bookmarking Tips to Make Money in Your Growing Business 
https://t.co/ihlSSnD6ZW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In three words I can sum up everything I've learned about life: it goes on. 
- Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worrying is like a rocking chair: it gives you something to do, but doesn't get you anywhere.
- Van Wilder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are only young once, but you can be immature forever.
- Hannah Marks #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be nice to people on your way up because you meet them on your way down.
- Jimmy Durante #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerful Social Bookmarking for Free Viral Traffic
https://t.co/rxFoVp9aHN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The true measure of a man is how he treats someone who can do him absolutely no good. - Ann Landers #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Use Social Bookmarking for Business
https://t.co/cDEQaKwuCl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Streams of Traffic For Your New Website with Wonderful Webinars https://t.co/172yOvKyyg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Veteran Social Media Marketer Reveals How to attract a massive amount of traffic using attraction mktg in Just 3 Mos https://t.co/HJpmMsXJX4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nowhere on your birth certificate did it say life would be fair.
- Trevor Jones #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Explosive Growth for Your New Business Using Social Bookmarks https://t.co/9KJzc13dJP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Natural Growth For Your Business With Social Bookmarks https://t.co/1zjPZHQTjg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We all take different paths in life, but no matter where we go, we take a little of each other everyhwere. - Tim McGraw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think BIG. There are unseen forces ready to support your dreams. - Cheryl Richardson #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who rejects change is the architect of decay.  The only human institution which rejects progress is the cemetery. - Harold Wilson #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The wheel of change moves on, and those who were down go up and those who were up go down. - Jawaharlal Nehru #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Website Page Load Time Makes Customers Abandon You Every Day
https://t.co/ZNhDTSxdpo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Use Social Bookmarking for Business https://t.co/rI4jzEVOeF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There comes a moment when you have to stop revving up the car and shove it into gear. -- David Mahoney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Calendar – The Best Free and Easy Business Organizer  https://t.co/fSDq36ZfGc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No Cash – Automate Your Emails For Free with Mail Chimp https://t.co/ccSWDwMpsl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Calendar – The Best Free and Easy Business Organize https://t.co/tOuKkD8FIf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most great people have achieved their greatest success just one step beyond their greatest failure. - Napoleon Hill #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Continuity gives us roots; change gives us branches, letting us stretch and grow and reach new heights. -- Pauline R. Kezer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are going to walk on thin ice, you might as well dance.
- Anonymous #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trust your hunches. They're usually based on facts filed away just below the conscious level. -- Dr. Joyce Brothers #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attention Baby Boomer's, Learn Social Media from another Baby Boomer https://t.co/EDCTmuhcZO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Easy Social Bookmarking Tips to Make Money in Your Growing Business 
https://t.co/ihlSSnD6ZW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nurture your mind with great thoughts, for you will never go any higher than you think. -- Benjamin Disraeli #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Explosive Growth for Your New Business Using Social Bookmarks https://t.co/UgxBjkLUuR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Circumstances of the world are so variable that an irrevocable purpose or opinion is almost synonymous with a foolish one. -  William Seward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Easily Solve Project Management Disasters with Trello
https://t.co/LsM8OkS5du]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free Webinar Solution – Google Hangouts for Your Business
https://t.co/1JxPhu7olQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop! Create Your Perfect Content and Explode Your Business https://t.co/rbT5qMydEh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Write a goal every single month to eliminate a mess from your life, and when you do - abundance will come in. -- Raymond Aaron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Death leaves a heartache no one can heal, love leaves a memory no one can steal.
- Unknown #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The choices we make, and the chances we take, determine our destiny.
- Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Growing old is mandatory, growing up is optional. - Tom Wargo #qusote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Create Perfect Content and Explode Your Business - Small Business Social Media Manager https://t.co/3XGjn7NtGm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every business owner can look like a true expert with content curation made easy.
https://t.co/rycSAOIceA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Content Curation Made Easy, Look Like The Expert
https://t.co/rycSAOIceA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook advertising as a primary means of marketing their business.
https://t.co/U5Y5A1HUG7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life's not about the people who act true to you face. It's about the people who remain true behind your back. - seventeen #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An easy and manageable way to drive more traffic to your website AND increase your reach online. https://t.co/lgn5fTVnz3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't listen or think about anything other people say about you. Just live your life and prove them wrong. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving people live in a loving world. Hostile people live in a hostile world... Same world. -- Wayne Dyer #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mind, like a home, is furnished by its owner, so if one's life is cold and bare he can blame none but himself.  -- Louis L'Amour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What you have become is the price you paid to get what you used to want. 
-- Mignon McLaughlin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Use Social Bookmarking for Business
https://t.co/cDEQaKwuCl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Natural Growth For Your Business With Social Bookmarks https://t.co/1zjPZHQTjg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every achiever that I have ever met says, 'My life turned around when I began to believe in me. -- Dr. Robert Schuller #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give to the world the best you have, and the best will come back to you. 
-- Ella Wheeler Wilcox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Calendar – The Best Free and Easy Business Organizer  https://t.co/fSDq36ZfGc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only those who constantly retool themselves stand a chance of staying employed in the years ahead. -- Tom Peters #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No Cash – Automate Your Emails For Free with Mail Chimp https://t.co/ccSWDwMpsl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Easily Solve Your Project Management Disasters with Trello https://t.co/eg9qkbwZXE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be a champ, you have to believe in yourself when nobody else will.  -- Sugar #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We spend our time searching for security and hate it when we get it. -- John Steinbeck #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am I not destroying my enemies when I make friends of them? Abraham Lincoln #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn to enjoy every minute of your life. Be happy now. -- Earl Nightingale #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High achievement always takes place in the framework of high expectations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@QuoTweety Thanks for the RT, I appreciate it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education costs money.  But then so does ignorance. –Sir Claus Moser #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Build your own dreams, or someone else will hire you to build theirs. –Farrah Gray #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@QuoTweety Thanks for your RT, I appreciate it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want your children to turn out well, spend twice as much time with them, and half as much money. –Abigail Van Buren]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Easy Social Bookmarking Tips to Make Money in Your Growing Business 
https://t.co/ihlSSnD6ZW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A truly rich man is one whose children run into his arms when his hands are empty. –Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Easily Solve Project Management Disasters with Trello
https://t.co/LsM8Ol9GC4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would rather die of passion than of boredom. –Vincent van Gogh #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Explosive Growth for Your New Business Using Social Bookmarks https://t.co/UgxBjkLUuR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You become what you believe. –Oprah Winfrey #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Use Social Bookmarking for Business https://t.co/rI4jzEVOeF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is never too late to be what you might have been. –George Eliot #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are no traffic jams along the extra mile. –Roger Staubach #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The person who says it cannot be done should not interrupt the person who is doing it. –Chinese Proverb #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Easily Solve Your Project Management Disasters with Trello https://t.co/eg9qkbwZXE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Easy Social Bookmarking for You in Plain English https://t.co/0eXFB9tJrc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A person who never made a mistake never tried anything new. – Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn’t fail the test. I just found 100 ways to do it wrong. –Benjamin Franklin #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In order to succeed, your desire for success should be greater than your fear of failure. –Bill Cosby #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Calendar – The Best Free and Easy Business Organize https://t.co/tOuKkD8FIf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No Cash – Automate Your Emails For Free with Mail Chimp https://t.co/ccSWDwMpsl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You take your life in your own hands, and what happens? A terrible thing, no one to blame. –Erica Jong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn the #history of #WWI through song, book an @Am_Songline concert today! https://t.co/CtEPq4PWDE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Limitations live only in our minds.  But if we use our imaginations, our possibilities become limitless. –Jamie Paolinetti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can’t fall if you don’t climb.  But there’s no joy in living your whole life on the ground. –Unknown #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the wind will not serve, take to the oars. –Latin Proverb #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Natural Growth For Your Business With Social Bookmarks https://t.co/1zjPZHQTjg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Calendar – The Best Free and Easy Business Organizer  https://t.co/fSDq36ZfGc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're offered a seat on a rocket ship, don't ask what seat! Just get on. –Sheryl Sandberg #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Website Page Load Time Makes Customers Abandon You Every Day
https://t.co/ZNhDTSxdpo]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>