<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@OddemocracyA @guardian Dump Bill Shorten first for worst sayings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulineHansonOz @getridofthedole All words Pauline Hanson he does not stand for anything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RitaPanahi They who said that does not live there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol. I think you could be right https://t.co/xDc3pczvwl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeamTAbbott @TurnbullMalcolm Yep but that dead duck is going to be there far to long. We going downhill hill fast and his helping]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$20.00 I would not give my 2cents https://t.co/MbK2vfVoJx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TurnbullMalcolm Sorry you deliver nothing. Waffle on not listening to your crap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8 people followed me and 2 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/ojFguIPFSW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought it was peaceful religion. Why the threats https://t.co/GeWIiKeukN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JulieBishopMP please get rid of @TurnbullMalcolm his not listening to the voices of Aust. I despise the man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whozenexxt @australian yep all the grass they smoking does take them there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please Australia junk the greens. They are not looking after our planet or you https://t.co/6aPYc6vjtv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 people followed me and 3 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/ojFguIPFSW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just like our Prime Minister. Waffles on about nothing https://t.co/e82YmIUXMQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marygnip it sure does. He will probably award himself next year. He that kind of mentality]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Welsh58 I am surprised Waleed was Australia of year. He seems to get awarded for dripple on the project]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 people followed me and 3 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/ojFguIPFSW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MariamVeiszadeh hopefully you fight against slavery and stoning of rape victims in Saudi Arabia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now she finds out how deplorable she is. Lol https://t.co/ihRfDXW5yy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StevensAsh @TurnbullMalcolm is on the path of destruction I am sure he will be rewarded as well. Oh what have we become]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Reach1SocMedia it used a hundred years ago I suppose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[13 people followed me and 7 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/ojFguIPFSW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@saul42 the devil will still reign for awhile. His not going anywhere soon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoyfromBurleigh nothing will be banned Once upon a time the safety of the nation mattered .Being popular and happy is our PM achievement]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes why. Why not put all our little ones of all races on bill boards https://t.co/nu07K02JKZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulineHansonOz . Will you  be able to be in house of Representatives at the next federal election]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 of the silent majority watching and waiting to make Australia wonderful again. Hopefully will get a true leader for our nation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VoteTrumpPics @_Proud_American @POTUS @FLOTUS @RightWingAngel only wish they learned how to dance . otherwise I loved it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@havenaar64 we need a huge change in our political system to stop morons from trying leech of the people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ANTI_ALP @TimesofIsrael well they should be  jittery a lot change will be happening.  No more support for Isis or The corrupt @UN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@havenaar64 not one politician has been listening to the people. They lining their own pockets at tax payer expense. Frustrated people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TonyAbbottMHR hope you watching how to defeat the political elite and fake news mainstream media]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What did you expect from the @abcnews. Hopefully our country got a wake-up call and pay attention to mainstream med… https://t.co/EwEZJM5M4S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PearsonElaine if you live in Australia or America you have freedom to choose to wear anything thing you want. Are you in Saudi Arabia now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The women that was stupid enough to march have no idea what they doing. So we have be tolerant of ignorance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rolandscahill @realDonaldTrump well only now I see why he asked that. Because Obama was tiny bit weird about Isis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wish they would march against stoning of females in the middle east. And gays being killed because of who they are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WhyIMarch because they do not know what a vote means. Idiots march for no ff reason. You do not present me as female]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PearsonElaine @hrw tell that to Saudi Arabia. Not the free world]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11 people followed me and 9 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/ojFguIPFSW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chuckwoolery Childish you mean]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 people followed me and 5 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/ojFguIPFSW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whome2013 it only takes one bad prime minister or leader of any country to destroy a nation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God is in control of everything.  Believe it or not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strangemans  And world turned out because of the money. Anyway everything comes to end. Evil will not prevail. GOD is in control not alah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Islam has their own god called alah. Set by Mohammed that the blind followed https://t.co/WCM5ZL3l6t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strangemans where did you get that from. I am stunned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australians do not like @TurnbullMalcolm or shortass. Now seeing Hanson as saviour.  Well she is really. No more @UN its ff useless entity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Australia. In few years we will  a Islamic country like Turkey and Indonesia. We have be fully clothed to go th… https://t.co/E6mBGQzF1g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only leftwing riot and cannot except democracy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything you eat at a take away has dangerous chemicals https://t.co/Hw0LvxuRRE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feminism died many years ago. Women of today have no idea what the f they standing for. Just watch what they actual… https://t.co/0lvEkK4veF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its means we are alive and have emotions. Can feel sad for others and happy with news of a new born https://t.co/uhCkwvakO7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our happy Pm @TurnbullMalcolm while most Australians are unhappy with him and he smiles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australians need a clean slate get rid of the rubbish that is leeching of the tax payer. I do not like where we going with 2 leftwings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saved from what. Americans are more in danger than ever https://t.co/7toHfrBAYf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His right. Its a joke and the tax payer is not laughing https://t.co/lIs8Gajhbk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LouiseMensch very sorry for you really]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8 people followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/ojFguIPFSW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Makada_ his right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 people followed me and 6 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/ojFguIPFSW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @TonyAbbottMHR take note .how trump defeated the media]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australians have no leader. Our suppose to be prime minister is watching and waiting for the media to tell him what to do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh really. What is doing in the liberal party https://t.co/dmzfRmEeSK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gideon41047393 Well they seem to think they know the struggles of normal people. They do not. Thank goodness Americans have woken up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its Hollywood for goodness sake their  whole lively hood is based on pretence and acting and far from reality https://t.co/rsP2yKcFhL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unbelievable really. She did the same thing https://t.co/4glcqlzaPE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 people followed me and 6 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/ojFguIPFSW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9 people followed me and 8 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/ojFguIPFSW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @UN is a useless entity and any civilized country should never support them. They have Saudi Arabia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taswegian001 @Si707 @mirandadevine If turncoat was a good pm all of Australia would like him. His just bad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think the world is going to be a better place your are fool
Its heading for destruction. Read the bible it's upto date]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RitaPanahi I never communicate with morons.Thank u for trying. You are a voice of reason in dark world of journalism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We were all activities at university fighting for justice. Then we grow up and see how to do it. Looking at the politicians]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More God in your life less stress more peace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@infinite_mind A good reason not to watch anything negative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taswegian001 I do not think he realize the Australian people do not trust him. His fake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taswegian001 @mirandadevine Did you see his smile about being Pm. He said it was exciting. Not one mention about Australia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taswegian001 @mirandadevine his worse than Gillard and labor on all fronts. His a fake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taswegian001 @mirandadevine End of the day @TurnbullMalcolm is fraud should never ever been in the lnp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taswegian001 @mirandadevine Well they will live learn  and journalists opinion used to count for something. Not so much these days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taswegian001 let's crown Turnbull the worst ever Prime minister of all time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hopefully this year will get rid of Turnbull and this ridiculous 2 party domination]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucasjlynch @YouTube Who said that. The golden age has been done and dusted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cmbrookins I am going to be the same facing fear each day. Each day is challenge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lyncsmith your right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaveMilford1 its a time of hope. Faith and hope. Without hope we will surely fail in faith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyNewsAust well @TurnbullMalcolm you doing it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[19 people followed me and 5 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/ojFguIPFSW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No more funds to the United Nations they are as useless as Obama https://t.co/UBtsucm1lH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama brother from another mother https://t.co/PwRpn2G92o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ResemblingACult @realDonaldTrump Trump has not been in power yet. So you really showing Obama failures]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OfficialSPGB @AP_President so glad you called the Obama administration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arcnus @robynlesley3 the average never look at what politicians do. That's why voting time they have no idea. And get Rubbish in gov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every American knew that. No secret https://t.co/yzvib4BQ3B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @politico Hopefully we can get there oneday for now I feel hopeless we have a very bad government]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What did you expect. They have no idea https://t.co/TrORjcLw2D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The whole world is asleep while evil is wide awake. Only few can see what's really happening]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TonyAbbottMHR I want you back to take over this mess @TurnbullMalcolm put us in . And defeat the media. People are waking up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So when the left tell you they fighting for human rights it's quite the opposite]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>