<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Fall in #love today. And tomorrow. And every day of your life. #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is when two become one. #Irish #Love #Storieshttp://bit.ly/29PPh9l https://t.co/vOWsGaciMt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell a #story to someone.. You'll feel better. The story will feel better. And the listener will be enriched. #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deadly goody bag. Only one throwaway handout in it. First race of year done and dusted. Now for the goody bag party.  #raheny5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Love can make  a night seem like a lifetime.  https://t.co/DrMu9HNrrl  #irishlovestories https://t.co/APoRX16Gh4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you were to be reincarnated as an animal, what would it be? #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go for a walk to a quiet place. You will meet yourself there. Or on the way. #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['I will love you for a thousand years, and for thousands more.'    #irishlovestories    https://t.co/DrMu9HNrrl https://t.co/Zn8msoqipp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leave a book in a public place for another to read and walk away today #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['I love you', says a whisper in the breeze.   #irishlovestories  https://t.co/DrMu9HNrrl https://t.co/TL0afDvVa4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trams are swift but must stick to the tracks. You on the other hand are free to go wherever you will. #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After the rain and the rainbow comes found treasure #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovers don't count time; for love has no end. #irishlovestories the best gift of all https://t.co/DrMu9HNrrl https://t.co/gEdh0TjPxo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heuston, we have another problem, sweetheart. #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheMichaelMoran I'm looking forward to breakfast, thank you for asking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dream so that you can fly. #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no such thing as a bad penny. Just bad thoughts.  #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't lose your senses in your story for your story is in the stars. #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Driver stays in bed. Train refuses to move. Tracks go nowhere.   #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never ask directions of a lost soul. #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Speak well before you leap into the unknown for they may be your final words. #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine everyone you meet is naked and you are wearing pyjamas. You are emperor. Enjoy  #sevenz.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TourismIreland an ad for Ireland without cliche alcohol. Yay. Well done someone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So what makes you think the birds in the trees know more than you do? #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eating chips and burgers after a training session does not a fitness programme make. #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Monkeys never need a mortgage. It's a human invention #sevenz Go find a tree and live in it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The punishment for killing another should be the taking up of that person's responsibilities for the life of the killer #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All parliamentary meetings of import should be conducted while walking barefooted in breaking surf. #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you own an apartment window box you are a small landowner  Think carefully on what you plant #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never base a life decision on what your parrot told you during a hungover revelation. #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A rainbow may follow rain but you will still be soaked without a rain cap in a shower. #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you've been around the block a few times you know the way home. #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A leopard doesn't change its spots so don’t put your hand in his mouth when he has toothache. #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be a bee in a bonnet or a marble in a jamjar or a sedate passenger on a bus. Your call. #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are what you eat you should read the menu carefully before ordering.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You could always pretend that morning does not exist #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're welcome. 
#backtowork 
https://t.co/jmIG9byUZG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Windmills are there for jousting against. They are giants. Don't be fooled. #quixote #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pen without ink is just a paper scratcher. #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What new year resolution might a mouse make if it found a discarded calendar? #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frenziedly digging your flower bed for treasure following a dream of unearned wealth only disturbs the flowers. And your mind. #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A wheel rarely rolls up a hill without assistance. #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My free newsletter will be sent next week.
To receive it please go here to subscribe
Contacts will not be shared… https://t.co/SxkWiv6jVn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beware when cats select a king for you have no place there. Hurry on. #sevenz #folklorethursday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many an oak tree has grown from an acorn long forgotten  by the jay that buried it. #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never kiss a frog without consideration for you may be turned into a jumper. #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jerry Lynch - U.N. International Day of Peace - 21st September 2010 https://t.co/E6bS98bGVV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arise and find your shoes for today you dance. #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Christmas #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevinnolan1976 yes a joy and a privilege to have been with you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barbarascully. Happy days for Paul. All those motor chases to watch. Enjoy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The voluntary worldwide agreement by unconnected adults that Santa Claus exists is proof that he does. Happy. 
#sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why should you go swimming with a dolphin when that dolphin never goes walking with you ?#sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catch a shooting star in your mind's eye and be at one with the universe. #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is a joy to be alive on Midwinter's Day. Salute Mother Earth. Salute you #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A seed of love can become a tree of life.  https://t.co/aW9n7AsbtW  #irishlovestories  https://t.co/DrMu9HNrrl https://t.co/Bv4d0oySS6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A flag wrapped around a refugee makes poor protection from the cold #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't imagine there's much of a career path for a #mime artiste on #radio, really.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good news for #2016. Wicklow Mountains National Park expands. The government has bought almost 5,000 acres of the Featherbeds for €800,000]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be inspired or be introspective just keep it to yourself. We're tired of listening to you. #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He was a lumberjack and had the mark of the chainsaw on his face when I first met him. #amwriting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make sure to buy yourself something nice if you find gold in your garden while digging  out weeds. #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jumping in puddles disrupts the equilibrium of the world. Be a jumper.  #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is universal and love is timeless.  https://t.co/aW9n7AsbtW  #irishlovestories  https://t.co/DrMu9HNrrl https://t.co/NtNIRoHrJ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pencil that appears to be broken in a water jar will always write again. #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love can take many forms.   https://t.co/aW9n7AsbtW   #irishlovestories   https://t.co/DrMu9HNrrl https://t.co/loC7GaYISE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is no surprise to hear the sea in a shell when you are standing in the waves. #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the bombed and terrorised and dead children of #Aleppo there is no #Christmas. Well may the survivors look at us and ask: Why?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love needs no spoken language to be understood  https://t.co/aW9n7AsbtW #irishlovestories  https://t.co/DrMu9HNrrl https://t.co/Cxtbf87L7L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Syrian pro-government forces have entered homes in  Aleppo and killed women and children, says the UN.  82 civilians were shot on the spot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Falling leaves are a promise of spring and a new beginning. Also when wet on tracks they delay trains.   #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True love is not for the faint-hearted, for there are those who would thwart the lovers' path… https://t.co/dQlIiyxLXC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arise when sleep will not come to you for you are taking up space in the bed that others could use. #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lose your senses in love for love is all you need   https://t.co/aW9n7AsbtW  #irishlovestories… https://t.co/51ERMieIT5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the only words you write are your name on a cheque, make sure the letters say what you mean. #amwriting #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love begins with a single glance.   https://t.co/aW9n7AsbtW   #irishlovestories  https://t.co/DrMu9HNrrl https://t.co/0wteYgaybs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hurrying home with your first-ever loan of a free library book. That. #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A warm shadow on a path on a moonlit night  https://t.co/aW9n7AsbtW  #irishlovestories  https://t.co/DrMu9HNrrl https://t.co/tkhmdPOWpv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sing away to your heart's content. Even if you get the tune wrong. Your heart knows what you meant. #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America in two halfs  #RIPJohnGlenn #DonaldTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tales of love warm the long nights and salve the soul  https://t.co/aW9n7AsbtW #irishlovestories… https://t.co/VrIWRDiYzg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Zesman nah. Just throw the book at them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The battery never runs down at the crucial moment in a real #book #amwriting #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is the ideal gift for you and for your love   https://t.co/aW9n7AsbtW  #irishlovestories  https://t.co/DrMu9HNrrl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go for a walk with yourself. Your mind will thank you for it. #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovers don't count time; for love has no end.   https://t.co/OOjw72DRob   https://t.co/DrMu9HNrrl https://t.co/PaY12Ly1Dj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making warm tea for a friend is a far deeper experience than pouring alcohol from a cold bottle ever can be. #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is the ideal present.  #Irish #Love #Stories  https://t.co/aW9n7AsbtW https://t.co/IfcrrGf7tA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Upgrade your mind today. It's free. #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is when two become one. #Irish #Love #Storieshttp://amzn.to/2c0eldI https://t.co/RukLv50XBO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's often better if your left hand doesn't know what your right hand is doing. #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is a wild flower met by a dusty track.  #Irish #Love #Storieshttp://amzn.to/2c0eldI https://t.co/YFQbPX78ri]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beware of the guy with the trick deck of cards for all is not as it seems. #sevenz #josh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True #love is the kind of rapture that stands between us and life itself. Read about it in #Irish Love #Storieshttp://amzn.to/2c0eldI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those born by the window can see further. #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be signing copes of #Irish #love #stories in #Lucan library today and tomorrow fri/sat. Drop in. Say hello.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you Manuel. #andrewsachs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Treat your heart to a cornucopia of Irish Love Stories.https://t.co/aW9n7AsbtW https://t.co/g2Mm92MHVv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't shoot the messenger before you hear the message. #sevenz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can buy copies of #Irish #love #stories in the. Winding Stair bookshop on Ormond Quay by the #ha'penny bridge… https://t.co/S4mkrcBynZ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>