<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaliaShadwell Yup &amp; it means less experienced people are making these assessments b/c turnover is so high - it's the main reason I left.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaliaShadwell As someone who has worked in the chronically under-funded mental health sector, I feel for everyone in this terrible story.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be fair, 25 mins is a very long time for @realDonaldTrump to concentrate on big political stuff. https://t.co/mJ3M38KhMd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LuciHoneychurch Lol thank you so much, that has to be the nicest tweet I've read all day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nytimes Sorry but I can't use one of my 10 free articles/month on a recipe.  Maybe after Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeithOlbermann Australia has a fair amount to apologise for.  It's shoving refugees into detention as punishment for running 4 their lives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My head says I need to stop reading so much about Trump, it's just too awful. Then my head says that's how dictators win. On I go. #resist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WWAustralia @__eclectica Thanks for pointing this out, I will cancel m'ship if they continue to advertise in Brietbart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So according to GOP @HillaryClinton should've disobeyed judge who allocated rapist case, but an AG shouldn't disobey Trump even if illegal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If only my son went to #Hogwarts I wouldn't need to label 20 pencils. They'd know who they belonged to, right @jk_rowling ? #newschoolyear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jeez there must be a huge #TrumpTantrum going on right now as he realises that actual reality isn't as easy as tv reality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sending support from Wellington, New Zealand - go @ACLU !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AP I'm sure @realDonaldTrump will stop such progress immediately &amp; get that driver's job back!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AntiAltFacts @AP It's 11pm here in New Zealand, perfect timing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AP He'd better quickly learn how to string together a coherent sentence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peaklabs You do know that Twitter exists in the Southern Hemisphere, right? We're kind of used to summer in December.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vincentdonofrio @womensmarch A great turnout today in Wellington, New Zealand.  Support around the globe!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WomensMarch in Wellington, New Zealand https://t.co/2cPUTa50Kw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Friday Trump becomes President &amp; on Saturday there's a National Prayer Service. Logical sequence of events.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@girlscouts The ones he sexually assaulted probably wouldn't mind a bit of your support too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@girlscouts How exactly does supporting someone who boasted of sexually assaulting females unite people??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iqmobile Ah ok so most current version not always being used, got it. Thanks for reply.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iqmobile I still don't get Flynn Effect role-is it that current IQ score may be higher than it would have been if tested at time of crime?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JayHarvie Let's just say that no man or woman will be left standing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JayHarvie Come up to Buckley Rd, Southgate, and you might change your mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not a good day to wear a dress in Southgate. Apologies to my neighbours #weatherbomb #wellington #itsabitwindy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Yair_Rosenberg If you're in Wellington, New Zealand at that time, you're welcome at mine :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChaseMit If only "trash everywhere" looked like that in my son's bedroom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaliaShadwell Things I Have Learned Since Moving Back to Wellington, No. 1 - enjoy a good day when you get it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sponsor a Habonim Dror tent! | PledgeMe https://t.co/BKwgBV9u7Z via @pledgeme]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matthaig1 Can we not use the word "swallow" in today's tweets?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucyastrid Yeah they're even weirder in the night. They say to stay in bed &amp; cover head with pillow.  Hopefully a quiet one tonight!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucyastrid First earthquake or just first one in the night?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewPStreet @smh I have also emailed them about this. Got form letter back, but important they get feedback.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DyscalculiaInfo I can't even get past the question in no. 5. Aren't 'sum' &amp; 'product' the same thing???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I emailed the Aust Salvation Army re: their withdrawal of support for Safe Schools - email address is in this link: https://t.co/33JWA8OXou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An earthquake in the middle of my relaxation recording - needed to do it again twice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnMetta Finger representation (what he was doing) has been shown to have strong r'ship to good maths later on. True story.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarrieHKelly I totally understand. Online seems to trigger people to communicate in a way they never would face-to-face.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarrieHKelly I know, it's like you see the best and the worst of people on Twitter isn't it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarrieHKelly Twitter u/stands diff between free speech &amp; online abuse.  Alt right don't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bencjacobs @guardian It's a sign of how scared he is to do the job alone. He knows he can't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanDG @islandbaynz That's really stunning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@geonet Yep felt that one in Welly. First in a while.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hereby rename 'aftershocks', GODDAM EARTHQUAKES! #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grantrobertson1 It was definitely a quake.  So over it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear aftershocks, you can stop now, I've had enough.  Thank you. #eqnz #earthquake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dragontam73 We're all ok.  Got some sleep after about 3am - very tired but no school or work today, all cancelled.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ground may have stopped shaking, but I haven't. #eqnz #earthquake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@guardianscience 1 example isn't evidence, and source pls?? An ethics committee allowed unnecessary anaesthetic and knee incisions, REALLY??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamiesont First laugh I've had in days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@trophimself I'm not in the U.S. either, but I think it's going to affect us all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@trophimself I started to laugh... but then I couldn't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@trophimself A year! But he made it sound so easy, why on earth hadn't had it been done yet! He's got a month!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok President Trump, so when should we expect ISIS gone then?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuliaIndigo @SeanMcElwee  Ahhhh ok.  It looks so red from my couch all the way over in New Zealand! It's very stressful! Good luck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanMcElwee I obviously don't understand U.S. politics because those numbers and maps they're showing look like Trump is winning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My holiday options in the U.S. are dwindling.   #uselection2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZStuff Note to self: always go to the toilet before getting into a lift.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GhostWhoVotes A bizarre result for a country that voted in Tony Abbott, Pauline Hanson, Cory Bernardi...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get a good night's sleep USA.  Tomorrow u need to save the world from a lying delusional racist misogynist narcissistic lunatic #NeverTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[D'oh! - Trump’s Border Wall Will Have 75-Mile Wide Gap https://t.co/886BzNlV4O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[35 mins to go till we get THREE DAYS of unlimited access to @nytimes.  Very excited.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A white guy in a hoodie with a gun at a Trump rally - are they sure he wasn't just trying to hug him??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iraglass @SpeakerRyan It was great. But I couldn't finish the episode. Too distressing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JulianBurnside I did. Got no response yet they managed to add me to their emailing list.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NetflixANZ I can only see Seasons 1 and 2.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll never be able to watch an American political drama series again. It'll never live up to real life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lying in bed listening to my boy, who struggled to learn to read, read #HarryPotter aloud. Thank you @jk_rowling for inspiring him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chris_arnade I live in New Zealand and even I wouldn't claim to be neutral about the U.S. election (though I do feel sorry for all of you).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good luck with everything, United States.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To rig election u have to get officials in every state to wk together w/out leak or sabotage. If HRC can pull that off, she SHOULD be Pres.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maryalicebitts "Are you calling my facial expressions micro?  WRONG! My facial expressions are huge.  Bigger than yours.  SAD".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SnazzySlaxxLorr @PattyArquette Except that, you know, it's actually awful &amp; we feel for all the sane U.S. peeps.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SnazzySlaxxLorr @PattyArquette Laughing all the way over here in New Zealand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So just to clarify, if he wins it was fair, &amp; if he loses it was rigged?? Even my 10 yr old has passed that developmental phase. #debate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@freakshow10  Might need to try Siri ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Slate Last time I checked, spiral notebooks had two sides.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@774melbourne I always thought it was the surname of the doctor who made the scale.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billyo40 @thehill Oooooh, thank you! And good luck on getting voted in :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehill Can someone explain to a non-U.S. person what "write-in" means. I keep seeing it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dragontam73 He sure is. You should hear what he says. Awful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And now I know things about @ScottBaio that I can never un-know....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlexPappas If Trump was able to think that thought, America wouldn't be where it is right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've decided that "do I have to censor to explain it to my 10 year old" is a really good screener for presidential candidates #trumptapes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnMetta I keep re-reading your article I, Racist.  It has had a profound effect on me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The article I needed to read (by @JohnMetta) : https://t.co/gj4CEjqq4L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsCastan Oh what fun I'm missing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, just watched @ThatSugarFilm - just the jolt I needed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NetflixANZ @fullerhouse Consider my present to be the 5 people above me. Much higher quality entertainment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got a length of 19 in https://t.co/X7ksYNsquf! Can you beat that? #slitherio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@karaschlegl @iDoogie Read this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smh All SMH &amp; Age links on Twitter &amp; FB are redirecting to a betting site so an explosion may have already occurred.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going to reinstall the Stocks app just so I can delete it again #ios10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iDoogie #imarriedanapplefanboy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wcl_library Having read his totally racist comments, it's hard to celebrate him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, it's not like they've ever misjudged public sentiment before...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewshubNZ I might let them know I'll do it for $100m. They can't knock back such a bargain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Wellington library app: https://t.co/CqIzYfk2UZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AntonyGreenABC Great talk and discussion Antony, thanks for popping in to Wellington.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>