<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[TECHNICALLY this image is Canadian (since it was dreamed up by one) How many days til opening day? https://t.co/i1dLkNBfYi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My nephew has Bat Moose PJs... There is no way I can explain to my family how #SPN  makes these funny https://t.co/sjZ7Q6UWmO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much better would the T-Mobile ad be if the little girl turned and said "yeah, whatever grandpa" to JB?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing anyone can complain about with #Letterkenny is that the episodes are too short and there's too few of them #perfection]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Letterkenny is offensive to people without a sense of humour is what you really want to say CTV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty sure the tone of my voice is set to a frequency that people only pretend to hear bc fuck if they actually listen to the words I say]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephanieBally @Engel82 what days are you in TOR so I can look at flights]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I think the only think anchoring me to my life is my dog ... srsly think about it Everything else in my life can function w/o me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd send in the Pepper spray...as in my dog.. because she just wants a perma friend so she'd befriend the shit out… https://t.co/YxvfcuWibN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kelios *fistpump* I'M NOT THE ONLY ONE Keep being told this isn't normal.. What 25+ hours awake Who cares? Can't do anything bc of the snow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That awkward moment when your alarm for your nightshift goes off... but it's your first day off and you still haven't gone to sleep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cop Spots Teen Walking Alone At Night. But Is Shocked After He Learns What's Really Going On https://t.co/lPN18dVISS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I remember, got sucked into watching Lethal Weapon as a kid bc it   ends with an Elvis Christmas song Still love the movie decades later]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephanieBally I know you would contemplating going solo... found a good flight/hotel/car package ...if i wasn't a weinie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephanieBally Just need someone to go with me that I won't want to put 6' under before the trip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephanieBally Last night I noticed I could see 2 of my boys at Spring Training AND go to Disney World for my bday......................]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephanieBally You know I love you BUT fucking snow here makes me want to punch you right now *smiley face* #sojealous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's what is and was and will always be right about baseball... even if he was a Spankee ;) https://t.co/vvkHBKDhCP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd be okay if the best part of the Grammys are the @jamescorden commercials :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Met some truly amazing men who were just on the cusp of figuring out who they wereThey have such beautiful hearts and the world knows it now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing makes me happier than to see one of the guys me and my family befriended as a Vancouver Canadian excel in their profession]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone wanna go to Disney World and Spring Training with me for my Bday?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mother Nature, seriously?! We had a fucking white Christmas you can stop with this snow shit now thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dammit Gray misunderstood them... they were saying Lily not Lucy :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darrenhayes Americans didn't care about WW2 until Pearl Harbor while the rest of the world fought... they're slow sometimes per history]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearHeartxoxo Okay good but know that I know because they're so good with Pep I won't forget Knowing her name goes far with me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearHeartxoxo She got a tip plus back tips bc I felt like such a fucking douchewad I never saw the sign that I could before (in3 yrs ffs)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearHeartxoxo I think it does... PS I feel like such an ASSHOLE I didn't know I could tip them!!!! ALL THIS TIME!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearHeartxoxo I think it was end of the day and we go there lots (probably more than I need to because I'm too lazy to do buttface's nails)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearHeartxoxo Plus I make sure Pepper's rabies tag is clean and legible so she's wearing proof she's not gross :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearHeartxoxo Okay well I don't think that would be an issue ... I was seriously worried it would come out of her pay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearHeartxoxo they all know Pepper and know I keep her up to date on everything Hell none of them know me it's all HI PEPPER LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearHeartxoxo I offered to wait and pay after she was done and she said it was on her so I over tipped her bc come one that's nuts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearHeartxoxo her co worker wouldn't get off the computer to do the invoice She knows Pep so knows she's up to date on everything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearHeartxoxo Oh hey serious question... If someone at PetsMart offers to do your dog's nails for free, does it come out of their pay?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow #Supernatural was filmed at my friends church @DearHeartxoxo just a FYI PS he told me mega spoilers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty much sums things up perfectly https://t.co/hqAmVJtZWO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone at work told me where SPN's filming today I tried making jokes about them reusing locations She didn't get them I felt crushed :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whomever runs this twitter is brilliant and I would be proud to work with them https://t.co/It2gjBOG83]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&lt;3 This https://t.co/0iB0mVgL8G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plot twist.... assholes come in all shapes, sizes, colours, religions and whatever other labels we like to place on ourselves and others]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WTF?! Returns thisMay?!?! What kind of nonsense is that!?!?! FFS...  Better be renewing Pitch too bc this is bullshit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing works better than a kick in the groin :) https://t.co/OYapsuK2mH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look up "Rougned Odor Meme" You get this... THIS makes me happy Gregorio being JB's teammate as a BJ not so much https://t.co/BwKbWGwveB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FudginRenegade But none of us did and we never came close to wanting to... French was our only claim with her]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FudginRenegade Every time I talk with you I think of my grandma and how I swear she really wanted all of us to learn Finnish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FudginRenegade OMG I quit Spanish bc it was too close to French it drove me crazy but Portuguese!!! That's... CAH RAZY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Dec I bought a new blanket for myself Now Pepper jumps on the couch and stares at me until I use it to cover her Good buy Lisa Yeah right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FudginRenegade Better yet when I've spent like 5 mins reading back conditions from Que &amp; get the "Do you read French?" msg from an officer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FudginRenegade I still laugh when I get the "Anyone read French" messages @ work so they can tell the cops what the badguys' conditions are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FudginRenegade Non, tous en Français :P BC y'know in Canada we have two official languages :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FudginRenegade FML If it wasn't for the officers I work with I'd have no idea how to make my keyboard English]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PS If you know where I live and you need a hot meal... ring the door bell Pepper will happily slobber on you before you have a bowl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not to be immodest but I yet again made another amazing batch of Vegetable Beef Barley Stew... Itès so good in this weather]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alright if Morneau signs with Minnesota I get a trip to Chicago in August to see Trick... come on Twins do the right thing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FudginRenegade I just need to figure out a font I really like]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OH MY GAWD YESSSSSSSS!!!!!!!!!! This would be amaze-balls! https://t.co/Io0WUpCW4y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pepper's really gotten into eating kangaroo treats like kangaroo ribs... can she be considered an Aussiophile now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FudginRenegade  Fam;ly because I LOVE the idea of getting a "semi colon tattoo" after reading about the Semi Colon Project]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FudginRenegade I don't suggest the wrist area... that hurts like a motherfucker That being said I so want to add to my Pisces symbol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I reflavoured a bunch of Pepper's bones with beef stock Wasn't sure I did it right but now she's just licking one of the bones so WIN for me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what I feel most Americans are like... my opinion could be skewd bc I live adjacent to WA State so I assume… https://t.co/lrVfwtaBB5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes all you need is to passionately lip-synch to @darrenhayes in the middle of Safeway to help you get through the day #truestory]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right now all I  can say is https://t.co/Qn2gxfSeLH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm such an asshole. Whenever I see Canadian geese in the USA I can't help but to say "Looks like some illegal aliens snuck in "]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I was a kid I wished I was American just so the Mariner Moose might come visit my school]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My dream Roast Battle @yamaneika vs @KTrevorWilson That would be epic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay I lie... I've actually broken my rule for @GregorioPetit31 I actually wrote on my calendar when his team is in Seattle UGH Only for him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting annoyed All of my guys have signed with some Even though I REFUSE to ackowledge someone becoming a BJ Why isn't JM signed yet?!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's still no standard in my Province for therapy dogs (emotional PTSD) but fuck it Pepper still is one She makes EVERYONE'S life better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone dented (like MAJOR dented) a co-worker's brand new vehicle in our secured work parking lot They didn't leave a note... pisses me off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kelios LMAO I was thinking "shitfuck there's no way I can learn to knit to make that!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NO WAIT! A lot of random friends have nonchalantly asked, "You know where we can go to a cabane à sucre, right?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Engel82 Random friends are asking what they should pack if they ever decided to visit you in the winter?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How awesome would it be if it was all just  to give everyone who has no common ground someone to come together to defeat?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HOLY SHIT! @yamaneika BEST roast I've ever seen... so glad I didn't go to bed right away after my last night shift]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is so cute! https://t.co/41T2mLepM5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate being a Canadian baseball fan right now... the sites I've been reading hurt me right to the core... If you don't get this carry on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaralynT86 are you okay?! I keep seeing shootings on your side of the river so I really just gotta know you're fine ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow is #bellletstalk Day Remember to use that hashtag as much as possible to help fund mental health initiatives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More to that... one of them was the woman who was with me EVERY STEP of the way at the ER after I was attacked by 2 men She'd never say that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know THE women who's image was STOLEN for a group who know NOTHING about them (see my last tweet) They would NEVER say something like that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[American anti-Women’s March group misusing photo of New Westminster police officers https://t.co/Tp3O8Ob3vI via @TheRecord WOW ++++]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really this song is about @11EdgarMartinez and Ken Griffey Jr as it is about Dave Niehaus (and my childhood)… https://t.co/JKGV5LFkBd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow is #bellletstalk Day Remember to use that hastag as much as possible to help fun mental health initiatives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WORSE DAY EVER! How dare he sign with the BJs ... broken hearted... still refuse to buy their merch... sorry Gregorio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rewatched the last two episodes of #Pitch as many times as I've rewatched Edgar Martinez bringing Griffey home in 1995 to beat the Yankees]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Pisces Is The Most Difficult Sign To Understand https://t.co/bCxCRrFH4v MY TATTOO IS FUCKING RIGHT THERE TO WARN YOU :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["They've been decaffeinated"  Roger Murtaugh ~Lethal Weapon 2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FudginRenegade RIGHT!? But I keep saying IF I could take her to work to sleep under my desk WOW would I be the nicest dispatcher ever! LOL😇]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I spoil my dog She jumps on the couch and beofre settling in gives me the "where's my blanket bitch" side eyes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My new brain bleach #Letterkenny  S2E1 12m40s That's all I need to erase the bad of my day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daisymay1017 Because we've learned to ignore the adrenaline that makes us want to be stupid... why can't we be stupd :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be sleeping for a night shift so I'll miss most of  #BellLetsTalk Day so Friends #spnfamily Please tweet the crap out of that hastag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[January25th is  #BellLetsTalk day ANY Social Media activity with that tag will help fun mental health across Canada +++++]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FudginRenegade Checked Just 1 noticeable scratch on my neck probably wouldn't be noticable if I didn't bruise like a McIntosh *rimshot*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FudginRenegade Y'know I work a 12 hour OT shift today while she gets to sleep and be a weirdo in the yard for my dad LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FudginRenegade I think it was more of a "shut your mouth I ain't playing Let me fucking sleep" bc I'm mean like that to her]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FudginRenegade Thanks I just keep laughing because now she's passed out on her pillow like nothing happened]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FudginRenegade In the next breath, I haven't looked in a mirror and my lip still throbs but I've lived through worse No blood so I'm good]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>