<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Qwine agreed. The cricket has done a fair go at it though to be fair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@winsordobbin nice work Winsor!! How did it feel to be back in sports land?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can he hold on for the overall? Looked good in the small snippets of vision today https://t.co/vluLF6BqcR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Six quality Victorian Shiraz from The Story, Balgownie, Tahbilk and more https://t.co/C14Kj5rnmj https://t.co/hwRqdVvRlq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Far too logical thinking there... https://t.co/881TOy1Dj0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The '14 @chapelhillwine Mourvedre is real good: https://t.co/f0LjBXs7hG https://t.co/zByPEVGlE9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BEER: Rabbit &amp; Spaghetti The Fox Hop &amp; Rye Lager https://t.co/eCd1sYbIgC https://t.co/5x79xODHc3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@g_mcfaul @jeniport and an exclamation mark :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[January 2017 tasting notes roundup https://t.co/AYICAxIBCA https://t.co/J0U8OjgeVw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@megabicicleta yep. They just assume you've been injured and riding again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matisonwines also much idiocy about preservatives and wine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OzWineGuy makes you think about the double standards doesn't it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheVinsomniac 2hr wait for the ballpit apparently. Will need many beers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheVinsomniac no but would like to go!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheVinsomniac @outofstepwineco handy piece of dirt that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's wine news: Ian Hongell has been announced as senior winemaker at @TorbreckBarossa  (after leaving @plwines ) #wine #barossawine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fixwine @Apple which one you at? Broadway store can be like that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndevineWines @GundogEstate @cathy_gadd it's nice, just a little overt and warm for big points.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep, it's a warm night in Sydneytown https://t.co/6Ow3gmXLeW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gundog Estate Semillon 2016 collection + 2015 Canberra and Hilltops Shiraz interlopers https://t.co/ZO7ocy0u1e https://t.co/rtknucMH31]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's wonderful screenshot - go AUD! Can it keep going up until May? Yes please! https://t.co/U03OnxlMUL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Juxtaposed: Delicious Grenache and more from Wes Pearson https://t.co/Zb6fm5aLB1 https://t.co/uctmc4zCmB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@g_mcfaul @SixersBBL I would have to roll some kid for a used one :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still can't believe that a standard @SixersBBL cap is $60. Madness. #BBL06]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rdhinds echoing many others who said that your writing is too good for the Terrorgraph. Onwards and upwards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mount Avoca’s standout 2013 premium Shiraz duo https://t.co/PS496MhwvF https://t.co/JvANtJcq2O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the 'places you'd like to be' file. Curl Curl Beach a week ago https://t.co/O7Djaw6Yjd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's roundup time! Monster January 2017 roundup edition https://t.co/A0ZHR7w3rP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jrhennessy dash cam videos are my favourite YouTube holes of all time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Balgownie Estate Centre Block Shiraz 2014 https://t.co/5yUbFTJckM https://t.co/GpSIPnRbr1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BEER: Lord Nelson Backburner IPA https://t.co/a0oetccmhY https://t.co/e66JVQjg4O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TashStoodley ha. Nah, if you build it they will come. It took about 12 months for my site to do anything. It's fun too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TashStoodley take it from me, no one reads those things :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@summerofcycle you're missing digital media. Number 1 source]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshElliott_29 serious questions to be asked about his management too. Dumb moves all round.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well priced red: Bremerton Coulthard Cabernet Sauvignon 2014 https://t.co/uvneXlCzp7 https://t.co/qP1llSNoNO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tim Adams Clare Valley Pinot Gris 2016 https://t.co/Ksj0U8A6t5 https://t.co/od3IC7P2r3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My forever Xmas wine: Primo Estate Joseph Sparkling Red https://t.co/cJcZuTiVFN https://t.co/7vblhn2f7m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RedtoBrownWine onwards and upwards. Kinda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016 was pretty rough. But you know what? Shit happens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[End the year the way you want to start it. Or something. Anyway this is good fizz. #NYE #Champagne https://t.co/o7Js7A9Iub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiebCricket solid crystal ball work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyanBuckland7 @CricketAus me too. No live matches]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheVinsomniac quite good film. You could drink several beers during]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@5um1th nice beer isn't it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anthonydanna @TahbilkWinery great vintage that 😉]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For anyone interested in this year's #ozpiereview results - they're up on Insta now: https://t.co/JrW3tlbcZX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CroBarFarm crazy. They're tiny tiny plots!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is incredible for Burgundynerds https://t.co/csBRtLd4rd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miketomalaris great news. TDU next please Tommo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The easy joy of Pewsey Vale Contours Riesling 2011 https://t.co/c2GZiWXE7F https://t.co/7JcFwEeaMo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great catch #smashemsixers https://t.co/f9NC5KyK3z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melkettle funny thing is that for all the hype they're just standard, average quality Apple earbuds sans cord. Avg sound and fall out too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melkettle they're average earbuds anyway. Just with no cords.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maxallenwine 19yrs is quite a stint. Well done Max.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BEER: My Beer of The Year – Feral War Hog American IPA https://t.co/koOFd90nBW https://t.co/ga4tskHZki]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeoffLemonSport at least he is the best gloveman in the country. Oh wait...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Topper's Mountain and a gregarious Gewurztraminer https://t.co/WRrodoZiR4 https://t.co/tdeNG4Ga2k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ozbrewsnews @wilsonscec the ferals have appeared!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ozbrewsnews @wilsonscec no Feral in the voting this year? Weird.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some handy wine conversions from Andrew Jefford in @Decanter : https://t.co/x4uBBc8aCS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VinMerrison @WineComAust @MarianneDuluk @TWE_Global @BrownBrothers @The_Impy you're crashing the lady drinks Ed?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buttery Chardonnay from Scotchmans Hill AKA give the people what they want https://t.co/pHhh60fong https://t.co/rRXpiqcoCI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FOXFootyLive @RyanBuckland7 such passive language from the AFLPA and their elected board members. No wonder they're getting nowhere...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BodhiEdwards being vegan would be miserable. Takes the fun out of food]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BEER: Modus Operandi Sonic Prayer IPA https://t.co/ztRnGp58tJ https://t.co/XgHlpG4PAH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BEER: Newstead Brewing Co. Two to the Valley IPA https://t.co/SrvnS5YB2s https://t.co/MnULL3VJk5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OzWineGuy it's good stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rory Lane's new super premium 2014 Grampians Syrah https://t.co/3ktz0QJ9NE https://t.co/uaT9lcP5dG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiebCricket @ESPNcricinfo especially because they were conjoined #littleknownwaughfact]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReganDrew sure was. Maybe they've learnt their lesson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big ups to @Pilurestaurant who replaced a lightly corked La Braccesca Vino Nobile di Montepulciano yesterday without question. A1 list too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Barossa: Schwarz Wine Co. The Schiller Barossa Shiraz 2014 https://t.co/GcT7nnAhcx https://t.co/we3oGREXEp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yalumba The Scribbler Cabernet Shiraz 2013 https://t.co/S7OV49SK5Q https://t.co/ttmAcOL8qw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheWineRules1 all a bit arse-about isn't it?! Wine body basically pitches idea to gov and then gov rewrites it for them because it was 💩]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheWineRules1 linked to trademark. Didn't know that. I foresee a busy year or so for wine trademark lawyers...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CroBarFarm I'm convinced volumetric is the future. Though depends on much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're totes popular https://t.co/opcvOGNuSU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WET Rebate round 4 – a new, somewhat fairer deal released https://t.co/EvEPosufLv https://t.co/fLFDeoj7iI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@frozensummers volumetric is the answer!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ruminski not necessarily. As long as you buy the fruit and then sell it under your own label you're covered. Bulk wine not eligible though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still, would be even cleaner if we ditch WET altogether. It's an inefficient tax that doesn't help premium wine (IMO). 3/3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sure there will be loopholes exploited in this new WET rebate arrangement, but at least small producers 'back in'... 2/3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This WET update is much better. Covers off growers, small producers who make wine from bought fruit and most legitimate producers... 1/3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In other words, as long as you buy/own the grapes and then make it into wine you sell (as a producer) you're ok https://t.co/bXnsE5pzxg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FYI Delayed by a year and up from $290k https://t.co/DmOqBcznRK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Karma in the cycling world https://t.co/WScG5uKrFg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The latest bargain from @Inkwellwines - a bloody good $25 McLaren Vale Mataro: https://t.co/5gMAagx97R #wine… https://t.co/lGD1cwDVGI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TashStoodley it's a hard knock life for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TashStoodley me too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sl_payne @Uber screw you uber]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheWineRules1 no. Also, spent the day avoiding Cyber Monday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @uber what's the deal with your app location settings now 'always on'. Ah no thanks....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@janeskiltonmw I bet the lifestyle team has great wine expertise *first article - 10 pink wines for summer*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@winsordobbin but how will you tap your watermelons Winsor???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Qwine @ReganDrew doing well there too Steve!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReganDrew @Qwine just checked and I'm only 25 off 2500. I've never even counted before. Need to pull finger out to get to 2500 this year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The '15 @Tapanappa Tiers Chardonnay is excellent: https://t.co/RVb39W6bcD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReganDrew ah no. Just over it. Thought I'd plugged all the holes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get there! https://t.co/tv5C5cAREZ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>