<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[My sister got Tyler's brooklyn jacket &amp; she looks amazing I'm crying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@B__Butterflies THATS TH ONLY TH ING MISS ABOUT MY GALAXY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Louis_ThighKink thanks just trying to help you be a legend ya know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[STFU IPHONE AUTOCORRECT SUCKS IN ALL CAPS https://t.co/0yWd4pLgCW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was having a peaceful afternoon writing fanfics then this happens can I ever just breathe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CHEEKY LITTLE SHIIIT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[listen LISTEN THE NERD GLASSES! The GREEN AND VLUE HAT YES HUNTY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Louis_ThighKink I'm a terrible influence ihms https://t.co/un5UpT4BKo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OH MY FCUKIN GOD https://t.co/RBM4f0XnUN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benwinston @KeepUpdated1D @NiallOfficial @Louis_Tomlinson don't forget about @Harry_Styles and @LiamPayne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_mybabyharry "what the fuck!!" Same]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Louis_ThighKink we all thought it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone on my tl is roasting zayn rn lmao omg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delete this https://t.co/kRGLayv8jG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danslarry you call that a flop lmao if I get 5 likes I'm pleased]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danslarry logs into tumblr once]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danslarry actually yes give me that hashtag validation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomlinsims ty for following back! love your account ðŸ’™]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@B__Butterflies keep that in mind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@B__Butterflies we need it to quench our thirst for merch though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me: this tea is so healthy I'm gonna cleanse my body of impurities

My sister: so there'll be nothing left of you then?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@B__Butterflies bitch! https://t.co/sqFTL18mHL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was scrolling yourssincerelylarry 's blog I swear https://t.co/LLUevnoADj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The last one I can't stop laughing https://t.co/ClytM8x1Jf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomlinsims slowly raises hand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@B__Butterflies who is it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had like five drafts and every night they get deleted. Twitter's probably like oh honey you're not funny try again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DiamondLarrie28 why's he smiling while talking about his mortal enemy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@misfitstylinson @B__Butterflies @steveaoki p l e a s e black beanies w white detailing omg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OH MY GOD WHAT THE HELL IS TGAT https://t.co/aBxMvrKr6q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LarryIsQueen01 @disneypuppies @B__Butterflies fuck me in the ass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@medicalstyles oh shit, maybe they'll add more?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@misfitstylinson @steveaoki just got one, expensive shipping though damn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[don't let me flop ik y'all are lurking at school https://t.co/cPTiRGiioA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wanna be known by you |-/ https://t.co/a7tDifpcJn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LarryEvakAsFk thanks love! Found the header on Tumblr and changed the color, icon from twitter x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UnbrokenLarry_ which instruments?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UnbrokenLarry_ if this ain't me, but you can dm me if you want?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UnbrokenLarry_ lol I want to be a creative writing teacher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd do the same, square up motherfuckers https://t.co/0cjjclopw8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danslarry I have a friend who's fluent in Spanish but needs help w grammar and writing but yeah separate classes would be nice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bambie998 bitch I ain't fat ðŸ˜¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I'm gonna do a free follow for active mutuals from one of my sidehoe accounts bc yall are lit ðŸ’™]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.... am I really getting emotional over not being able to like the aimh tweet. Time to sleep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who didn't see it coming tho I like everything at least 2% relatable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AM I ON FUCKIM LIKE LIMIT I FAVORITED THIS LIKE 3 times THIS WEEK AND T UNDID IT AGAIN https://t.co/m7LglEwNjc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@medicalstyles I would spill that everywhere omg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@medicalstyles so is it like caprisuns w straws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@medicalstyles wait.. does milk rly come in bags]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taintedjmb oh wow you're rly pretty I love your makeup x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome to the team that stays winning https://t.co/iZQiEamBeN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@medicalstyles physically I'm fine, emotionally I'm bruised]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anathemadaniel that's what my sister told me and she knows everything lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only people w Niall icons that are bitchy are narries that's a fact https://t.co/2ApEWaUnor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT WAS A COMMERIXAL JUST NOW https://t.co/W1hB8MNhlt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danslarry THE DTRANGER THUNGS SEASON 2 trailer DID YOU SEE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danslarry dan punches Phil in the throat bc he thinks he's been kidnapped. He runs out the front door and is hit by a car the end]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danslarry bitch!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danslarry idek where to start w this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@B__Butterflies BITCH!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@medicalstyles thanks (: you're so nice x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@medicalstyles I did about a year ago. Broke and stress free âœŒï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me while lady gaga sang born this way https://t.co/Py7fclhTlc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fucking tease https://t.co/H8AwNWSxPX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@B__Butterflies sigh. My notifs aren't working]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Larry is gucci, all other ships are just knock offs w messy stitching]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Louis_ThighKink yes. How about harry putting on lipstick and kissing Lou's collarbones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IM SITTINF WITH MY FAMILY LMAO SHIT https://t.co/LSdZCUg5Ko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[well played https://t.co/5pbpMXQp1l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Harry_Styles post hq's of your new tattoo or it didn't happen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[or kale in fancy script]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so excited for my eye dr appt on Wednesday when I get my new glasses I'm gonna try again lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been zooming and staring at this every day waiting for enlightenment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHY TF DIDNT YOU TAKE .0005 seconds TO TAP ON HIS ARM AND FOCUS YOUR 2005 FLIP PHONE https://t.co/m7O4qPIAIW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@B__Butterflies me neither tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@misfitstylinson I hope I don't miss it when it happens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@misfitstylinson me neither I thought I'd seen it all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IM CRYING https://t.co/BTtDCh7fdL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who's your first love @Louis_Tomlinson bitch we all know it's harry https://t.co/lxp3Mdi4r7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's your body count @heartachee https://t.co/P98jrT8nM9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's your first impression of me? @misfitstylinson https://t.co/lERHXzTudz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you still texting bitches yes or no? @judgmentalgay https://t.co/xkDiKwkPjh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would you have my kids? @B__Butterflies https://t.co/LQXbSU5upp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will you be my valentine? @Iightninglarry bitch I thought you'd never ask ðŸ˜ https://t.co/wQ4JdW6ckG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would you give me head @Iightninglarry LMAO https://t.co/hNwpwr0eFg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danslarry y'all fakes, blurryface is my fave member]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ME AND NICOLE WERE CONCERNED TBH https://t.co/V0IxboEC62]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@B__Butterflies im hurt that you hashtag exposed me like this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@supportlwt your account is so cute thanks for the follow love ðŸ’™]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@misfitstylinson they have their own rainbow themed bedroom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LarryIsQueen01 @B__Butterflies what was this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This isn't a joke it really happened lmao ihms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me: why does no one ever ask me to rp I'd be gr8
Someone: hey wanna rp 
Me: leaves them on read, eats crackers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Same! I live only an hour away from NYC and whenever Louis is there I'm like conflicted.. I don't wanna bother him https://t.co/hZA4t11Acc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm kinda worried I'm gonna overplay the starboy album. I've got the cd in my car, a spotify playlist, and sing six feet under 10x a day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@medicalstyles and threw the pickles into the crowd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks I'm trying! https://t.co/y4gogJg6il]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[gonna get a bath bomb and lip scrub from lush, watch some gay porn, and eat chocolate covered pretzels in that order]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm gonna be single on Valentine's Day and I made such elaborate plans to treat myself lmao it's gonna be lit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@medicalstyles yeah it can be intense ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>