<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Diverse Teams Are Smarter https://t.co/gkMlUjZBfL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retailers, You're Not The Brand Anymore: The Shopper Is https://t.co/wgKMMVRrsS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ineffective Sales Leaders Can Cause Lasting Damage https://t.co/EiqD4cWLCd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future innovation core lies at the edge. @Paul4innovating HT @jhagel  https://t.co/USQEyNLBLw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gaslighting: Know It and Identify It to Protect Yourself - a behaviour worth understanding  https://t.co/nwBvKboCyz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boards Must Be More Combative https://t.co/OnU0e4mxvF https://t.co/LM0sTHXrGG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History Tells Us What Will Happen Next With Brexit And Trump HT @colduthie great read  https://t.co/mxFVHv0vRr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a match #AusOpen amazing champion @rogerfederer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @optus Check out my @Speedtest result! I know Sunday is supposed to be laid back but this is ridiculous!!   https://t.co/8PSKtswzzZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Surprising Connection Between Video Games And Business https://t.co/98eWysYK4U @IanAltman https://t.co/flmJD8ekXe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Google, Twitter, And LinkedIn Employees Are Kicking These Seven Work Habits  https://t.co/OQy4t5aqw4 https://t.co/gOP8wWOI9v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[bcg.perspectives - Saving Globalization and Technology from Themselves https://t.co/Vt96kdku7p https://t.co/UqNU5ZJOLo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Online isn’t killing the American department store, they’re committing suicide​ @NeilRetail  https://t.co/DaCjmHmEo5 https://t.co/MoKwC3ZT98]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rosshill photo from the post 😃]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Board Oversight of Cyberresilience https://t.co/liiPQAFCKi https://t.co/AFYrXxkZlA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How One Brand Used Instagram to Generate 150,000 Leads https://t.co/KvePhJLsH2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sportswear pushed global apparel and footwear sales to 3.8% growth in 2016  https://t.co/ka2rOguzNW https://t.co/vU7nIH7mPk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9 Leadership Lessons From 'Hidden Figures' About Workplace Diversity And Inclusion https://t.co/RZnYo6p4JV https://t.co/FJnU68eR6E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How The Most Successful People Turn Down Extra Work https://t.co/63HIMGODzG https://t.co/x3yuWfHt6o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If You Do These Things Every Day, You’ll Become Smarter https://t.co/wJARAmHtg7 https://t.co/qK7Q1L9ZlP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gfreney thanks for the RT - hope all is well?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Followers Don’t See Their Leaders as Real People https://t.co/Ny0nbPTMWo https://t.co/j7yMpd0UCy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make Operations Your Secret Weapon - Here’s How https://t.co/6Mkwo042VK https://t.co/urlAEIQMCu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrSimonMorris thx for the RT support]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon puts virtual Dash buttons on its homepage | TechCrunch https://t.co/JlKo85Tlq6 https://t.co/uSDLdDSF0Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PwC’s Quiet Revolutionary Tim Ryan https://t.co/nYFMHUyVHu https://t.co/dHKYt1q5PU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The competitive edge for Retail Executives in 2017. Clarity, consolidation, connection @_rachel_kelly… https://t.co/Ilabn2MWU1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To Defuse an Argument, Think About the Future https://t.co/zjk3QZmzvc https://t.co/APd0CFIoHH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beat Generosity Burnout https://t.co/ssHiBVmgxR @AdamMGrant @rebrebele https://t.co/FgEu6h8DMW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three Reasons Why CEOs Need To Be More Vested In Digital Transformation https://t.co/BxRaqkgrLQ https://t.co/9d6S0sbtMR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Your Mindfulness Efforts Aren’t Working https://t.co/4pwCFGYuWL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Career Needs Many Mentors, Not Just One https://t.co/HOHEO8PnhX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[15 Surprising Things Productive People Do Differently https://t.co/te7dJKkprG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Mistakes You're Making When Building Thought Leadership https://t.co/Afc7NcLALY https://t.co/9w7RsS3jsk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being a Strategic Leader Is About Asking the Right Questions https://t.co/UWBvrqvib6 https://t.co/KUYk1Bwld6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know that smiling face on the left @stevehopkins https://t.co/InyQFyQy1y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your beliefs are being challenged  @TEDTalks Playlist  https://t.co/RHDsd2Cy10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 Advertising Trends That Are Revolutionizing Offline Marketing  https://t.co/TExTxIqgy3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meeting millennials where they shop: Shaping the future of shopping malls  https://t.co/BCAiyrEM83]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Managers Can Make Group Projects More Efficient https://t.co/kXrOfwYfet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Top Psychologist Says You Can Be Too Emotionally Intelligent. Here's Why He's Wrong https://t.co/WgRctgHGMc… https://t.co/zYFxw706WV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[things you should do every day to get smarter https://t.co/CobpKIqfOc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A simple strategy to keep your best employees from quitting https://t.co/afXVgUqVmS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Study Reveals How Damaging A Toxic Boss Really Can Be https://t.co/q68KaiFcmW and business leaders are too often to… https://t.co/OeENDBSbfH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Amazon grocery service posing a new threat to supermarkets has been hiring in Australia for a year… https://t.co/eqMnxdhINO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retail: Consumers Differ On eCommerce, Physical  https://t.co/3fDFjDEm3q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Deloitte: What are the biggest #retail trends of 2017? Read the new Global Powers of Retailing report https://t.co/nDeeeHNvTW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mitsmr: How to construct strategic narratives that enable #innovation https://t.co/7YWE6vTKab https://t.co/vgctT08s1L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Quid: The science behind internet addiction https://t.co/Fyfp6ai9HR by @Quid https://t.co/l7FZBYjD6r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @iSocialFanz: Permission to NOT keep up with the Joneses, Kardashians or GaryVee! #FOMOFanz 012 https://t.co/bakx1WwVkO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Trust In Leadership Leads To Better Employee Performance https://t.co/LM3Ybrk45S https://t.co/bG033j6zP0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 10 Differences Between a Mission Statement and Purpose Statement https://t.co/D7PLjSE3Ez @StanPhelpsPG https://t.co/52Nix5yk7W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 Ways To Make Your Job Meaningful Again https://t.co/vMA1fCFtlg https://t.co/tqE7A3u1KP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 3 Company Crises Boards Should Watch For https://t.co/IAissFgB3V https://t.co/ZVXraslaHO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Launch Lessons from 37 Minutes in an Amazon War Room https://t.co/Px0QzJX8OZ https://t.co/UgeL4fVLZG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Journalism That Stands Apart https://t.co/J8XnWrpxee - inspired articulation from @nytimes HT @rossdawson https://t.co/LcFoIwhTqs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Politicians cannot bring back old-fashioned factory jobs https://t.co/hrnbdVDjjK HT @jhagel more of us need to unde… https://t.co/HndNKWhi39]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are online retailers falling in love with physical stores? https://t.co/1pkoUbFlby HT @SaundersHoward https://t.co/zyQ7T7JG3l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ensure 2017 Is YOUR Year: 3 critical things to avoid! @ColinShaw_CX https://t.co/xcMOpnFoKa https://t.co/mlAmO1d6pl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 30 Best Pieces of Advice for Entrepreneurs https://t.co/WDO24UGLGO feat @AdamMGrant https://t.co/mvrGlWiGqL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unethical Behavior Begins With Minor Transgressions That Swell Over Time | https://t.co/9ZdYMhZx9M https://t.co/vDVexhUx4L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Curator's Picks: Top 10 TED Talks of 2016  https://t.co/maZtZf6Nqr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 sentences successful people never say - Business Insider https://t.co/g4vGPhUv79]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Mindfulness Helped a Workplace Diversity Exercise https://t.co/cM6rSKewV6 https://t.co/DnN28IlfPM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon Announces a Card That's Almost Too Good to Be True  https://t.co/JtKD8Waeq4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the Archives: Establish a Personal Advisory Board https://t.co/LDHV6H8weX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should we forget the New Year’s resolution? - Just Imagine https://t.co/mHrR9RHhcw a message for every year by… https://t.co/hB6WRVVZ50]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Goals Change over Time, and What to Do About It https://t.co/XVaOB0g0bC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What To Do When a Friend Betrays You @KareAnderson  https://t.co/ziwAU0Buyx - insightful read https://t.co/7nFr3w4eXk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Workforce Agility: Are You Ready Now? https://t.co/GKHceoM82j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 Competencies With the Greatest Impact on Leadership Effectiveness https://t.co/hQ8SZKnX1M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Workplace Anxiety Can Paralyze Your Team: Here's What to Do https://t.co/ND5x8DM7Je]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I studied the future of sex for 9 months and this is what I learned.  https://t.co/MVn3QykBtz @bryonycole]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Culture Change Is Essential For Digital Transformation https://t.co/ZXLTEg0E3K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding the Healthy Tension Between Being Confident and Collaborative https://t.co/aLgn0LtJYC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to Be a Great Leader? Do This 1 Thing First (Most Bosses Do the Opposite) @jeff_haden  https://t.co/cnVKKZUs1K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What I Learned in 2016 and What the Future Holds for Those Open to Unprescribed Possibilities @briansolis  https://t.co/j7WahSPyRr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thoughts on Food Trends by @SaundersHoward (vid)  https://t.co/JEoS18jcki]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There Are Only Two Kinds of Terrible Bosses HT @AdamMGrant https://t.co/et7BvgIEes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@sherylsandberg and @AdamMGrant on the Myth of the Catty Woman  https://t.co/s8ao0A4yqn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrSimonMorris thx for the RT - I hope all is well?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Mistakes Employees Make When Challenging the Status Quo https://t.co/Sgd2D50Drg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What You Need to Stand Out in a Noisy World https://t.co/cTNzfgtSgo https://t.co/AZGR4ymTUv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Resisting The Lure Of Short-Termism: Kill 'The World's Dumbest Idea' @stevedenning HT @jhagel  https://t.co/5PZnotTzRQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Some People Get Burned Out and Others Don’t https://t.co/rICQH5P2AX https://t.co/I9lTm4wJ8t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dennisprice thanks for the shout out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business and Life are a Game https://t.co/XwNm3SY42p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Resisting The Lure Of Short-Termism: How To Achieve Long-Term Growth https://t.co/2FcvZfnVvi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Best Strategic Leaders Balance Agility and Consistency https://t.co/imcMAPn5ue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Screw "Personal Branding": My Top Three Social Media Resolutions For 2017 https://t.co/y8FNDDoqMw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 1 Simple Behavior All Great Leaders Leverage https://t.co/V2MnybNu1P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If You Want to Get Promoted, Say So https://t.co/LlN2Gu2Fm4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Philanthropist who has given away entire $8 billion fortune flew coach and carried plastic bags  https://t.co/JY88a2uPAz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maps and globes https://t.co/n2SRSuVaT3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From Hands to Heads to Hearts - Hat @jhagel  https://t.co/ENj0DCjbpS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retail futurist @SaundersHoward on the year that was, and the year that will be https://t.co/lHKHotREWe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Principles of Strategic Leadership https://t.co/sUgWSkflTV HT @AndrewGoodlace https://t.co/Krn5f0I41b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_rachel_kelly @retailfocus the Apple Store in London - for you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Congo_  thx for the RT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Coming Tech Backlash  https://t.co/A3HDtnbhMy HT @jhagel https://t.co/nrI8MI50yw]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>