<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[How long before Trump flips out on Twitter ... Schwarzenegger challenges Donald Trump to switch jobs https://t.co/dXIivFw5Tb via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well hopefully that is correct. https://t.co/2V1CIiBWef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coltheman1 @NZStuffPolitics is the painter using paint with nasty chemicals in it that harm the environment. Hypocrite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tiger Woods. I think I'm going to cry myself to sleep. Devastated. 😢😢😢😢😢😢😭😭😭😭😭😭]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bumped into my third form teacher today and it got a bit emotional! Nostalgia. Sectare Fidem. SPC!  @paddywhack19 @JordanFNg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This https://t.co/ozqUmH63tq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All happening today! ... A teenager has been arrested after a forklift was stolen in Auckland and driven at running police officers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['straya: A Canberra man who walked down Bunda Street swinging a hammer has been given a 12-month good behavoiur bond.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['straya: A teenager has been charged following a siege at Barrack Heights. The teenager climbed onto a house roof and threw tiles at police.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The mind of a lunatic - https://t.co/mbJO5EhYCA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wyoung1409 @damienmgrant nope. If Bill English needs Peters after the election I could live with that though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MervRobertson @theboltreport Bolt has it in for Turnbull because he toppled Tony Abbott. Turnbull has turned out to be a weak leader.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see @TheSergioGarcia playing brilliant golf @EuropeanTour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I reckon Tony tapped Turnbull's phone ...  Who heard Malcolm Turnbull's phone call? https://t.co/RLy6DW5pjP via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tiger chunks a 100 yard shot into water water. https://t.co/NPD0F0iF2Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@88TheDon annoying. How dangerous can a bit of damp ground be? What ever happened to reserve days?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GuyHeveldt hard to watch. Waiting for him to withdraw it seems. Hope I'm wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonkudelka Tony and Trump would get along nicely, can talk about global warming, boats, carbon tax and death cult. Shirtfront him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Trump is destroying the relationship with Australia because his ego is so fragile. Congratulations America. Well done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tiger's going to retire soon. Looks injured. Body language is miserable. Very Sad 😢😭😭😭]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The clown opens his mouth again. Such a fragile ego. Paranoid what people say about him. https://t.co/HjKU1hbslq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[shit he looks hurt, not walking properly, grimaced after swing, hope to god i am wrong https://t.co/DIJQK8tvPs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[what is he doing!?!?!?!?! https://t.co/DIJQK8tvPs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sounds like Trump has another hissy fit when someone disagreed with him, or did they both flip out? #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So basically Trump throwing his toys out of the cot @SkyNewsAust #pvonewsday #auspol @vanOnselenP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now would be a good time for @TonyAbbottMHR to make a comeback and say he will shirtfront @realDonaldTrump #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump go to bed it's late]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HAHA Donald Trump was yelling at Malcolm Turnbull then hung up on him. HAHAHA!!!!! #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[angry potty mouth https://t.co/WFb9lVZfdg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[haha poor Turnbull ... No ‘G’day, mate’: On call with Australian prime minister, Trump badgers and brags https://t.co/K53kHU2a2C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FUNimation Goku Super Saiyan for the first time, or Maijin Vegeta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beyonce is having twins https://t.co/6dnQzFsYEg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Peter Thiel saga is an early contender for media beatup of the year. Trump supporter Trump supporter Trump supporter Trump supporter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jazr0d @KiwiSAHD @Suzyiam Suzy has blocked everyone. Very abusive and sensitive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Russia charges cyber-security experts with treason https://t.co/pQ0HuK0Pxe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LouHou @nzherald bloody idiots. They never learn. People are sick of their constant whining.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He said he disagrees with it. What more do you want? Easy for Little to shout cause he knows he'll never be PM https://t.co/XAzHTgk9MF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[September 23 will be the end of Keys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clean coal is an oxymoron.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Problem with media is they're obsessed with being the first to report something to show off, rather than waiting until all facts come out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You forgot to ask me https://t.co/tceXbothV8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattHallSmith21 their sports reporters are pretty good though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haha sounds like a smart move https://t.co/9noe9DzcVm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labour and Greens unveil election t shirt https://t.co/sjcRQUFInM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter what policy Bill English announces tomorrow ... https://t.co/jBeSm7N7Vw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 News recap - NZ is a terrible country,  possibly worse than Trump's America, and that will only change if Little becomes prime minister.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear NZ media, i dont give a shit if Peter Thiel is a Trump supporter. Just more media bias.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@purpleP47 @coltheman1 @TonyStuart55 what poll was this? I missed it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not happy about something ... https://t.co/OnDrXbDbk5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RaymondTVLand @tvland i love the scene where Amy's mother tries to do the same and gets the food all over her chin haha!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bet if the left had their way, they would break in and try and cut the phone cord so English cannot speak with Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do the left want? For Bill English protest outside the White House or resign immediately?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can just imagine the outrage of the Twitterati if John Key was still the prime minister and made comments about Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone please tell the NZ media, mainly the far-left Dominion Post, that Bill English has already said he disagrees with Trump's policy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cringe, and then there is that stupid logo of his https://t.co/Au02nRAbWB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huge Stream of Lava Plunges into Sea | Video https://t.co/kEUYayZ0vh via @LiveScience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little and co. "English should criticise Trump "
English "We disagree with the policy"
Little and co. "English should criticise Trump"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rather have a relaxed cruisy PM than an impulsive angry man. https://t.co/PAIPTWIien]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coltheman1 @NewshubNZ rather have a relaxed cruisy PM than an impulsive angry man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill English says he disagrees with the policy, what more does Andrew Little want him to say? It'll never be enough. Getting angry again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilary Barry is making Andrew Little look like a complete muppet right now @1NewsNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coltheman1 no, media will only ask Bill English then bang on about it on the news so the lefty whingers can get angry and shout]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GhostWhoVotes Tony must be close to breaking point now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LouHou @TheDweck only for lefties. Only wrong when right wingers do it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For more on this story about Donald Trump we cross live to NZ parliament]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eats, shits and talks out of the same hole. Just like modern humans. https://t.co/C4Jnocvg9e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big deal. It's not like it's the end of the world. https://t.co/PVZSpWa67e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's a ticking time bomb. Not long until he explodes. https://t.co/ql68xJpVQA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Close Views Show Saturn's Rings in Unprecedented Detail https://t.co/AGfcwtP4Ri]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exactly what he wanted https://t.co/visbW2mdLx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[haha ate and shat out of the same hole, bit like modern humans ... Scientists find 'oldest human ancestor' https://t.co/O0BYrfk0Qz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Opposition will be very upset https://t.co/JCUdHldvxf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Takes one to know one https://t.co/2Wk1E6FoBG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coltheman1 @wyoung1409 HA I'll take a listen on demand tomorrow haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coltheman1 @wyoung1409 he got angry and smashed his glasses]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coltheman1 is he serious? If that is his career highlight then I feel sorry for him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coltheman1 @1NewsNZ the only reason angry andy is shouting his mouth of is cause he knows he'll never have to deal with Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice full toss from Southee. Another six. #NZvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do these bowlers know what a yorker is!? #NZvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is simply awesome! ... Tokyo Olympics unveils Goku as a brand ambassador https://t.co/JGGnJOFmmw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, Barack Obama and Jimmy Carter didn't do the same thing as Trump's Muslim ban https://t.co/KUspyVig2o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's facile claim that his refugee policy is similar to Obama's in 2011 https://t.co/Ub5eVmB74m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Angry Andy bitches and moans about everything. Easy to sit on the sidelines hissing and spitting when you are not t… https://t.co/7ns5ljESCP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What date are you challenging him? https://t.co/NgD1M3VkrX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@purpleP47 @pukeko65 @JennaRaeburn @JoelRowan they certainly work harder than some of the lazy bastards in this country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pukeko65 @purpleP47 @JennaRaeburn @JoelRowan some of the nicest people i know in NZ are immigrants. Always helpful and polite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I can't imagine you tweeting with a calm face or gently touching the keys on your phone. Always smashing them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital menu boards at Subway Manners St are out of order. First world problems.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[says the man trying to start World War Three https://t.co/H3vpWyJpmt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I knew it, media and Opposition using Donald Trump's policies into a chance to criticise Bill English.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sounds like he is planning something #auspol https://t.co/YhEBYSHnmy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matt Brown: Roger Federer the undoubted GOAT https://t.co/Mql7yYVYJu via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RamjamNZ One News reporting it was only about 400, dont know why the media is saying it was a big turnout lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How many citizens of the countries that Trump has banned have killed Americans on American soil since 1975? Zero.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who knows, could be a few more epic matches between Nadal and Federer before their careers are over. Both legends. That'd be nice! #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roger Federer wins the @AustralianOpen and his 18th major. What a match. Legend! Champion. Love it! @rogerfederer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roger looked down and out, but has fought back. Incredible match. #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federer has made more than twice as many unforced errors as Nadal #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roger might have his mojo back #AusOpen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federer is having more miss hits than Tiger Woods #AusOpen]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>