<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome research: Anti-inflammatories 'no better than placebo' for back pain https://t.co/STJ3c9vhsb via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome game of footy on the telly tonight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Preventative medicine: the argument for and against https://t.co/Ve33v0st1E via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people never grow out of it "Why children find 'poo' so hilarious..." https://t.co/Rw3t9ZlJhz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Thing or Two About #Twins https://t.co/7IS9JzfRbJ via @NatGeo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@breakfasters @scidocmartin just listened to Weird Science from Weds. Surely 'Kissing with Confidence' by Will Powers was the track to play?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's the benefit in making human-animal hybrids? https://t.co/iAFaiO4dfu via @ConversationEDU#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[managing the PhD - keeping a journal https://t.co/Oq09l4JUiz via @ThomsonPat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is your lab named after you or your research topic?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ANeuroPsych @m_spencersmith @AliciaSpittle @ParkvilleGeek @jane_ot a nice accumulation of evidence nevertheless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enough with the Doctor Who gender debate – it's time https://t.co/lotkVZXJdT via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dietary guidelines don't work. Here's how to fix them https://t.co/y0brQMPtlQ via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@twisteddoodles thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TwinsATR cartoon of the month https://t.co/IGzfeNNNfG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@twisteddoodles awesome, can I use this in my #twin research presentations?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, @Beyonce is having #twins. Shall I start knitting the bootees now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrMel_T yes, right at the back and one floor down ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NHMRC SRF application submitted. Given it my best shot. Now onto projects. Good luck to everyone doing the same.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen up: a plan to help scientists get their research heard by decision-makers https://t.co/Cc1LN7Zm36 via @ConversationEDU#]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New research on treating depression https://t.co/nMCrtp9ipj via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just popped up,in my feed - Interesting. Age Limits - Jan 25, 2017 https://t.co/2PISsu97gA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SophiaFrentz i have tried and I kind of agree - an ex student used to bring boxes back from NZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBC News - Which foods can improve your gut bacteria? https://t.co/lp2z0EQQVW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll just leave this here.  "Wrinkled sack' with huge mouth, no anus could be our oldest ancestor" https://t.co/GMGoP1h5lB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SophiaFrentz it's still happening - pic of sick kid recently with a heap of lollies. Why would you want to make someone sicker ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just sent someone a letter of support in which I offered 'un-kind support'. Worst place for a typo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These cute identical twins kept each other alive by HOLDING HANDS in the womb https://t.co/w7yipxWB4T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Hottest places in hell' reserved for those remaining neutral: Former US Ambassador unleashes on Trump - The Age https://t.co/DD94xbZPgs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can I form a resistance group called Omega?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sugar is as bad as smoking for pregnant women https://t.co/0x25r2MxPK via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WTF now it's getting scary https://t.co/IaljP14B87]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whereisdaz @BronwynHemsley @EvaAlisic agree that current commercial 'anti-aging' treatments are bogus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whereisdaz @BronwynHemsley @EvaAlisic I would never say 'stop' aging. It's inevitable as taxes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BronwynHemsley @whereisdaz @EvaAlisic &amp; Rumanian orphans'  telomere loss decelerated following rescue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whereisdaz @EvaAlisic sorry should have checked. Most are associations but some promising initial studies (as is the case with epigenetics)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvaAlisic @whereisdaz @guardian lost of evidence, see 
PMID: 26785477 &amp; PMID: 26975532]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future of stem cells: tackling hype versus hope https://t.co/HvnzVAo9Yx via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrScienceLover awesome you got expenses. I have heard "Sydney or Canberra'. Even further.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrScienceLover ditto with SF, although California is friendly ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whereisdaz @BronwynHemsley true, applies to posters too, &amp; of course attendance. Sickens me more coz I've supervised many Muslim students]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MicrobialMe :O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder how many non-US research scientists won't be able to present their data at US conferences? #nomuslimban]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ParkvilleGeek @jane_ot @AliciaSpittle ;) and ways to improve IQ? Or is this harder? Or less relevant to life?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jane_ot @AliciaSpittle @MCRI_for_kids great. Cd benefit from this myself ;) Evidence that younger kids are more plastic/benefit more?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jane_ot @AliciaSpittle @ResearchGate thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone's Knockin' At The Door.
Somebody's Ririgin' The Bell.
Do Me A Favor,
Open The Door And Let 'Em In.
- Paul McCartney
#nomuslimban]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jane_ot @AliciaSpittle can you please link me to reference(s) on ways to improve cognition (&amp; related phenotypes) in children. Feasible?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[what's the evidence that we can improve cognition in children?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let this be acknowledged "Documentary sheds light on Aboriginal people kept in 'human zoo' - ABC News" https://t.co/nbsvcEXFTG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not too deadly after all. "Welcome to Australia, a land of creatures out to kill you... maybe" https://t.co/sSPY8ZiOTQ via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must always look back to look forward because history repeats itself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How parasites and bacteria could be changing the way you think and feel https://t.co/FU8ISy1mWy via @ConversationUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scientists must fight for the facts https://t.co/CZu4AEdTQE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet the bi-racial twins born with different complexions https://t.co/FKPRRwe7Lb via @ABC7NY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australians All Let Us Rejoice... In Changing The Date https://t.co/7auf27kF2w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's been around 150 years since the last American civil war. Just sayin'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What your brain structure says about your personality https://t.co/QqSg2Gbw1z via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a child's humour reveals about their psychological well-being https://t.co/Kb9W4pVOdQ via @ConversationUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surprised that it's only 10k years "How we discovered that people have been cooking plants in pots for 10,000 years" https://t.co/Iv8vWGYSaE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Racist idiots. "'Bomb it': Canberra theatre threatened after displaying Australia Day billboard" ABC News https://t.co/MXCx8pEVyl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In utero conditions can affect a teen's brain development: Factors such as placement in womb &amp; access to nutrition https://t.co/IcDEbGp0Ja]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG this is so close to home. "Why we lose our hearing and vision as we age" https://t.co/0IEobCbuIF via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelenPilcher1 @JackDAshby shows even tarsier twins can have different personalities ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You put your left foot in... "Brexit in doubt after court ruling" https://t.co/roOGJ97CLo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shame is Spiderman! #Bodyatlas https://t.co/0dTNyFqtk4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone else hoping for a re-telling of Sampson and Delilah in the USA?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey, they got Al Capone on tax evasion didn't they ?...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome summer student Yvette presenting her work. She remembered all her LINEs. https://t.co/FMCKjXCXxU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WomenSciAUST I'm looking for someone to help mentor, via email, a young Indian school student who wants to be a woman in STEM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five common myths about the ageing brain and body https://t.co/NOJepOTpYo via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New science minister needs to maintain momentum and push the innovation agenda https://t.co/GgSSH3Gsau via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ParkvilleGeek I have just Pub-Medded that for the first time. Was pleasantly surprised]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now let me see, who has published most on #epigenetics and #twins?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woke up this morning at the sky over Melbourne was briefly blood red. #Melbourne mourns and moves on but doesn't forget.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, waterfalls are good for you "Does waterfall aerosol influence mucosal immunity and chronic stress? "https://t.co/KjdPNVzMFi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bribing kids to eat vegetables is not sustainable – here's what to do instead https://t.co/LciqBDDer1 via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Treat_Me_Gently @FeliceJacka @ConversationUK yes, most plausible; likely inflammatory factors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hankering for some anti-establishment? Listen to last week's #skullcave on @3RRRFM for heretical music &amp; spoken word https://t.co/blccAbr5Gr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This looks extra spooky today https://t.co/ZHqnQqiMIY via @youtube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Google can you please develop a search filter that excludes any references to to #therealdonaldtrump ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've joined Stepathon to help ill children. https://t.co/WQ3N46rxZv #stepathon2017 via @MCRI_for_kids]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Dry' and 'try' January campaigns show moderate drinking is not just about units of alcohol https://t.co/AIbHFXbRCU via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Into early life origins? - must go to @DOHaD2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Songs in the key of Trumpyness: Menon https://t.co/4y8kml8DAd via @torontostar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul McCartney would also have been a perfect choice for Trump's inauguration - Fool On The Hill Live https://t.co/n765WLZDu0 via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[REM would have been perfect for the Trump inauguration: It's The End Of The World As We Know It (and I Feel Fine...) https://t.co/odGlEeFk9X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@meganchapman yes &amp; treating 4 casualties]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AliciaSpittle @carmencpace not familiar with what OT does. Examples?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG, something bad's going down in Melbourne. The hospital's been put on trauma alert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Puns are sign of punchy and not puny intelligence "The Power Of A Great Pun" https://t.co/IERWDB9GTh # v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just eat more oily fish and skip the pills MT 'Can good fat boost your fitness level? https://t.co/eGytVacgb1 via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From diet to blood pressure – it's not just chromosomes that help determine the sex of a baby https://t.co/HXJ0M82GlP via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this really the final word on whether calorie-restricted diets make you live longer? https://t.co/X97CT7lhNp via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breast milk banking continues an ancient human tradition and can save lives https://t.co/EVXnS5JAgU via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eating nuts daily reduces risk of infectious disease by 75%! Also  reduces neurodegeneration, diabetes, CVD, stroke https://t.co/VKcmTmLMkX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go nuts! Nut consumption and risk of cardiovascular disease, total cancer, all-cause &amp; cause-specific mortality: . https://t.co/VKcmTmLMkX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quote of the week from my mum "I always thought that you would be a doctor as your homework writing was unintelligible at times!!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AliciaSpittle if I cd help enable prediction of CP @ birth, what kind of early interventions cd be used? Physio; anything else?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Physical health ignored in people with mental illness https://t.co/fJawwL3NyH via @ConversationEDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...and is then replaced by Donald Trump https://t.co/EVWXtFsnFP]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>