<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone looked so bored listening to Nicola talking about cats at the end there ðŸ˜‚ #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does Emma keep lying that the showmance comes across as real? I've seen more romance between a pair of pigeons riding in the lane #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_georgiaspencer because calum is about as interesting as my big toe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slimey OHara ðŸ˜·ðŸ˜·ðŸ˜· hope i never have to see him again #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just catching up on bb now.. yesssss ding dong the weasel is gone ðŸ¤— #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jeanie_Beans I'd explain but i honestly couldnt be arsed ðŸ˜‚ bunch of teenage school bullshit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think the rest of them think this is how they should behave now that they know theyre hated and jedward are liked ðŸ˜‚ cringe #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theres no backtracking out of this one Calum ðŸ˜‚ #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didnt give you the opportunity to say anything ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ jamie you were terrified in case he zoned in on you shut up you dick #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At this moment i dont think theres anyone more detestable than Jamie OHara. He's so vile #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The blair witch ðŸ˜‚ i love it.. its so fitting too #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rachelglass_ a popularity contest for a load of arseholes ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People carrying on as if someone was killed ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ would yis all cop the fuck on #Gossies2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessieFullerr lol fb knew what they were doing here https://t.co/8V2e1stnSz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calum woke up from his coma #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WOAH WOAH WOAH. Hold on Calum Britney Spears IS life you prick #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I havent changed my bed sheets in 6 months ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ stop they need to just win immediately #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@giveawaydowly exactly!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fucking DELIGHTED Jedward are standing up for themselves. Be respectful? Nicola hasnt been respectful since day 1? Why is it ok for her #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hahahahaha Calum is SICKENED he's nominated ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ good riddance #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Since when is Calum Nicolas bodyguard ffs #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God I seriously hope Jedward win to sicken the bully pack aka nicolas lap dogs #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I dont just wish Nicola to be evicted, I hope she falls off a cliff in the process. Such a terrible human being #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nicola is such a wanker #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pair of rotters ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #cbbbots]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am i the only one who thinks speidi were taking the piss in their interview.. they stood up for the people they liked the least ðŸ˜‚ #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jessica is an absolute babe.. #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why arent people voting to save Kim?? Shes pure comedy gold #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fizzlol i dont know i miss it :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nicola is starting to sound a bit like Kim ðŸ˜‚ DONT YOU START ME LOVIE #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nicola needs to cop the fuck on attacking Jedward constantly. You're getting enough camera time as it is you dickhead leave them alone #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jedward right now #cbb https://t.co/41gb6rjSYF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nicola is totally put out by Bianca ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The snapchat app is worthless to me without the white moose cafe ðŸ˜£ðŸ˜­ #whitemoosecafe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bianca and Jamie are the least convincing showmance ever #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonc1245 @NicolaMcLean @Mrjamieohara1 2 of the most disgusting creatures I've ever laid eyes on. They actually deserve each other]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NORFLDN im so excited!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not surprised you've never been put up for eviction Calum, i forgot you were there love #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've had to lower the volume of my telly while Staceys interview is on #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBUKpolls should have been jamie or nicola]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That dont act like you know me song was so fitting for stacey ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hughie_maughan exactly ðŸ™Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nicola if being grown up means being like you I'd rather be childish like Jedward any day #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Respectable? Wtf? You're anything but that Jamie ðŸ˜· #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHAT IS BIANCA DOING?????? #CBB https://t.co/ZpOmYm4uNc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealMattLucas @POTUS jesus thanks for reminding me, i feel dirty now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When theres a loud sex scene on the telly and your ma comes teeming into your room to look for something. Jesus christ #Trainspotting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jamie is definitely gonna be one of those dads that the kids beg their mam not to go see every week. He's vile #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I liked Bianca until she started messing around with that KNOBHEAD #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does Nicola insist on talking absolute bollox constantly #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you hadda told me 2 weeks ago I'd hate the majority of the housemates more than speidi i would have laughed. Jamie is my most hated #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesss delighted shes gone #cbb its not Geordie Shore you're on chloe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That Jamie fella is such an arsehole #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["He doesnt know your name" ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ i fucking love jedward #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never thought I'd hate so many people in this house more than speidi.. #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aishnan no i think shes just in that spare bedroom they put them in when they get too carried away on the sherry!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aishnan theyre plying them with the drink.. i think theyll be joining us on the dry january after their carry on ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aishnan so was nicola she could barely talk at one stage ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/Ud5jFl1wkw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kim fucking a drink over the security girl "oh lovey" ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kim doesn't even know who shes fighting with anymore ðŸ˜‚ "I've had enough of this" - shut up then!! #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[James C melts my heart ðŸ˜‚ #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eileen Grimshaw is as thick as shit! #coronationstreet #corrie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kim is off her fucking trolley but i sorta love that shes giving it to that tramp nicola ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I normally like James J but NO ONE shouts at jedward like that. For jesus christ sake #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus Christ the vein in James Jordans neck what the fuck?! I thought it was gonna pop ðŸ˜± #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SweetLikeAli @whitemoosecafe or maybe we just like a snapchat thats actually decent and not trying to sell us absolute shite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You havent got a chance with him ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ At least Staceys honest #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously can the please stop putting these geordie shore people in? So so cringe #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm as fake as your face ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚BOOM! #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@goss_ie no @whitemoosecafe on the list??? The only snapchat worth watching, the best snapchat in the world oh yeah #Gossies2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why dont they send that head melter jamie to hell, he's an awful prick #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good riddance Ray J. Boring as fuck #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've now watched Austin in 2 series of cbb and i still have no idea who he is. Jesus he's horrible #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has Ray J talked about the sex tape yet? ðŸ˜´ most boring cbb ever #cbb2017 #cbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I dont think we'll be getting a "Davids Dead!" Moment from any of these dickheads so far #CBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its like being in Syria living around here lately #Dublin #shooting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MissCatBradley oh maybe not. I was at an xmas special in rte and ronan had a massive sock down his trousers. We were all about 8!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MissCatBradley i think i was in the audience for that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dave__Fleming fanni healthcare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MissCatBradley sheila will buy loads but we're not allowed to eat any of it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MissCatBradley oh she will!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MissCatBradley well now theres no need for that. Tell carole to get a hold of herself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MissCatBradley but why not go for the better ones?! One day you might realise you lost the moon while counting the stars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MissCatBradley celebrations tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@virginmedia @rachelglass_ well its a bit jaysis late now hf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ugh that im a celeb after show is the worst. Some of the most annoying people going presenting ðŸ˜© #ImACeleb #getitoffmytelly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gail must be up to her bollox in debt with all the husband funerals she's had #coronationstreet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im actually crying here ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ Martins heaving reminds me of myself after a jagerbomb #ImACeleb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚"Adam was losing his tiny northern mind" love Joel #ImACeleb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah jaysis phelan spittin all over the gaff ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ VINNAAAAGHHHY #coronationstreet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the first time this Phelan story is getting interesting ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #CoronationStreet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd dunk that Martins head in those beans.. such an annoying twat just eat them #ImACeleb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aww I love how cute Larry and Scarlett are ðŸ˜ he's such a gent #ImACeleb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus give me strength.. johnny just happens to search the bin at the most convenient time. Get lost corrie #CoronationStreet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FacesByGrace such a lovely girl, hope you're ok. Take your break and come back soon xx I'm gonna miss siennas little smiles ðŸ˜Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know he's old enough to be my granda but I've always thought theres something so sexy about Larry Lamb ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ #ImACeleb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FacesByGrace please dont share less grace, i look forward to all your snaps. Dont mind them, theres people who LOOK for problems ðŸ˜˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chall2450 @jk_rowling we all wish your business didnt affect us but unfortunately it does. You're very close minded if you think otherwise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mean girls with cheese and crackers. I don't really think life gets much better than this]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>