<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Get out of the meeting with my fisheries researcher on recreational fishing regulatory regimes abroad, see this..… https://t.co/7csyOLJFxO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yup. Think about ways of providing safe downside options for GOP who break ranks.

https://t.co/PTBMrFfE39 https://t.co/team3t8uiQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@guywilliamsguy Some details on that:
https://t.co/lEmIGqBpF3
https://t.co/yuZWlaFsvI

https://t.co/JSMg3raulr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the same calculus applies to impeachments. https://t.co/kAO2mG1NjO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bechhof I'd do it differently: let regions outside Auckland specify that they want even more migrants.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bechhof Auckland needs to sort its housing market out, which requires fixing land use planning, meaning infrastructure funding changes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DeGraw_Sushi I'm advocating the government staying out of who fellates whom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@moturesearch Is a nice piece and sheds light on claims like "If migration's so great, why is Auckland productivity so poor?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And don't forget @moturesearch's work on Auckland productivity, cited in our report!

https://t.co/LDSwiCHj3E… https://t.co/x03dSIHNZI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jodiecongirl We need exit options for any principled GOP in the event of an unsuccessful impeachment attempt. 
https://t.co/5aVRspAlQ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd noted that Pence had deleted his anti-Muslim-ban tweet.
https://t.co/PTBMrFfE39

Source:… https://t.co/vAqItgRBQt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fellatio is a private matter among consenting adults; the government shouldn't have a say. But the 2011 Thiel citiz… https://t.co/VQQfsptNbW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GraemeEdgeler No way! Can they undelete tweets?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who have the ability to do so might consider signalling that they'd help any GOP congressmen in the event of… https://t.co/DpSKPb2cub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canadian schools see the opportunity to do some good, while also attracting some great grad students. 

NZ: (sound… https://t.co/VdKdV65HI0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada is putting NZ to shame through all of this. https://t.co/wi0CbkZEfq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deowll1 @ross_marks @DomPost Well, I got my 2 year work visa on the skilled migrant category 2003, then permanent residence in 2005.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS Is Grey's law; I can't take credit for first use. 
https://t.co/wr0OxRXb47]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Matthew51824627 I'm confident enough in NZ culture to know it wouldn't be harmed by admitting a few thousand in response to current mess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Matthew51824627 I can't see any of those being a risk if NZ simply admitted *people who already passed US vetting*.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Matthew51824627 New Zealand has had superb success in migrant integration, thanks to our liberal labour markets.
https://t.co/teLKQxAs2a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melulater Mixed methods. To answer some questions, we looked to existing NZ and international lit; for others, to the data lab.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America has gone mad. New Zealand can, and should, help those hurt by Trump's racist travel ban.

Me in the… https://t.co/mxzIbhJ8gy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melulater Mixed methods. Some literature survey, some primary research in IDI data. Have a read through.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DearMama_ And there's a great way of opening the door: Canada's sponsored refugee system.
https://t.co/hclOqAtaKu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kumararepublic You replied to a thread on immigration. Guess my bad for thinking you were referring to immigration.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kumararepublic Are you still talking about immigration?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VernsCave @lifeafterkey Yup. We totally hide our membership list. On our website. Here. https://t.co/o7UGE9AXBR
#Sneaky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kumararepublic Income mobility in NZ seems reasonable, at least out of the SoFIE data.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@s1moncox @peteryeates @nz_nicola I'd noticed it last week; the numbers seemed out of line with OECD stats, but looked like a hassle to sort]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The lower Trump's approval rating goes, the more I worry about mechanisms like Hess &amp; Orphanides 1995 AER.

https://t.co/S6YR4NGjgI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BJDugdale @BenRoss_AKL Those cut are banned. Levy better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenRoss_AKL Do a GST-income tax switch like the last one but make fiscally neutral only for residents. Net tax increase falls on tourists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BJDugdale @BenRoss_AKL Have you listened to Labour and the Greens lately? 'Cut migrant numbers because infrastructure'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenRoss_AKL @BJDugdale @kumararepublic That proposal is a less harmful way of addressing things if policy shifts that way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BJDugdale @BenRoss_AKL @kumararepublic Yeah. We say 'If infrastructure makes you xenophobic, don't ban migrants, charge a levy instead.']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SFEnZed Will tweet it when it's up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brycepearce @pv_reynolds @Trabaq Problem is if location of spend diverges from location of cost. Spend up in city, cost small town.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pv_reynolds @Trabaq Haven't yet. We did put out that SEZ report.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Trabaq @pv_reynolds Distorts choice of whether Council should provide additional services if they'd be GST-free if Council-provided.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Trabaq @pv_reynolds Hey, I know and agree. And it's central what told Dunedin to build that daft stadium too. But it's the world we're in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BJDugdale @BenRoss_AKL @kumararepublic Read what we actually said in the report on that one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pv_reynolds @Trabaq Not in the politically feasible set. Central thinks local/regional staffed by muppets who'd spend on popcorn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pv_reynolds Lots of systems better than current. Regional council level could work too, sure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Trabaq @pv_reynolds Don't rebate GST on rates. It messes up Council choices to provide services or not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pv_reynolds How much gets spent in Milford relative to tourist burden? Peak load there seems high relative to population.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pv_reynolds Figure out what tourists pay in GST, apportion some across councils proportionate to rough tourist imposition on infrastructure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LostArcNZ @five15design @kumararepublic @paulbrislen Seamus had a few thoughts on a prior iteration of that.
https://t.co/9Zmb4Pwipm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pv_reynolds @Trabaq I don't think that quite does it either. Consider tourists who rent the campervan, stock up, then drive without spend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSpinoffTV @SpinoffMusic 2002. Because of this. 
https://t.co/4vJxuD2JIq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pv_reynolds We'd proposed a potential solution in our report on Special Economic Zones, but other mechanisms could work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pv_reynolds No disagreement here. Mechanics around a concrete solution debatable, but totally agree on the problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pv_reynolds Yup. We've argued for that to shift Council incentives so they stop blocking urban growth, both density and expansion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkHubbard33 Reddell has an interesting story of how you could get to productivity losses. Just near impossible to test.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@five15design @paulbrislen Pretty sure you've called me/ NZ Initiative 'neoliberal' before. Don't like current infrastructure policy at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@five15design @paulbrislen Watch for my piece in the Dom, I think it'll run tomorrow. On how NZ can and should help in current US mess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@five15design @paulbrislen There are real infrastructure costs, and there are messes in how Councils have to finance those. But agree.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkHubbard33 Nope, missed it. Thanks for the heads up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Were they dairy sheep? https://t.co/BJdz8dolGU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@five15design @paulbrislen I hope not. But there's lots of political pressure to turn people away, with infrastructure costs the reason.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@five15design @paulbrislen It's better than banning migrants or using other ways of cutting their numbers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@five15design @paulbrislen They are! Recommendation is conditional. "If you think infrastructure strain means ban migrants, levy instead."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greg_a_cole No, it was by deliberate design. Officials told them to exclude permanent residents and they added them in. Is malice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TeamEcon https://t.co/ESNBBDxpYi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@transparency_a1 @hamish_keith It would be pretty awesome if he were and if he took on the suggestions there made. Low likelihood but still.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate those maps that forget to include New Zealand. https://t.co/AWGo8uX11a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@transparency_a1 @hamish_keith Watch for my piece soon to be coming out in the Dom Post on what New Zealand could be doing to help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jodiecongirl @econwithdustin Funny but not haha funny that in absurd times the name Milo is all over the news.

https://t.co/qzqtKiZKUk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jodiecongirl @econwithdustin Have seen one tweet from a US university warning their students on non-US passports against foreign travel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winston on job-killing migrants: https://t.co/FfhB1qrPxR

The employment rate:
https://t.co/57pMK30Jy8

Us:
https://t.co/teLKQxAs2a
#rpt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not quite sure how immigrants are stealing all the jobs when the employment rate is near record highs despite strong immigration.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For all the weekend's fun, Trump still has about an 80% chance of being President at year-end.… https://t.co/OSMz9c1ALq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jodiecongirl If they were born in a banned country, they're kinda under the radar until they hit a customs checkpoint.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It may be some time before I'm willing to fly to the US again. Good thing we visited family there last year. https://t.co/LWJ3xOuKYo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jodiecongirl I love the sentiment. But if a Muslim scholar is in the US on a Green Card, this means she cannot come home afterwards.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greg_a_cole The ban includes US Permanent Residents who were born elsewhere but who have families and lives in the US. Sympathy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is good news. But it will be terrible news if nobody else in the GOP moves to support McCain. He's taken the f… https://t.co/7sgRNN89Ss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Noahpinion Do you remember the '95 Hess &amp; Orphanides model? A variant on it may apply. 

https://t.co/ZFE1sk943u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've seen this sentiment all over from Canadian universities. Nothing from the NZ ones. Canada's closer and more ab… https://t.co/PBkRW6eFZO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EHFNewZealand @rafmanji @AshleyCnz @MLaCorte_ @kiwiconnectnz Done! Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS @robhosking Huh? I'm saying that if the govt were quiet because it were mulling appropriate response, it ought to speak up soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nigelwallis I agree a billion percent. Unfortunately, NZ political discourse at a spot where one needs highlight 'what's in it for us'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS @robhosking I'm just hoping that the current silence will be followed by the results of a weekend's thoughtful deliberation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And Canada stands to gain a pile of fantastically skilled H1-B workers if they go ahead with this. Great initiative… https://t.co/ZSohuygIiH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rnzbrentedwards Those interested can catch our report here:
https://t.co/teLKQxAs2a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Zealand is great for migrants, and migrants help make New Zealand great. https://t.co/g18IjP1siZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And I'll be on with Hosking a bit after 7. https://t.co/VQ4Ff16txe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another Canadian school moves to help... https://t.co/Ullg4fVtxG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshgans Think it is still the case that the number of Justices on the Supreme Court is set by simple statute. Longshot but...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has any NZ university reached out? https://t.co/Jb9nr62gzy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saskatchewan has about the same population as the South Island. https://t.co/O267NIvXCD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Faffinz @_chloeswarbrick We go through the evidence on those effects.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CMRanapia @OliverCarle @keith_ng Not saying not to. Just don't expect big results.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CMRanapia @keith_ng He's already thrown away tons on foreign students]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keith_ng @CMRanapia He will channel enough us govt business there that it won't matter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CMRanapia @keith_ng It sounds nice but Trump doesn't seem to care about costs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonSorens What difference would it make where the Republicans support trump in this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonSorens They could if the GOP weren't corrupt power-worshipping sacks of shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ssheere01 The Scotland win over England just now was pretty good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricCrampton On the plus side, she has the place almost to herself. Queues for face painting later shouldn't be lo… https://t.co/YghnXOVpNX]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>