<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The Canberra perks that make diplomats stay over going anywhere in the world https://t.co/eOsjF8swfj via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Prayer not protest': Pro-life supporters defy police outside ACT abortion clinic, by @alexmback https://t.co/xBhd046v7X via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Antill Street house where Joe Cinque was killed to be razed for public housing https://t.co/vzUGZEolif via @allhomescomau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian Border Force chief Roman Quaedvlieg could replace NSW Police Commisioner Andrew Scipione https://t.co/SYrW2lnodl @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge urges law reform after man moved into late ex-wife's ACT house and wouldn't budge for a year https://t.co/MBxUasvQYW @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rodney Culleton was never elected to Senate, High Court rules https://t.co/2phXt8iUv5 via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good. Lord. Donald Trump tweets he will study 'dumb' refugee deal with Australia https://t.co/lpr2N08Ub6 via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canberra jail escapee got girlfriend pregnant while on the run https://t.co/KHxNhS9wyx via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No ‘G’day, mate’: On call with Australian prime minister, Trump badgers and brags https://t.co/hhwMG7yOBa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ANU comes 7th in Times Higher Education's most international universities ranking https://t.co/AFpasZvQ9V via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Such a lovely person': Bourke Street victim named as former Canberra student Bhavita Patel https://t.co/tiB6lz3RcS via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pimpama deaths: Slain mum Teresa Bradford had been trying to relocate https://t.co/8K1WtugXr5 via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bourke Street: Sixth victim dies in hospital https://t.co/cj5MiyU92B via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Susan Kiefel rewrites script, sworn in as first female Chief Justice of the High Court https://t.co/8LFSj5VcbJ via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump's Muslim ban excludes countries in which he has business ties https://t.co/h5zx97smrP via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trade unions royal commission star witness who revealed blackmail fined for underpaying carpenter https://t.co/sJZS9qCv1z via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia Day honours 2017: ACT campaigner Marion McConnell recognised for drug law reform push https://t.co/ktdQAR3RCt via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where are the women? Australia Day honours list dominated by men (again) https://t.co/92sEhSQiuo via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three years on from brain injury, Matt Pridham just wants a job https://t.co/ltyyjNwkZr via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rejected candidate applies to Supreme Court to have ACT election declared invalid https://t.co/jBTO0jfrnA via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Shoot her': Canberra knifepoint robber jailed for 'frightening' attacks on woman, taxi driver https://t.co/49OJe0YKPL via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bourke Street: Bail justices say they've been unfairly blamed for CBD rampage https://t.co/mFz8srayzF via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have no advice for Gladys Berejiklian but I do have some for the media | Kristina Keneally https://t.co/U9Mn4L1iYq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House press secretary attacks media for accurately reporting inauguration crowds  - CNNMoney https://t.co/qOPglSyUsJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baby becomes fifth person to die from Bourke Street carnage https://t.co/i4fDfTiwUi via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Counselling session left me psychologically damaged, says public servant https://t.co/uhayOQEAV0 via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man who drove ex-wife into Lake Ginninderra given suspended jail term for "terrifying" ordeal https://t.co/8UBvWGUbzL via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live: Pedestrians hit, gunshots heard in Melbourne CBD https://t.co/9aIiLNiMe5 via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['I'll burn your pretty face': Canberra man allegedly threatened woman with flame https://t.co/z9iDJqUleo via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mexican Drug Kingpin El Chapo Extradited to the U.S. https://t.co/3wgNm7ioqU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['They know we're coming': epic case against the Commonwealth heading to High Court https://t.co/1thn6Gu3IS via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CFMEU engages barrister for inquest into Ben Catanzariti's work site death #canberra https://t.co/r47gz1tVgM via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Journalist criticises Mamamia and Mail over lifting of investigative article into child abuse https://t.co/J9nsw89S6u via @MumbrellaNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canberra man accused of hospital assault 'forcibly injected partner with heroin', court told https://t.co/Pqoyz30Cyd via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this. Obama’s Secret to Surviving the White House Years: Books https://t.co/YMixVWWtHv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Breath Becomes Air review - a surgeon’s life cut short https://t.co/rdHoaJszCU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alleged robber left sledgehammer marked with his name at scene of crime https://t.co/bXvwRowwRQ via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liberal MP Jai Rowell accused of leaking to Labor to 'destroy' party colleague https://t.co/9j6QoCKgvB via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mauled tenant who lost finger launches action against 'preventable' pit bull attack, by @mickinman https://t.co/QRStEycNYH @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man faces court six years after allegedly setting off fireworks in nightclubs https://t.co/sawrPx6GIQ via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crying 'fake news' is handy for politicians but toxic for democracy | Lenore Taylor https://t.co/Ed4Ak7R4Tu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another Day in Paradise review – a raw, emotional insight into Bali Nine artist's life on death row https://t.co/eA3jrgAPo5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Summernats: The street where you don't go #canberra https://t.co/7TCMdg5xSS via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Trump supporter' pleads guilty to child pornography charges https://t.co/hErveHDgip via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Government knew of potential problems with Centrelink system https://t.co/YwcfZteeAt via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waramanga man broke visitor's arm with baseball bat after car egging https://t.co/D6frKB2UtK via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loyal public servant to 7 prime ministers rides into the sunset https://t.co/a1vOGxuZUM via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Almost 3/4 ACT's 37 prosecutors are women; they are paid 18% less than their male colleagues' https://t.co/4tA7ScQ7Yj via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['They don't care about average Australians': Centrelink staffer speaks out about debt controversy https://t.co/jFF0cCGsdr via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meryl Streep called out Donald Trump's bullying and lies. Trump just hit back - with more lies. https://t.co/i356KvB1Qx via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doing a runner: Ex-public servant loses taxpayer-funded trainers, by @noeltowell  https://t.co/nDihwyVc8Z via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calls for ACT to again lead prison syringe program debate reignited  https://t.co/2fJkzIcmsN via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canberra carpenter fined $38k for ignoring order to compensate unfairly sacked worker https://t.co/IYp8nHrDQh via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spying fallout: East Timor to tear up oil and gas treaty with Australia https://t.co/kMcXoTF2GZ via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best investigative journalism of 2016 https://t.co/APq5XM7Y95]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man sues television archives after it lent equipment to competitor https://t.co/tJQRxfBK4s via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which Michelle Obama Will We Get When She Leaves the White House? https://t.co/oInZNbYArt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prenuptial agreements offer glimpse into secret lives of couples https://t.co/cD8cHmPqmM via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Cop killer' David Eastman takes fight against murder retrial to the High Court https://t.co/44PpqZpda4 via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['No apology' from Barnaby Joyce as government doubles down on Centrelink debt clawback https://t.co/vXxtsCj4Cu via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why the press is 'utterly unprepared' for Trump https://t.co/wZHRcPHY3X via @poynter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canberra man who allegedly fled cops 'shoved bottles of French champagne down his pants' https://t.co/6EjHeMvizc via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['The worst year of our lives' https://t.co/uhmmqofbgR via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkusMannheim I was expecting this tweet. Comma!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DFAT's costly 'Taj Mahal' headquarters was resisted, by @MarkusMannheim https://t.co/F3V4Jc73eX via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Triple-murderer grandfather charged after cellmate fatally bashed at Long Bay jail https://t.co/id2mRIxEbp via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could not stop reading this. Amazing story. The Fighter - https://t.co/FxQulOy7h4 https://t.co/2L1EPSzbry https://t.co/ILJJoicgnb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Murder, domestic violence and a death in custody mark grim 2016 in ACT's courts https://t.co/GP3Ml3mAIx via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canberra man charged with drug-drink driving four times in four months https://t.co/QpmyIrngMg via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Pope and the cartoons that defined 2016 https://t.co/dnDUBkC3T3 via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Identities emerge of seven arrested over foiled Christmas Day terror attack in Melbourne  https://t.co/KbEhfEKR2c via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Comanchero bikie accused of blackmailing drug dealer refused bail https://t.co/LJULWA3bCV via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ACT's peak legal bodies say boosted efficiency, resourcing would ease court delays https://t.co/1vccArso0W via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Car bomb' rams into Australian Christian Lobby headquarters in Canberra and 'explodes' https://t.co/sen5E2oaNQ via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NSW couple tried to have man's 14-year-old son and girl killed, court hears https://t.co/O6HFbVsQKl via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interfaith advocate Dean Sahu Khan, also a veteran ACT prosecutor, recognised in 2016 Multicultural Canberra Awards https://t.co/afj8E1hz8F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man charged with murder over Joondalup court stabbing  https://t.co/enhbQIp7q0 via @watoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Berlin Attack Is Right Out of the Terror Handbooks https://t.co/Icph5Aa9dE via @newyorker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A jury hasn't been able to decide if a woman who killed her mum with a hammer committed murder https://t.co/6VMuHKZeTK via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An @ACTSupCourt jury in Gabrielle Woutersz's murder trial has been discharged after failing to reach a verdict. More @canberratimes soon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ACT's top prosecutor hits out at 'unnecessary' delays in family violence court cases https://t.co/m6ac3uARgV via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is disturbing... Illegal Thai fishing hauls a possible threat to Woolworths sushi partner's supply @GuardianAus https://t.co/NrtP2iM2RD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['The system failed him': Coroner hands down findings on death of Paul Fennessy, by @alexmback https://t.co/ZCGxOThqf2 via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canberra barrister appointed as newest judge in the Federal Circuit Court  https://t.co/jivCgwcoWe via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['I live in fear': Wife recalls drowning fear as husband drove car into Lake Ginninderra https://t.co/bpILrQj9Oi via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Josaia Vosikata has been sentenced to a maximum of 22 yrs 10 mo imprisonment for murder Daniela D'Addario murder. More @canberratimes soon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Henry_Belot thanks Belto :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natashaboddy thanks Tashy :) xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@primroseriordan thank you lovely lady x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eddie Obeid’s sentencing the final plunge in his tumbling fall from grace, by @knausc https://t.co/mKxIRBp6Jl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eddie Obeid to face his own 'unpleasant reality' https://t.co/9Fk5QbD9zg via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Booooooo.... Robbed! Cricket Australia shuns Canberra fans next summer https://t.co/CROX121I92 via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Question of alleged failure to treat Steven Freeman's brain injury to be raised in inquest https://t.co/0yJ7oK7xAQ via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Daily Mail's pathetic pants-shaming stunt on Sam Armytage demeans us all | Brigid Delaney https://t.co/wg6l4YJSiF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Commonwealth prosecutors' no vote on pay deal indictment on 'nasty bargaining': CPSU https://t.co/SQbQ5ErxZv via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Only one piece of the puzzle': Baird government calls for national privacy laws https://t.co/klPSBMDEKs via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Canberra Good Food team's 20 favourite restaurants https://t.co/vLdm8vD0eh via @goodfoodAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canberra light rail worker thrown two metres by electric shock  https://t.co/DvoLwOGc64 via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Queanbeyan police accused of trafficking methamphetamines across NSW/ACT border  https://t.co/5JJmKt1PkR via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lockout, last drinks laws relaxed after review https://t.co/eA994RMoMO via @smh]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>