<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoKiwi55 still a start, more legal action is happening]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a hero!  Who is the federal judge who placed a stay on Trump's Muslim refugee deportations? https://t.co/GpsWaEjpi4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real community engagement style with Kia Ora Newtown opening today.  A place to have real conversations. https://t.co/TcPzUBDqwe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$3m for quake prone buildings: Fantastic initiative from the Government and WCC to secure prone buildings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Summer bbqing with the Greens and getting ready to change the government. https://t.co/rir4Dz6Slo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An innovative and pragmatic solution to buying in a hot market https://t.co/hQ3Sml2aGu https://t.co/LGAQZD8fiC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mural escapes quake demolition - good work WCC!   https://t.co/KQuU0EXssf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Climate change: Data shows 2016 likely to be warmest year yet-when will politicians finally act?   https://t.co/YEZP9q8MZW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sympathetic to this owner but will cost the city quite a lot so further analysis required before making any changes  https://t.co/Tcde6m39xu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or do you mean mothers should stay at home?  Family First calls for subsidies for stay-at-home parents https://t.co/aMxiFiLVWb via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Swedish six-hour workday fails, misleading headline, trial showed benefits, more trials needed.   https://t.co/RIQkTyhneJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Queue for the Cable Car right on Lambton Quay - our famous cable car always a hit with tourists https://t.co/SYaPMRHmHP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy New Year Wellington!!! https://t.co/DqQgSyuz6Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bears Ears and Gold Butte: Obama creates two nature preserves- wonderful legacy Obama! https://t.co/MxiU9bR3SF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting closer to nature and this wonderful creature at Wellington Zoo. https://t.co/GMdE3KcoqK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Road toll at nine after grim day: terrible and a waste of precious human life.  Driving safely a must. https://t.co/PjzyTdW7ez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you WCC for keeping the gym open so some of us could work off our excesses from yesterday and today too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George Michael has died - report: very sad news, one of my favourite singers from childhood. https://t.co/c2bOBKDmHm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy holidays to all, may have you have a safe and restful break.  See you in 2017.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good news you may have missed, worth a read after a sometimes grim year https://t.co/RTGhoNAiSO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New cabinet line up-nothing exciting here but at least climate change is with a very senior minister https://t.co/260TG0ARC4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you Catherine and Steffan for your many years of service, best of luck for the future https://t.co/Njn6ixJhlJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spend the money in Kaikoura, not in Wellington building unnecessary tunnels https://t.co/AHkkeszvbD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AceMcWicked @ScoopWellington a policy that may or may not have wide support]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[School and sun is out, watch out Wellington, the city's children are on the loose. https://t.co/3JqR4RjQ9f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would I lie to you led by politicians.  Best game at ICA party, tell 3 stories, only 2 true and guess which one is false.  Interesting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good AGM for Guardians of the Bay as they prepare for the court case against the runway.  Important to have all arguments before the court]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bad news, time for politicians to take action on climate change.  NZ response disappointing https://t.co/RDjZGwZ0V1 https://t.co/69teK2mjmH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Standing in solidarity with the Pike Families, justice for you now. https://t.co/pyWHAqSGv7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Summer in Wellington https://t.co/dpCNQr77DU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovely summer evening party tonight, thanks Mt Vic Residents Association for organising. https://t.co/1xItfvWYNv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Much better model for car use than a lot of personal ownership costing owners many thousands https://t.co/N8Pksd5BEQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prince of Wales Reservoir consultation on today until 2 at Massey, come on down https://t.co/rixqKgQvzk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Wellington-Wellington Summit, packed out room from all sectors with @justin_lester and councillors https://t.co/TJgNAmj8BW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good to be singing carols for cleaners with Living Wage campaigners and @justin_lester and Brian Dawson tonight https://t.co/uX1PKtwsWw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Updating Kilbirnie residents on what we are doing to address stormwater issues.  Progress made but more work needed https://t.co/1wiiUMYDkY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Xmas Aro Valley, thanks for the warm hospitality at the party tonight. https://t.co/35AGced2GP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another good school holiday programme from Aro Valley and good value too https://t.co/p9G6sBLHE7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaxRashbrooke Willis Street, behind Press House]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good, we need this information https://t.co/N8bRzM6Mn7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Latest building development in Wellington, the new Press Hall, great to see another good building being built https://t.co/XZ5kpM2oYn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A reminder of how much sugar there is in our drinks.  6 teaspoons for women and 9 for men is the max recommended https://t.co/eh8GLi4LdH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thorndon fair now on, beautiful food and goods, come and support a good cause. https://t.co/3wobPxxQ69]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@M_Cropp @ChrisCalviFree thanks, up now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Logan_B_Morton Yes, have some concerns about Frank Kitts Park redevelopment but do think a Chinese  Garden would be great]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see my initiative of last year being repeated, let's take advantage of these great fares https://t.co/H99RFpRM55]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Logan_B_Morton Also, we can't afford everything!  The reservoir is only one project that we need to do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Logan_B_Morton We are not, we are getting on with design but believe that funding should be equitably spread between local and central govt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wellingtonians worst at recycling?  Not exactly, exciting opportunity to do better with our new waste plan https://t.co/c0UExuSPib]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not true, the city will provide water, this is not a helpful approach just after an earthquake https://t.co/w09yWuk3vR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to President of the Oriental Bay Residents' Association standing down tonight for his years of service. https://t.co/eQcDuPHvnh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done Minister Joyce and mayor Justin Lester.  How we need support for those in earthquake prone building https://t.co/Gv0xGox17t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boat capsize: Five dead or missing - terrible news after a horror fortnight for our country.   https://t.co/h6abEMd9Mz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrating the 40th anniversary of the Mt Vic newsletter and the launch of the Mt Vic Hub, proud of my community. https://t.co/hWIPsuf5kw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[agreed, wasn't part of the decision but understand it was done bec it was safe, also many people live here, evacuating population a big call]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quake puts some deals on ice: we will be back on our feet soon, public safety first then back to business https://t.co/dtchZtclIi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come on down to talk about the proposed Prime of Wales reservoir.  We are here at Massey until 730. https://t.co/sN3ZHgn7ZH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrSeaRotmann @justin_lester @BaysGuardians @NewshubNZ thanks, resilience to quakes and climate change has to be the priority]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NZ School of Dance, your best performance yet, we are lucky to have such talented performers in our city.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to the excellent ICA for another thoughtful seminar on earthquake issues for inner city residents tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rahul_nz Thanks, yes a similar process has been going on for some time, still ongoing, do you know about Project Kaka?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another good day in the Aro Valley as we talked about how to make this brilliant community even more brilliant. https://t.co/X50ffc7miS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clifton Terrace car park to reopen tomorrow, NZTA say engineers believe the motorway is safe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A beautiful day, just the right tonic after a hard week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks everyone for your hard work this week and for just keeping on going, let's hope next week is a whole lot better!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A little relief then...https://t.co/qZnP4SMhgV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exciting news for Wellington https://t.co/hRaaQPiFMZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A little alarmist, public safety is critical, we just need to make sure that these buildings are safe  https://t.co/F0tXRvFAlO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pretty appalling waste of money Auckland Council by-election to cost ratepayers more than $100,000 https://t.co/CudNmOvsCc via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proud of the kids at Clifton Terrace School for leading the charge on waste education, showing adults how to do it https://t.co/RtW478lcJR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mad as a hatter:  Brian Tamaki blames sinners for quakes https://t.co/0cOm4VETPb via @nzherald https://t.co/OKjufAgwMh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Officials are not being over zealous, please be careful around Molesworth Street https://t.co/TKMOTsA07U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tough day people but hopefully the worst is over for most of us, thinking about the people of Kaikoura tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please call the Council on 4994444 if you have any flooding issues today, a big thanks to our infrastructure staff who are working so hard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A horrible day for the country, my thoughts with the families who lost loved ones and thanks to those who have worked to clean up the mess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope everyone is ok out there, staff working hard in Wellington to make sure the city is safe.  Stay tuned to media for more information.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poorly judged https://t.co/GP4CSLi2Lp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So proud to present Clyde Quay School with a certificate giving them a bronze award in the Enviro Schools programme! https://t.co/gp1uznE1RP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to the amazing Stephanie McIntyre winner of a Welly award, so well deserved. https://t.co/XTOGcRuT3D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to the new Tawa Community Board sworn in tonight, looking forward to working with you all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations John Fiso, winner of the Education Welly tonight, proudly supported by WCC. https://t.co/4y5L4ghTJf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Green co-leaders at our open home tonight.  Go Green Team 2017! https://t.co/PFTbPGivDX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, no, no, America what were you thinking?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learning about bee keeping at Te Aro School from the kids who know what they are talking about. https://t.co/JWyzpqT9m2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why the need for a review?  The answer should be obvious - let her go to see her family https://t.co/xEQyFWtWrG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And also another brilliant Fawkes Fair at Clyde Quay School, thanks to the hard working parents and teachers https://t.co/qtV53ZNl2N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As always a great Spring Fling at Papawai Reserve in Mt Cook.  Thanks everyone for a great afternoon out. https://t.co/5Qru5mbQla]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rather extraordinary, hasn't happened in Wellington yet.. https://t.co/N073GMeAHv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScoopWellington No talk of a developer yet and must protect views too, good design also must be a priority]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some good results here and a few things to improve on https://t.co/sHmhlxTtkd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very good, no room for excess spending https://t.co/N2O2KhzRHC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good, a hotel better than a carpark https://t.co/mKinDGSARG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, New World (Willis St), I do not need a plastic bag for one apple]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not exactly affordable but good re the reserve land https://t.co/HP8Q41n01a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PIppi the cat missing (Mt Vic)-my neighbour's beloved black cat is missing, she is micrchipped.  If anyone has seen her, please get in touch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't legislate against stupidity but council and the community have done a lot to address these issues https://t.co/Us8rt8pQME]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Needs to happen, this is one of the best pieces of public art in the city https://t.co/XUbWOmodcb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More than $200,000 needed to get a new Ferns sculpture flying above Civic Square in Wellington https://t.co/XUbWOmodcb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch out Mt Vic, all of the Mt Vic kids out for Halloween https://t.co/vVUVYSBe8C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great initiative, let's see more of these days https://t.co/C76iM22J09]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>