<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I have 15 new followers from Ireland, and more last week. See https://t.co/o8AcOjA5ia https://t.co/vKoSOU9ijG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlannaFeeney @avenuedublin @EwilsoO And you put the Gin in Ginuary!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks again to @AlannaFeeney @avenuedublin and the crew @avenuedublin for last night. The Sea Trout was amazing! https://t.co/5xBjX8fHiH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How was Costa allowed run the full length of the pitch and have a shot on goal? #LFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great article in today's @IrishTimes by @MalachyClerkin The interview with @RichieSadlier is excellent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have 22 new followers from UK., USA, and more last week. See https://t.co/o8AcOjA5ia https://t.co/j6qADy4GhH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EatDrinkRunFun I doubt he has a website!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EatDrinkRunFun There's a place called "Campbells" in Sundrive. Proper old school. He's the grumpiest man you'll ever meet, but a genius!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheCellarMaster What do you make of this carry on Alan?? https://t.co/TwexliRF9a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wayne Rooney only 96 goals behind Liverpool's top scorer. #LFC #Rushie #346 https://t.co/oEXbDzhCfm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My better half @EwilsoO is going to @avenuedublin for lunch today, I'm so jealous! #DineinDublin https://t.co/kE1dUbCwwP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First run back since November. https://t.co/0ZRbMvo8TY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best of luck to @blindrunner777 and @johnoregan777 Enjoy the adventure Sinead and John. The running sounds great, but not the flying!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have 15 new followers from Spain, and more last week. See https://t.co/o8AcOjA5ia https://t.co/HBVWDI3Pig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SakhoLad Not series, but great one off documentaries on Netflix: Only the Dead, Barkely Marathons, Welcome to Leith, Dawg Fight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SakhoLad Check out Quarry on Sky Atlantic. Seriously dark stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EwilsoO Your new favourite book! https://t.co/kUud8GFzAB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@avenuedublin @NickMunier @Karl_Bowe @GastroGays @gnelis @DermottRJewell @DublinBuzz1 @DubCham @FoodDublin @ClareWithTheHai I want all of it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulCooling Via @nprmusic: All Songs +1: How Aaron Dessner Helped Lisa Hannigan Beat Writer's Block https://t.co/4kLxPDJD24]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conor_feehan A guy who lives near me just wished me a Happy New Year... for about the 8th time in the past week! It has to stop!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time takes a cigarette, puts it in your mouth
You pull on your finger then another finger, then your cigarette… https://t.co/Se7t7DEIlS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm tethered to the logic of Homo Sapien 
Can't take my eyes from the great salvation 
Of bullshit faith 
#Bowie… https://t.co/ctFNTbFIN6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the day that's in it, there's only one album. #Blackstar #Bowie #GoneButNeverForgotten https://t.co/SACDIUQzIy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@avenuedublin Unfortunately most of them are Porn-Bots or people offering me 5000 followers for $100!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have 20 new followers from USA, and more last week. See https://t.co/o8AcOjA5ia https://t.co/LpAlfFHzqX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's way too much cool in this photograph. @davidbowie_news @PIXIES @thecure_ @SmashingPumpkin @foofighters to n… https://t.co/DoEylsGvTX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tome to watch "David Bowie:The Last Five Years" #Bowie #Blackstar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AngeCMJ No problem Ange. Send me through an email and we'll get on it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AngeCMJ All good Ange. I hope you have a great 2017!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have 10 new followers from USA, and more last week. See https://t.co/o8AcOjA5ia https://t.co/4NJzwg60oo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@avenuedublin @NickMunier Have a great evening guys. See you in January!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lunch time view. https://t.co/0HPk58fgmA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@avenuedublin Chilling out in Lisbon at the moment. 17 degrees and sunny!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have 18 new followers from Ireland, and more last week. See https://t.co/o8AcOjA5ia https://t.co/aRWe41ddeD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bowie_giorgia He spoiled us for decades, but he kept the best for last. We are so lucky to have lived in his time! #blackstar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best Christmas ever! @LFC pyjamas and @lowtheband socks. Life is good!! https://t.co/mVzhZ9fVqR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas present!! I love it!! https://t.co/LInI9mHIzr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@avenuedublin @NickMunier @AlannaFeeney Thanks for everything during the year. Looking forward to seeing you in the New Year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WalkinstownSV Could you tell me what time you open on Christmas Eve please?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@killianbyrne Eat, drink and be merry in December. Train hard and be good for the rest of the year! That's my motto.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The same number of people who marched against water need to come out to support @HSHIreland People's lives are at stake here. #apollohouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilM91 @HSHIreland The whole Apollo House movement has certainly raised awareness. It's a brilliant initiative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I drive down Dame Street every morning at 6:40. I have seen a major difference the past 3 days. Nobody sleeping rough. Thanks to @HSHIreland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have 24 new followers from USA, UK., and more last week. See https://t.co/o8AcOjA5ia https://t.co/pkWrvRRctV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I walk with the force. The force is with me. I walk with the force. The force is with me. #RogueOne #EVELIV https://t.co/4norkHGKTO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhilM91 Certain occasions demand IMAX. It's Hunty's big day out! #StarWars #EVELIV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Star Wars day! Imax in @cineworld Parnell Street. #StarWars #RogueOne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I dropped in to @HSHIreland in Apollo House today after work. It was very heartening to see the donations being handed in. #HomeSweetHome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't beat a glass of red in @avenuedublin on a Saturday afternoon! #Christmas #Dublin #dublinatchristmas https://t.co/l8P4l0v8j8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulCooling It looks the business alright. It's a great country too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NigeCarroll The more recent stuff is a bit to far out there for me. But the earlier material is nothing short of stunning! What a voice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NigeCarroll You need to check out Scott sings Jacques Berel. There's a brilliant "Best of 1967-1970" called Boy Child. #ScottWalker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Album of the year? No contest. #Bowie #Blackstar #Lazarus https://t.co/B9d4HY6sNt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @lowtheband for a very special night in @cccdub And thanks for the socks... to keep me warm (literally). https://t.co/VS4reDc90e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Erik_Koskinen I loved your set tonight supporting @lowtheband]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most bands sell the "album cover" t-shirt, @lowtheband sell "album cover" socks! https://t.co/IrHSGqLBqV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best socks ever @lowtheband #Low #Christmas #Dublin https://t.co/fVk7DLteZZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevinly @TMIECS @lowtheband @foggynotions Mo messing with you..,Straight to the top man!! Enjoy tonight. I'm looking forward to it,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My epic run of gigs comes to a close with @lowtheband in Christ Church]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevinly @TMIECS @lowtheband contact @foggynotions I think he's the promoter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have 13 new followers from India, and more last week. See https://t.co/o8AcOjA5ia https://t.co/ar4DFozcBi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cmacconiomaire Hi Colm. Can you let me know stage times for tonight please? Is there support? I'm looking forward to it. Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@killianbyrne @Prunch22 @robcullen79 @LFC No bother Killian. I'll get in touch with Rob.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great gig tonight @hypnoticbrass in @sugarclubdublin One seriously talented group!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KoolF1Kat only one thing for it Lynda, you'll have to unfollow @radioleary 😜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally @Rick_Stein revealed the mystery of the Pink Shirt on Long Weekends this week!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sugarclubdublin Do you have the stage times for @hypnoticbrass tonight please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘He gave his musicians the freedom to play as a child plays – fearless and free’ https://t.co/CQ9Y2vPXRF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow! What a performance from @LisaHannigan tonight. One seriously talented lady.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off to see @LisaHannigan tonight in @Vicar_Street with @PaulCooling Really looking forward to it! https://t.co/GFGf7Dy0tU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greatestalbumof Sorry, I didn't see that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greatestalbumof I'm confused. U2's Boy was released in 1980??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've just joined DEXTER Squadron. Click here to join: https://t.co/ZtC5nb22wg https://t.co/Jlt3fCYm2a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putting up the Christmas Tree listening to this beauty by @lowtheband Can't wait to hear it live on Tuesday! https://t.co/SVjqX7u1SD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is important... Shame on you @Aldi_Ireland Support Local Business. Buy Irish. https://t.co/pjc6qcjEfx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dan0mah You can tell that to the judge!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dan0mah @codingbocs I'll hold you to that. That tweet could end up costing you millions!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dan0mah What rate of commission am I on??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have 17 new followers from USA, Ireland, and more last week. See https://t.co/o8AcOjA5ia https://t.co/9w9g1QYUSI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlannaFeeney @NickMunier @avenuedublin @SnapDocklands I have to say, the duck terrine last night was one of the best dishes I've ever eaten]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KoolF1Kat @AlannaFeeney @NickMunier @avenuedublin @SnapDocklands @GateTheatreDub Enjoy your day Lynda. The duck terrine is stunning!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to @AlannaFeeney @NickMunier and all the team in @avenuedublin for looking after @SnapDocklands so well last night!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is without a doubt the funniest thing I've seen all week. Stick with it, comedy gold!! Thanks @LovinDublin https://t.co/JVZKAzI18M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What delights are in store for the @SnapDocklands crew in @avenuedublin tonight?? We can't wait to choose from the… https://t.co/qCIGPPNbAc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big night tonight! @SnapDocklands Christmas Party in @avenuedublin Can't wait!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@trublu1972 Yeah. It shouldbe great!! I'll keep an eye out for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@trublu1972 Hi Colm. Are you in @Vicar_Street]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to @agnesobel in @Vicar_Street tonight. https://t.co/6jaIILi2wM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dublin.. you're looking well! #LoveDublin https://t.co/tiBMZNertC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@avenuedublin @AlannaFeeney @NickMunier It's my favourite month. After all, I put the "Dec" in "December"!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishRunningGir I went through a phase of falling a few years ago, 3 in as many weeks! Thankfully it passed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have 8 new followers from Japan, and more last week. See https://t.co/o8AcOjA5ia https://t.co/zsckWQUuhL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the best thing I've seen all year!! #Yoda #StarWars https://t.co/qqWGt6SxyD via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EwilsoO This is you!! https://t.co/mnKTvZEcrh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes you just forget how good some albums are! #TheBand #MusicFromTheBigPink https://t.co/ussRZWC7rr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Connoed @avenuedublin @NickMunier @EatDrinkRunFun @monablake99 There's always one. Empty vessels make most noise!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My man of the match today! #Liverpool #LFCSUN #Jurgen https://t.co/ZOZV4nkmwF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@avenuedublin @NickMunier Let' see how much is left after Friday! #SnapDocklandsChristmasParty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have 10 new followers from 🇺🇸 #USA, and more last week. See https://t.co/o8AcOjA5ia https://t.co/IyMAK2Kqdq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Christmas Menu @avenuedublin is looking good!!!
https://t.co/dSL8mnVNAI]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>