<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanielBShapiro She pointed out that she conveyed "aloha" to the Syrian people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's doctor: "I’ve never been able to find anything wrong with him.”

Me: Trump needs to get a second opinion. 

https://t.co/glSrCRswDm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contradictory message: Reject discrimination of Muslims &amp; discriminate against Israelis. No, it's wrong regardless… https://t.co/0AbxOCSAQ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a relief to hear that the President doesn't share the anti-Islam views of his top adviser who he's trying to p… https://t.co/eiPvG6fV8w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A headline like this would once have been shocking - unfathomable in the U.S. - but in these dystopian times, it's… https://t.co/WymGkPZE9d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bannon is quite possibly the most dangerous man in America today. https://t.co/k0l2Cq5pTu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sure Bannon is holding down the fort in Trump's absence (and when he returns). https://t.co/FHI3i8XxhD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The natural consequence of a right-wing gov't that faces no external pressure from U.S. or domestic pressure from t… https://t.co/h52NQBs1GW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gabbard's "fact-finding trip" = a mtg w/ Assad &amp; conveying "the love, the care &amp; the 'Aloha' of the people of Hawai… https://t.co/9gnZ6Gep4K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump lost popular vote by 2.8 million votes - he's got no mandate for his extremist agenda. Dems must block his #SCOTUS pick, end of story.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3rd poll I've come across that finds more Americans supporting Trump's travel ban than those who oppose it. I think… https://t.co/FWK3Os1YwI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not sure why I'm getting these sponsored ads, but the "Sessions is a civil rights champion" part is hilarious.… https://t.co/oTUejYmL42]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, basically, Trump is running the White House in the same way he ran the Apprentice. Unfortunately, the consequen… https://t.co/4Nt7lWK7jW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thejpc The idea that the West is anti-Islam is key to their recruitment efforts. Trump's rhetoric/policies is Exhi… https://t.co/oKXPGpB5eh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It makes a big difference, b/c providing radical Islamists with additional ammunition helps their recruitment effor… https://t.co/vSgiv2EQnD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@haaretzcom #Hezbollah is presently embroiled in Syria's civil war, but terror group is Israel's top external thre… https://t.co/Wxtm6mDzDH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tens of Thousands of Israelis Could Die if Key Security Weak Spot Exploited, Experts Warn  https://t.co/rNPkSJDyBG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spot on NYT Editorial: Bannon is positioning himself as the de facto president. He's extraordinarily dangerous.  https://t.co/nVzXVBHc9m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's an updated list:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaxAbrahms Your tweet/op-ed is exactly what ISIS wants.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The WH's entry into Holocaust denial territory would be more shocking if a White Nationalist weren't the #1 aide. Also, Trump was a Birther!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@talschneider Looking forward to their side-by-side statements on the threats posed by Mexico.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there any group that the 10-day old Trump Administration hasn't managed to offend yet - other than White Supremacists &amp; Jihadists?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lrozen Spicer also said the other day that Trump is a "family man" with a "big heart."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Washington is even less safe today than a day ago. https://t.co/pvfWvl2sU8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LahavHarkov It would be amusing (scary?) to see Johnson &amp; Trump together, instead of all the photoshopped ones.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrKinKam @MaxAbrahms But does Max Abrahms know whether rumors of Assad's fatal stroke are true? This could be a po… https://t.co/TydGhIU8k5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Job Opening: Netanyahu spokesman Ran Baratz, who once said President Obama was an anti-Semite, is leaving his post. https://t.co/r4XVQk9w7R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["One posting [on social media] hailed the U.S. president as the best caller to Islam'."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White Supremacists &amp; Jihadist groups have something in common: they support Trump's travel ban EO https://t.co/PYeHlNeSd9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ironic since Ford's founder Henry Ford was an America Firster - but so extreme that he was removed from America Fir… https://t.co/EQWL18xDaN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@barak_ehud Barak: If Israel becomes a bi-national state, there will be generations of bloodshed, as in Belfast, B… https://t.co/QL62UqAjQA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fmr PM @barak_ehud: Under Netanyahu, Israel is becoming a bi-national state w/ a Jewish minority - it'll be the end of the Zionist dream.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The USA: "A nation that built its brand around the world as open to the world's needy and ambitious is now viewed..… https://t.co/PhcYLgxaAy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have a 0.00003% chance of dying in an attack by a foreign-born terrorist, according to @CatoInstitute. https://t.co/u7JvedfRBu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those of us who study the world - incl. leading conservative foreign policy experts - think you might take your own… https://t.co/VOeuY965YX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, therefore, we should conduct ourselves like those regimes? No thanks. https://t.co/76wWsZCUXf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glad to see some GOP Senators speaking out against travel ban, but for sanity to prevail, important to go further b… https://t.co/44SX2W8wBP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a week, the U.S. has switched from being a force for good in the world to an embarrassment, a rogue state in nee… https://t.co/GOghc8qtGM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jacobkornbluh Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jacobkornbluh What is their stance on the White House's implicit Holocaust denial?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 2020 U.S. presidential elections: Are we almost there yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bisma__Sheikh I really don't know. You'd have to ask @FoxNews.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bisma__Sheikh Not clear how accurately this poll reflects current sentiment but the polling firm is legit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AulaniMulford I hope it's not a poll that is representative of the nation's attitudes...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IlanBenZion Sorry, but Education Ministry is too busy outmaneuvering Bibi on settlements to worry about shortage o… https://t.co/eriTNQdLth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanielSeidemann If you're going to go the extra mile, please add Justice Ginsburg's health to your prayers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, it's been almost 3 months, but now even harder to comprehend than in Nov. how a top-notch Clinton/Kaine team lost to this abomination.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former PM @barak_ehud says what Labor's leadership should've be saying: Likud is harming Israel's security. Precise… https://t.co/P0vgsg3o74]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We didn't do such a great job vetting our new Commander-in-Chief but at least we're carefully vetting disabled Musl… https://t.co/Ph3MG5hvDx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@run_gabi_run Yes, it boils down to leadership. Messaging is key. Labor needs to offer a clear message to counter B… https://t.co/lSUt4gH9mO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@run_gabi_run It depends on (a) leadership - missing for years now from Labor &amp; (b) making a clear security-based a… https://t.co/8YwJOdJj0G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @StavShaffir, a rising star in Labor, is calling for a "restart" in center-left camp &amp; building a leadership will… https://t.co/8o5qBoK7t6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another senior security official - former NSC Adviser Brig.-Gen. (Ret.) Dani Arditi - has joined the Israeli Labor Party. h/t @talschneider]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #MuslimBan is not just a cruel idea, it's a stupid one. It will embolden jihadists &amp; fuel resentment that may lead to homegrown terror.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Failure to mention Jews in Holocaust statement, silence on rising tide of bigotry, &amp; elevation of Bannon's role in… https://t.co/0Thfvsp8AK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[However, Republicans in the House/Senate did not run openly and proudly on these policies. Their hypocrisy &amp; opport… https://t.co/07yQyVIsRx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Republican leadership is complicit w/ Trump. We may be stuck with the sociopath for 4 years, but in 2 years, we can shake up Congress.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labor Party MK @StavShaffir: "We know that 99% of former officials in the security establishment agree with our [peace] camp's positions."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We could've had our first female president. Instead, we're marking a milestone for White Nationalists. https://t.co/L6XmaPjfFu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danielstrauss A big CONGRATS to you! Very proud and can't wait to see this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnshelPfeffer It's a race to the bottom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While most Americans abhor Trump's xenophobic actions, let's keep in mind that some embrace it. They're called Whit… https://t.co/5d46XnEQ2t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SiegelCaryJ People who come to this country are carefully vetted, but this is about playing to people's fears, not border security.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZivGuy Begin subsequently took in hundreds more Vietnamese refugees. Today, Likud embraces racism, demagoguery, &amp; xenophobia, not Zionism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZivGuy Netanyahu needs to be reminded that Prime Minister Begin's first act was to grant permanent asylum to 66 Vietnamese refugees.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bibi's embrace of Trump's xenophobia is profoundly un-Zionist. Israel, like the U.S., is a diverse, pluralistic society built by immigrants.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haven't they been doing this already over the last year? This is what we call policy continuity. https://t.co/vIC6vRSWqD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Israeli PM Ehud Barak is apparently now a Nike employee. https://t.co/b12pjGk8XW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're just beginning Week 2 of Trump's presidency. https://t.co/QPb2i538wJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanielBShapiro I'm not shocked. Bibi &amp; advisers always identified w/ GOP; undercut Clinton in '97 &amp; Obama in '12 e… https://t.co/Woq2lKNWxV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fmr U.S. Amb. to Israel dismayed over Executive Order targeting Muslims &amp; refugees. Reports today of people being t… https://t.co/6bHOEOzdpd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Results of "Likudiada" - the Likud's mock primary - are in. An unimpressive list of mediocrities. Party isn't rushi… https://t.co/Uvd4UpNYbS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Labor Party is planning for post-Herzog era, whose days are numbered. That explains recent addition of high-pro… https://t.co/9g58Z9Wvr7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two top retired IDF generals - Maj.-Gen. (Ret.) Amiram Levin &amp; Maj.-Gen. (Ret.) Yom-Tov Samia - have joined Israel's opposition Labor Party.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bibi era provides a preview of Trumpism: greater divisiveness, less tolerance, erosion of democratic institutions,… https://t.co/Ykt8kTluhm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On #HolocaustMemorialDay, important to remember the millions of victims &amp; not repeat historical wrongs. We can't turn our backs on refugees.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today, the Pentagon will deal with America's top national security threat: Donald J. Trump. https://t.co/457ambGEmM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1st week of Trump's presidency confirms he's every bit the dangerous, authoritarian demagogue he was during the campaign - and maybe worse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CA Gov. Jerry Brown: "Familiar signposts of our democracy—truth, civility, working together—have been swept aside."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanielMillerEsq Temperamentally unfit to be a dictator? You clearly haven't seen Hitler's rant about his pizza arr… https://t.co/JDMEOUwgfI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoothWilliam If history is any guide, Cuban cigars &amp; pink champagne.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're suffering from Bibi-fatigue, don't despair. Netanyahu, Israel's longest-serving prime minister, has a suc… https://t.co/8817VhPOv5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just as I was about to stock up on avocados https://t.co/ilwPGjRr4D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In other words, Americans will be paying for the damn wall. https://t.co/p9VHVHilwC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ronald Reagan opposed construction of a fence &amp; called for an open border with Mexico.
https://t.co/6yV3PvOjh2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanWilliams @barak_ehud How much is @Nike paying him?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to former Sec. of Health &amp; Human Services Sylvia Matthews Burwell for becoming @AmericanU's 15th president &amp; 1st female president!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @attilus reports that Labor Party newcomer @GabbayAvi - an ex-minister in Netanyahu's gov't - is 2nd most popular person to lead party.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Internal poll in Israel's Labor Party: Amir Peretz is easily the favorite to lead party. Current chair Herzog scores at bottom. H/t @attilus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As we are a nation of immigrants, I hope he'll protect all of us from Trump. https://t.co/KZbRsN8OpK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We may finally get to the bottom of the 1876 presidential elections. Did Hayes legitimately defeat Tilden? Happy my… https://t.co/kkNV9CAmJa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TulsiGabbard meets w/ Assad on secret trip likely funded by him &amp; is now his mouthpiece. She belongs with Trump, not w/ Democratic party.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ibishblog Agreed. I learned a lot from him in my IPF days. Impressive, eloquent thinker and - as you say - dedicat… https://t.co/ID76h38mm0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My guess is that they're not sharing secret risotto recipes on their private email accounts. Too ethnic. https://t.co/88sJt6vkoo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the Trump Administration's idea of a two-state solution https://t.co/hvplEF8aMx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chances for a deal under Netanyahu slim to none, but imagine public support if the opposition actually proposed alt… https://t.co/OSZ7xTkSWE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The INSS survey demonstrates Israelis' readiness for far-reaching compromises for peace despite Netanyahu government's anti-peace policies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Regulations are not out of control; they're necessary to protect Americans' safety &amp; health.

Trump, on the other h… https://t.co/R9sbgU7MNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @ShibleyTelhami finds that, contra Trumpism, attitudes of most Americans toward Muslims improved in past year.
https://t.co/BX7M8uZtNc]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>