<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Financialization of Rents Gets Taxpayer Guarantees  https://t.co/vmajvA7fmV They released this SEC filing 1/23/17, an Obama fast-one!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[United Arab Emirates Cheers Trump Immigration Policy - Breitbart https://t.co/70SjCj7lNy via @BreitbartNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PETITION To President Donald J. Trump, Attorney General Jeff Sessions To Investigate/Prosecute  George Soros, Et. Al https://t.co/Bi5oxQMUq7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why isn't Afghanistan on President Trump's list? https://t.co/C1bRaW1lsN Many other places should also be added to the list!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Open borders left, refugee contractors plan days of action https://t.co/LFMzIGNnyv #NPNA Agenda: Replacing old Americans with new Americans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CHSommers @KatiePavlich @shane_bauer Well, the protestors were nudged a bit -&gt; https://t.co/wJmKl01GWA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious Cartoon Brutalizes Starbucks For Hiring Refugees Instead of Citizens https://t.co/huHgyPJZCM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump was right about Schumer's fake tears. Audio Just Leaked by @NumbersUSA  - https://t.co/24EeGTIpQ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you know abortion in the EU is unlawful after 12 weeks? Only in America can a baby be born full term &amp; killed the same day via #abortion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shocking: Trump Trade Admin Has Just Called Out China, Says White House DONE With Their Scam https://t.co/PX4mYwnxSz #GREATNEWS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marklevinshow @CR Good article-don't jump the gun. Let's hope he's got the backbone of Justice Scalia &amp; doesn't cave to pressure fm Kennedy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnDuval1 @NancyPelosi is doing the work of her evil mentor, certainly not a representative of God! #ProLife #DefundPlannedParenthood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shooters_Wife   @NancyPelosi really thinks if she answers very serious questions by confusing the issues, we won't notice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shooters_Wife    @NancyPelosi thinks people opposing her are as befuddled as her supporters are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WATCH – Anonymous Goes LIVE: ‘The Take Down of George Soros Has Begun’ https://t.co/Yx7ZleUo5O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenSchumer "independent justice"? Ginsberg is "independent"? Kagan, Sotomayor? Every1 of left wing judiciary has spit on the Constitution!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Makada_ @lsferguson @CBSLA  Is CA a member of the Union? They have no right to secede to Mexico. That's treason!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobertPBayer1 @FAIRImmigration @EconomicTimes Good point. Democrat purposeful agenda of Failed Schooling has far-reaching repercussions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@frankgaffney @DailyCaller There shud be more countries added 2 no-travel EO. Just b/c they're UK citizen, not = safe. London has Sharia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mchooyah You are right, Sir. I *know* the point you're making. Thank God for His provision of forgiveness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NOLAnews There's no provision in the US Constitution that allows cities, w/out voter approval, to reject federal law willy-nilly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PressSec GOOD JOB TODAY, SEAN! It's been so obvious how press corp twists truth.  Finally there is someone to correct and call them out!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn something about previous immigration bans: https://t.co/AtLj4he846]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's nothing wrong with vetting immigrants. Even Heaven has a gate. https://t.co/WG8Nmqoqw4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There were no such protests when Obama restricted Christian refugees to the US inspite of their slaughter in Syria! https://t.co/Kf05KGirxe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheDemocrats Can't you read?! US Cases of Refugees arrested/convicted on terror charges, &amp; other heinous crimes-&gt; https://t.co/YD7jisbswk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moving a muslim to USA no guarantee he'll assimilate! - From US Helpers in Iraq to Sex Criminals in Colorado https://t.co/wYsPIKSuBF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxNews @FoxNewsSunday ALL IMMIGRANTS MUST BE VETTED! - From US Helpers in Iraq to Sex Criminals in Colorado https://t.co/wYsPIKSuBF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Did you cave &amp; agree to take Australia's rejected asylum seekers? This is no "deal"!  https://t.co/WPHVfj4XIM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxNewsSunday @KellyannePolls RefugeeContractors knew ExecOrder was coming but put people on flights anyway! https://t.co/OBc48y9sIZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump  Rohingya are economic migrants, fake refugees, do not admit to US https://t.co/FPqY6T5x4U via @wordpressdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Refugee cap of 50,000 for FY2017? As of today we are at 32,094!  https://t.co/d11oQ94Ld0 via @wordpressdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RickRWells #Mexico has ruined America by all their exports -&gt; salmonella lettuce, heroin, drugs, thieves, gangs, commie ideas, freeloaders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lagop We must outlaw #abortion -&gt; https://t.co/CDSQ8O1InO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mfrperez @MarkSteynOnline @PhelimMcAleer @annmcelhinney @CRTV I had no idea EU prohibits abortion after 1st term! https://t.co/CDSQ8O1InO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did u know abortion in the EU is unlawful after 12 weeks? Only in America can a baby be born full term &amp; killed the same day via #abortion!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marksteynonline Thanks 4 highlighting this book "Gosnell: The Untold Story of Americas Most Prolific Serial Killer" https://t.co/abq0JAGywO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joe_America1776 @ConstitutionNat   @ProjectVeritas already exposed them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shooters_Wife ...and USA @POTUS vowed to protect his people. Who do you think will win? @realDonaldTrump will win of course! #MakeMexicoPay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProLifePolitics @ProLifeAction We finally have a @POTUS who will fight against ProLife-blacklisting by media. https://t.co/5zsQu7PvsW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Trump Watch! Don't leave the Rohingya ( from Burma) off extreme vetting list! https://t.co/uq35KXj5uS via @wordpressdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Please take note:  Another 500 refugees added since yesterday; come on Donald! https://t.co/dAD05rl8HJ via @wordpressdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marthamaccallum is doing good job on #first100days. She seems to understand what @realDonaldTrump is doing, but presses the hard questions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MTD213 @GCDUNHAM1 @BillCassidy but never, never let govt workers, no matter how high their position in office, 2 dictate or rig my coverage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MTD213 @GCDUNHAM1 @BillCassidy If we could choose the insur co nationwide, choose how much coverage, &amp; dicker over rates, we'd be betteroff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @POTUS -&gt; Trump Watch! Don't leave the Rohingya off extreme vetting list! https://t.co/uq35KXj5uS via @wordpressdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking news! Reuters is reporting that President Trump will sign executive orders on refugee… https://t.co/lnG3fBDVeS via @wordpressdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BillCassidy @SusanCollins #RINO Heathcare replacemt bill will retain all Obamacare taxes! https://t.co/EFKNJ1UDIS @realDonaldTrump #StopEm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GCDUNHAM1 @MTD213 Exactly, neither Federal nor State govts should be interfering! @BillCassidy BAN OBAMACARE!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamiedupree You're the typical reported as described here! You're NOT doing your job! @SatireWorks is right! https://t.co/51sxxu8LF3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Deplorable_Left @CharlesKrauthammer was wrong when he said amt was too small to try to retrieve! When ur $20T in debt? Fund Hamas? #GoTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Conservative_VW Soros funds this destruction. Why hasn't Soros been put into Gitmo with other terrorists?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@senJohnKennedy @SteveScalise @BillCassidy People&amp;doctors know what they need: direct access w/out interference https://t.co/CWapzIMVoV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BillCassidy  You MUST allow people 2 decide what healthcare insur they want, not the state! Liberal governments will force people on O'care]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@weknowwhatsbest @GaetaSusan Supplying aid to the enemy, Hamas, and they still refuse to admit Obama is a #traitor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Ryan Allies 'Alarmed, Angered' by 25-Year-Old Julia Hahn - Breitbart https://t.co/rjtebWMZK2  Must be a good move if Ryan is angered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rasmussen: President Trump’s Approval Index Booms Up Since Inauguration - Breitbart https://t.co/tsn2zR7JFL via @BreitbartNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@janedmunds @DarrellIssa @realDonaldTrump You're an absolute moron.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnDuval1 @wordpressdotcom Trouble is, there are too many that won't read this &amp; too many who read it, but won't believe it! Great Article!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TruthFeedNews @DMashak Does @PRyan really believe that illegals w/ CA driver's licenses, who were paid 2 vote &amp; 2 protest, did *not* vote?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump On 1/20/2017 you told them, to their faces, in front of the whole world that their thieving days are over! GOD *Bless* You!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatDollard    yes, stealing political &amp; social power, but don't forget tv's &amp; sneakers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Blessed are the peacemakers..." of which Obama is not included. Obama has departed leaving nothing but chaos &amp; rioting in the streets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KenMac55 Impressed by the whole Trump family. Bible teaches 2 judge a tree by the fruit it bears. We see the meaning of that wisdom here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RickRWells @POTUS Pardoning Clinton &amp; assoc's is no guarantee they will behave in the future. It'll encourage more institutionalized crime.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toddstarnes @ABC  @shepnewsteam of @foxnews said "anarchists" too strong to use as description of "protestors". Smith coming out as leftist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coverage comments by @chucktodd @nbcnews more generous towards new @POTUS than @shepnewsteam @foxnews. Makes me sick!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FLOTUS Mrs Melania Trump is an exquisite beauty with class &amp; grace. She is really someone we can look-up to. So proud of First Family Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StocksAlotTEMP @Snap_Politics Burning garbage? Doesn't that create carbon polution? #HowDumbCanUB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Revelation1217 Why do think Bill Gates gave away Windows10 free to every user? It's the most invasive software of all!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@foxnews Show the whole parade, the bands &amp; troops, not just black car!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Frappingline @JoyAnnReid Obama supporters don't work; Trump supporters are responsible contributors to society.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RIGHTZONE Repairing the damage &amp; moving ahead is a #YUGE job. @Potus Trump with our prayers of support is up to the challenge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SlabbedNewMedia @BillKristol @POTUS  I believe @Potus Trump is sincere in his words to do his best to #MAGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TEN_GOP #PitifulChumps working 4 *evil* influences. They'll never know joy &amp; satisfaction of Family Love, Work Well Done, God's Forgiveness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ultraconcept  Police &amp; Natl Guard are there... arrested 95 all ready]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TEN_GOP These #anarchists R professional troublemakers imported fm all over world by evil elites like Soros.  Arrest these #PitifulChumps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BillKristol @SlabbedNewMedia WE DON'T NEED EMPTY WORDS. @POTUS TRUMP WILL ACT TO RENEW AMERICAN FREEDOM!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephenfhayes Others talk abt freedom &amp; liberty, but @Potus Trump will act to bring it back to us!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephenfhayes When @Potus Trump mentions putting #America1st he's talking abt Freedom/Liberty  for Americans thru job opportunities!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McClatchyDC That's because most @realDonaldTrump @POTUS supporters are at work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarrellIssa @realDonaldTrump      #LockHerUp should be number one priority]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PamelaGeller @gatewaypundit CONGRATULATIONS!! Thanks for your unrelenting fight against radical islam!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Previous presidents squirmed during Pres Trump's speech which highlighted their failures? #HireAmerican #BuyAmerican @realDonaldTrump @POTUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump CONGRATULATIONS, MR. PRESIDENT! LONG LIVE AMERICA!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxNews @BillHemmer @ShannonBream THANK YOU!!! :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@foxnews @BillHemmer @ShannonBream Let us hear some of the music being played by our natl choir &amp; band!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Numbers of refugees arriving this month are through the roof! https://t.co/snwlbQR93J via @wordpressdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RudyTakala What time does Obama leave?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I pray 4 the well-being of you &amp; your family &amp; 4 the successful administration of your duties in Making America Great Again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatDollard Surrender implies u were once opposed to those who overpowered you. Obama never opposed radical islam! Obama always supported it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RickRWells Obama's accommodating his puppeteers who fear Trump &amp; have called for more redistribution of USA wealth  https://t.co/kVxTgsuCPb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNN: Assassinating Trump Could Keep Obama Admin in Power https://t.co/8dCPDEPLjn  @CNN can't get over being exposed faking news! Shameful!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/IB8M55kjb7 Aren't actors supposed 2B good at character study? #BarbraStreisand clueless! She loves Clinton/Obama Jew haters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US B-2's kill more than 80 ISIS fighters in Libya https://t.co/OalnjcD6j2 WHAT WAS THIS ABOUT? Why now? Why from Missouri? Don't trust Obama]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terrorist Freed by Obama Placed 130 Bombs Across U.S. https://t.co/DfQYhBmAWM  WHAT'S OBAMA'S PAYBACK GOING TO BE?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Davos: More Redistribution Answer to 'Scary' Populism https://t.co/kVxTgsuCPb Elites fear #Trump &amp; #Brexit will hinder their "progress".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama Commutes Life Sentences of Four Mexican Cartel Leaders https://t.co/aTj3YmR66P AND WHAT WILL THE MORENO BROTHERS GIVE HIM AS PAYBACK?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Obama's Walking Out Of White House With Boxes Of "Fine Art" https://t.co/OJV3cgSo9V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AGJeffLandry @Louisiana_sos  Fight Obama's Takeover of Louisiana's Election Process!! Keep Louisiana https://t.co/Q46oOHLsNs]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>