<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@TLC @MyUmami79 @TLCmeNow at least this was a great result, was very chuffed for them both as they had the right attitude]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MyUmami79 aww not quite result i was after, but you carried yourself well..Janice shouldve played things cool, hope you work it out though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HaunSoloProject LOL good timing alright, we were just talking about him earlier :p (was okay @realjonlovitz it was good talk LOL)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kristintbooth looks better than some of the supposed art we saw at the museum today LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlamedaDowning  @kristintbooth @Eric_Mabius @geoffgustafson @RealCrystalLowe @MarthaMoonWater because im a day ahead can i watch 1st? :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@didileard @jamienotis thats a prerequisite for that show isnt it? :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasegunn @realDonaldTrump that is probably next.....he is mad you know...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RossLTaylor thought Kane had lost it with some poor fielding placements...the bowling wasnt too great, but we'll take any win over them :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[good result there @BLACKCAPS, we'll take it...wins a win]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@braydenwalker1 @lauramcgoldrick @scottbstyris @simon was thinking 330 might be....we shall see...but probably not, but great last over :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimHipsley if its wonky for both sides then its not a problem...harden up...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeorgiaLove71 @radiosportnz is that @bawads ??? always a great commentary when he's around, the king :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SoCaliGirlO2 oh yeah im glad i live where i do, it doesnt stop us all being affected in some way though....we're on the same side here...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BLACKCAPS last time you put building a partnership we lost 3 wickets....so just dont :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WisemanSara @realDonaldTrump @Avaaz i wouldnt have opened with Dear...theres nothing dear about the mongrel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamBuzz last thing we need is you getting more clucky.....oh look seafood :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Andrew_Mulligan oh dear nevermind :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KarenDavid @onceabcofficial @Disneyland @OnceABC  thats good casting, she could pass as your taller sister, but does she dance as well?  :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AllOfMyHeartTV @IamLaceyChabert @brennan_elliott @hallmarkchannel looking pretty smooth there Brennan :) (and Lacey lovely as always :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SWTGallagher @cricinfo probably someone who isnt even aussie, like many of their successful musos/actors :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenealogyPBS yep we all had them from somewhere to somewhere... the girls who left their families i find remarkable and brave...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dastmalchian i can see how you find it hard to tell the difference, they're the ones with the hate in their eyes and zero heart...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CoryBooker good on you, ive been watching from afar and am so glad to see you manning up and not sitting idle, damn shame you even have to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FretlessMonster those were some cool cats those pioneers..and Marvin, Sam Cooke....mucho awesomeness poured out of them too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[rellie in Canada just had an adorable baby girl...good to see he kept up the family tradition of beautiful girls (us guys, not so pretty :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sonia_mafs im just glad she has found her thing she wants to do and that its something positive ...im pretty proud of her for that :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sonia_mafs i hope you dont mean the idea of marrying....im far from ready for that (besides shes too young) :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GenealogyPBS @PBS is there any word on a new series yet???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HaunSoloProject good on you girl, give them nazis hell for me :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[lil miss starts her endeavour to become @sonia_mafs pt 2 not getting hitched to a stranger (no way), shes training to be a social worker :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SoCaliGirlO2 some are being handcuffed and asked what they think of him.....now he thinks hes king, is just a fucking mad dictator]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealCrystalLowe i cant go near this without my coffee...too much thinking required......oh look, brews up.... :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tom_MAFS @KortKneee_Rae good, just checking i didnt have to send either of you a cake with a chisel in it (i bake like he does taxes)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[every good rocker needs a (mostly) darling daughter to mellow out with in their old(er) age...happiest of times are to come im sure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[have got my best friend visiting for a few days (arrives tomorrow) then he heads home to find out what sex his baby is...i say a girl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hallmarkmovie i cant think of any other reason to :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sumostevenson @Blitzboks and good sportsmanship/humility shown by the captain, well done...excellent to watch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sumostevenson those people doing that are the morons who are only there to  be seen to be at events, they wouldnt even know what rugby was]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[shades of Hitler right there definitely....my answer @realDonaldTrump is a fucking asshole at best... https://t.co/bPWLyODf8K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MilesDavisLive yep, just as ugly and shitheaded in cartoon form...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SoCaliGirlO2  like it really matters? that kind of thing should be left behind closed doors, cant stand anyone preaching to me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tom_MAFS @KortKneee_Rae i hope neither of you have got Trump to take care of those taxes for you :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vurnt22 seems for now at least one ballsy judge has stuck up for what is right...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hallmarkmovie only that some of my ancestors left there in the 1700s :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sumostevenson i mean marketed as its own sport..its still great to watch :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sumostevenson there was a time when it was...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kristintbooth @hallmarkmovie i for one (amongst many) look forward to the new fllm (and the following ones) :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bhmfan Obama is both white and african :) (im distantly related to his mum :), whereas Trump, fuck knows what planet he's from....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LZZYHALE @1200WOAI good to see @DamonJOfficial rocking out too...is that Pete Willis' gatt? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vurnt22 great that he lived to be remembered and that you have cared enough to do so...so kudos to you both]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BLACKCAPS @RossLTaylor fingers crossed for some more big ones for ya..a win or 2 would be good as well :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FirstDates @MerlinFDC4  that guy was hilarious, just what the batty old bird needed :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if only more of you americans spoke such truth....
https://t.co/rasFRgswZ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KarenDavid as much as i dont like my birthday being lauded id be happy if a clone of yours danced for me like that anytime LOL #CuteAs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MyUmami79 mum has a brother we're trying to find but our laws here are rubbish so its  tough going,but love when others have great results]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MyUmami79 @TLC yes indeed, we watch all 3 versions of the show, and love them all..even an old badass like me gets a bit of a lump going :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TLC @MyUmami79 i hope we see plenty of those beautiful smiles this coming episode...will make sure i have a clean hanky too LOL #Prepared]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MyUmami79 @TLC @mslisajoyner @ChrisJacobs you'll be (hopefully) pleased to know ive told family in the US, UK and here in NZ to tune in :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@moniquethestar couldnt give a damn as long as there is some bog roll LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patvalley sir even? usually people calling me that want something, guess the same can be said for Benji type dogs? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blairwilki2 @kristintbooth you are not wrong :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClayneCrawford i have to agree...sorry but its true :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patvalley good morning reginald!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RachelDeAlto i think im guilty of that being a permanent thing...it comes in handy when researching genealogy though :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kristintbooth good luck with the headache...and the kidlets :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dantebrown @LethalWeaponFOX @LethalWriters watched the ep last night, sorry you didnt get that trip to NZ (which is where i live) :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edovdkolk you seemed to have gotten the wrong memo, im pretty sure that was Elvis Presley, #ThereCanBeOnlyOne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisJacobs @mslisajoyner must say i love your empathy and sincerity in presenting #LongLostFamily, it must provide great comfort to all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MyUmami79 @TLC @mslisajoyner @ChrisJacobs will indeed be watching, fantastic heartfelt episode this week, remarkably courageous mum/girls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MyUmami79 @TLC @mslisajoyner @ChrisJacobs oh good that tells me one reunion went well...that makes me very pleased, congrats to all :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MyUmami79 @TLCmeNow @TLC just about to watch the 2nd episode of the What Happened Next....hopefully better outcomes this week? #Hopeful :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keeshasharp doing a beer run for @ClayneCrawford  ? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dantebrown @LethalWeaponFOX @LethalWriters still waiting to see this lineup of girlfriends of his as well :). loads of potentials there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dancedeadly666 @keeshasharp @DamonkWayans i voted for you all for the Peoples Choice awards but none of my picks won anything...ripped off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DamonkWayans @dantebrown @keeshasharp how long til he becomes a cop? just putting it out there, let's not tell Trish just yet :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LethalWeaponFOX what???? 2 weeks??? no no no none of this waiting nonsense...im calling @keeshasharp .....sort it girl.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DamonkWayans @keeshasharp i think there might be plenty enough Murtaughs to go around no? :p #WearABoxWednesdays]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keeshasharp @LethalWeaponFOX any news on that yet?  it SHOULD be a certainty...or im blaming that screwup @realDonaldTrump for that too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dantebrown @keeshasharp @LethalWeaponFOX @LethalWriters LOL write me in, i'd do a cameo for free LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keeshasharp @dantebrown Mums are on a need to know basis :p...stay strong lad :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keeshasharp ive found some real shockers in my genealogy....who the hell calls their kid "Submit" ????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keeshasharp gotta grab those zzz's when we can...hopefully not when you're talking with him but :p (avoid those daggers hubs :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xXgertieXx @LethalWeaponFOX @DamonkWayans @ClayneCrawford someone has to, us men can be pretty hopeless otherwise :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GabbieRaeRocks when will the album be out? ..dont do a @Real_Sykes on me here :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LethalWeaponFOX @DamonkWayans @keeshasharp had a pal like that when we were teens, always showed up for grub my sister called him Lunchbox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keeshasharp @adeleBlim @MrGeneHong @LethalWriters probably for the best that idea she failed at that rhythm gymnastics then? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarbaraNiven @dailykos the facts of anything and everything would be good, i would've thought essential...but hey that's just me being real]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keeshasharp tomorrow for me, but seeing as im here i may as well laugh at yours and @DamonkWayans  replies to people :) #ItdBeRudeNotTo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@avancenz can't say i blame her after the sexist pigs didn't give her the head sherangs job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshgwal definitely could pass as her son at least :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRue had the same thing for the last Die Hard film funnily enough....was brilliant :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DamonkWayans shades of @fotc #1 man Murray...."whos present?" :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LethalWeaponFOX @ClayneCrawford @JordanaBrewster i reckon the wife would want him to move on, @keeshasharp's friend wouldve been nice :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeriWilsonauthr  i think @cindy_busby wanted a rather exotic kiwi guy in the sequel.... its either me or @russellcrowe  (im cheaper :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeriWilsonauthr @cindy_busby cupcakes dont tend to last long around me, certainly not long enough for me to wing any your way :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cindy_busby @awonderfulmovie @hallmarkchannel @TeriWilsonauthr @RyanPaevey i'm on Teri's case, if i have to throw ideas in i will  LOL :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ange49nz at least they are on...phew....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@awonderfulmovie @hallmarkchannel @TeriWilsonauthr @cindy_busby @RyanPaevey ....now about that sequel folks??? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@c_rollyson pleased to read it, you were all very endearing so its not hard to care :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Eric_Mabius sounds just like home at the moment...and this is meant to be summer ? :)]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>