<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/GWuM2PigKl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justice Department to challenge judge's halt of travel ban https://t.co/6MWoxPSr0M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arabs Should Look In The Mirror Before Criticizing Trump’s Travel Ban https://t.co/DuqHLh0diP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Hundreds of Rohingyas' killed in Myanmar crackdown https://t.co/TEMUii814D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can now take a course at the world’s best universities for free https://t.co/OmOXN9LTIU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Norway PM held at Washington airport over 2014 visit to Iran https://t.co/JAhVQWm34v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/WiqvcOd0Mg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/blbXuAhitg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/RRdgkj9Uif]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Palestinians claim U.S. threatens 'severe steps' if leaders sue Israel in world court - Palestinians https://t.co/QtW2jik4Ri]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White supremacist Richard Spencer hails Trump's 'de-Judification' of Holocaust - U.S. News https://t.co/IKEV2gEIvH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fields Medal mathematics prize won by woman for first time in its history https://t.co/Gv6mblMqW0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All six of America's 2016 Nobel Prize winners are immigrants https://t.co/UsoN28VkaP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harvard president hits back at Trump's immigration ban: 'Nearly half of the deans of Harvard's schools are... https://t.co/ePtSJoiF8t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In response to #MuslimBan, Jewish university declares itself a ‘Sanctuary Campus’ https://t.co/PTOiTNAdGv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jews Hand Muslims Synagogue Keys When a Texas Mosque Burns Down https://t.co/cGS95ceJ6m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Detroit family caught in Iraq travel ban, mom dies waiting for approval to come home https://t.co/7tEFUbncQA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Man Is the Most Dangerous Political Operative in America https://t.co/vIxc8uzaT5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jews across America are rising up against Trump's refugee ban: 'We haven't forgotten our history' - U.S. News https://t.co/DNyPlHOvZD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Muslims got blocked at American airports, U.S. veterans rushed to help https://t.co/VRUyerSFVc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instagram photo by FALLON JEWELRY • Jan 28, 2017 at 11:41pm UTC https://t.co/PtUkucPNGg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chuck Schumer Cries Over Immigration Ban https://t.co/yjXSbmi6P6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Americans raise over $800k in one day to rebuild mosque burned down in Texas https://t.co/NbQY0id2IJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/EISqnnALWL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jihadist groups hail Trump’s travel ban as a victory https://t.co/yo1BFJkc6s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump but what if the bad never actually left? What if they were shopping and changed or delayed their flight? :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instagram photo by Chris Rock • May 21, 2016 at 11:36am UTC https://t.co/emHQ0fP1TS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet the rookie federal judge who halted Trump’s refugee deportations — to save a Syrian https://t.co/n8THOKcgee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Respond to Donald Trump's Betrayal of American Values https://t.co/1TZjoVox6C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lyft will donate $1 million to ACLU after Trump immigration ban https://t.co/CPvGAPr8Yr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Syrian Christians turned back at airport https://t.co/ssmWhfr653]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Ryan: Trump's executive order is not a Muslim ban https://t.co/rDFNUWgqNC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/x21Yr00tfZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There is nothing wrong with America that cannot be cured by what is right with America."William J. Clinton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federal judge blocks Trump immigration ban nationwide https://t.co/nxEhwCFjgH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking: Judge stays deportations; Trump order barring refugees, migrants from Muslim countries triggers chaos,... https://t.co/ecsDhje7i6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Announcing the NYU Immigrant Defense Initiative | NYU School of Law https://t.co/pYVSNXV3Hc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 1939 the US turned away a Jewish refugee ship. This Twitter account commemorates the victims. https://t.co/CcVfTv7rsg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mexico voices strong protest after Netanyahu tweets about Trump's wall https://t.co/KL0RZQJP8t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['It's Tearing Families Apart.' Three Stories of Lives on Hold Due to Trump's Visa Ban https://t.co/w7qeh0H37Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Groundbreaking Gene-Editing Therapy Eliminated Cancer in Two Infants https://t.co/8PpVsU8CSi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Forgotten Stories of Muslims Who Saved Jewish People During the Holocaust https://t.co/pJRNUuO8Au]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump didn’t come up with the list of Muslim countries he wants to ban. Obama did. https://t.co/UDOShmDx8m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/R7yG7r64Pp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YahooCare your service is the worst. Hackers take control of emails and change recovery emails. You do nothing to stop it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scientists turn hydrogen into metal in breakthrough that could revolutionise the planet https://t.co/A5W9o3PLZO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/ouDaClTy2Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion | The State Department’s entire senior management team just resigned https://t.co/VTD7BtuSZt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/gnj2VnX2W6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/0Ls2erUNlM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrantRumley @ilangoldenberg they are allowed to marry more than one -- things could get even more interesting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@issacharoff also no messages from @WhiteHouse or @realDonaldTrump at all. Total blackout.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adamrasgon1 @GrantRumley tirawi is pushing Zaki to undermine rajoub. Same old boys game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adamrasgon1 @GrantRumley who will it be? Abbas Zaki nominated himself and Rajoub wants it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/9zo16r8O29]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JSchanzer Trump himself made the pledge to move it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How is it that we don't have an app to count  number of protesters?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@POTUS a Palestinian state please. WIN -WIN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/uOlZYrI4AM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Palestine in the Age of Trump https://t.co/RUlxMzLQvO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/dlQ9fh1xdj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese president calls for East Jerusalem as capital of Palestinian state https://t.co/2MW0Fs27Bb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/KumS5xr1i4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pelindabaX Jordan can't contain 80% Palestinian population from going to the streets and protesting. It's extremely dangerous for Jordan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pelindabaX it is already being used by many groups as a recruiting tool to threaten US interests. It's an invitation to attack Americans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hidden Dangers of Moving the U.S. Embassy to Jerusalem | RAND https://t.co/UpAMPTFFGo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/F1dV4OZxXJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook https://t.co/g5oTHctbeM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook https://t.co/F5rNAoAl0Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Palestinians  protest @realDonaldTrump pledge to move US embassy to Jerusalem https://t.co/ZnNPntsayB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Palestinians  protest Trump's pledge to move US embassy to Jerusalem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YahooCare hackers change recovery emails and block us from gaining access. What r u doing to solve this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook https://t.co/qAwn8tNDnc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CIA releases 13 million declassified documents online - BBC News https://t.co/HCXs6SgT2j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/oTQyOQrSGQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook https://t.co/XdGUF8V25x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook https://t.co/kQMigmCb8g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook https://t.co/gt2XSfB2L2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women Reclaim The Streets Of Cairo Through Stunning Ballet Photos https://t.co/MMrdWGWSqq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump if @CNN viewers begin to like you more, you will always have Ivanka to thank her for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook https://t.co/nr75PEagVi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NasserJudeh You will be missed by many as FM but many more who like u, r happy to c u contribute in other ways withs less constraints.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking: Istanbul Nightclub Attacker Captured – Turkish State News Agency https://t.co/q9KClu9SWQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you know anyone at yahoo, please DM.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump no one can argue with you on the red line issue. Not even Obama.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook https://t.co/WJuPhtNjKz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook https://t.co/GwUDpZBNlS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/wvBFgJnPVD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook https://t.co/Y6iVNqTReE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YahooCare worst email service ever. My email is still hacked. Thanks for doing nothing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jacobkornbluh @BarakRavid Saeb Erikat does what he is known best for: leak leak leak.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MBRachid US policy in the region will not change. It will continue on its course which will be dictated to Trump the way it did for Obama.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The long history of the U.S. interfering with elections elsewhere https://t.co/C6b5gYtx5h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook https://t.co/vlQTiejsdN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook https://t.co/hCp4XkBDDA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@20committee @maggieNYT @shearm @nytimes the rumor is true :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report: Russia Has Trump Sex Blackmail https://t.co/EpvKBOHThA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FBI chief given dossier by John McCain alleging secret Trump-Russia contacts https://t.co/e5svaJbozx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelCohen212 Does "in my life" refer to you or the passport?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[اللي بيقدر يقدم

Looking for the next opportunity to grow your startup? @WeMENA2017 offers up to $150,000 for top... https://t.co/MqkjzYb8gi]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>