<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Had Uber model been an Apprentice task Kalanick would have been fired first off! $3bn loss + awful worker conditions https://t.co/r0Y0YbgT33]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MICL_Morgan but do engage google and or click on the further reading related posts which do offer more numbers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MICL_Morgan well there's that fact that Uber's a private company which doesn't release accounts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber's Master Plan, The Short Version https://t.co/LlZrPuaFzI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ahatami @FT @sytaylor that was from sept 2016 btw. And it is hype.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@triblondon nope. I think the distribution densities are insightful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@triblondon yes but there is also the factor of publicity to consider. Original petition had loads]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ToruOkada69 @OSFJustice @ahope71 because proportionally it is, but "urban thing" also works]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonyveitchuk dyslexics have rights too. Je suis dyslexic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OSFJustice @ahope71 it's about the distribution. The pro one has only just started.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robmacksmith no. It means that everyone who is anti Trump lives in London]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The pro/anti Donald State-visit petition looks like it cd turn into that second Brexit vote some ppl were on about https://t.co/5qfJh2At6A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon. The new gosplan https://t.co/gS1OMRnASs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Julius89812447 Sorry don't really understand. Have followed you if you want to explain to me by DM (longer form).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crookedhubert yes. I agree. I hope they do. But I'm also annoyed they're so self absorbed most other times to notice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crookedhubert Sorry. I don't understand your point. It might be because it's too nuanced for Twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crookedhubert no they don't. Uber drivers don't use uber.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crookedhubert yes, it's about time people realised that using an Uber is no different to buying sweatshop clothes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dvdbllrd We need to cultivate MORE SMEs, not more major corporate or government monopolies. (IMHO)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dvdbllrd This would keep the system honest and competitive. Especially if the master app required competition based on "all in" cost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dvdbllrd If the issue is "friction" no reason why small local companies couldn't be part of master app that lets ppl hop from one to other]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dvdbllrd the issue with Uber is that it's an unethically constructed monopoly. What's wrong with lots of competing local companies?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dvdbllrd personally I don't think it should be socialised. It should be forced to operate at a profit!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Alheri @GeorgeLakoff was it not linked to these VWP changes? https://t.co/XsMfKRP6Ti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dpinsen i didn't take offence. It's just sometimes people's expectations are a little high.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dpinsen this is the sort of faux opportunistic self promotional compassion I have trouble processing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dpinsen thanks for scoring my tweets. Feel free to unfollow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dpinsen because last i checked tech companies were doing their best to disrupt all low skilled jobs &amp; make it impossible to earn a living]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dpinsen I feel the same way about the faux opportunistic compassion coming from tech companies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dpinsen yes those are my sentiments precisely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dpinsen you're missing my point. Outcome is right one, but reasoning for it is saddening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JayGeraghty I'm sorry. You're going to have to actually structure a sentence together. I don't speak Crypto absurdity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JayGeraghty what use is that information to me? I'm very happy for you that gt has your number. Well done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JayGeraghty if i was, i wouldn't tell you on twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dpinsen and not for the greater sin that Uber is and always was taking advantage of labour rates.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dpinsen yes it's the right outcome. But it's annoying it's come about coz of ppl's want to reflect reactionary social media kudos pts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dpinsen my point is that if you want to show solidarity to migrants you shouldn't empower a service that exploits their labour willfully]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaneferro thanks very much! I only did two shifts. Pretty pathetic really. But hard enough!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaneferro Will shut up now. Have got it off my chest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaneferro Let's not forget they ultimately want to fire all the drivers anyway and replace them with self-driving cars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaneferro yes. Especially if they're liberals. Sorry. But hypocrisy is hypocrisy. I feel v strongly about this. (hence video)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaneferro Fundamentally, Uber's biz model is OPEC-ian - involves subsidizing costs until competition wiped out &amp; labour power wiped out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaneferro "oh but it's so convenient, and so cheap". Yes upstairs downstairs labour was also "so convenient &amp; so cheap" for elite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaneferro I can't tell u how many blue in the face arguments i've had w/ ppl trying to explain y Uber is exploitative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@callan_m it's crazy that it takes an immigration EO for ppl to figure this out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@callan_m I just think ppl r such hypocrites sometimes. They're happy to condone exploitative corps until their own agenda changes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_TechBanker that said, either way, I'm glad there's an uber boycott. About time. That's all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_TechBanker I'm happy there's an Uber boycott, but it should have been due to an obviously exploitative model not this boycott thing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaneferro my gripe is with ppl who make empty social media gestures 4 kudos pts but continue bad real-world behaviours regardless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaneferro that's generally my issue. It's an empty feel-good gesture - &amp; ultimately hypocritical given willful exploitation blindness b4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrew_graham it's not that easy to transfer ratings history, and some have Uber specific lease agreements.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaneferro Well to be clear, it's not that easy to just switch. Drivers have ratings invested in Uber &amp; sometimes leases]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@callan_m problem is, if they did that, they would never make a profit in a million years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@callan_m sadly, we are so deep into the flawed business model, that is now true. But they could admit they're employees &amp; create payroll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaneferro that may be true. I don't know details of the communication. If they signaled "low rates" despite boycott that was dumb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@callan_m when it's a scab, it's someone who defies a picket in favour of big boss. In this case, they r self-employed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@callan_m I don't. These r private contractors. Many of whom have invested in ratings &amp; contracts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@czwalsh @shaneferro taxis are a super low margin business even in the medallion format  https://t.co/ZmjUENW3lX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@czwalsh @shaneferro Because the cost of service is ridiculously expensive. Human labour IS expensive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sociopathblog If Trump's EO made people realise Uber is an opportunistic migrant exploiting company there is a silver lining]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaneferro Look, I deleted my Uber app over 6 mths ago. Not a fan of the company. But being outraged by drivers who choose to work is silly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaneferro but that's the problem with a service which has totally variable &amp; discretionary charges in general!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaneferro but i think it's ridiculous that the trigger for the switch is their lack of respect for a boycott they can't afford to observe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaneferro I'd be very happy to see entire world switch to a service that doesn't undercut competition below breakeven costs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sociopathblog it's ridiculous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sociopathblog That's my point tho. Uber's been exploiting migrants since getgo. But private contractors not supporting boycott flips ppl?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@callan_m those drivers wd have taken that decision probably coz can't afford not to take this work?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@callan_m I just think punishing Uber PRIVATE CONTRACTORS for not respecting a boycott is weird way 2 show solidarity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaneferro so my presumption (and it may be wrong) is that Uber drivers can't afford to not take biz.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaneferro pls do correct if i've misunderstood. But outrage is cause Uber didn't respect the boycott right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaneferro that defies logic. If you're angry about a service not respecting a boycott, why would u not b angry about a competitor?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_TechBanker or at least they used to have higher "cartel" style earnings (according to uber), hence prob can afford to strike.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_TechBanker The migrants boycotting JFK were regular taxis to my knowledge. Higher earnings than Uber drivers!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@callan_m That's my point tho. If u want 2 show solidarity, don't empower a business model that is highly exploitative on an everyday basis!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaneferro we're perfectly happy paying them exploitative wages for the below cost services all other times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaneferro sure. But i don't understand why depriving migrants of income they can't afford to lose is deemed solidarity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber drivers (often immigrants) barely make minimum wage. But deleting the app &amp; depriving them of income is a sign of migrant solidarity?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Internet of Things: "Hotel ransomed by hackers as guests locked in rooms" https://t.co/peea2DPY0Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JayBut707 yes good point. He's basically come up with the idea for THE TUBE!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having clocked self-driving taxis will only create uber gridlock Mr. Musk now wants to dig up half the city https://t.co/qZ07egBxuS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnb78 if you're an AV reader i wd hope you appreciate that my views tend to be nuanced coz I think absolutism on either side is unhelpful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnb78 but I'm now out of time. And bowing out not because "i can't face the opposition" because personal time is a thing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnb78 I hv endeavoured to respectfully defend my case ( esp. coz I see myself as a moderate who is Pigeonholed as both left or right)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnb78 it's because people jump on tweets and assume all sorts - out of context - that I think the medium is flawed for serious debate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnb78 and while I endeavour to be thorough and non contradictory I can lose track of multiple threads]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnb78 I specifically state earlier that my argument does not apply to the U.K., which is a much more complex case]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnb78 just because there are facts doesn't mean they're not biased by context or omission]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnb78 no you are. I was always taking about the US. And PS that's the nature of all fact based narratives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnb78 just to be clear https://t.co/DYCz3H3BUL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnb78 and I agree with you that there will be many justifiable exceptions which should be given a chance to sort their documents out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnb78 again, my point is simply about respect for the law. You need some sort of stick to at least get the thing sorted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnb78 well shame Obama's policy worked so well there are still so many indeterminants left]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnb78 I haven't pretended. It IS still a thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnb78 again, presumptions. I have stayed clear of political declarations. It's so typically lazy to just assume people's politics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnb78 doesn't change fact they should either be legalized or leave, and that everything else is an unfair contradiction]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnb78 I admire your commitment to going off topic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnb78 a loophole closure enables that process.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnb78 again you're clutching at straws. If they're so compliant why aren't they should be fully legalized]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnb78 again not when you strip out joy riding (cases when cars r often recovered).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnb78 @j0s3fk I think you're the one who lives in an idealized paradoxical world where tracking = security unless it's illegal migration]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>