<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheNakedPun That movie was a blast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahGPerry This was an extraordinary piece of writing. I am so pleased you are recovering.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah, the replete pleasure of seeing T2: Trainspotting in a packed out  @CameoCinema. Edinburgers enraptured. Bliss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomwfreeman @RobGirvan I have so much time for Moana. Moana is Aces.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oo, yes. I loved The Storyteller. 5 year old Katie positively thrilled to it. John Hurt was so wonderful. https://t.co/hz16kTvILA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoyed discovering that '45' is South African slang for penis. How apropos.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobGirvan The greatest trick the Devil ever pulled was convincing man Disney films are wholesome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatrinaConaglen "Oo amazing! She can read! She possesses a basic human competency!" 

Ugh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatrinaConaglen Also, congratulating the film for making Belle a bookworm is utterly ludicrous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatrinaConaglen "Yes, he's cruel, aggressive and taciturn but he's a good person inside. When he's not shouting at or imprisoning me!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God, I hate Disney's Beauty and the Beast. Grooming a generation of young girls for abusive relationships.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When do we go into our bunkers again? Is 60 or 30 seconds to midnight? ... gonna start stockpiling tin cans either way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can we Ludovico Technique Trump with a triple feature of Time of the Wolf, The Day After &amp; Vera Drake, please? Stat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisHewitt You are going to invoke the rage of the Lin Manuel-Mirandarites now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Virtue-signalling is such a bullshit phrase. Surely a million times better than arsehole-hatred-bigot-fuckwit-avarice signalling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of my favs. So many great signs around the world today. https://t.co/G4PbVdm2o7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are there any add-ons that take all mentions/pictures of Trump and turn them into a picture of hugging otters? Would be handy today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatrinaConaglen Every time too. Between this and seeing Manchester by the Sea this week, its a good week for Casey Affleck impressing me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatrinaConaglen as the Assassination of Jesse James by the Coward Robert Ford. This is Correct.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to interview with Casey Affleck. Very much appreciate that he refers to the Assassination of Jesse James by the Coward Robert Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems perversely hopeful to plan the release of Jackie - a film about presidential assassination - for the day of Trump's inauguration.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mr_orgue Yes, yes I would. That would be a blast. Later on in the run? I have multiple deadlines &amp; then holidays for the next few weeks...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The loneliness of the characters in Moonlight made me heartsore. What a beautiful, blue, soulful film.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mr_orgue I CAN HEAR YOU!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mr_orgue You have my bow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The absolute state of this. Mind boggling. https://t.co/A7MPCMJWAr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jslaterwilliams Because hearing about the repeal of the ACA is fucking sickening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jslaterwilliams Biden maintaining composure on hearing of his veneration is as delightful as everything else is horrifying at the moment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jslaterwilliams Bury yourself deep in the bosom of Obama and Biden fawning all over each other, Joshi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NathanaelSmith It is resonating in a way that films rarely do these days. Shows the beauty of faith, doubt, and sacrifice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatrinaConaglen ... especially as one who gleefully apostatised.

Other people were Fairly Pissed about it, mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatrinaConaglen How remarkable to see a film legitimise the struggle of holding faith, though. Dark nights of the soul are compelling ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatrinaConaglen ... spiritual dilemma compelling, and was more curious about the interiority of Inouie.

Also, far too little Driver.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Admired 'Silence' a great deal, particularly for the lyricism of its visuals, but felt Garfield struggled to make Rodrigues' ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatrinaConaglen And pure, boiling, hotter than the sun rage. I loathe him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would like to see stats on how many viewers are having panic attacks/nervos/coronaries right now. I'm someway between all three.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatrinaConaglen 'So we've been told and some choose to believe it/but I know they're wrong, wait and see...' 🎧🎼]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Here's to the ones who dream" is reminiscent of "The Rainbow Connection" which, needless to say, is a Lovely Thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stugone Speaking as a pacifist, I wish bloody violence upon this person.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KickingParis Patrick Stewart was reading the script under these precise circumstances and had to pause to pour himself a stiff drink.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The usually-almost-unbearable poignancy of Paul Simon's lyrics is proving particularly unbearably poignant since Fisher's death. What tunes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ross_maclean Yes, I cringed when it was discussed, but agree it proved cathartic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ross_maclean Yes, Bill had so much grace and perspective in the face of terrible pain. Especially in the meeting with the son.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ross_maclean Yeah, just finished it. Rate it highly. Bill is one of the most remarkable people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ross_maclean In bed. Kitty Genovese doc. Wine. No inclination to step outside.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@karlitooo Merry Christmas lovely handsome!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@salihughes Wouldn't be wearing red lippy without your encouragement. Thanks for all the wonderful writing. Merry Christmas!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatHarleyUK Awww. For that, have a Christmassy hug.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatHarleyUK Only if you hate yourself (and women).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stugone Emoji strong arm, emoji thumbs up (my computer doesn't have emojis).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stugone I hope she is lifting. It is the bollocks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stugone I am genuinely amazed. Dieting is a tedious mindfuck, and that's a huge amount of weight to have sloughed off. She must be nails!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I get so much writing done when I have a deadline. 

About 3% of it is actually what I'm being paid for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stugone Remarkable. Well done her. Also, butter is delicious, so now I want to gorge on it, but it feels against the spirit of these tweets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jslaterwilliams I meant aural diarrhoea, of course. Liquid diarrhoea is a tautology.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jslaterwilliams Ohmifuck. So patronising. So reductive. &amp; the Sweet Child o' Mine cover was liquid diarrhoea, poured straight into my ears.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joannechocolat I was a vainglorious cow with a terrible singing voice. What does this say about me?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The list itself is brillo, but the sound cues in particular are a joy. https://t.co/UGep9Z58SO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheNakedPun I also want to see numerous shots of Tom Cruise realising something important.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stugone Y'all don't hear me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stugone I lack the mental acuity to have figured out a decent No Scrubs reference.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stugone Don't go chasing waterfalls, now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SimonNRicketts This is beautifully written, about the most rubbish of things. I wish for you nothing but love and kindness from everyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ye God, Teyonah Parris is charismatic, fierce, sharp and sexy as fuck in Chi-Raq. Her scenes with Angela Bassett are electric.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jslaterwilliams Netflix has all the mega lols.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattzollerseitz I've reported him before and wondered if a critical mass of people did likewise he'd be shut down. Little hope.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nigelfloyd I mean thanks for the recommendation. I am not, alas, The Civil Wars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nigelfloyd Thank you - that's a haunting, beautiful cover.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamnotwaynegale I am not exaggerating in saying discovering Hamilton is my highlight of 2016.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GuyLodge I'd say she was just pissed she got flat out the very worst outfit, by a comfortable margin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the stern corrective to a great deal of self-pitying angst I've been feeling about the state of the world.… https://t.co/RmYkGGawAq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You should listen to it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the words are weft.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's just so mad and informed and unlikely and musically deft.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean, there's a cabinet meeting played as a rap battle, and the Revolutionary War is set to a John Barry-esque extravaganza.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the by, Hamilton is a fairly staggering artistic achievement, regardless of how your milage varies on the musical front. I love it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobGirvan Congratulations. She's gorgeous. What a lovely thing. Well done to your lady, good work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jillgeoghegan @Drapers @AmandaWakeley Christ Jill you look stunning. What a gown.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seeing Arrival today was the most therapeutic, cathartic experience following this shitshow of a week. Tender, simple, humane. Beautiful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@weegiejoe Sartorially elegant mofo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is my earworm this week "Cunts are still running the world"? ... https://t.co/yMZwlZit2Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everybody knows the fight was fixed, the poor stay poor and the rich get rich.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so grateful for the hours of revery @underwaterraven and I have had together drinking in those lyrics, that voice, that mordant genius.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jslaterwilliams I am swearing more today than I did even in the wake of Brexit, which is saying something. Fuck Tangerine Kingcunt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're looking for catharsis amid this fuckopalypse, I founded bench-pressing to "Know Your Enemy" by RATM surprisingly therapeutic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish all the Trump voters and Leavers would just hurry up and get on the B ark.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@behind_theseens @NathanaelSmith racism, sexism, a massively manipulative right-wing press, Murdoch, Russian govt interference, stupidity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NathanaelSmith oh, you've just joined us? I couldn't sleep. Update: Everything is Awful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@newjorg Thank you. Impotent rage and anxiety isn't fixing things on it's own, alas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just quietly, I don't actually enjoy feeling sick with worry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@g_rantontweet Vasa is also So Choice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@g_rantontweet Are you in Stockholm? If so you have to go to Skansen! It's the tits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary Rodham is nails, man. https://t.co/BAWXu58mxp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatrinaConaglen What a world. What a message legitimately entertaining the opinions of that monster sends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Several times a day, I am stopped short by the thought that a candidate for US Presidency stands accused of raping a 13 year old girl.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobGirvan @AJ_Crews That's reassuring, as is 538's forecasts. I get freaked out by the prospect of stealth Trump supporters. I am nervous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AJ_Crews Oh yes, I know. It is so perfectly in keeping with this ridiculous, mind-fuck of an election year (A FUCKING YEAR) we have endured]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AJ_Crews Fitting? I would spit tacks. Alpha men and their dongs, fucking shit up for women since *insert date here*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AJ_Crews Weiner is the worst. The doc was fascinating, such self-obsession, such hubris. Poor Huma.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tomwfreeman They threw in a free set of ginsu knives as a signing bonus.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>