<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate @Simplex2014 but nat govs do not want a  directly elected commission. It's not the fault of the 'EU'. We are the EU!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate so if i can steer you back to the accountability of commissioners? You have neglected my points.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate that's an issue of oversight and UK can hardly lecture Eu here. Look at Osborne's new employers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate and if just vote for party proposed candidate... how is that different to now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate so you accept that direct election could be hugely problematic. How would they be replaced too, if directly employed?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate yes. We are a union. We pool part of our sovereignty (like with NATO) All act for benefit of whole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robbeardmore7 @Simplex2014 @jonloveridge83 @ianbetteridge @IanJohnson1973 what inequality? In particular?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate unless we have a whole new layer of directly elected governance but that would lie above nat govs surely?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate but what if that person clashes with nat gov? What legitimacy would they have? Could they refuse proposals? #nightmare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaesurBiey did you ever apologise to @Harryslaststand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate i made my point. Yours was different. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate in effect we vote for comm same way as we do PM: party choice. Although PM has vastly more powers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate election of comm with different party affiliation could reault in very odd and unproductive stand offs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate Because the position of comm is very different. In effect s/he is an ambassador, proposing gov sponsored regs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate maybe each party chooses 1 per 1% national supprt and another X non affiliates by direct public election.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate but i can also see merit in a proportional selected body of party affiliation with some 'cross benchers'. Expertise is key.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate because they are a legislative body. And accountability would be increased by election.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yup. Although no one will ever accuse me of being 'cowed'. 
 https://t.co/tUizQQMtcu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have 333 followers. Does that make me a mini beast?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate they don't wing it, proposing their own laws. They represent HM Gov.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate but this is a sideline. Why would direct election of comm improve accountability from present? They answer to HM Gov.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate and a warm welcome to you too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate which are routinely ignored.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate and the leader can change. Without any consultation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate irrelevant. They have no control.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate @jonloveridge83 @ianbetteridge @IanJohnson1973 they don't vote for a leader. Members of the party do that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate not even that. They vote for an mp. That person can (and have) swapped sides.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate @jonloveridge83 @ianbetteridge @IanJohnson1973 sorry chaps. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate @jonloveridge83 @ianbetteridge @IanJohnson1973 why does 29,000 votes make a difference?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate @jonloveridge83 @ianbetteridge @IanJohnson1973 it's not diff. Our own leaders are not directly elected.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate @jonloveridge83 @ianbetteridge @IanJohnson1973 you wave this 'directly elected' like it solves a problem. It doesn't]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate @jonloveridge83 @ianbetteridge @IanJohnson1973 how would direct election increase accountability?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate @jonloveridge83 @ianbetteridge @IanJohnson1973 no country has asked for direct election. Ruling pol parties want control.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate @jonloveridge83 @ianbetteridge @IanJohnson1973 36.7% of the vote. Even less of the electorate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate @jonloveridge83 @ianbetteridge @IanJohnson1973 no. How many Brits voted for our EU commissioner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate @jonloveridge83 @ianbetteridge it's a facile argument. Why would an elected commission improve accountability?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate @jonloveridge83 @ianbetteridge @IanJohnson1973 how many voted for our PM? 29,000 and yet she represents us all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate @jonloveridge83 @ianbetteridge @IanJohnson1973 none. How many brits voted for our commissioner?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even now, i reckon, most Brits would fail an EU quiz. Just the most basic facts about how it's run, how legislation is proccessed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios and we can, sorry could, veto. As can the other 27 countries. Unless big bad Junckers is stwonger than likkle Bwitain?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios yeah. I saw that film too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios what about if EU thrives while we don't?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate @jonloveridge83 @ianbetteridge  most uk govs of last 50 years have been minority. Laws made in spite of desires most of pop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate @jonloveridge83 @ianbetteridge @IanJohnson1973 we should elect both. However. EU is a supranational org. Not the same]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios you are ideologically opposed anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate @jonloveridge83 @ianbetteridge @IanJohnson1973 I can propose a law. The power is also in PASSING legislation. MEPs do that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate @jonloveridge83 @ianbetteridge nat govs don't want directly elected commissioners; it would detract from their power.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate @jonloveridge83 @ianbetteridge @IanJohnson1973 we elect gov, they choose commissioner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate @jonloveridge83 @ianbetteridge @IanJohnson1973 which our gov does through its chosen representative in the commission]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios reform is needed. Sadly we will now play no part in that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate @jonloveridge83 @ianbetteridge @IanJohnson1973 why? What would be the advantage?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios i meant wrong about brexit. What metrics?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios that's not an EU.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios how can member states realise what it is when it is member states? That's the issue with the UK. We liked to play outsider.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate @jonloveridge83 @ianbetteridge @IanJohnson1973 that's not an example of an egregious eu rule btw.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DD_DailyDebate @jonloveridge83 @ianbetteridge @IanJohnson1973 yup. What's the issue? Who would you like to have that power?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios why should they? Would we if France had? We already have a bunch of concessions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios Trouble is, if the EU fails, we suffer, in or out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios what will convince you that're you're wrong?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios hopefully.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios er no, the 27 other states said fuck off to Dave's fantasy back bench wishlist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios but it is the largest, most successful free market in the history of the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios the eu is more than a market. Thankfully.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios so you'd reject it however democratic it was, or not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios you said 'legislate'. It can't. Weasel words. The nat govs propose through the commission.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios we have the US controlled WTO, the IMF, world bank, Davos.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios @GuyVerhofstadt so you want unecelected commissioners from non member states? How does that help?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios and i asked why should it be? Would nat govs even support that idea?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios my bad faith answer could be: no. Detractors are just idiots. And how does that help the debate?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios that's a bad faith argument.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios and how do you get trade and cooperation without a supranational body overseeing? Good grief.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios no. You made factually incorrect statements about how EU works. Argue by all means. But don't wilfully misrepresent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios well the 27 nations (plus others keen to join) disagree. Thankfully. Bye.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sillymoonman @danielh_g @BraddJaffy @Lord_Nicol don't you do even rudimentary research before making accusations?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sillymoonman @danielh_g @BraddJaffy @Lord_Nicol ask him yourself: @BondevikKM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios @GuyVerhofstadt eh? What isn't?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios  I'm not implying, I'm directly accusing. Almost every claim you made was wrong. And comes straight outta the Paul Dacre playbook]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios @GuyVerhofstadt actially i didn't engage in ad hom. Unless you consider being a Daily Mail reader insulting?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios @GuyVerhofstadt *crickets*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios @GuyVerhofstadt look what would have happened without EU following banking crisis. Far worse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios @GuyVerhofstadt which do you read?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios @GuyVerhofstadt you demonstrably don't. But hey, carry on claiming otherwise. You know Twitter is a public forum?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios @GuyVerhofstadt sure. Sorry about that. But how about you make some statements that aren't factually bollox.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios @bobreeduk council of directly elected ministers you mean?! Fuck me mate. Read a book and not just DM. This is embarrassing now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios @bobreeduk so? Neither are the civil sevants who draft UK laws. Commissioners do the bidding of nat govs. They ain't kings!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios @GuyVerhofstadt which laws have you objected to btw?

This is how you try and block them:
https://t.co/l62N8wqG5l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios @GuyVerhofstadt what do you call MPs in UK? How often do they reject gov legislation? Invariably a minority government.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios @GuyVerhofstadt yes on the behest of their national governments. How should it work? What's your scheme?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios @GuyVerhofstadt by rights you should have said 'faceless' by now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios @GuyVerhofstadt and only EU policy decided by EU. which nat govs can veto anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios @GuyVerhofstadt by representatives of member states, subject to approval of MEPs you mean. But no, you cling to your DM headlines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios @GuyVerhofstadt no. They regularly ammend and reject legislation. You'd know that if you'd done even basic research.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios @GuyVerhofstadt meanwhile... the House of Lords... the Judiciary... the monarch... the WTO, NATO, IMF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios @GuyVerhofstadt they don't. They can't pass anything without approval of Eu Parl, who can also remove the whole commission]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios @GuyVerhofstadt how is it not?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios @GuyVerhofstadt so you ignore the fact that your statements were plain wrong, demonstably incorrect and carry on regardless? Cool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios @GuyVerhofstadt yes. And MEPs are the ONLY ones that can make it law.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios @GuyVerhofstadt and as a side issue, what would be their legitimacy? Betting that electoral turnout would be very small.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evropaios @GuyVerhofstadt why? What would a directly elected commissioner do differently? MEPs have the final say.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Charliec87 so... not the EU's? Steady on]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>