<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@mlheenan Mine too! There are so many great picture books out there. Looking forward to connecting, sharing &amp; learning together! #tdsbEd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not just for Primary Ss! Great picture books can spark creativity &amp; innovation for our Middle &amp; High School Ss too!… https://t.co/tWi9ritqXM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annamayking1 Of course he does! He was an honorary guest at this week's meeting. Super helpful in making sure it will be fantastic!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do we know &amp; what do we wonder about pulleys &amp; gears and the human body? Grade 4s &amp; 5s starting their new Scie… https://t.co/0Pwud8u5dd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow! Impressed by the creativity &amp; skill in these paintings by @bradparolin's Ss. TY for inviting us to your galler… https://t.co/KPtbJREblx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsAFitzsimmons Me too! S said that he loved learning about them with you last year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're taking some time to investigate the morals in these fables. What life lessons might be contained in these pag… https://t.co/ybTaWc2pcU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starting our day w/ my friend, Anansi. What makes a good fable? How might we use them to  help impart life lessons?
https://t.co/JU2YkYKdsI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dougpete Thanks Doug. Have a great Friday everyone! @ancasterLC @mrsmaurinaedhs @SStephanian @HWDSB @MrsBoate @sabinasayed19 @lstrangway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jodhaJAL Would 💜to but I have a group in for Dance @ lunch. You could come visit while we're eating if that works. @Steward_JAL, join us!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exploring the culture &amp; contributions of Blacks from around the world, today we're learning about my friend, Anansi. https://t.co/WqM5hIH3g5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Steward_JAL Awesome. I used the @DoInkTweets App on an ipad &amp; it's super easy. Let me know when you're free &amp; I'm there. #PicForward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alright JAL! Tag...You're it! We've been having a blast w/ @PicForward. Check it out &amp; consider participating. Let… https://t.co/z5atWDMEAp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A full house w/ the gr 5 &amp; 6 Ss for JAL's Spelling Bee Club. Impressed by the skills of our Ss &amp; their willingness… https://t.co/gZfF8WZr8r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[J &amp; S are excited about seeing the Leafs play. Could it be because they're 4th in the Eastern Conference Standings?… https://t.co/Yyhx89qjg8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just when I thought we were all in agreement that we want the nicer weather back. J &amp; N decide that perhaps we need… https://t.co/PXykIqOKaj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just when you thought it was going to be safe again to head outside without all of the layers...Happy #GroundhogDay… https://t.co/1wFTo5KHvh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why can't we get to decide? Why do we have to wait for Mr. Groundhog? Happy #GroundhogDay. Let's hope Spring comes… https://t.co/LebcgHQMl1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone is trying to be the star today. Mr. Moose is pretending to be Mr. Marmotte and he's not having it. Happy… https://t.co/3gHIr6k4kM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On days like to today don't we all wish we were groundhogs? Happy #GroundhogDay @PicForward. #PicForward https://t.co/qX8W9x8hZo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On way to hockey, dad literally made a pit stop. Ended up in a world of giant groundhogs. Missing my tournament but… https://t.co/ROumi5AJgg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 1st of our #PicForward pics are in! We know about the groundhog, but what happens when the moose sees his shado… https://t.co/vh8LGfPRhK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's #GroundhogDay &amp; we're working on #PicForward. Here's a sneak peek of what we've done so far. Stay tuned for th… https://t.co/xXjWHZ76Bm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrsGeekChic @PicForward Great idea!!! I'm on it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@PicForward is an amazing challenge. Always happy to participate! Thanks for taking great pics every month for the world to get creative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I always have fun w/ #PicForward. Can't wait to see what my Ss will create. Starting to work on them today! https://t.co/uea6W6eWsb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lynda_watters Cool! I'll take a look. Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annamayking1 You have amazing Ss who are so welcoming &amp; such a pleasure to learn from. Their visits make my day! Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having a great time w/ this month's #PicForward pics. Check it out at https://t.co/PCbz6IaXWx and be amazed by what… https://t.co/ipiVJdGKlL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who will win this epic battle in the world of the giant praying mantis? I think I'll let my Ss decide. Stay tuned t… https://t.co/YGOMYfhBE7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strange things can happen when we fall asleep. Who knows where this guy may end up. Remember to stay focused when i… https://t.co/SgTdv5Y4fw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder how Mr. Moose might explain this one. When real meets fiction, things get a little difficult to explain.… https://t.co/0qUisZfnfj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just when you thought it was safe to feed the birds. What has caught their attention? Loving the new #PicForward pi… https://t.co/cdwM4QsWyU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will our heroes get their items back from the cave? Has Mr. Bear already eaten all of their supplies. How will our… https://t.co/8Fg9MhZ2RS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dawnsonea JAL's Movie Night is on Friday, February 10th from 6 to 8 pm. Flyers will be sent home to families with more details on Friday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAL's @WEMovement Team working on a banner &amp; announcements for Movie Night on Feb 10. Join us for food &amp; fun while… https://t.co/EGQA5kc9l6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a fantastic idea @RJLANGTDSB! https://t.co/6sKzXNCeyK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got a visit from my buddy in @annamayking1's class. "It's made out of a pentagon, 2 triangles &amp; a rectangle." N roc… https://t.co/iHjqzs7jYE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exploring le Carnaval de Québec &amp; learning about the cultural &amp; religious significance. Also discussing similaritie… https://t.co/lbpEg50JRr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The gr. 3s &amp; 4s are trying out our 1st- &amp; easiest 😊 -word list. Again our student leaders are working in teams to h… https://t.co/vuKDlkykz8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're interested in What's Going On in This Pic from @nytimes. What can you infer? Why might this be important? To… https://t.co/nlKkbbbUeZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taking some time to check out le Carnaval de Québec. What might we see if we visit? What might make Québec the perf… https://t.co/TMx7JtzaJo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you a #tdsb Teacher looking to learn about all things Google? Have no fear, #TDSBCamp is here! Join us on Sat.… https://t.co/d2Iy4pAIfq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is the 1st meeting for the JAL Spelling Bee Club for gr. 1 &amp; 2. Student leaders are helping younger Ss w/ thi… https://t.co/Jy1rkj3LQZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taking a look @ videos about Light &amp; Sound and Conservation of Energy. Here's one of my favourite. Sound Is Mighty? https://t.co/xWqAcecHFL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ABrownTDSB Fantastic! Such great work. Thank you for sharing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@g_lim2 It definitely was. Ss realized what their foods were really made of. It made the case for enjoying some foods in moderation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks! Getting ideas of how we might use this idea. Ss excited to read content for them written by other Ss. They… https://t.co/he0hCGD0kj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So excited!!! Thank you so much @McM_MsT! https://t.co/aNUcIwxvBf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McM_MsT I shared them briefly w/ some of my Ss at the end of the day &amp; there was great interest in reading them. Might this be possible?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McM_MsT These are so amazing! What a fantastic idea. Thanks for sharing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smarterteacher Sorry about the delay. Thanks for sharing the link so quickly @SciTeach7Davis!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SciTeach7Davis Here's the website: https://t.co/LtayVq41LC @smarterteacher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smashing food! We're finding out the amount of sugar, salt &amp; oil in some of our favourite foods. M had pizza for lu… https://t.co/6LxOa51LRk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Geometric Concepts do you see in our Kandinsky (&amp; @ABrownTDSB) inspired Art pieces? Polygons? Acute or obtuse… https://t.co/AUPdmc6RtV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Checking in on how we are feeling. How do language &amp; exclusion impact actions not only in the US but here in Canada… https://t.co/BMPBaJEBQA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tough conversations this morning. Taking some time to also read some of my favourite picture books to invoke unders… https://t.co/bW4tpmAzHK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeacherHann It's a pretty powerful way to catch at a glance what was learned. I'm sure things we may have forgotten come up. @AlanaGuinane]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mlheenan Thanks! @jodhaJAL @curly_sue10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jodhaJAL I'm loving them! Had to stop watching tv &amp; decided to have some fun. Have a great night. See you tomorrow! @curly_sue10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@curly_sue10 Thanks! @jodhaJAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reached for my H2O bottle &amp; thought I would take a pic of this week's #jamicure @jodhaJAL @curly_sue10. Had to take… https://t.co/aByEaPkda7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chalet03 Awww...félicitations!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow! They are amazing!! Thank you so much for sharing, Alana. https://t.co/4vnpAwWRou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlanaGuinane There really is a lot going on, all the time. Sounds so great! What do they use? Any examples to share?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JFVandermeij Cool! I'll take a look. Thanks for sharing! @GILBERTSJ @CanadaGrant @raycmercer @s_m077 @LukePersaud @TeacherHann @tina_zita]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McM_MsR TY. @ the end when some of my Ss saw it, they thought it would be great way for us to do weekly reflection. Some trying this wkend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JFVandermeij Definitely a great read! @GILBERTSJ @CanadaGrant @raycmercer @s_m077 @LukePersaud @TeacherHann]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Heathermyrvold I'll check it out. Thanks Heather. @jodhaJAL @pernilleripp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mariamartella Awesome! Thanks for the help Maria! @VP_JosephBrant @jodhaJAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait for February's pics @PicForward! Looks like they're going to be great fun to use to create. Looking forw… https://t.co/IMzNF6kIjV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alright @VP_JosephBrant! I know you. Must have a great suggestion for @jodhaJAL. Can you help? Any suggestions… https://t.co/maBysGNnEh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrsGeekChic Aww...Thanks! Had lots of fun &amp; perhaps w/ some more practice I might be ready for a stylus. It's tough work! #SketchnotersRock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anasutanto Of course! They're $2 @ Dollarama - Brimley &amp; Huntingwood. 💓 that they're all in 1 place &amp; that I don't have to photocopy pages.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For this week's blog, I decided to reflect through sketch. Here's what we were up to this week. https://t.co/fNpjkbLblV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A little #mindful colouring to end a great week together. https://t.co/5ZVwgFhzzV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can you help @1GRTeacher or @Heathermyrvold? https://t.co/UZHJ8FTUPd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ABrownTDSB Thank you! It was such a great idea. We're learning to look &amp; find Geometric Concepts in everyday life. TY so much for sharing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 1st of our @ForestofReading Silver Birch Book Reviews are in! Taking time this weekend to read. Next week we'll… https://t.co/Z3lu62vki1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to @ABrownTDSB, Ss are hard @ work incorporating Geometric Concepts into Kandinsky style abstract Art using… https://t.co/D9vrN6smqs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CurlingLibrary It definitely is! I was talking w/ my Ss &amp; they have some great ideas of how it might work. Let's chat soon @dianahalezoux.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still trending...#tdsbEd is made up of some amazing Educators who are connecting, sharing &amp; learning together. https://t.co/ExLD3BDAbJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iniyal Thanks for joining us tonight Iniyal! It's always a blast learning from you! #tdsbEd @MrsGeekChic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsLauraCollins @MrsGeekChic TY for joining. Only as awesome as the group of awesome Ts that we get to chat w/. Learned lots tonight #tdsbEd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrustyTina @tdsbEdChat @MrsGeekChic Thanks for joining! I'm so excited to talk about Picture Books for our next chat. #tdsbEd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@madamepryor The hour does fly! #tdsbEd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you to everyone for joining us for another great #tdsbEd chat tonight!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZeliaMCT @tdsbEdChat @MrsGeekChic Thanks for joining us! Always a great hour of learning. #tdsbEd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrKocan Me too! I've just got to take the time to get the studying done. Luck to you w/ it! #tdsbEd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jodhaJAL @HollyinTO I'm good on Mondays if that works. I have a few clubs going on during the rest of the week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lflfilipe No problem! @MrsGeekChic &amp; I believe that our best resource is one another. It's a pleasure to learn from &amp; w/ everyone. #tdsbEd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jtrinh45 It's a Forms Add-on that can be used to offer feedback &amp; make your life easier. #tdsbEd https://t.co/vB1U3UYIKJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrKocan I love that you can embed a calendar into Sites so that parents can refer to it! #tdsbEd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HollyinTO @jodhaJAL ABSOLUTELY! Just let me know  when works for you both &amp; we'll explore! #tdsbEd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A9: Definitely Sheets is something that I need to learn more about. Also interested in exploring more extensions like docappender. #tdsbEd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jodhaJAL You can assign different students different assignments. There are guardian permissions. Happy to show you. #tdsbEd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZeliaMCT They are so much fun! So many great things that can be done. @LOGICSAcademy also has lessons that you can use w/ Ss. #tdsbEd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lflfilipe Thanks for joining us Luis! Enjoy the rest of the evening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A8: Wish you could differentiate w/in assignments so all could access same one w/ different entry points that aren’t as obvious. #tdsbEd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lflfilipe @ChrustyTina It takes some getting used to but the archive is a nice way to review it all &amp; catch anything you missed. #tdsbEd]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>