<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Bout ta get lit in @98FM , spitting the hottest fire ! Bars n Bars n Bars ..........]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I can categorically say, that the Presidents hands are the same size as Kawhi Leonards." @seanspicer https://t.co/D2QIsfKmC7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesvmcmorrow "Lil Uzi Vert had the hottest bars on Bad&amp;Boujee!" https://t.co/ZxhvRfmLuf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The last U2 album was straight fire!" https://t.co/9TxejlcDcY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesvmcmorrow making music inspired by mocha ? https://t.co/Hth2X5H6CF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GregByrne84 I hope so. And also a bit Escape from New York]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For The Day That's in It, top 5 dystopian films- Fahrenheit 451, Mad Max, Soylent Green, Children Of Men, Mad Max 2. #headtothehills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lukesitalsingh thought you were just going to use that photo of me doing karate?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GregByrne84 fair play, I think you'll do a smashing job! #rolltide https://t.co/NC0pVs5Pye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lindsayzoladz @Medium laughing at Catholicism produced the worlds greatest sitcom https://t.co/Eu2HnMxmss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real recognise Real !#boutdatlyfe https://t.co/SufvyvIWQH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding your new favourite band of a Thursday , good times. @PillowQueeens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YoungScientists shoulda workd up a formula to measure how bad a feat.verse has to be b4 a fire song becomes trash? #LilUziVertTheorem #bars?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shout out to Dead Prez getting that straight VW paper! #itsjusbiznizfam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be fair, the one where she plays a rock singer was bollox. Saw it on a plane recently, not a patch on Deer Hunte… https://t.co/w0jQ3tdj3V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidpreece12 especially a penalty save]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sure Jools is pure bum every new year, but fuck me , Gilson is one fantastic drummer. #coolforcats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marvin Gaye's Family Gets Boost from Songwriters, Musicologists in 'Blurred Lines' Appeal https://t.co/NghMwLGs4f via @thr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidpreece12 jumping into a set position is a sign of poor preliminary footwork in young keepers. Leaves you flat footed and unbalanced.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesvmcmorrow turn the bottle , never the cork. Works on all sparkling wines. Safety first. #winelife #grapeexpectations #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@foggynotions @whelanslive deffo had Matt Sweeney on guitar that night, saw with my Mum. Brilliant show.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelRoeMGMT probably a signal failure on the line.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My song of the year you say? Why it's only @forth_wanderers I'll have you know. https://t.co/iEk0Wa56FC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discover the Classic Samples Used On Outkast 'ATLiens' https://t.co/b7racbXdjI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maccabi vs CSKA on euroleague SkySports atm if anyone fancies some sound fundamentals and below average athleticism ?! #pickandroll #layup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesvmcmorrow rivals Seagal's On Deadly Ground power point presentation #globalwarmingsucks #UnderSiege2paidforthismovie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeMFurlong forget the D4 slums!Come kick it in the Rathmines Eddie Rockets, after all , Dublin 6 is gods country.#D6forLYFE #RATHGARIST]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelRoeMGMT my brother @GregByrne84 is a fellow Toffee, I'll feel bad for both of you when Jose buys Coleman then sticks him on da bench]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes it takes a stranger to put your own life into words. #boutdatlife #D6orNothing https://t.co/8jOJT1wvIV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesvmcmorrow @JimmyKimmelLive Sanchez hat trick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spot suitably BLOWN UP! https://t.co/NHQ5AN8848 #righteouslicks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeMFurlong Dundalk FC jersey .... has to be done]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesvmcmorrow Boyz II Men's Hanukkah album almost as good!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight,SEEN YOUR VIDEO play The Replacements almost hits! Yule  night!One rehearsal , immeasurable talent! Co-op Newmarket Sq #seminal #ehh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesvmcmorrow wanna put a Clipse covers act together for the summer wedding season? #sweetcaroline https://t.co/ZpRmmsYLal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesvmcmorrow if you can't stick the landing, don't expect the spoils ! #mantra #lifechoice #thosenoodleslookdelish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesvmcmorrow make this happen https://t.co/PIK89BRduO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SheaSerrano on the reals though, have you seen Sugar? Beautiful baseball film . Same directors as Half Nelson.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Elbridio where's his penguin???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jervis St bringing it this Christmas ! Cockney monsters doing Christmas songs! #terrifying https://t.co/JeBDXtWGJg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Are Ryan Reynolds and Ryan Gosling the Same Person?” by Shea Serrano https://t.co/ejCLaeJ9Uu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeMFurlong Dundalk to spend their millions .... https://t.co/tZez8qPRjD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesvmcmorrow Houston and Lean: A Hip-Hop Tragedy  https://t.co/OJoYlGjA8j via @hprocksoff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's feeling the album and all, but this here is still Hanks main jam! Head noddin' at 14 months! @BIGBABYDRAM  https://t.co/mFkLi6IEvM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesvmcmorrow @TheodoraEtc no respect for that plastic faced muppet since he Fredo'd Richie Sambora! Also he cost Hillbot the election!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phlaimeaux @MmrghHmph it's in the water! #streetfootballers #cultured https://t.co/l40lMSz1Hf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hanks dinner Jam for the night that's in it!!  Boz Scaggs - Georgia (HQ) https://t.co/TqWdgf0s8O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeMFurlong so young, so full of promise, such a high bass. #MarkKing https://t.co/tY5gJGyyi0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bawwby stay connected https://t.co/6knKtWrdX5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't fret World : Cubs Win = Biff Wins = H O V E R B O A R D S ! ! ! !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But he's cool with Irish people right? #orangeisthenewblack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phlaimeaux you watching on CNN ? You thinking about incorporating a Magic Wall touch screen into your shows? Worth the cost !! @JohnKingCNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phlaimeaux Tron Honeycomb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Elbridio don't fret , shit will work itself out!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would love to see Gary Neville and @JohnKingCNN go head to head on some magic wall skill based competition . My money's on Da Wall King]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZachLowe_NBA love how he says  "i4 corridor ",lilting brogue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love John King in the background perfecting his touch screen game! #cnnelection @JohnKingCNN #magicwall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZachLowe_NBA future Lowe Post guest me thinks!?! Has the posture of a former division 2 shooting guard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neylapekarek @lilly_44 @thelumineers @HillaryClinton thinking of y'all tonight!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rembert I just really want him to finger draw a big green Irish heart on the screen. Just to give us late night Mick viewers some shine!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesvmcmorrow if she wins, Trump should be forced to carry her around Master Blaster style. Also US water supply more fucked than MadMax3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesvmcmorrow @AerLingus Four Four Two?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait till Trump wins and makes Gary Busey the new American Ambassador to Ireland! #diplomacy https://t.co/8vJ3A8OUmb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeMFurlong you ever had Poutine before? Believe me when I say you'll love it. It's why Canada has socialised heal… https://t.co/8N24PIWNEp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mollylambert we put our glass bricks in the ground in Dublin #glassbricks https://t.co/Od79MWmDt7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richiejape @delorentos @atticaaudio would kill to see the nude version of this snap! #charitycalender #housewiveschoice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lukesitalsingh for shame]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not able to get Radiohead tix? Don't worry, they're playing my free gaff next Tuesday night!!!! BYOB , amber grill battered sausages served.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wichitarecs what a find!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mollylambert it's as good an album as I could have hoped for!! Great review by the way!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been looking forward to this record like an excited kid!! https://t.co/6FzfNpxkIY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesvmcmorrow the bit where E from entourage gets smoked..... real tears!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump shoulda rolled with the "United States for United Statesians " slogan. Catchy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shout out to Quiché, you're straight delicious ! Finna open a Quiché only spot and call it "Songs in the Quiché of life". #noveganoptions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Molenbeek fought back against Isis – with football https://t.co/kpdCQ3zDT0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@commoonicate and delicious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelRoeSH Creep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesvmcmorrow Trump must have one, will be mega cheap by then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimcarrollOTR drums that good don't age!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimcarrollOTR Still swear Malice owns that track]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesvmcmorrow hit that Pomerol yo! Merlot rich and full bodied! #winelyfe #ibeenaterroirsincethepublicschoolera #CruTangClan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chuffed to get my copy of this fantastic book with the legend JonnyBoyle!Congratulations @D_O_Callaghan,a wonderful… https://t.co/6NfjPweJtg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CathalFunge @TXFMDublin absolutely sir!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shout out to @CathalFunge for always supporting Irish Music @TXFMDublin #lynne4ver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimcarrollOTR @TXFMDublin but the people need to know about how SST started out selling old radio parts! #nevergivejamesaplatform]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I remember one time leaving Phantom towers at 3am, and someone threw a pint glass at my head outside Whelans! @TXFMDublin #notafallfan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimcarrollOTR @TXFMDublin i wonder if Shane driving a taxi in Phibsboro is still looking for some Husker Dü to make his night? #cdskips]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeMFurlong @BVB it's Berlin , tops off sir, tops off!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such a pleasure to talk to @D_O_Callaghan tonight about her fantastic new book. The Drum Thing - Deirdre O Callaghan https://t.co/FFetDdFs63]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where my Dad learned to swim. Sunset over Dublin 8. https://t.co/McbntqVO0J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phlaimeaux Heino and Marks and Sparks. Poshest wank ever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@berkwin @DPAmicrophones @ianaccordion I'm loving your sport goth vibes Ber!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesvmcmorrow "so tell me about your journalism degree and how much money you still owe your parents"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elmetalesasi @mollylambert I also remember there being some Tommy Lee vs Sevendust drummer beef. I'm sure it was very Jerky.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elmetalesasi @mollylambert they appeared on an episode of MTV cribs together, Sevendust own Destiny Childs old tour bus. That was the crib.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elmetalesasi @mollylambert married drummer from Sevendust is a fact I somehow know despite my love of music. #fingerlessgloves]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesvmcmorrow goes without saying. You don't think Lil Yachty ain't  hitting da stage without a full length floss game check? #worldstar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesvmcmorrow your Full Length Mirror game is strong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pattonoswalt @wallacedewey props for Hannibal Brooks too, lost WW2 classic! https://t.co/XHamfkzB5T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow night in Bello Bar will be chatting to @D_O_Callaghan about her new book!! https://t.co/P3Twtzmba6]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>