<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Reminder: Trump conducted an affair while his wife took their three children to... https://t.co/qbAKgjmRF0 by #dianahess22 via @c0nvey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @samsung @axios "May" build, I believe as usual you getting ahead of yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeBates Until people stop laughing and applauding his not so funny comments he going to keep acting as a clown. #unpresidented]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BraddJaffy @KatyTurNBC Awww ask Donald for some pills he is taking, hahhah.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ananavarro Ayy no Ana did you watch Mad-dog smiled and put the penTrump signed Islamic ban in his packet? Don't think so Bannon is POTUS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You should not be calling Obama dumb right now Trump, you're not looking good. https://t.co/EIQvVGsBtg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@USAneeds @NimaTavRood Jesus!! Are you correcting me right now with this tweet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@USAneeds @NimaTavRood Ahh nahh you not worthy. https://t.co/JJF7iZtLKF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Thomas_Hern1 Oh really! https://t.co/MqNblkg3gF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@USAneeds @NimaTavRood I almost blocked you, but nahh is better to enjoy your ignorance's comments and troll you like the trash you are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@USAneeds Hahhaha obviously dear "im" only white trash like you will assume those things base on my skin color and hair.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@USAneeds I did vote for Romney, not for McCain, I assume because are a white guy You're a trailer trash hillbilly… https://t.co/yNUfrM4wBN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@USAneeds @SuperButtHead1 @NimaTavRood @KeithOlbermann @YahooFinance for Trumpkins like you anything that disagrees… https://t.co/0v6lrjyQ5O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His way of conducting foreign policy  is going to get us kill!  #ImpeachTrump https://t.co/P1J0akvecF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What other country will this Fascist going to offend? #ImpeachmentMarch #ImpeachTrump https://t.co/RqmXvMuj9S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rulesthemall That was Vicente Fox ex mexican President, not looking so fake to me, this is dangerous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rulesthemall  threatening Mexico's sovereignty with the garrote is stupid. If you want to end war on drugs, ask the US to stop consuming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TrumpInaguration #CrowdSize #sizematters #ImpeachTrump #RESISTANCE https://t.co/CyMwBINwUl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rulesthemall Not really, the same was reported on AP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rulesthemall @SuperButtHead1 @NimaTavRood @KeithOlbermann @YahooFinance yes and if those words are not there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SuperButtHead1 @NimaTavRood @KeithOlbermann @YahooFinance Why none of the governments won't talk aout the call? Uhmm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SuperButtHead1 @NimaTavRood @KeithOlbermann @YahooFinance Why because the ERN in Mexico denied it, why they didn't share transcript?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SuperButtHead1 @NimaTavRood @KeithOlbermann @YahooFinance No fake news, it sounds exactly like something Trump would say, (Chicago)!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SchreckReports @KatyTurNBC What ?!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BraddJaffy what a ridiculous picture!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanRather Trump already started the movement here are 3 of his latest pieces. https://t.co/7kfSCpuob1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoWhatsRightToo @thehill It is always fake news to Trumpkins when the media uncovered Trump lies. https://t.co/JA9S3OKXRe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@11groverbeac @wikileaks Please! https://t.co/70nMuEyWaN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@11groverbeac @wikileaks Jesus what the heck!! Child sex trafficking? Misinformation? You know that was already proven fake right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@11groverbeac @wikileaks For what?? Why not a petition for Trump Impeachment?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My brother-in-law put this together, I just had to share. #TrumpLeaks #TrumpArtworks https://t.co/icV3KBwglR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the message Sally Yates left for Justice Department lawyers before she was... https://t.co/KMOf0eJewU by #NevaSMarxova via @c0nvey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ass @realDonaldTrump  ask if that was a surprise about Gorsuch! No really MSN beat you to it. https://t.co/TqpAybiOMU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @WhiteHouse No thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BraddJaffy @KatyTurNBC hahahaha hope so, so they can block his ass like he deserves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Not watching!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not watch tonight's Trumps Supreme Court Announcement, low rating for his Apprentice style show. #boycot… https://t.co/6bEUWwgRRx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the message Sally Yates left for Justice Department lawyers before she was... https://t.co/ZgJ0oGiheE by #gbollmann01 via @c0nvey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Zac_Petkanas @Montel_Williams Of course he is going to denied it and say the media is lying, he just has to much work to do at WH.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeconboy @KatyTurNBC @PressSec @SenateMajLdr @SpeakerRyan it already happened last attack in Yemen  8 years old  Americans girl got killed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatyTurNBC Oh Lord 4 long years ahead!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AFineBlogger I will on that!💯]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Thank you I appreciate your interest I will take note.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I hope NEVER! #ImpeachmentMarch  #IMPEACHTRUMPANDPENCE
#impeachalready]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barrypa51500599 @austin_dma @Montel_Williams @realDonaldTrump  you think I'm took offense of your ignorant comment… https://t.co/bdpEgcJfiC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@austin_dma @Montel_Williams @realDonaldTrump So we can have hope history will repeat itself? https://t.co/7KLSLQ7x6k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JSavoly Man I was just going to tweet that same meme you beat me to it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ananavarro My new hero everyone need to follow #NoBanNoWall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sean Spicer sucks at Twitter. And reading. And his job. https://t.co/6RLgyWRqP8 by #Roxy4080 via @c0nvey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls She is right you are pathetic, obnoxious hope they Stop putting on tv so much. https://t.co/S7H8IrsCf5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SocialPowerOne1 confused??? https://t.co/VCz1dxaxc5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScratchPolitics @KellyannePolls @WhiteHouse uhm I think she is tho. https://t.co/La5P6uQqmE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Liar there was not delta computer outage, FU Impeachment is coming soon #ImpeachPresidentBannon #NoBanNoWall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Montel_Williams Yes! 💯 Thank you Montrel. https://t.co/Lc2pqAW06b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[72 years ago today over 7,000 prisoners of Auschwitz were liberated by the... https://t.co/AwAnp7swMQ by #AdedapoLinda via @c0nvey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @TheBrodyFile @CBNNews No thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Listen Mentally ill orange Julios you are the one trying to start WWlll you're imbecile. #impeachalready #impeachment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigKahuna919191 @ehalliday07 @SethAbramson I'm not defending Hillary or Obama in any of my tweets the elections are over.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wlnecro @realDonaldTrump But he still ill #impeach no crazy man should be our POTUS is dangerous, this is not who… https://t.co/dqPDpn8TKE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[we know @realDonaldTrump is mentally ill he shouldn't in the WH, either fooling anyone by imposing Bannon on us.… https://t.co/FvO0O16fLL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me waiting  @realDonaldTrump tweet on Judge who stoped #MuslimBan #NoBanNoWall #TrumpYouLost #ImpeachmentSoon… https://t.co/ISnWBSd09J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ananavarro you have seen nothing yet #25amendment #ImpeachmentMarch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SocialPowerOne1 @politicususa There will more to come #25amendmentnow #nomuslimban #NoWallNoBan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#resist Trump's Immigration Ban Excludes Countries with Business Ties https://t.co/ZR7cTJTywq via... by #stacy_friday via @c0nvey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@weaselrina @activist360 @AlexanderChow I will also include Bernie Sanders in that pile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ananavarro @RepCharlieDent Could be the only one who has cojones!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/JzRwsCNP00 @SpeakerRyan @realDonaldTrump @POTUS @RandPaul #unpresidented #ImpeachTrump #Resistence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#thewall #mexicowall #TrumpLiesMatter #MAGAbyImpeachingTrump #MexicoWontPay #RESISTANCE https://t.co/gyGGqJ4jjl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xmaddogxdoylex @BenBerkon @realDonaldTrump I don't have to, DT doesn't write or speak proper English   and he is your "President".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jh14569 @BenBerkon @realDonaldTrump  Is that you Fidel Castro, I rebuke you to come out of his body now in the name of Jesus! Hahahha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBSEveningNews Stop giving this bitch time, we will switch channel , she is DT regime propaganda minister #Liar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EagleEye556 @BenBerkon @realDonaldTrump Donald Trump is not worthy to be call Mr. President, period! he is Donald,… https://t.co/NATTBJknfV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenBerkon @realDonaldTrump He is no worthy of the word Mr. President, not even worth of Mr. He name is Donald Trum… https://t.co/6fWhEqEGdw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ananavarro Pretty close!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please don't Retweet is going to hurt @POTUS feeling you Know @realDonaldTrump  get crazy about ratings. https://t.co/2yGmVWmmkR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PonsFaciaBella You right my apologies, I started, just don't compare a black woman to a monkey very offensive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RaptorRCX @PonsFaciaBella @FoxNews Troll with 7 followers just go to bed adults are talking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PonsFaciaBella @JSLtruth Thats the best you can do? Because if that's it your profile pics looks more like my GIF.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xdelmar59 no but carnival is almost staring.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JSLtruth @PonsFaciaBella I'm telling you Trumpkins are not smart. https://t.co/AVY6gcGBBp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crabioscar @Mjorees @mcuban on Facebook comes all the time, if I see it I will pm you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PonsFaciaBella @FoxNews When, what era? Before slavery or before women could vote? https://t.co/5G9f7OWqS9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ABCWorldNews WTH??🤔]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd been trying to break this story but couldn't confirm. Tip of the cap to... https://t.co/shqfGpTVno by #Politics_PR via @c0nvey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jzimme750 @DeadlineDominic @POTUS @realDonaldTrump @abcnews @KellyannePolls Executive orders? Most of them w/o specifics #alternativefacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@numero9of11 @DeadlineDominic @POTUS @realDonaldTrump @abcnews bellow my answer https://t.co/I2WuXMHrh5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#thewall #Miami #MiamiMayor #santuarycity #RESISTANCE https://t.co/IjAApFN14P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the winner of today internet is.... Jake Tapper!!!! https://t.co/uyoYZ7r28b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @seanhannity @FoxNews no thank you https://t.co/AOd0kx9XBy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bananabee1800 Oh boy you're an idiot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bananabee1800 Nope because  Americans aren't​ working for $3.p/h  We don't do chip labor. FYI there's a book call economic for dummies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ianmcnamara5 @FoxNews and you by yourself pay for it. Trumperers=Dumbass https://t.co/0FQdTRZlOS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lspreack @FoxNews 
1. Us 
2. Us 
3. All of the above.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bananabee1800 @FoxNews Yeah must of the goods we buy in USA are from Mexico or China just check products, good luck with that though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BackInTheFray @FoxNews You think Trumpeters think about that ? Noo the puppets who think he is Jesus. They dumb as rocks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VicenteFoxQue @realDonaldTrump Trump is an ignorant you think he thought about consequences? No even his team.… https://t.co/Ct6OW65XUg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNNPolitics Ppl don't be so negative about this, it is good news in this Gingrich may move to Italy! Rejoice!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@madams3196 @FoxNews Hahhaha yeah what ever make you happy! https://t.co/LP2qEOPzwb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@madams3196 @FoxNews Make up your minds Trumpeters did or didn't Obama create jobs? Answer is yes, 4.7 unemployment TD so lucky.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyannePolls @POTUS liar you and your #alternativefact  kellyann is Trump propaganda mouthpiece and lying puppet.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>