<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I hear every second word works @kristenauthor @AirPowerHistory]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What self-respecting historian has a tidy desk @kristenauthor? I'd be worried if it was.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I cant wait to read your forthcoming journal article @AuthorClaireG!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A reflection of state based recruiting @AuthorClaireG? WA men associated in civilian life shared common exp on WF. 11Bn, 16Bn, 44Bn etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely @AuthorClaireG. I write about Lyons in "Beyond Surrender". Have you met @iandloftus? Similar interests between #twitterstorians!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sure do @AuthorClaireG. McKinnon was captured at Fromelles and died from GSW at a German field hospital at Douai eight days later.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sure am @AuthorClaireG. Fair few WA lads captured at Pozières, Mouquet Farm, Bullecourt &amp; Lagnicourt. Happy to help wherever I can!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @rjm037!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theres plenty of that going on too @rjm037. Submitting in June.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1200 pages into @StephenKing's #TheStand. I get a prize for finishing it, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The director's cut @ChrisBernath? 20 mins of "The end" by The Doors as the finale never lost its sense of irony.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like to think of it as my own 'Limitless' experience @Sjgray86]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish it would happen more often @Sjgray86]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Same thing happened to me recently. I felt productive without typing a single word. @Sjgray86]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well that escalated quickly. https://t.co/OzzJIumZz5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely @mesutuyar10. None of the 60 Aust POW died Ottoman captivity were officers. Of the 337 Aust POW died in Germany, 2 were officers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry, @iandloftus. Mentioned in Dispatches.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conditions there were pretty good @nigel_atter. Hardly a hell-hole, as this photo of Australian officers fro May 19… https://t.co/IQvRkpOio8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Escaped, recaptured and an MC for his efforts @iandloftus. I write about Lyons in "Beyond Surrender" &amp; may have some material for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Captured Aust officers considered Krefeld "one of the best" camps in Germany @nigel_atter. Pre-war Hussar barracks… https://t.co/XaPpcLny4D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The one, the only. @Taff_Gillingham @greatwarfilms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good qn though. I'll see what I can dig up. @lawrencema_85b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aust POW data cross-referenced with @CWGC and @AWMemorial @lawrencema_85b. Ottoman/German POW stats would be British. 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Close to 1000 Australians taken POW German troops on Western Front May-Nov 1916. All but 26 survived the war and re… https://t.co/xE69K9kKkV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great photo @FrancesBekafigo!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grim lessons learned on the #Somme. II Corps notes, August 1916. https://t.co/ackKGRUbyc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember the dead but fight like hell for the living. Great #RemembranceDay address by @jeff_kennett this morning. https://t.co/LMi43nXvFn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[400 men &amp; 25 officers @AustGreatWar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mustangs supporting Old Faithful. #3RAR  #77SqnRAAF https://t.co/hWlMu31zg3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading @StephenKing while @Stranger_Things soundtrack plays. Could there be a creepier, more suspenseful way to spend a Friday afternoon?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wally Peeler reflecting on his VC action at Broodseinde in 1966: "I never saw the faces of those I killed ... Simpl… https://t.co/M6oepG3Zn1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Questionnaire Bill Gammage sent Joynt VC for "Broken Years" research in 1967. Feelings before first action?: "Afrai… https://t.co/mQDLOnT7K2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great value to those writing histories of recent conflicts too @LearningArmy @DeadPrussianPod @AWM_OHP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Curious Beersheba will be the major commemorative focus @PPDaley. By 31 Oct 17, AIF lost 36,000 casualties in 8 wks Passchendaele fighting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hold your horses folks, #Beersheba's centenary is next year. This piece by @PPDaley on the complexities of  commemo… https://t.co/VjrrjM93jE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoyed looking through @AWMemorials' Hudson bomber today. Inadequate armament against Japanese Zeros earned it nic… https://t.co/uLVGAwqFlp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flares would make perfect sense @ReturnedFTF.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would I be right in thinking those light trails are mortars @ReturnedFTF? Can't think of too many rounds with such a high-trajectory.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yours and @JohnBlaxland's were the  standouts this morning @RhysCrawley. Congratulations both!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You would think so @AustraliaWW1. But #Somme weather reports show a number of fine/sunny days in October 1916: https://t.co/71b4fPVOkz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haig also met Gough that day to discuss operational planning on #Somme: "Watch weather and execute plans after 3 fine days" @AustraliaWW1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Initial comments from my last substantive chapter. "OK in broad. Some repetition and much verbose languague." Looking forward to the rest!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't have a house in Scotland or can churn out a draft in 27 writing days, but coffee and Mogwai are my staples too @RobertFoleyKCL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If thats the case, prolly relaxed atmosphere compared to France too. Interested to hear what you turn up! @AimeeFoxGodden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doubt it worked on an official level, but maybe on informal battn/company/platoon level. Probably no different from Brits @AimeeFoxGodden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["No other Australian more influential than Bean in shaping the way #FWW is remembered and commemorated". My latest… https://t.co/t7ZjZsL7lK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Psy_Historian Downloaded, saved and printed. Ready to rip into new and engaging aspect of RAF Bomber Command.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In a word, the crew simply disappeared". @WW2Researcher @FrancesBekafigo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll shout the first round of pink gin @WWATMD @kpbushnell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Historians skeptical sea monster involved in sinking of a German U-Boat in First World War. Who would have thought? https://t.co/MRXcnEr1YG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @AndrewFaulkner9 @issuu. Glad you enjoyed it! @AWMemorial]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get it written @ClaireDavisPHD, but also trust the writing process @PhDForum @PaulineZardo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great photo @FrancesBekafigo. Palpable sense of anticipation and dread as engines idled and crews ran through pre-flight checks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Curious that over 8 million combatants taken prisoner in FWW @Artistwar, yet few artworks represent that wartime experience.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WW1_Series Any idea of the air-speed velocity of an unladen carrier pigeon?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its the small details of that film that resound with me. Reveted trenches made by crew who fought the war. @greatwarfilms @wordpressdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting little war memorial near home. Wonder when Iraq and Afghanistan will be commemorated on local memorials… https://t.co/SYVRZ7nxyT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didnt listen to mine either @Vanda_Wilcox @Mick_Cook. Excrutiating!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me too @AmeliaVonVixen. Absolutely nothing like the book.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And to top it all off, singles you out as an "Adelaide journalist" @AndrewFaulkner9. Blistering.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The book is much better @KarlJames_1945 @StephenKing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Academia at its best @Brynley_H. Strange he wasn't a reviewer though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching Kubrick's adaptation of The Shining for the first time in decades. Unlike @StephenKing's book, it hasn't aged well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*inhales to the tune of Up There Cazaly* @stephenstockwel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who would have thought @KarlJames_1945? https://t.co/xq8pZq8Zzi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thabks chum! @Brynley_H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not mentioned was the development of the bangalore torpedo for wirecutting @ProfPeterDoyle. Raids=laboratory for technical/tactical success.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phosphorpus too @ProfPeterDoyle, as @Brynley_H mentioned. Nasty, grisly stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the Western Front, raiding success depended on effective planning, preparation, a good fireplan and surprise: https://t.co/NjXel33yzS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pte Alfred Jackson, 54Bn AIF. Captured at Fromelles and spent remainder of FWW in Germany. Still retained sense reg… https://t.co/YTnMfccBuC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New street nr home. Named after Joe Honeysett, snr public servant 1920s-50s. Served WW1, captured by Germans, won M… https://t.co/Rkp9RwysRs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty sure there was a Pte Baldrick in that formation @prior_robin @ProfPeterDoyle. No idea what battalion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not so much in memoirs @ProfPeterDoyle. Moreso in raid orders, after action reports and lessons learnt pamphlets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some regularity in 1917 @ProfPeterDoyle. Also rendered enemy MG positions unusable during withdrawal across NML. No idea of numbers made.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No 28 'stinkpot' more practical @ProfPeterDoyle. Horrid overwhelming smell forced enemy in dugouts to surface. https://t.co/2nUkF51pGx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not just Punjabi Muslim/Pathan POWs @SubedarKhanOrg. Two Indigenous Australian POW ended up at Zossen too. See: https://t.co/GXqyA5aZIV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This pattern more common for AIF in mid-16 near Armentieres @ProfPeterDoyle. Flanged cog made by Engineers with ent… https://t.co/PUiKfocZd7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raiding icon, but practically useless in a gunfight @ProfPeterDoyle. Revolvers, grenades more effective at close quarters when raid sprung.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great piece on #3RAR at Maryang San by @AWMemorial historian Mick Kelly. Fought this week 65 years ago in Korea: https://t.co/csxMmhfTWX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For more on Noble and his current deployment to Iraq, see https://t.co/STSWiJ4Rdi. Courtesy @siobhanheanue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gulf War, UNSCOM and Operation Habitat too. Australia has had troops in the Middle East for over 25 years, not alwa… https://t.co/1P54aJiSOH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chem suit worn by Capt Roger Noble while attached to UNSCOM in new MEAO display @AWMemorial. Brig Noble now Dep Com… https://t.co/irVLy3EgMV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sallyjsara's headscarf and microphone in the new Middle East display at @AWMemorial help tell the story of journal… https://t.co/ledQM8XTKb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Follow up question or joke" @Mick_Cook @pptsapper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's still one more quarter. Give them timr @drewfore @w_westerman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last game of the season and I had no idea the Swans had so many supporters  @w_westerman #AFLGF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missed that bit @sommecourt. Seems pretty conclusive then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agreed @sommecourt. Could also be someone entirely different. Fortunate in that German photos of Grant and Carter named them in caption.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sommecourt This photo from AWM purports to show Bright (far right) in Germany. Records show he stayed in France. C… https://t.co/mshsiTYesY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Therein lies the mystery @sommecourt. Garner was from 17Bn and would have had a different colour patch. Diamond, black over green.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sommecourt Captured at Peronne 11/09/18 and spent the remainder of the war working behind German lines. 2/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have @sommecourt. If those are 4Bn colour patches, based on my list of known Indigenous AIF POW, he could be 7701 Pte Walter Bright 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The experiences of two Indigenous Australian #POW who spent last year of #FWW in the "Crescent Moon" camp nr Berlin: https://t.co/K4jnqfOHxW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think @KarlJames_1945 should have one of these in his backyard @ChrisBernath. For his son, of course...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theres also plenty of trench remnants there too @JoJohook2003. Had the pleasure of being invited onto property to check them out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thats right folks, Escaping The Great Escape. https://t.co/e92JAvNYVU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Long-winded! @DeadPrussianPod @iTunes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drewfore would approve @robtswthrayguns!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really enjoyed your book @TonyHorwitz. So far my favourite read for 2016. https://t.co/1CaVn3KjOk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My pleasure @AirmensBar!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>