<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishTimes @IrishTimesSport He should be sponsored by VHI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Classydelilah Ireland's not a bad spot ðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bailly seems to have Jones syndrome..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nic_nak86 bolloxs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nicky Butt will be getting his papers I reckon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pa_Ward1 @utdandy Luke Shaw refused to take the stairs again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4th penalty to Everton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leah_thoma @AlphaAcessories  Could u glam this up a bit plz https://t.co/iJmKqWyqZV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any sign of Ebola?? https://t.co/CdeneIHnbY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@talktoBOI All good thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@talktoBOI Hi is the app down at the moment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South stand has smoke bellowing from it at old Trafford apparently.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OfficialRyy It's fuckin West Ham...And Danny fackin liar is crying into his pillow..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#roomtoimprove Right lads I'm off on me holidays... Again. https://t.co/OQ0Thgi06p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#roomtoimprove Did a brick fall on her head.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GaryLineker @sportingintel Oh make a bag of fuckin crisps out of it...Sour grapes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#roomtoimprove Bunny Boiler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#roomtoimprove whole shagging life's a holiday.. Imagine living next door to them...Where off on hols  again mind the dog.. Bye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#roomtoimprove Robbie f all wrong with the leg saw ya getting into a car in the AIG advert ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ and who's yet one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyNews Quorn ran straight through me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RandomCorkStuff @keveb09 The most expensive built Aldi in Europe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@7clarkyred Up next The ring of fire..Jonny cash.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PercyToplis Did ya see the tennis celebration .. Mercenary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MailOnline Yeah break your fucking leg and check out the hospital bill without the E111 form]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Norn iron on Trump's banned list.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@meurig73 And that's just his looks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DeadlineDayLive Someone robbed the shopping basket cause all he's good for is delivering takeaway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shaw mentally destroyed from that injury.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plz not 90mins of that something good tune.. Ffs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MetEireann Thank God..We missed you Rain.. Welcome back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Johnludds Bigger than Tim Peakes new stint in universal studios.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JBurtTelegraph One chromosome away from a carrot...He should be sponsored by the NHS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sport of kings ...Along with greyhound racing... Barbaric https://t.co/HfGhfzLauB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CSM0611 He won't last the course they'll give  him enough rope...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CSM0611 NYC my 2nd home.  the greatest show on earth Carl.. They hate the prick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@permanenttsb Coke and sex toys!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarm0161 Universal studios presents Tim peake starring in Mythical Space Odyssey 2..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CSM0611 what happened the trooper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Hurt as Bird in the movie The Field.My favorite all-time performance. https://t.co/QYrnmV4Vri]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Hurt in the movie Champions was a brilliant performance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mccarthykanturk Build a wall and keep them out.ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump It's Clare co council you had your beef with over the golf course wall..Not the EU..One chromosome away from a carrot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@7clarkyred Fuckin Charlton is a greedy bastard after this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pjstretfordend Heartbreaking to see him out there last night]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@watpoae He was in cork last summer I got kicked out for throwing beer mats at him and McAteer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@watpoae Turned the dispicable cunt off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full kit wanker alert... Home kit for Wembley confirmed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gary Neville the pundit...Right I'm off to bed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way this is played out, masons gonna come out with a head transplant...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Bruce your genes got rinsed on this fella]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't cover your body in tattoos and go down like that ffs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pjstretfordend Shocking performance tbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyanRMUFC All that money and gets an Aldi blade all-round]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@C_bearage77 Your streams ok he's scored ðŸ˜ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lunerbase  nightmare and the match on as well like]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great the washing machines packed up https://t.co/YMTxwXaqr9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Breaking911 Will mexicans be required to wear armbands next...This cunts a monster]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@C_bearage77 Close the tunnel the bromance between those two will be unbearable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a 100m player on that field tonight and a sweat shop turning out merchandise for him.. Laughable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@C_bearage77 Did you see Pogba come out of tunnel by any chance cause he ain't on the pitch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lunerbase piss poor Tony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had it coming pile shite out there tonight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Cadbury's premier league 2018 though ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the away jukebox stuck ffs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[De Gea in line for Trump's wall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[T2 tomorrow ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I #ScrumTogether with @DoveMen to win #IREvFRA RBS 6 Nations tickets. Pick your match by 8pm &amp; you could too
https://t.co/ETLqhHSwge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PercyToplis He's no David Silva thats for sure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@business Keep them coming Theresa...The Empire is crumbling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep them coming Theresa...The Empire is crumbling. https://t.co/x3eqpoBY70]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tim Peake is heading back to universal studios for another few months.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyNews About two days ago ffs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PercyToplis  Another classic https://t.co/20meVZmGyV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#operationtransformation Not long to go for the ten at ten. https://t.co/DYddpZeTbC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thetwicket @IrishTimes @bboyd27 @IrishTimesOpEd You're the one that wrote a complete article on it Ffs..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomaswjones86 Or things to do if your with a Bunny Boiler.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Cadbury's premier lge ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CadburyUK @Lunerbase @premierleague Who has the record for stuffing cream eggs up their arse?? And don't say Kenny Daglaish he's retired.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JBisaRED Give the mcanns a ring they'll know what to do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@C_bearage77 Blindness since then, you can't read the bullshit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OpinionLine96 Asked a driver on the Ballincollig X service last week what is the earliest bus on this route...Eh I dunno he says.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Airport staff involved k'ell. https://t.co/tqIGnU0L7Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IWCare Is there a problem with supply in Ballincollig Co Cork..Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IWCare Is there a problem with the water supply in beech pk,Ballincollig.. Thank You.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DeadlineDayLive He goldfish died]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IndoSport Fuck off kimmage you crank]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Curt_AFC @ajplus  Just as fans boycott the shithole]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCSport Ffs they're selling effergies of him already...Oh wait there baked potato's.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Orrible_Ives I suppose Taylor Swift is just a complete fuckin Psychopath then..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishTimes He say's a lovely mass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SnakehipsSam Abused the shite outa the ref and then unleashed hell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RyanRMUFC @C_bearage77 @jose When I saw the selection yesterday I decided to check out retirement homes in my area.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AwayDays_ God save the Queen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SundaySupp @SkyFootball They already sell Baked Potato's outside the ground I thought...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring manufacturing back to America.So the factories come back.But the majority of manufacturing jobs are done by Robots.@realDonaldTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Breaking911 Gobshite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you parade Madonna out as some kind of icon you truly know your nations fucked..She collects kids like fridge magnets ffs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaraCompass @glen76stephens Cock ring??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shanks what should one do?? Long ball my son... https://t.co/TXyUINgCjI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sat night that means 5hrs of Bob Marley for me.ðŸ¦]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>