<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[my gender studies instructor told us to write an auto-ethnography  on our sexuality and im like WHAT sexuality â‰ï¸ðŸ¤”â‰ï¸ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[cant wait to go to seattle and get poked with a needle!!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[dallas can come home now plz ðŸ˜¢ðŸ£ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[cant wait to move in w/ the best boy ever this summer ðŸ˜­â¤ï¸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["did you buy a lotto ticket with your lucky money?" "i bought GROCERIES" "well fuck" #chinesenewyear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smallhouseplant i thought this said MILK and almost loSt IT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[how am i supposed to pack a BACKPACK for a 3-day trip to seattle when i try on 14 different plain white tshirts before leaving my house???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you just write about sex and killing yourself and how you hardly ever went to school âœ¨]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[why does the 1975 have to come back here i thought i was finally over that band ðŸ˜­ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this was the final result https://t.co/84mqup1TxU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[true love is me spending 5 mins trying to decide which bitmoji encompasses my true feelings for dallas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[low key all of ridge ðŸ¤” https://t.co/TcZLt8IOcS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yes hello bernie the love of my life https://t.co/j67n4aUYil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOT TICKETS TO THE XX TIME TO CRY FOREVER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[me now that i'm moving apartments again: looks at every ikea hack to ever exist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kyla_annee happy birthday little one ðŸ’•ðŸ’•ðŸ’•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*puts on glasses* "wow i look like a nazi"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my boyfriend looks like a hot dad who is about to take their kid to baseball practice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[me: about to drop my psyc course so i can go to seattle instead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[do not come 2 my work 2 watch football today i want to go home early THX world]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[she cant be what you need if shes 17 ðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[also: how do you fill out a rent cheque??? ive wasted like. 5 so far ðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my sister has been gone for like two weeks and her cat basically thinks i am her mom now and i hate it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[would probs give my rent money for someone to drive me my bf and my two cats back 2 vancouver rn ðŸ˜…ðŸ˜…ðŸ˜…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[xmas dinner: me schooling my dad on social media, public spheres, and literally everything to do with a computer ðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[xmas in maple ridge is seeing your gr 8 science teacher at the haney buying a 26 of rum ðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PSA: if u cant afford to tip then dont eat out ðŸ˜‡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[holy fUCK https://t.co/Q8jkSy2yfz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[life realization: the last time i used my coffee bean grinder was for weed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if my neighbour  could stop grunting every three minutes that would be great]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the real question is will dallas go for pho with me when hes off work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[rearranged my bedroom about 4 times before giving up and drinking wine ????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so far i've washed my hair donated clothes played with my sisters cat cleaned the entire house and drank tea i am a productive adult]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[well my first mistake was eating vegan stir fry before hot yoga earlier 2night and thinking i WOULDN'T almost vomit during childs pose ðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[honestly the robbers video changed my life STILL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[google search: chicken finger delivery vancouver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TransLink is there a 3 coming to 50176 been here for half an hour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[accidentally getting drunk midday was not how i planned on studying for my exams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yo someone hmu w/ a second job im dyinG HERE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my level of excitement for @Japanesehouse and @ambbain on thursday is real ðŸ™„ https://t.co/Ejgs2UlZh4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[about ready to stress cut my hair off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my life is 100% over because i just realized i lost my favourite pen at work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KARISSAPUKAS loved this video! and your constant positivity!!! ðŸ’•]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when will the world let me live and when will i go a month without almost ripping my nipple piercings out by accident]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["imagine if you liked drake AND beyonce. i like one more than the other. IM SURE YOU CAN SEE WHICH IT IS"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i spent a good month or two crying over the 1975 yet again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i started dating the nicest boy ever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i finished half of my degree]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i was essentially homeless for a month and slept on ppls couches]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016 was rlly weird]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[adulthood is asking ur parents for a toaster for xmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@micaelaaleslie @Gdans1975 2018 is cancelled]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i would for sure saw off my own leg to see jamie xx again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wonder if dallas would kill me if he came home and found a giant pillow fort in the middle of my apartment ðŸ¤”ðŸ¤”ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[idk whats worse hearing my neighbours fuck from a wall away from me or hearing the baby living above me scream for 45 minutes straight ðŸ’¯ðŸ‘ŒðŸ¼ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[holy fuck did that election actually happen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[honestly idk how my school decided to give me a bursary but thx now i can go buy some makeup ðŸ™ƒðŸ™ƒðŸ™ƒ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heyjennna leave my asian ass alone im just trying to serve you food and beer!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@heyjennna and then proceeding 2 b blown away when i say im chinese and fckn white]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[u know what i hate the most about being chinese is ppl asking my race like it matters 2 them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VPL im having troubles logging into my vpl account online can you DM me?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[honestly FUCK food poisoning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[half of me is happy, half of me wants more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if u live in mt pleasant and havent ever been 2 snackland ur missing out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when u try 2 surprise ur bf by going to his house and all he says is "why are u here" THX :)))))]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yep settle down is still a jam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["do u wanna stay for a beer?" "no i have to go shampoo my hair"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you're mad thinking you could ever save me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smallhouseplant for real!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["im not fucking raising my kid in london itll get run over"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smallhouseplant send me 12 thx :)!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[honestly what possesses ppl to live in surrey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*dallas trying to help me study for my midterm* "WHO IS KARL MARX????"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so excited to see @Japanesehouse in dec maybe i wont be blacked out the entire time ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UNIQFIND i sent a laptop skin back for an exchange at the beginning of the month. can you confirm is was received? should have landed oct 7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[me: when can i apply for another loan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i love living in a house where my roommate doesnt give a fuck about my life or my schedule ðŸ˜‡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[cannot fucking get over this new @boniver album]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[as emo as it gets tbh https://t.co/TEDXjTwdQI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["jeggings are the future i swear" my cOworker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ok i used to be a literal squirrel baby https://t.co/oSPViIjQch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SHUT UP I LOVE YOU, YOURE MY BEST FRIEND]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[s/o to dallas for being the best boy ive ever met :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[how rude the 1975 decides to do their live lounge when im in the middle of a wisdom tooth extraction]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*contemplates putting on eyelashes to go to get my wisdom teeth removed*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*me at lany* "matty healy who??????"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[prepping to hangout with @micaelaaleslie by eating all my peanut butter now so she cant judge me later]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LANY IS TONIGHT ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OK i need to see disclosure at contact thats all bye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my sisters boyfriend doesnt know when halloween is or what a spaghetti squash is. #german]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[need to get my neck cracked asap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHY'D i just watch a 10 minute video on gin for my new job?????]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[honestly dont know where id be without @socialeyeslash foxy lashes ðŸ˜­ðŸ’œ @KARISSAPUKAS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[don't belong to no city, don't belong to no man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UNIQFIND how do i return a laptop skin? unopened bought the wrong size and just want a refund]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["DRAKE IS HERE???" a direct quote from my mother]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*laying in bed w/ dallas* "do you ever like....miss harambe?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*rolls around in bed* me: my names jenna young and i dont care]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["what are these small straws for?" "cocaine" "ok"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[dallas is the greatest bf ever and im forever grateful that he continued to like me after i drunk texted him for like 6 hours #truelove]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>