<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Young woman on train: "Do you know how I can't survive without wifi?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@radionz that seems like a bad idea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mjollnir I no longer know. Is it helping or is it Stockholm syndrome?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mjollnir oh god foam rollers are evil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greencatherine @mjollnir I read that as "sense OR compassion". Still worked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@opendatanz “Localities data” good luck with that one!! Fire has been actively fighting that since forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WasPhantom "I'll hold my beer"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cortesi on the plus side, nobody will have better backup testing than @gitlab soon. Nothing fixes backup process faster than data loss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cortesi @gitlab I’ve been there. I managed to use replication logs to bring the backup up to date but wow it was a horrible night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrismcdonough do other languages have adverbs?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reddit now spinning out megathreads on a daily basis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kamal_hothi After watching my wife do a uni degree I realised I’d never be able to, the nonsense would drive me insane.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DylanReeve @SwiftOnSecurity @pwnallthethings You know @SwiftOnSecurity is just gonna be tweeting that image of her head in her hands again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@svs It wasn't a bad decision, but it put then in the wrong position. You can't half-dodge an oncoming train, they needed more action.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@djhdcj @NZPrivacy so many things about that case and judgement I don’t understand as a layman.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@djhdcj @NZPrivacy the suggestions were consistent tho - [21] (c) intent, (d) harm to ordinary person, but not (e) harm to her?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@djhdcj @NZPrivacy of course, and perhaps she is more resilient than the objective person (who was found to be harmed), still seems weird.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@djhdcj @NZPrivacy [74] seems to be the key to it, and I presume is why they’re appealing so they can fix it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@djhdcj @NZPrivacy so I see, and they were light on testimony too. Feels like a prosecution screwup?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@djhdcj @NZPrivacy was the evidence her actions, or the judgement of a psychologist?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@djhdcj @NZPrivacy The article implied that the judge felt it didn’t, based on the womans actions after. Feels like a lot of wiggle room?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We’re going to Candy Mountain Charlie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realGollumTrump @keith_ng Unconstipational is my new favourite word]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StevieBuckley lots of people never figured out the timeline thing, even after the end of the movie. I think it depended how you saw it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Change in newborns named Donald in 2017, by county #missingvisualisations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tmcw yes, but only if they’re in biotech.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Philosopher discusses when it's ok to punch Nazis https://t.co/CD2jaKgUza]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kiwiana10 @rmi Not sure I agree with that. Do we have data?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarabeee Website resets, regular employee transitions are being mixed in with policy changes and serious departures, it’s not helping.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exhausted handwringing about things that are perfectly normal parts of a transition is overshadowing the bits that are genuinely concerning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is amazing! https://t.co/foGTSOln9N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For anyone baffled at Trump, we've seen this before - there's even a song about it! https://t.co/EcWLzQeKsV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@caycos no, but it looks like it solves the wrong problems at &lt;govt level.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@caycos Slack, trello, Google suite, office 365, dropbox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StilettosinSols That's amazing! Congrats!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kamal_hothi @rmi awesome, fed back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kamal_hothi several people who might otherwise be interested are assuming the pay is low due to industry. A salary range might help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cortesi I have a list of other things I'd like you to arrange.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m confused, are we arguing with paid agitators and pundits now? I’m pretty sure we could spend that time more wisely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I queried it I was told cats were already getting payments if they turned up within hours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have weird dreams. I was on a task force looking at extending WINZ opening times so sugar gliders could collect payments.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patstokes not to mention bizarre. He probably just excluded at least 50% of the people in his life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HaikuGeek it’s always possible to escalate anger, de-escalating is more difficult. I think you’ve err’d in the right direction :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@themikeking @radionz @TheWirelessNZ @mosaicscience I sent an email to https://t.co/D0nVmz4HhI I’ll let you know what I find out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@themikeking @radionz @TheWirelessNZ @mosaicscience Hah :) :( I wonder how much it'd cost to do the information gat… https://t.co/1vCHMXAIxc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@themikeking @radionz @TheWirelessNZ Did you see https://t.co/KESYs2ruBC ? I know it's not quite on topic but their… https://t.co/W41udy4TDm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@megahbite @jemyoshioka I see you ignored the kitten who was clearly a major part of your development team on the photo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just watched a woman walk across a road, then call her two unattended dogs across in front of a car, what the fuck!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tslumley @aschiff @fogonwater @tuureiti Firebase is great for that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GracefulLillian @rmi Serra bought some clothing for Ava, stellar was nearby, the inevitable occurred]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a cat I don't wear clothes HELP https://t.co/uwquQXjwMd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kirsty_johnston that’s a whole queen-street-apartment-block’s worth of avo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keith_ng woah woah, we’re after a *different* apocalypse that’s all. #singularityorbust #zombiesareoktoo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front-end dev job going at @Koordinates , if that’s your thing you should apply, they’re a great bunch. https://t.co/iWZOXhMXno]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wombleton have not committed a single patch with comment “JUSTICE RAINS FROM ABOVE” today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@starlajo Haha the Orange. I remember that. I was always sure you were responsible for a wave of orange that swept… https://t.co/FFH1Rsxxxu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@slyall I wonder if he thinks a casual read of his twitter feed would encourage a cautious person to take a risk working with him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If attending the last bargaining session before a strike by much of your workforce isn’t the job of a DHB CEO, what is?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jemyoshioka THIS SIDE HAIR. THIS SIDE HAIR ALSO.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jemyoshioka I'm imagining you starting with a blank sheet of paper and before anything else writing "THIS SIDE HAIR" on one side]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alydenisof I ask myself that all the time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zeldawilliams How do you even describe that mood!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DylanReeve don’t read the comments. OH GOD DON’T READ THE COMMENTS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading discussions between Americans about health insurance is amazing. So many relaxed about people dying due to lack of care.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CapturedApp Heya, I just upgraded to Sierra and Captured stopped working  - I can't trigger capture, even using the drop-down. Any ideas?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patstokes I think you should know, a toddler solved the Trolley Problem.

https://t.co/MhF4P2lNu7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@asmith Sent just now, thanks!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sule_io @asmith @kitehq How!? I've been emailing and tweeting and following for months! How do I get it!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tanya We're all mad here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrismcdonough Forgot you weren't a kiwi!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gnat Love the lights there :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jsrnz @kiwibrew I’m not sure we came through unscathed to be honest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jsrnz Onesies in public? so comfy tho I guess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jsrnz HUMAN. DRIVE ME TO THE PLACE WHERE THE KIBBLES ARE MADE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Organisation for Cray Producing Countries calls on America to limit cray production to avoid a collapse in the price-per-gb of raw cray.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TorDotComPub Download buttons are just hanging for me, is there another way to get the eBook?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rmi the third type are arachnophobic, in which case both apply.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rmi There are three types of people in this world. People who have read Worm, and people who have made a Terrible Mistake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rmi Outside on the road, Skitter giggles to herself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some serious feels in this thread (17yr old who survived ovarian cancer), but how incredible are her medical staff? https://t.co/Bhwhl3tB9b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“When you feel you have agency, information is entertainment. When you feel you have no agency, information is depressing.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jsrnz tracer vs tracer. We’ll both die of old age before we hit each other.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theskaterdev You rarely realise how it makes people view you, or who it hurts - they won't tell you. I'd stick to… https://t.co/wB0PLMM05u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theskaterdev I try and avoid things that will probably hurt others, even if I enjoy them. There's so many things I… https://t.co/FuWkRTtRCF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theskaterdev Probably true. But it’s not that hard not to do accents. Small steps eh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theskaterdev they’re not gonna tell you, they know you’re kind at heart, but it can hurt them anyways so others have to let you know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theskaterdev It’s not about policing yourself, it’s about respecting others who have been through some shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keith_ng It’s an energy field created by all living things. It surrounds us and penetrates us; the cray binds the galaxy together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theskaterdev Racists mimic accents of groups they disparage, so doing so is a negative thing. Don't be like the ra… https://t.co/0qsL72lloE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theskaterdev Kinda confused, are you trying to compare mimicking the accent of a group that isn't discriminated against to one that is?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StevieBuckley @CoderMay It's amazing how much more attractive a job is when the people you'll be working with are wonderful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theskaterdev It's racist behaviour, by association if nothing else. Sometimes it isn't the intent, it's just how a… https://t.co/3YD2qcuDrC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@caycos Found it at https://t.co/Q9jq12bZkS after creating an account]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone know where I can get daily temperature numbers for Wellington going back to at least 1980? #opendata]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jsrnz The worst bit is when you win a round and get a bunch of kills and you think "its working!" But enemy team was just bad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just seems like alienating your intelligence and security services is kind of a mistake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lancehodges @KirstiGrant thanks :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They did it. They really did it! https://t.co/7YUgra4Mp9 Darude - Sandstorm, NYs celebration in Helsinki / Finland 100]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TradeMeProperty @AlistairNZ Collaborative shortlisting and easy rejection lists :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annettle Serra has been getting that, couldn't sleep 2 nights ago because of it]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>