<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[5 key things for HR to pay attention to in 2017

https://t.co/YuUXusI7bx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good roundup of company statements on trump immigration ban @jenamcgregor @RexHuppke https://t.co/SJE13lT3a0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great news for CEB https://t.co/QWjvjOb1xu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hiring freezes are rare these days – they limit employers’ ability to access needed talent &amp; demoralize workers https://t.co/IEf6utjbqK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hiring freezes limit your ability to trade up on talent https://t.co/OTnGSKd00i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now is the time for companies to figure out how to address the CEO/median worker pay ratio. https://t.co/2ou7ZZRhds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seventy-three percent of executives expect the frequency of change to increase this year. https://t.co/WTKziPJcqP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Major changes in areas like public policy and technology will shape both employer and employees challenges in 2017. https://t.co/uUFJ3xv2J5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How about a rubber match in Jan of 18? @JoeNBC https://t.co/TG06oRQpXn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[National champs! https://t.co/XQmJoBaZYX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[smart insights from @jenamcgregor @Josh_Bersin @mchui on what to expect re talent in 2017 https://t.co/B4HbruSFQ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[good thoughts on importance of building capabilities to make perf reviews work rather than getting rid of them https://t.co/jkJK5iCEPd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With Congress back in session, what happens to CEO pay will be on the list of focus areas
https://t.co/RP2mUDAqfs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What executives who care about talent should be thinking about in 2017

https://t.co/Lp4NHGjgTe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Managing reputation will be a key component for HR in 2017 @KarenHigWork 
https://t.co/FQl02oKd7C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even if OT rule is overturned impact is already felt by significant number of employees 
https://t.co/AH3etEphR1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you ready to answer these three talent questions as an executive for 2017? https://t.co/RQl9YmSVJk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More companies are using their HR strategies as a PR tool.  But does it work?  @pbump https://t.co/NL870mGrE8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even if the CEO-median ee pay ratio is eliminated, companies should still be prepared to release the information https://t.co/RP2mUDAqfs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Managers - holidays are when most employees decide to quit; have you talked with them about 2017 plans? https://t.co/3DpwWvXWtb @balancegal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good take on managing today in uncertainty @MT_editorial https://t.co/PBwRQ1AYu2 for more see https://t.co/yxNnFaAu38]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lyft advertises this way because hr is the new pr @pbump read this for more detail https://t.co/WSXWwRzneB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CEB podcast on how to lead through uncertainty.  Worth a listen. https://t.co/yEOVc3FZZO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expectations of raises are low, question is how to tweak your benefits package to find and retain talent https://t.co/vNcZoUGwN4 @MyShar0na]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[smart from @RavinJesuthasan on buyers remorse from getting rid of perf scores https://t.co/gDs2Qigh8U CEB work https://t.co/jCtaEHioun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the full CEB piece on this https://t.co/gDs2Qigh8U check here https://t.co/f175NDMDgS @rzgreenfield]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Siri or Your Spouse? People Will Soon Be Talking to Bots More Than to Their Beloveds https://t.co/dF469rVIUj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One third of employees believe brexit is limiting their career options https://t.co/qb2dGxwsaX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HR as PR? @lyft takes @uber on why riders should pick them: answer lyft treats drivers better @JustinJBariso    https://t.co/WSXWwRzneB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MJ_Coren @binarybits agree about convincing needed, but company commitment to training and development will also be needed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation debate not just abt which jobs are destroyed/created. Should be abt people impacted @mj_coren @binarybits https://t.co/8x7sUcO2j8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[first #Polaris flight @united for me, so far a really good improvement]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For advice on how CEOs can avoid this https://t.co/rRg5n02pt3 this is a good read https://t.co/G0NFjDCwAL @CEBTalentDaily @jenamcgregor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smart insights from accenture on improving gender diversity https://t.co/6QU3qlrjjP @ElaineKTurville @Accenture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge blocks overtime rule; should companies increase comp or save the money? https://t.co/IafaiosIfd @marianne_levine @LisaPiazzaSHRM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump election likely accelerates companies focus on improving D&amp;I https://t.co/slN9BxlNR9 @AndrewWinston @grossdm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See our new executive guidance on driving performance in volatile markets 
https://t.co/yxNnFaS4UG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Companies should prepare to share CEO-med pay-ratio; data exists already, do you want to control message?  @HayGroup https://t.co/DhGKW019QL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wait and see is a bad approach during periods of change and uncertainity
https://t.co/f2NYZ4e5f1 @CIPD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[how should CEOs talk with their employees about the Trump administration? https://t.co/G0NFjDU7sj @alexiaer @BryanLlenas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top Workplaces — and all workplaces — must focus on retention https://t.co/gf130Gusof @RexHuppke @CEBTalentDaily]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some additional thoughts on how a trump administration impacts work in 2017 @behpi @CEB_News @FastCompany https://t.co/tBwmiZQJm0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some additional thoughts on what a trump administration means for HR @Josh_Bersin https://t.co/tBwmiZQJm0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[how trump election impacts ACA, Immigration, and other HR poicy implications https://t.co/tBwmiZQJm0 @KatMMoody @robmoss @katelunau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes can you ask McConnell what advice he would give to schummer?  Would be interesting to know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait until this is open! https://t.co/PDBcXHl118]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool insight: ee's hired in q4 turnover at higher rate because often skip year-end review: takes 12+ months to get feedback #ReimagineHR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inspired by enormous impact #SpecialOlympics has.  Tears to eyes. #ReimagineHR https://t.co/RkWOmV4ovl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Cheese_Peter: Companies not governments need to set social policy: https://t.co/VkYjOOXX5q #ReimagineHR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cheese_Peter companies need to take lead on brexit rather than wait for government to decide #ReimagineHR https://t.co/uLwXLvZ3B6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kicking off #reimagineHR. Great 2 days ahead of us to advance the science of HR https://t.co/LdQiCQXF1w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to London ReImagineHR starting on Wednesday! https://t.co/LBghH2cJIM #ReimagineHR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tasty coffee @RareBirdCoffee in falls church city; well worth it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One benefit of delayed flight -- flu shot. @fly2ohare @ElaineKTurville]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamMGrant @facebook making a good call on keeping (and improving) performance reviews than killing them.  https://t.co/hvNbqFcKOO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jenamcgregor sharing insights on new LinkedIn features. helping you look for a job behind your boss’s back https://t.co/tD4vMGZrGz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Commuting doesn't have to be wasted time, some goal-setting on your way into work could set the day up for success: https://t.co/6hPD8HdJwC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @RollsRoyce for hoisting the most progressive group of D&amp;I executives in Europe today https://t.co/U3BuUang7m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rob cross: avoid collaborative overload by always taking a direct report to meetings #ReimagineHR https://t.co/RvEhah27HZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rob cross: people not tools critical to making collaboration work #ReimagineHR https://t.co/wQpen4y1Ul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StanMcChrystal how leadership skills change #ReimagineHR https://t.co/GTIJFw8fgU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StanMcChrystal must understand communications to understand leadership #ReimagineHR https://t.co/Ed2v3ilVno]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ValeriePlame listening to great insights about building trust #ReimagineHR https://t.co/zaffTFA9Gm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HighGroundHQ @HDScorp talking about boom boxes and talent at #ReimagineHR https://t.co/eufATrRWmP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eacushing teaching CEB #ReimagineHR how to play @Playworks https://t.co/vY2Q1a8i7u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A full house for CEBs #ReimagineHR https://t.co/mUcUFIWFht]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@odivina Omar -- looking forward to connecting next week at #reimaginehr https://t.co/B6DgY3lHXh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FastCompany @StephanAarstol not 25 hours a week, but Amazon trying 30 a week https://t.co/kAQJ9ZeF2S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[slower, and usually slower quality talent is the state of recruiting at most organizations https://t.co/ObrEJWBHsq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[maybe not the five hour work day, but the 30 hour work week is alive at @amazon https://t.co/kAQJ9ZeF2S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Cards Against Humanity for Kids Is Coming via @RealSimple https://t.co/wLGuiq8taK @ElaineKTurville]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you have any employees about to leave on vacation at the end of august, this is worth a read

https://t.co/S8DkQhilku]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can cross something off my bucket list -- CEB data in a #usatoday infographic https://t.co/BNrgmmZojA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If parents care more about college tuition $ than retirement, employers have an oppt to adjust benefits https://t.co/1J7hqgg7a7 @nasiripour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HarvardBiz @beygelman for more detail on how to get career pathing to work see: https://t.co/tvsw70N8Ax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@landisl @k9lifesavers can't beat puppy day at #CEB.  You can adopt this one. https://t.co/0YX8vhoACb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drshow this might be an interesting topic for an upcoming show https://t.co/HpSS7SMzZj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[great review of HBR focus on d&amp;i by jenna louie @CEBTalentDaily https://t.co/RA2bQDRUBQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Massachusetts equal pay law a benefit for all @MsJessicaCash @jenamcgregor  https://t.co/7WibEwLNyZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmilyRPeck it is working hard, but according to this research anything after 25 hours week has diminishing returns https://t.co/Yypxo2kdfe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcuban @StephanAarstol #sharktank idea making great progress in HR space #5hourworkweek https://t.co/fJi2LWguad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmilyRPeck @HuffPostBiz Companies that hire in multiple states should follow this rather than have diff rules https://t.co/HpSS7SMzZj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shannonsmedstad @CEBTalentDaily not only does it improve productivity, but it also makes you a more attractive employer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton  good news for employees https://t.co/HpSS7SMzZj and not only piece of important policy in MA today https://t.co/n1w5VXGYyU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When employees don't take their paid vacations, should we start offering them paid, paid vacations? https://t.co/tBiZrGVlJF h/t @EmilyRPeck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@changemblog new insights from CEB -change managers should be where change is occurring (not necessairly in a COE) ( https://t.co/FOdJe0mcWv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[just over a month from away until CEB's reimagineHR in Miami -- largest ever gathering of senior HR executives https://t.co/QTYc63tJ8G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Josh_Bersin but a lot of those vacation spots are making it easier for you to do work from them! https://t.co/5rfdoPTz1E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jack_welch jack is right: employees most likely to make quit/stay decisions on vacations, birthdays and reunions https://t.co/ONffqi7JYQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CEB doing some great things with @LeanInOrg
@CEBCareers #WomenAtCEB https://t.co/0vf3v0L8Qn @MsJessicaCash]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New research suggests working longer hours may reduce productivity. If that's true, the implications are profound: https://t.co/Yypxo2kdfe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How JPMorgan's recent min wage hike is another example of HR becoming a kind of new PR: https://t.co/4jlcttarea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top British Firms Show Little Progress Toward Gender Parity on Executive Committees https://t.co/ySIVKHGgcT

Crack… https://t.co/VFMKHp7cEt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which Employers Offer the Best Work-Life Balance? https://t.co/QpIHrcZsZ2

Indeed has compiled a ranking of the 25… https://t.co/22IgipP7IT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JPMorgan Isn’t Alone: All Employers Are Under Pressure to Raise Wages https://t.co/Ouh85TeSuA

Guardian reporter t… https://t.co/rgPhio6Xg1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brexit Puts Pressure on Science and Agriculture https://t.co/P9TI6h0qSZ

In the wake of last month’s Brexit refere… https://t.co/nzmfBVX1pH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Working 9 to 5 Is Going Out of Style https://t.co/hworevCfEf

Employers and productivity experts have lately been … https://t.co/6WyUYPnrtx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Lesson for Fired HR Leaders? Don’t Drive Change Alone! https://t.co/Ay6x9dGOog

In an interview a few years ag… https://t.co/ebtbo743nf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What If Meritocracy Is a Myth? https://t.co/bEoYDj1ee9

At the LSE Review of Books, Dan McArthur praises economist… https://t.co/VmJY9bcia4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America is Failing at Putting Ex-Prisoners Back to Work https://t.co/Mxvk4upD2g

Some 70 million Americans have so… https://t.co/Jlx2UdvA18]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>