<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Genius move from Uber: commoditizing suppliers, just like MSFT did with PC makers - https://t.co/s90J2v3mkp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As I read this, the only thing I can think is “too little, too late Walmart” https://t.co/7KNPIUSAAe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great empircal study using passive FB data that demonstrates that opposites don’t attract after all https://t.co/nmTqLQ7oev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClarkeMoore @EsotericCD @benshapiro a mix of all of them. Google CEO said 187 employees were impacted. It's likely they came from all 7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two infants treated with universal immune cells have their cancer vanish https://t.co/gpyP0Qg5I9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JDVance1 what data do you see to support immigration reform targeted at ME countries? I don't see what any crack down accomplishes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EsotericCD @benshapiro if company has many employees impacted, it's reasonable for CEO to speak.Cultural fascism argument isnt proportional]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sclarsic also I'm pretty sure @JoshuaBaer would get involved as he runs largest incubator in Austin @CapitalFactory]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sclarsic yes, but get out of SF. Go to gerrymandered districts in red turning blue states and districts. See Austin, TX as a great example]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fake News Is About to Get Even Scarier than You Ever Dreamed https://t.co/nzvV5drUTO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greater Equality Makes Societies Healthier. Only problem is lack of provable causation https://t.co/k7XaxRINfK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Is a Successful Society? https://t.co/nfpZL4Azfy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Young Billionaire Behind the War on Bad Science https://t.co/TnRxbwabt7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How many House Republicans are 1st or 2nd generation immigrants? Enough for a legit threat of impeachment?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[instead of asking "should we take refugees" we should ask "if US broke out in massive civil war would you want Canada/Mexico to take you in"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My first ever fox news retweet. Wow. This is weird. And it feels good actually https://t.co/24KzxMMFvu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost straight along party lines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NAFTA and other trade deals have not gutted American manufacturing — period https://t.co/nXKTz9n0o0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating look into India 3 months after pulling 86% of its cash circulation. https://t.co/rTg1Az5cME]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to Trump, Scientists Are Planning to Run For Office https://t.co/YNVHM1lgsJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ezraklein @JDVance1 my intuition is that graph will look like elephant chart that got coverage in 2016. Maybe no spoke for wealthy though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ezraklein @JDVance1 may not be perfectly clean given many state medicaid but I want to better understand class perception/ jealousy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ezraklein @JDVance1 listened to podcast. Do you have a graph showing ACA benefit distribution (y-axis) across income earnings (x-axis)?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasonlk thought you would like to see this $100M seed valuation claim. Transparency first, right? https://t.co/lqBLMPKTrF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshuaBaer read this on fundraising in not SV https://t.co/U6qaSZQdAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In case you're interested in investing in AirBnB properties.... The Rise of the Professional Airbnb Investor https://t.co/x3FvKE9kT9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superb. Understanding the historical cycles of US political ideology  https://t.co/AMGgEmCBxK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Packers Falcons game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ntarun given changes in how we search - mobile, voice, and in time AR - it feels limiting to regulate search as a utility]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ntarun depends on how much you consider search a social utility vs just a product in Google portfolio that they leverage strategically]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting conservative take on Trump's inaugural address. I mostly agree with this https://t.co/g6w5XaE706]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The "forward 30 seconds" button on podcasts destroys podcasting advertising revenue. Big tension between consumers and producers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Admirable goal, but unfortunately required cooperating from the other side, who used his goals as leverage against… https://t.co/PCoyMl10hZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wore men’s clothes for a month – and it changed my life -  The F-Word https://t.co/CRI20YNmOi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer vision is diagnosing genetic disorders in babies https://t.co/L6wRzaVaaT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taxis are lobbying for a 50 year ban on autonomcars in NYC https://t.co/Jjjs8Decuu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instead of asking "do we let refugees come" we should ask "if armed militias/military destroy your house, do you want Canada to let you in?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not healthy. Intelligence community should not be instigating conflict https://t.co/DqJlSnAYCz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Real Reason Your City Has No Money https://t.co/wXXhio4DVI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing. All electric buses https://t.co/oZQgu5GSic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing -a significant majority of Americans across both parties want @realDonaldTrump to delete his Twitter account https://t.co/DFG7usFi7H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ramiessaid 3/ definitely no copyright issues)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ramiessaid 2/ , bulk data usually available for sale, no real ID required to scrape, CAPTCHA may or may not be present,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ramiessaid 1/ curious if you have any resources regarding legality of scraping data from courthouses (funded by taxes, scraping against ToS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smoking Costs the Global Economy Over $1 Trillion Annually https://t.co/dVfUnlMDhT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A spoon that enables the disabled to feed themselves. Amazing https://t.co/Kd88nOOCas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Platform strategy applied to.... children's toys? Yep @joshuabaer https://t.co/r1MM3fR8Mz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deep learning 2016 the year in review https://t.co/z5jlmeR9z3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama Administration's Biggest Missed Opportunity to Strengthen Middle Class &amp; National Security https://t.co/AT2Lbt0bN9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@salesforcestart hi guys, I have some questions. What is best way to talk to someone on startups team?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump And The Batman Effect https://t.co/NWt1p4jNa0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A brief history of Mitch MccConnell. He was a staunch liberal at one point. Really. https://t.co/0ZKAQjsD5k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The United States Is Set to Take Manufacturing Crown From China https://t.co/jUajBqiCjx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much would it cost to geoengineer thicker Arctic sea ice? https://t.co/2eXIW5H0Uz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Afghan War and the Evolution of Obama https://t.co/CqmByqw9kB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Curse of Credentialism https://t.co/YwE3qYo6o9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DNA editing via CRISPR is going to change humanity, many species, and Earth in profound ways https://t.co/32igrB89KV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is work necessary? Maybe not https://t.co/rFYp7U2h1K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where I can find a list or calendar of open calls for accelerators, incubators or VC funds in the CEE? https://t.co/I4A4Lei0pY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very excited to see Trump swing a few bats at the pharma industry https://t.co/XzNpxn1zIc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HoganBrogan @arlogilbert and mostly earlier stage SaaS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arlogilbert no. Went last year. Loved it but not s good use of your time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[how an elite education makes us dumber. Don't be offended - this is a generalization so don't take it too personally https://t.co/i2dcmxQW99]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For all you AI alarmists out there https://t.co/74qmGDYFxS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In about 10 years, it will be cheaper to build new wind/solar operation than run existing fossil fuel operation https://t.co/WQQrj1hs69]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can aviation get better, faster? YES https://t.co/pFHntBhy62]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jerry Seinfeld on his new show https://t.co/IQJUvp7mFj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool read from Uber on what it will take to get flying car Uber service in cities https://t.co/hZjzwrMrFo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good tips on corporate gift giving https://t.co/5tMEjCMZhD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DashlaneSupport are you building support for Touch ID on Mac app? If so, ETA? thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do so many news websites include a stock ticker with that that day’s price movement? Feels like antiquated practice to me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That amazing feeling when a prospect signs a contract 8 minutes after a first phone call, which lasted only 20 minutes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HoganBrogan recognize they don't have talent or capital to try to rebuild sub-par uber competitors. Also, self driving cars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HoganBrogan Ride Austin only worked because of a few million of effective charity capital, for a clearly inferior service. Most cities]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HoganBrogan Uber won't reenter for $50M. Fighting Austin is about sending message to all other cities: do not try to regulate us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best part of Sunday morning - reading @ExponentialView by @azeem and @inside AI by @robmay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The North Carolina GOP’s Power Grab Represents the End of Democracy https://t.co/ljy2UohCmA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now you can fact-check Trump’s tweets — in the tweets themselves https://t.co/BNEMTUFk43]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should this qualify as fake news? We know the stats on it are false. How will Facebook treat this? https://t.co/DejyBw0a4J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bgarrou @TexasVC @mercuryfund @KauffmanFDN @Entrepreneur fyi, it's condescending to call them fly over States]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just found a software developer on LinkedIn who only works for local governments. Brain nearly exploded.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arlogilbert @googledevs your mouse movements are too similar to that of phantom JS bot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@asanwal as you noted in your post, autonomy breaks uber. I wrote about this a while ago - https://t.co/0mbINP8abP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why The Mainstream Media Can't Hold Trump Accountable https://t.co/G2XdbqYoeH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@google, please make iMessage app for @googleassisstant for large group texts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnCarreyrou @WSJ how is she still CEO?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just published “The Ultimate Lie” https://t.co/Q7ShNncQtc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arlogilbert mine is faster than door-closing speed :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Metabolism scales exponentially across all life on Earth - plants and animals. Incredible. https://t.co/do5hCb2UbV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Hide $400 Million https://t.co/6LpuF1yffM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating interview with digital chiefs at WaPo talking about changes since bezos took over https://t.co/LRtFfotQJG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This will be a major public health boost if it really works. All new sugar! https://t.co/CnbxyRy1ZU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Diners are dying in New  York. Long live Seinfeld! https://t.co/l33X611Qzb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best piece I've ever read on the opportunity for voucher based schooling and charter schools https://t.co/dLK6S9lkBi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arlogilbert check out new @SparkMailApp. Just got Mac and iOS apps. Best email apps I’ve ever used.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanielleMorrill @friendswbrains I think w legit data science u could create liquidity around specific intellectual niches, sapiosexual, etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanielleMorrill @friendswbrains I also know someone made a tinder clone that focused on LinkedIn profile data. It wasnt well executed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanielleMorrill @friendswbrains a lot of people have been trying to crack platonic friendship. Haven't seen any work at scale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanielleMorrill @friendswbrains I love this idea. Will beta test the shit out of it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasonlk or "here's more money"]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>