<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Agile Malcolm:
- Public $ for 'bit less filthy' coal
- Mining lobbyist as climate advisor
- Boast Aust's 'vested interest' in coal exports]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who said this?
"The reality is, you are not going to see another coal-fired power station built in Australia. That’s, that’s a simple fact."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile, https://t.co/nRvmpImP1R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Power prices could double with new coal-fired stations: experts https://t.co/9843AJhVr5 via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“No, new coal is not feasible: on price, reliability or emissions” https://t.co/C0VjbKfJ6b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[um, Malcolm, I'm not sure that's your best argument https://t.co/0lScboL6FZ https://t.co/4G3a3F4yvG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clean coal, Malcolm? Tell us what it costs. #auspol #npc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want less of something you raise tax on it, says Malcolm...
Carbon cough tax
#npc #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and yet, nearly two thirds reckon raising more revenue from companies is better than cutting taxes https://t.co/YnmmvdW4qO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Despite that, most people want to push ahead with the TPP and think 'free trade' agreements generally good for most… https://t.co/ruMgs6S4OM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[40% Aussies think basic political &amp; economic system needs fundamental change. 44% want refinement. @EssentialVision https://t.co/0g0eNnI1Yn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmilyMillane as I typed that, got an email about RSSS being moved to a new yet to be built building - that's what i remembered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmilyMillane vague memories it's getting knocked down?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We have “a half pregnant higher education system”, says Minister. Oddest metaphor yet for  deregulation https://t.co/LT5qxdV7Eo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@FourTet's playlist of artists blocked from USA under #TrumpBan https://t.co/5EfW5vcdGm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[contra: Weak and Incompetent Leaders act like Strong Leaders https://t.co/7Ym4TBYrXj https://t.co/HwXcP9rFmJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Trial Balloon for a Coup?” by @yonatanzunger https://t.co/kDUxD0TjWZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abcnewsCanberra @abccanberra and warm in winter!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[State renewable energy targets 'will be vital to meet emissions goals' https://t.co/fpG9vxy2MX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[cf "a confidant dismissively predicted that Trump would rarely climb a flight of stairs." https://t.co/8CszW6pVj8 https://t.co/6mVscA9bpd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FBI Uncovers Al-Qaeda Plot To Just Sit Back And Enjoy Collapse Of United States https://t.co/MwdoxYjSjN via @theonion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surprising bit of casual racism there, even in the object explanation https://t.co/kOWPWi8Lln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You're soon going to remember what it feels like when America WINS!" https://t.co/rOnNXKMaD4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[nascent fascism captures US executive
mw our PM's spine is MIA &amp; colleagues say he'll achieve nothing
- @c_s_wallace
https://t.co/RGBlIg9APN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 2014: "Clearly climate science is telling us get off fossil fuels as much as possible". As director of Exxon...? https://t.co/GfetcH724o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An odd thing to bring attention to at this point https://t.co/1cfCdDVx0n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Debate about #AustraliaDay has gone on far longer than 26 Jan has been a national public holiday. Get on with it, #ChangeTheDate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should the ACT allow billboards? https://t.co/eNKfWX9BLG #CBR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Companies that want to "come &amp; do something monstrous &amp; special -you're going to have approvals really fast" - Trump
https://t.co/cn3NvMj509]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I am, to a large extent, an environmentalist," Trump told the auto execs.
"I believe in it [the environment].
But, it's out of control."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump seeks to revive Dakota Access, Keystone XL oil pipelines https://t.co/esDaSiLByM "A dark day for reason" - @billmckibben]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Extend RET ‘to cleaner fuels’ says gas lobby - we could call an 'emission intensity trading scheme' oh wait https://t.co/ACZPcuOQgW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, new coal is not feasible: on price, reliability or emissions - Aust Industry Group's @TennantReed https://t.co/73C04o17iN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember when Ian MacFarlane said "you're not going to see another coal-fired power station built in Aust. That’s a simple fact"?
Good times]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“What he’s saying is so serious, so grave, if you take it all seriously it’s a world crisis” https://t.co/9bsHPavy8K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Few Aussies think cutting the RET will push power $ down
In fact, half think it'll push prices up
&amp; they're right… https://t.co/QAZ7hxSztS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrap Renewable Target = higher power prices. Shown in report after report. @TheAusInstitute brief:… https://t.co/BglKQsA6cF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abbott and Joyce reheat the war on the RET. Again. https://t.co/i30syoVn9K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don’t be tricked into thinking your actions on climate are meaningless under Trump. You are more impt than ever" https://t.co/kfKDMnX5BR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[anyone for an "artesian health spa" built in the flooded Hazelwood mine pit? https://t.co/K27aeoDzL3 via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brave &amp; personal from @mikeyslezak - so many feel this, so important how we share and channel https://t.co/PgMOR263VM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Super-low-cost renewable power– "base-cost” – w force a revolution in way grids are designed &amp; regulated" https://t.co/r0AsxgFQlm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[voters increasingly think economy getting worse
only LNP voters likely to think is getting better
@EssentialVision 
https://t.co/DmeFv7ely5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[voters increasingly think their own job will be less secure in two years time -@EssentialVision - https://t.co/iTbKMDMR5M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More voters blame energy price rises on privatisation than renewables – polling https://t.co/rp7jBkISrd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Important thread - Rick Perry is soon in charge of DOE. what is he up to? https://t.co/NuL7hG4vyv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull's new love for new 'slightly less filthy' coal power makes no sense. New renewables are cheaper. https://t.co/2EwcAOI0GV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aus PM boasts our "vested interest" as "world's largest coal exporter"
Aus paper says coal is renewable
this is fine
https://t.co/gh03WlEuRg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canavan spruiks Dept's clean coal briefing to the Oz but apparently wont release so public can make up their own mi… https://t.co/ItHYAL3Iu0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[scathing. no full records, no way to see if they're doing what's intended. no audits since april 15 https://t.co/NUMi0e2Ph5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A colleague struggling w some bureaucracy once sent them an invoice for his time. They withdrew the claim. https://t.co/UdQ9xiEyp1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[in 2015, analysts asked Minerals Council about costs of a clean coal revolution. "They declined to provide detail"… https://t.co/DZmUg1x0pH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coal is the future, says Minister in article not once mentioning cost of new coal plants https://t.co/Gy1yIeUHgm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisFinnigan if recent devs a guide, be dark, boring, badly made &amp; bad for context. Eg 12 lv Mayfair crowding 2 lv heritage melb building]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“light rail is most progressive thing to happen in Cbr since the int airport,” says developer in LR corridor https://t.co/nErmF0tpSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poll shows most Aussies think federal politics is full of corruption. No wonder they want an ICAC https://t.co/eSTP5loXkn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Totally Enormous Extinct Dinosaurs - Waulking Song (Lone remix)’ on #SoundCloud #np https://t.co/ThR5ot6jzj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["ok ok ok I'll resign... but it was within the rules"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The long-term effects of bestowing lower class with a sense of dignity are currently unknown" https://t.co/zly0bbIEjq via @theonion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rumplestatskin although they have now stopped making donations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AGL fined $124,000 for failing to declare political donations at time it was seeking approval to expand csg in nsw https://t.co/2dRRSWbWbv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@verybrownguy i dont read it as denying the need for redistribution.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@verybrownguy have you read it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JimboStanford and here in our own way I guess!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JimboStanford thought this was v insightful on work culture, unions, dynamics fueling right populism, at least in… https://t.co/OpRuX0TCM2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Need a broader revision of culture that makes those who struggle feel like losers." Fascinating piece
https://t.co/7bjr9J7KgQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[whoever put the "eject" usb drive button right next to the "format" usb drive button]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so... what does 'convention' say about replacing a Senator who has defected from the party they were elected in? #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[accusing ABC of "fake news" = accusing our most trusted news source of lying for political purpose
Deeply worrying https://t.co/JAFiIDPEps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Govt taking 'investment approach' to welfare
but of course, not health and education
https://t.co/w2W8hfhENE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matt Canavan reckons this is fake news. https://t.co/izTTP7lRGX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NAIF is not even set up yet. Perfect time for them to consider a $1bn loan! https://t.co/wk0ILHtS8B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In India solar already cheaper than imported coal, soon cheaper than domestic coal. The door is open, if we're will… https://t.co/Pkw8nycdoH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["will be non-transparent to Aust Govt what is going on, who owns it, who are directors. ... is a national security." https://t.co/8oKLRzCvCO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Step one: stop building new coal mines https://t.co/uLhwq5lmHs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["But it was just a projection" - would be more credible w a firewall btw Treasury's projections &amp; Treasurer's office
https://t.co/whRkPyG7is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More &amp; free parking for APH workers. not even be bothered w "direct action" - offering payments not to drive to work. has worked elsewhere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$200m over 4 years for "Regional Jobs" package... for all of Australia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[great news. meanwhile, states continue with plans to privatise land registries https://t.co/0h8t8DUE5g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[urgently needed investment https://t.co/eJ9Znf7u7o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016 was 1.27C hotter than 1880-1900... https://t.co/B6KSdb7EfN https://t.co/OAJKo7KoPi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[India's plan to step away from coal casts doubt on Adani mine https://t.co/XcAS0Gr781 via @ABCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TroyCHenderson or, i guess, supports better 'human capital allocation'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TroyCHenderson guess testing only whether the unconditionality of the payment undermines desire for work, and only among unemployed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If our Reef was a dam, would it get more funding?" 
Indeed, or a coal mine! 
by @QldFarmers &amp; @QTIC in @qclnews
https://t.co/GGNiA0ghFd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TroyCHenderson @BasicIncomeOrg shouldnt they also be trailing w employed?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[not for one second. maybe for a couple of seconds tho, he clearly did https://t.co/vW4DOptsth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[State, local, federal govts sign Townsville "City Deal". No mention: Adani, coal. Where is the "adani jobs bonanza"? https://t.co/eHZDvoClxD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Aust lobbies China-led AIIB to add coal to lending priorities
Canberra to defend lucrative exports" https://t.co/m32bXc0LA1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George wants to turn Australia's system of government in the USA's https://t.co/62mn5FcR8c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[strange pleasure in reading Kim Carr's estimates cantankerousness in Hansard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickPfitzner @KetanJ0 but shouldn't that leave dark areas rather than light?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KetanJ0 forestry, surely?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[bravo, we need this and more
but the climate only cares about the other half of the equation
@NoNewCoalMines https://t.co/TWFDaIKGWR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There comes a time during the writing of a govt report when someone suggests bringing in an editor to “plain English” the text." &amp;^$#@(&amp;^(%]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ABC bias? big business gets 3-5 times more attention than small to med business despite smaller companies making up… https://t.co/G3irI9DQBf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FJKeany but press release is against counterfactual which isn;t shown in the figures?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[just out of shot, i'm sure, are the representatives of the generations that will inherit the consequences of our en… https://t.co/tGTTzvOrIA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why ‘dole bludgers’ knock back work https://t.co/mn6aJ6qoKs https://t.co/gRk9UWkmP1 has a go at the Tele's front page attacks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["when things are good in Qld resources industry, then Qld's in good shape," 
https://t.co/jL1VdAhWqL um actually:… https://t.co/3pvDNIbBoG]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>