<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Another shot from https://t.co/PO8pcGSKp2 #auspol https://t.co/3hRcwZxYoa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the https://t.co/PO8pcGSKp2 website someone has been suspended in PMO for linking to indirectly #auspol https://t.co/OKgJUIMjSY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pauline Hanson has put this out on Peter Georgiou's behalf. I want to see him, with Pauline, on camera, with today'… https://t.co/oekILLD4CU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["They're genuine refugees" - says, get this, Scott Morrison. Relevant to @oliverlaughland great column #auspol… https://t.co/oS4xjUXCZD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@belinda_merhab sorry Belinda, thanks for pointing this out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Oz is running w Hanson getting "choice" of new WA senator, even tho it will be forced by court ordered recount… https://t.co/dUt08zKriw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump will either screw us on the number of refugees we take, or some other demand, but this won't end well for them https://t.co/9uSn5sXVkD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jason_a_w @kloussikian in it he says he hates unpaid internships, but says IA ppl don't make living wage &amp; will train "citizen journalists"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FULL REPORT: Culleton culled &amp; Hanson welcomes his brother in law, hoping he'll stick w One Nation #auspol #auslaw https://t.co/3S5N5Mpj51]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkDiStef he was joking "I'll try to get in Senate, tell em I'm Paul Karp". I said "you're way better dressed. I need some powder blue"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulkidd volunteering doesn't create an employment relationship. As long as it's not a fiction (eg if someone took a salary) hard to stop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulkidd hmm OK will check it out. You're right, I don't know special legislative regime for political staffers well enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulkidd but also, even if not technically eligible, someone else could take the contract and Culleton could "volunteer"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulkidd don't see why not bankruptcy doesn't stop you working ever again...will check though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rod Culleton was not eligible to stand and not validly elected, high court rules #auspol #auslaw https://t.co/3S5N5Mpj51]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ironically, Culleton losing this case is BETTER for him bc his brother in law likely to fill seat. If he'd LOST One Nation wld've #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JacquelineMaley it's silly isn't it that one can't say "brash" but one can use universally understood euphemisms for same?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Big personality': Australian PM puts brave face on phone call with Trump #auspol https://t.co/61UAz4CFpw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judgment says in fact and in law Culleton was convicted facing sentence regardless of later annulment #auspol #auslaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This means regardless of Culleton's bankruptcy hearing he is gone, out, ex senator do not pass go do not collect $200. #auspol #auslaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#breaking High court: there is a vacancy, Culleton WAS INELIGIBLE at election time. Willbe recount of ballot papers to fill. #auspol #auslaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull: If ppl leak what was in a conversation, that is very disappointing. Trump gave me commitment, confirmed several times #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull thanking Donald Trump for sticking by commitment. "I'm quoting his spokesman saying it's cordial - I'm saying it was frank" #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrickkeneally not before deporting all adherents of a certain minority religion there...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull handled both those interviews very well. Dealt a shit hand, cage fighting with a pissed US pres, still swinging #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull: "I've enjoyed my dealings with president Trump, we've had very frank, very forthright discussions" #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*Literally* a couple of hours ago it was confirmed by embassy. It was *literally* the president who called it a dumb deal #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull: I'm very disappointed about the leak in Washington of what purports to be details of the call. Pres DID NOT hang up on me #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull: It's been confirmed by spokesman, it's been confirmed by his embassy. We expect deal to continue, commitment's been made #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm pretty sure Russia selling Alaska was the worst deal, not the US-Australia refugee resettlement deal #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull quoting US embassy staff in Australia at 1:15pm Canberra time may just get them sacked rather than keep the deal...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull: it's not a deal he would have done, or wld regard as a good deal. But: question is will he commit to honour it, and he has #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very persuasive...You got him across the line? Ahhhh...he's called it a dumb deal on Twitter in the last hour! Much persuasion! #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember when Rudd let a journo listen in to him humiliating Bush on the G8? Fun times. #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God isounds like Turnbull actually stood up to Trump. What a hero. Shame about the refugee deal. Maybe we should just take em, hey? #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulkidd @dannolan yeah we're taking them, controversy is whether they are explicitly linked. Guess we'll find out if we reject them now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Joe Hockey managed to get tickets for Pauline Hanson to attend the inauguration, I think his diplomacy skills are up to this #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somewhere Pauline Hanson is ringing the PMO to offer help reaching out to Trump thru that economist who works for Malcolm Roberts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I remember when ANZUS was just another daring deal. We dared to dream...And I hope that President Trump finds it in his heart to say yes."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Turnbull going to say?!? "Well, when President Trump studies this so-called dumb deal, he will find much to commend it!" #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One Nation are being helpful to Turnbull: "I told you so" #auspol https://t.co/VtKpYFLSWJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He can't successfully book a Bruce Springsteen &amp; the E Street band tribute act, but boy can he shred a refugee deal in under 2 weeks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@liamvhogan he's so avuncular though!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The PMO be studying this Tweet harder than a lovelorn 16yo studying a text after a roller-coaster date https://t.co/ATy2XHZZMK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkDiStef yeah, I was like, hanging shit on the journo when it's obviously a real ambivalence in Washington, that will end well!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scott Ryan says #ausunions members don't have control on donations. (1) they do, thru union elections. (2) what about shareholders? #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull: "I don't belong to anybody". Is that the same as nobody's man? #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah we've got round to donations all the same. Turnbull: "I put my money - my after tax money - where my mouth is". #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull: "I received the assurances I did from the president himself, confirmed by WH spokesman." ALSO THEY GAVE ME A WEDGIE #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the plus side for Turnbull, all the focus is on whether Trump grouched at him not giving $1.75m to the Liberal party #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wouldn't discuss publicly a conversation in which a person was really mean to me and hung up first either #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dougalrobinson like "no plans"... "my intention" can change at ANY TIME.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ACTU vice-president Sally McManus likely to be union body's first female secretary #auspol #ausunions https://t.co/P4TjiVtBXL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grhutchens bars close at midnight, that Kings X was trashy and shit even when people went there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grhutchens also Sydney's nightlife fell from a low height. It's not lockout's fault that you can't eat at 9:30 at most restaurants, that...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grhutchens I blame BOF. He was against a lockout and backed down. Baird trimmed it back. Would've been hard to backflip totally on though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So if Baird backed down on greyhound ban, &amp; Gladys undoes council amalgamation. Baird legacy boils down to privatisation &amp; infrastructure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labor claims Malcolm Turnbull's $1.75m donation 'bought' the election #auspol https://t.co/4qYDpykCaZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Malcolm Turnbull targeted by GetUp ad accusing Liberals of failing to oppose racism #auspol #18C https://t.co/5R2DYZ2qso]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull's strategy may not have been too bad...try to keep #NPC focused on ordinary folks, then reveal $1.75m donation on #abc730 #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull: we're proud we have non-discriminatory immigration program. I don't provide commentary on other countries' programs #auspol #730]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull says we have to "raise the standards of journalism", as if all unnamed sources including from @zdaniel are made up! #auspol #730]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joyce tells WA Liberals a One Nation preference deal risks feud with Nationals #auspol https://t.co/GqpL46gZ6E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From technology agnostic PM at #NPC at 1pm to clean coal true believer DPM at 6pm! #auspol https://t.co/lkWxhW2AUZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, that went well! #auspol #NPC https://t.co/7YsoA1FWDw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coalition's renewable energy target won't last forever, says Turnbull #auspol https://t.co/NCcrqD0ESx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull: "my donations to Liberals have been regular &amp; generous ... disclosed as per the law." HERE HAVE IT 6 MONTHS LATER #NPC #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull: "I would have no objection" to real time disclosure. Why don't you release yours?! #auspol #NPC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually, this seems to suggest businesses get a privileged place ahead of activist and union groups.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewtonMark yeah actually I think you're reading is correct and I've been too optimistic...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull says "we're putting people first" in passage about health/Medicare. Stealing Shorten election lines now. #auspol #NPC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good on Turnbull for recognising biz, activist groups and #ausunions are legitimate ways to collectivise #NPC… https://t.co/8agO4TWbw4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expenses released every month! Wait til next year to find out if I donated $1-2m to Liberal Party. #auspol #NPC https://t.co/zAcDsQepnM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull: Coming into politics after a lifetime of business, I immediately found the term “entitlements” very inappropriate. #auspol #NPC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull added this passage to his #NPC speech from the one media sent. Told to bulk it up? #auspol https://t.co/SXZ2g4BxpQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull: "W/out competitive biz tax rate Oz will be less able to attract investment." Can't be left behind, Oz jobs offshore #auspol #NPC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull: altho disappointed US withdrawn from TPP we continue to open up markets with India, Indonesia, EU and UK #auspol #NPC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(admittedly in defence of free trade, but still).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull: "banner of Australian first" is "false promise of subsidies and trade barriers" #npc #auspol. Scomo said Australia first first!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnbull: "We cannot retreat into the bleak dead end of protectionism... Political opportunists want us to turn inward" #npc #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We believe in creating opportunities, but we also believe in providing a helping hand." Turnbull boilerplate wet liberal #npc #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BobNew8 gift, paid for by TA. We won't know re travel to/from for about 6 months. But as he's sports minister, it wld be defs within rules.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I wanted you to be the first to know..." #auspol https://t.co/wtk4wa7XpK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HannahD15 oh fuck I had no idea! Sounds great! Can't wait!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jasemurphy it's in his portfolio though. It's not just a meeting, it is legit to watch the Aus Open final.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HannahD15 the only universal is stuff I want to do is a right, stuff other people want to do is a "nice to have".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HannahD15 people talking about anti-discrimination clause in Const Recognition as "one clause bill of rights" as if it's a bad thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HannahD15 rights discourse all over the place atm. Religious groups calling for enlarged right to freedom of religion in SSM debate. 18C.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hunt, the new sports minister, went to #AusOpen women's final courtesy of Tennis Australia. Great portfolio! https://t.co/eY1FfSIsnh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UPDATED: ACTU secretary Dave Oliver resigns and calls for 'renewal' at union body #auspol #ausunions https://t.co/1C34exoR9a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Culleton: I am a law abiding citizen I am not going to disrupt anything that might be happening (re whether will return on Feb 7) #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asked if he's going to office "no I have to go home now". Asked if he'll come back on Feb 7, says "yes unless court orders" not Sen #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asked why Gaegeler didn't find he was a Senator, Culleton notes "well he didn't say I wasn't either". This is actually correct #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Culleton basically arguing that absence of an order restoring his privileges as a Senator does not mean he isn't a Senator #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Culleton: I'm not in a state of denial, it's just nothing  has been decided #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Culleton has noted Gaegeler referred to him as senator. Incorrectly claims that means he is still one #auspol https://t.co/KvF54Yavud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Culleton says Gaegeler just didn't want to frustrate the full court case that's why he didn't make orders #auspol #auslaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Voters approve of free trade deals but oppose big business tax cuts, poll shows #auspol https://t.co/6McXp4j1R5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Culleton still currently in high court building. Not clear whether he will return to his parliament office as he said he intended to #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Culleton also told journos in high court he is going back to his (parliament) office this arvo. He still has the badge! #auspol #auslaw]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>