<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@laurburberry @TwoFeetMusic much love girlyâ¤â¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The next month is going to be my month.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No Ed Sheeran for meðŸ˜¿]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting acknowledged in class due to the extra hours you put in during the week .. is the best feeling ever. Just get me into a college!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MissClaireG HOW I FEEL EVERYDAY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel this is the leaving cert. https://t.co/5Q4S6uS6OI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a generation we need to stop letting people influence our decisions and our paths and trust yourself for once.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sitting in every weekend studying and watching sad movies by myself has just become my life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Irish oral Monday and safe to say I can't even read the poetry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The script definitely have the best music videos.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@louiseashex the addiction is so real! Hahah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@louiseashex my parents tried to take me off it for a day I lasted less than an hour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My problem can't go a day without at least 4 cups... https://t.co/MVl3JUt1w6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leaving Certificate project maths is the most stupidest thing they've ever introduced...please relook at the syllabus and consider students.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like I'm hitting the dam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd love a rose gold princess ring ðŸ’•ðŸ˜¿ðŸ’“ðŸ’—ðŸ’˜ðŸ’ž]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@riasmyth_ well darcey dresses up and loves every moment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@riasmyth_ for Halloween though!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@riasmyth_ hey darcey loves her jumper!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting an A2 in English made my day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonyposnanski @realDonaldTrump as usual he contradicts himself!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grace4usall @davidmackau no lies there you can quiet clearly see lots of space.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidmackau the real question, how did he become president then?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I dislike VP Pence more than Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just want to sleep for a few hours and dance. Letting everything around me disintegrate for that amount of time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Migraine has been three days long and I know this ones not lifting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@meganlewislike trump has a lot of say in this world as America is a super power! It will have a lot of effect in the economy!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starbucks are the best they went out to get me soya milk because they had none #starbucksfam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Literally best part of my evening was ringing two people that just are my loves!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurenBateson if I even make it that far #stressedout]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm literally falling to pieces , not even caffeine is helping me what do I do?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing cheers you up like @MissClaireG â¤â¤ https://t.co/1VClBkrquY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#GourmetCoffeeDay https://t.co/KSPw1UlUkG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you go on school trip you really realise how alone you really are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lost my streak because he seen me three times.... @hchris801 https://t.co/zQnS80oBij]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I'm crying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know it bad when your nearly crying in prep.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woke up and thought it was Friday... it's only Tuesday:)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Way to stressed out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm in love with benedict cumberbatch and the director &amp; writer of Sherlock. If that was the end what a way to end it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[inthestyleuk's photo https://t.co/SUi4bEy0z6 OH MY GOD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump you speak like you've completed these tasks when you haven't even been inaugurated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Literally in no way ready for the mocks and leaving :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The xx's new album is so damn good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's official I just need to get to college now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm in love with Leeds already! https://t.co/PhFXQRNoI6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rjohnston_23 thank you!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[School currently make me feel like this : https://t.co/zN2FT7Cfqt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Literally so grateful right now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dublin bus get your shit together please the 75 has been on the board for 20mins saying it'll be here in 4mins.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiting for the result of your audition is killing and its only been 1 day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@riasmyth_ @JamieGuildea yes that what I mean I want them to live in the wild and not let them get killed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamieGuildea @riasmyth_ care about the animals forever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited for Leeds this week more amazing dance classes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just auditioning with people who actually love dance and have the same drive honestly makes me feel at home.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well today just made me want to go to college now not next September !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People complaining about freeing the whales when in fact they kill and eat other animals as there diet. Think of all the animals please!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well done me bought a load of new ballet stuff , vs underwear , sweater and hair stuff and I can still look at my card and not freak.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump having Russian hackers helping him win the election hmmmmmmm help from Putin ?????? #trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JBohan_11 nah don't think so..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a day https://t.co/PhSRHLZYk1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bet you never thought of that. https://t.co/hcdK8FEKaa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm about to sleeeep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm starting to get more and more nervous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Literally Ed making me cry already]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamieGuildea fair play I got none.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NathanReynolds fat chance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NathanReynolds what would u do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be quite honest I hate going on nights out recently.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thing I've really learnt in life so far:
1) never ever ever forget
2) only sometimes forgive
3) people are not who they seem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't miss me to much :))))))))) @NathanReynolds https://t.co/nDEDmALbtf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toohungry_2care THANK YOUâ¤â¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone complaining about homework when I've just given up because my college audition is Saturday... #itsallornothing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stephenreilly29 worse then pulling teeth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@riasmyth_ oh so I know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@riasmyth_ whooooo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Evan13_ MERRY CHRISTMAS #TOES https://t.co/XDbOIx5uB5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goals or what https://t.co/KhdlmxGK9Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much homework &amp; study ... so little time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#howmanytearsmustyoucry?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bullhorris SHOW ME]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['True love is letting you win in 8ball' @NathanReynolds let's me lose every time. https://t.co/Ak4RZlnCKz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Evan13_ and for paying in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NathanReynolds your the same https://t.co/oYlD0VXZJ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Danojones1998 happy new year ðŸ–¤â¤ðŸ–¤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy New Year from @MissClaireG ! #puking #NYE2017 https://t.co/3WxKUmjZDB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well yeah https://t.co/7wF6l21hMV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy god I'm 19 this year and next year I'm 20 wtf. Slow down please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well I'm angry still.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LaurenBateson sorry x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight was the worst night hahaha best part of the night was a croissant and coffee and rice cakes and Nathan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beaa_p thanks girlyðŸ’˜ðŸ’˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone know how much a tragus piercing is in drogheda??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taught us a lot of life lessons. Hopefully 2017 can continue to do so. 2017 is a big year so let's hope it goes to plan! Good luck &amp; love x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To all the beautiful countries I've visited , to my amazing dance teachers and family and wishing us all luck in 2017. All in all 2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well to conclude 2016 I want to thank everyone who has been in my life be it for short or kind periods. You've changed me for the best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SO to blighe for recommending shooter and ruining my mocks and leaving very.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I put myself in such a bad mood.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staying in is becoming more attractive then going out recently. #canistayinNYE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Evan13_ I'm in need of this]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>