<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Horribly tragic https://t.co/DEGhCCPfIR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, that's a first. Trudeau 1; fox 0 https://t.co/TLAHPJpnkV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because trump wouldn't give him a job? https://t.co/kkTYwDrGp5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Checkout article @guardian on what Trump is eating. Nutritionists: what does that do to your judgement?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To all #journalists: suggestion - do not cover Trump's tweets. They are not news. Do not attend WH briefings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Alternative facts' is not #publicrelations. It is lies. A real PR person does not present 'alternative facts' on behalf of his/her client]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyNewsAust Your two hosts think they're amusing. They are not. And woman yesterday dressed inappropriately for news anchor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricLiptonNYT @Reuters seems it has been confirmed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, since most of 9-11 hijackers were from Saudi Arabia, is SA on the list? https://t.co/X58ILN4IbR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would she have been turned away at the border of NY? https://t.co/fr7ln0OnSa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a good thing #mediaasopposition https://t.co/snvXsYPWlU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such a brilliant actor. He'll be missed https://t.co/zBOphPxYwn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jaklacroix @dailytelegraph it isn't]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US media must act as #oppositionparty. It's not a parliamentary system with opposition. It is media's job to keep #Republicans honest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scary https://t.co/O6eyoWF2Xl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More 'alternative facts' https://t.co/fFFhr6048f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She is a horrible human being https://t.co/6fbWvs5qkt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[News media have a lot to answer for in terms of not fact checking Trump. Keeping @KellyannePolls on regularly does… https://t.co/v2G8aQcoGn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scary - as it will mean removing facts or worse, not releasing them at all https://t.co/0mM89YV3Yz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things just keep getting weirder. All the more reason for journalists to do their jobs - which sadly they didn't do… https://t.co/F4wy4VRDU6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@akarl_smith @businessinsider with alternative facts?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@enews does anyone really care?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[where is the proof! https://t.co/MAgFmLgVLp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stephenfry It is indeed Australia Day. Eat a sausage, drink a beer and wear thongs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scientist whose miracle made a paraplegic walk again named Australian of the Year https://t.co/qXFGh7NyAk via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How quickly they caved https://t.co/LtSU4us54Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where did this concept of #alternativefacts come from? An alternative reality?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@strawberrynet:January 14 – &amp; still order. I ordered December 23. That is 3 weeks, not 3-7 days or even 2 weeks. 😒absolutely appalling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honestly, when did America become less about ethics &amp; morality &amp; more about 'who gives a f***?"? https://t.co/Qm3pPrAhM0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blahblahellis Actually saw one story..&amp; no celebs have left]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Rubio will do nothing to make Republicans angry with him or break ranks https://t.co/CrIKWIr7iw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If she's focussed on women's health, where is her public stand on #PlannedParenthood? https://t.co/yD3ojEnSkJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not a shock for Hungary https://t.co/rBUzvSOmWN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good. I think there are other MPs who have rotted the system who should also go https://t.co/snnRVeL55I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1621588044. Got some bull**** about 3-7 days shipping - more than 3 weeks now. Poor customer service. Very angry https://t.co/LdfqXaoNQF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not happy with @Strawberrynet. Ordered Dec 23..they said 3-7 days, poss. 14 - still have not received it. Not happy with customer service😒]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN Does this mean her PhD will be revoked?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dangillmor Because everyone thinks their question is smartest &amp; they'll get the story. But, you are right - with PEOTUS rules have changed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure if @BuzzFeed story is true - need to see facts &amp; sources - but their right to publish is inalienable. But don't present it as news]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffreyGoldberg Many people have asked themselves the same thing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smh She should go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not a shock. Seems several #Fox men have thought it was OK to behave this way https://t.co/2F9JKmaE7u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My son Jordan King-Lacroix (@jaklacroix) published: https://t.co/aErrZh7AB0 &amp; here https://t.co/8z7tnhNlBq and here https://t.co/Vo3DiqbvxC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy sh*t! https://t.co/xuwzI4mMdy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@THR And with good reason - not as intellectual and gripping as usual]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HuffingtonPost and yet US claims to separate church &amp; state. Not a Christian country, eh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBSNews Thin skinned and childish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HiddenFigures is a fantastic film. Moving &amp; uplifting. See it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@usnews this sucks. not really news &amp; all you want is $. If you tweet something, there should be info]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sunriseon7 3 is hardly an Aussie invasion, but nice that they've been nominated https://t.co/ICnxFdMHBg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brothers from different mothers.... https://t.co/VMgv5LSlkD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inappropriate &amp; must be changed https://t.co/u6JldJfAsA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jayrosen_nyu @MeetThePress which they seem to do on regular basis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating in it interpretation of the constitution &amp; whether the framers wanted to include the president w/regard… https://t.co/L3yLCV8hwC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TMZ mistake in your story - it's her second child]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yup - what US media is doing re Trump https://t.co/hbwSqorEu3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there one honest politician left in Aus? One person who does not take advantage of the taxpayers, on either side? https://t.co/0zv43EG2wb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy sh*t! You'd think if they're getting paid this much, they could at least do their job - challenge Trump on lie… https://t.co/SF8zGCvbYB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricLiptonNYT  you are right. One might question journalists' ability to do job in general. Asnwer: Stop reporting everything Trump tweets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While I'm a great believer in whistleblowing, I'm not certain Assange is telling the truth &amp; what agenda suits him https://t.co/utnOzXK0F3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This, as well as 'in God we trust' and 'God bless America' proves US is truly a Christian country. https://t.co/EqqgPZCT4c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry, folks, this is astonishing &amp; not a little bit scary https://t.co/tyheUVS13k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@megynkelly  not per se a Fox 'star' but rather a woman who presented on Fox. Now she will present on NBC. https://t.co/mSMrqDf72K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent. People have spoken. Keep an eye on this to ensure they don't sneak another one past https://t.co/QmLGTNtBQa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just an excuse to charge us more money. This is truly not necessary https://t.co/veL7dPsAsS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@voguemagazine hardly a business leader. She's no Bill Gates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This can't be a good thing.. https://t.co/lo6FQrQMIv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keithboykin Not a shocker. So they can get tax cuts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was OK. Not brilliant, too many things going up left unfinished
https://t.co/brWK71XCUX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mashable Artists are supposed to sing, not lip sync. No sympathy for her]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jayrosen_nyu Agreed remarkable. All the more reason for journalists to do best job possible in demonstrating diff between truth &amp; lies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricLiptonNYT continue doing the excellent reporting job you are doing. 4th estate is only true counter to Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yet another reason not to go into the ocean, where there are things waiting for kill you https://t.co/XRcDAPokE8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Except it wasn't the UK, just the PM. Rest of tories don't agree with her https://t.co/79U2RnChv5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the f*** is wrong with people? https://t.co/e3AukMy2Sl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israel is a Jewish state &amp; democratic. How can @JohnKerry make this comment when US is Christian &amp; allegedly democratic? Same for #UK gov't]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@guardiannews Because Australia is 20 years behind the rest of the world on this issue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JohnKerry says Israel can either be Jewish or democratic, not both. What the hell does that mean? As if US was not Christian....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HLNTV @RobinMeade woman doing #MorningExpress should learn to speak - Uluru requires appropriate pronunciation &amp; sacred indigenous place]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN what was the original budget? maybe stick to that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jray05 @CJR clearly he can swim and pitch at the same time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCBreaking why is this news? Aren't they both owned by Murdoch?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBSNews @CBSThisMorning Not a great interview. Hardly worth the time. He said nothing and avoided questions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN based on what proof? Trump's say-so?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it appropriate for US journalists to cover Trump's tweets? Not much depth in 140 characters - let him hold a news conference #journalism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US journalists should rethink how they covered primaries &amp; campaign. Need to re-assess what their job is. &amp; many TV types not really journos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doesn't the US currently have a sitting president who manages diplomatic affairs? Why is preselect making policy, doing deals?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is an inappropriate question to ask or discuss. &amp; Trump's daughter &amp; son-in-law are Jewish, are u ready to ask… https://t.co/ydyq6GBJKP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disrespectful that #bobdylan can't find the wherewithal to attend #NobelPrize ceremony https://t.co/Wj4nfNfDDt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyNewsAust @IndustrySuper so what to do about it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wonkette @EvanHurst it really sucked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this making anti-Semitism OK? https://t.co/ynPYItx8UD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would love to know #jenniferlawrence 's make-up for recent #passengers premieres.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[married to mitch mcconnell. just sayin' https://t.co/Uq7hzeDtxc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DRUDGE_REPORT she's just against romney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is @CNN giving so much time to #nigelfarage? Why think a Brit can answer q's about what Trump can deliver? Too much time for this guy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@people Stop promoting this like it's the new normal. People feel badly about their bodies for many reasons including ageism. Don't feed it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Horrifying https://t.co/Nqixadi3we]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[not sure about this https://t.co/Q97UC4No8m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Qantas Seems it finally took off to London-delayed 4 hours. He'll be Oxford by 6p instead of 1p - at least it's a day before the ceremony.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>