<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Bearing in mind that America has been at war 93% of the time: 222 out of 239 years since 1776.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is time that our politicians re-evaluate what future contributions it is reasonable for us to make in respect of this alliance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Considering that the Coalition government in Australia  have led us into three wars, contrary to International Law and U.N. resolutions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[or contrary to our national security interests, he should be held accountable for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The quid pro quo must be watched, and if Turnbull gives away something that is vital to Australia's national interests,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What will it be? Sending our young men and women into a Syrian or other conflict?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Trump gets Turnbull out of a political jam, then he will expect something from Turnbull (Australia) in return.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is a transaction President. He does and expects others to do deals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The really serious issue here, is what is the quid pro quo?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a lot of talk in Australia about Trump yelling at Turnbull (or Mr. Tumble). My view is "who cares".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sea surface temperatures on the edge of the ice are also running well above normal in many places, further inhibiting sea ice growth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Compounding the warm air is warm water.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[said Jennifer Francis, a climate scientist at Rutgers University who studies the Arctic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The ridiculously warm temperatures in the Arctic during October and November this year are off the charts over our 68 years of measurements]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In other words, it was so warm in the Arctic that despite the lack of sunlight, sea ice actually disappeared.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[further slowing Arctic sea ice growth and even turning it around for a few days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The oddness continued into November. A large area of the Arctic saw temperatures as much as 36°F above normal,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the end of the month, the Arctic was missing a chunk of ice the size of the eastern U.S.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Temperatures stayed stuck in their September range, pausing sea ice growth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The latest twist in the Arctic sea ice saga began in mid-October.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I've never seen anything like it this last year and half," Mark Serreze, director of the National Snow and Ice Data Center, said.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[what's happening in the Arctic right now stands out for just how outlandish it is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the hottest year on record set three years in a row, global coral bleaching entering a third year — the norm,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even in an age where climate change is making outliers — lowest maximum sea ice extent set two years in a row,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This follows the previous winter, when temperatures saw a huge December spike.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intense warmth in both the air and oceans is driving the mini-meltdown at a time when Arctic sea ice should be rapidly growing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sea ice growth slowed to a crawl and even started shrinking for a bit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But in the depths of the polar night, a strange thing started to happen in mid-October.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Usually that serves as a cue for sea ice to spread its frozen tentacles across the Arctic Ocean.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sun set on the North Pole months ago, not to rise again until spring.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i.e. as much as 30°C or 54°F warmer than in 1979-2000.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[temperatures over much of the Arctic Ocean were at the top end of the scale that day,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While the Arctic as a whole was as much as 3.34°C or 6.01°F warmer than in 1979-2000 on December 22, 2016,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Within the Arctic, the Arctic Ocean is warming most rapidly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To some degree what IS happening in the Arctic is driving global warming over the whole world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strange things are happening in the Arctic now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And a big portion of it came from just five glaciers, about which scientists now have more cause to worry than ever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[suggests that the Greenland ice sheet lost a whopping 1 trillion tonnes of ice between the years 2011 and 2014 alone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A satellite study, published recently in the journal Geophysical Research Letters,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More than 40 percent melted last year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This suggests more and more of the sea ice is melting every year. The Greenland ice sheet continues its dramatic melting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By contrast, in the 1980s, about 20 percent of the sea ice was old and about 45 percent had formed that year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[said Kit Kovacs, a senior scientist at the Norwegian Polar Institute.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[with only 3 percent of the ice considered old, meaning it had been around for more than four years,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the day when ice reached its maximum in 2015, 70 percent had formed in the previous year,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[was the lowest since 1979, when record keeping began.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In addition, the sea ice extent during the summer months (the Sun doesn't shine there in the winter)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The average air temperature above Arctic land represents a 5.4-degree-F (3 degrees C) increase from the average air temperatures in 1900.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Arctic is getting warmer wetter and weirder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If and when this happens, the West Antarctic ice sheet would also likely to show irreversible melting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once global warming pushes the melting process past that line, it begins to perpetuate itself."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prof. Sergei Kirpotin, a botanist at Russia's Tomsk State University, says: "There's a critical barrier...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The West Siberian bog is estimated to contain 70 billion tonnes of CO2.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[triggering the release of methane, a greenhouse gas twenty times more powerful than CO2, from thick layers of thawing peat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As the Arctic continue to warm, melting permafrost in the boreal forests and further north in the Arctic tundra is now starting to melt,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We know this is due to climate change (human-induced)."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[in a press briefing at the annual meeting of the American Geophysical Union.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[said Rick Spinrad, the chief scientific officer a the National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration (NOAA),]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Warming is happening more than twice as fast in the Arctic than anywhere else in the world,"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And more than half of the Greenland ice sheet melted in 2015.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and sea ice extent was at an all-time low since record keeping began in 1979.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2015 was the warmest on record for the Arctic (until 2016 came along which blew all previous records away)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Arctic is warming at an unprecedented rate, new research suggests.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nowhere can the effects of global warming be more acutely felt than in the Arctic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Either way, what they say should be dismissed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[is either stupid, or deliberately arguing the contrary view for reasons of their own.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone who says that such a powerful correlation does not so strongly suggest causality to the point that it cannot be credibly denied]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This increase in CO2 has already caused a substantial rise in temperature.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and can be well accounted for based on the simple premise that about 60 percent of fossil-fuel emissions stay in the air.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This recent relentless rise in CO2 shows a remarkably constant relationship with fossil-fuel burning,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 2013, CO2 levels surpassed 400 ppm for the first time in recorded history.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During ice ages, CO2 levels were around 200 parts per million (ppm), and during the warmer interglacial periods, they hovered around 280 ppm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Levels of carbon dioxide (CO2) in the atmosphere are higher than they have been at any time in the past 400,000 years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We have dramatically increased the level of carbon dioxide in the atmosphere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and methane levels have increased 148 percent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Since the Industrial Revolution began in about 1750, carbon dioxide levels have increased nearly 38 percent as of 2009]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[mostly by burning fossil fuels, but also from cutting down carbon-absorbing forests.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[humans have been artificially raising the concentration of greenhouse gases in the atmosphere at an ever-increasing rate,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What has scientists concerned now is that over the past 250 years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Temperatures are certain to go up further.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and the rate of temperature increase has nearly doubled in the last 50 years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The global average surface temperature rose 0.6 to 0.9 degrees Celsius (1.1 to 1.6° F) between 1906 and 2005,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[primarily due to the greenhouse gases released as people burn fossil fuels.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global warming is the unusually rapid increase in Earth’s average surface temperature over the past century]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Answering these questions is perhaps the most significant scientific challenge of our time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much more will the Earth warm? How will Earth respond?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can we be certain that human-released greenhouse gases are causing the warming?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How does this warming compare to previous changes in Earth’s climate?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But in the past century, another force has started to influence Earth’s climate: humanity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[as the atmosphere or surface changed, or when the Sun’s energy varied.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Climate has changed when the planet received more or less sunlight due to subtle shifts in its orbit,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Throughout its long history, Earth has warmed and cooled time and again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global warming. It is very serious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What they get is slogans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No wonder people turn away from traditional politics. After 30 years of stagnant wages and declining standards of living, they want change.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and I suspect it means as much as the one from their opponents: "jobs and growth", and that is precisely nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[but alas, we have an ALP which has exchanged its high Labor traditions for populist slogans, like "jobs, jobs, jobs" whatever that means,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we had a Labor opposition worth having, it would oppose committing young Australians to fight in such wars of Imperialism,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Middle East is a quagmire where great powers are vying for control of oil and gas reserves]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>