<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@WhiplashUnited I noticed earlier today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The immature child in me wants to point out this is my 6969th tweet. https://t.co/xObK7a8PEb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RedwingRider13 they're gonna lose someone in expansion. Plus I have wanted Trouba forever. My dream will not die]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RedwingRider13 maybe they'll trade us Trouba]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSportsJim good thing we assigned him to GR, traded him and kept Drew Miller instead......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSportsJim or actually Patrick Eaves]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@3rdShiftHockey don't make us send in the Cassowaries. Also Thor is Australian....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@3rdShiftHockey this will do wonders for American / Australian relations. I'm bringing the boot. https://t.co/lPrOieARQi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@3rdShiftHockey Helm has more hat tricks than Datsyuk. Elite. Also it's now officially on. Imma find you in October.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@3rdShiftHockey also frass is um, well look it up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@3rdShiftHockey as chief commander of the Downunder Darren Helm fan club I regret to inform you that you about to catch these hands]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@3rdShiftHockey are you sassing elite finisher Darren Helm on my TL?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@waratahjesus @Aussie7s that's awesome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nbauer10 I hope your day is can bottle too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnthonyRescan if only it were that easy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnthonyRescan do you need political asylum? https://t.co/7SoqJti1gh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dez_Walker unfortunately I think you are spot on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dez_Walker it's a sad state of affairs when it's come to that, but I hear ya.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dez_Walker this is not going to end well.  Stay safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dez_Walker disgusting. Why are their faces blurred out.......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dez_Walker another banner day for humanity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@3rdShiftHockey @DraftLiljegren when is Dan Cleary getting recalled. Need more veteran grit. Plus he has his own hockey school.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Friday morning Bondi https://t.co/QOlbCzqcx1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSportsJim @MGoFour great work on the Voltron reference. https://t.co/7Fyhkno3yD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This might be the best one.....gold https://t.co/wXTHdqcE5f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Twitter can you help? https://t.co/Ka68mcDHW4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Turnbull gets the bill for his phone call with Trump https://t.co/8tSfSkha9z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@puckinbourbon they were doing that beforehand. But yay we are relevant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shot in the back. I'm lost for words. https://t.co/iKVJdjdmmO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnRBielski @StephaliciousD we would run out of water pretty quickly. Plus our kangaroo transport network is already stretched to capacity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephaliciousD @JohnRBielski as long as you bring Wawa mac n cheese and a Jims cheesesteak with cheese wiz we good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnRBielski @StephaliciousD ps. bring Wawa &amp; Jims. Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnRBielski @StephaliciousD we cannot take in that many people seeking political asylum.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephaliciousD @JohnRBielski about that....I wouldn't say everyone. Maybe don't turn up on a boat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KingJakeCSGO are you going to answer me or just pretend like this never happened?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickPfitzner it's where I'm headed, that and the Bingham Cup. There are a number of gay pro rugby players as well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KingJakeCSGO you haven't really answered my question. I know plenty of gay hockey fans so you're cleary misguided.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KingJakeCSGO @_MAF29 way to stereotype you muppet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So by your logic because hockey is a contact sport there can't be gay players or fans? https://t.co/NIL85EwTRl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should come down under mate. @nbauer10 @SamBauer11 https://t.co/UcnXOd9Xn7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Red_Wings_Vines it's likely the Wings will pick top 3 at this rate though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Red_Wings_Vines did you take into account Vegas having the same odds as the Wings?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DBozz71 @EkbladJesus it's February 1st here. Count it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DBozz71 @EkbladJesus Riley Sheahan per go.....nevermind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSportsJim @SamBauer11 @nbauer10 I fit your criteria. I will also do a segment on the importance of Sunday Lamb Roast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamBauer11 @TheSportsJim @nbauer10 can we be foreign correspondents?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please trade him to Detroit. Ok thanks. https://t.co/PKu4AM8qQ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSportsJim Wings will be top 3 at this rate. Nolan Patrick, Nico Hischier, Timothy Liljegren are named to get familiar with]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSportsJim it gets a bit messy outside of the top 2-3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lottery Division Update: Wings climb to 3rd outright with that loss. Coyotes can close gap today with a win. https://t.co/HciFMl1Ion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSportsJim focus your energy on who the Wings will draft in the top 3. It's much easier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So has a team ever given up 3 SHG in one game?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here comes thy false hope I've grown so accustomed too. But nice work Jensen on 1st NHL goal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dodgers52 @Isaac_Smith91 clearly; they swept the series IIRC. Kershaw pitched the Sat night game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dodgers52 @Isaac_Smith91 yeah I was there. Great time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dodgers52 @JPhoenix7 @Chelle0219 this is the greatest subtle tank in the history of sports.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Way to keep that trade value up Tats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Isaac_Smith91 I mean there have to be at least 8-10 fans in Australia. I bet we could get that to like 15.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Way to boost your international audience https://t.co/L0W95EcGNm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DraftLiljegren it's all about draft position so yeah.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flyers what even are you doing? 6 SOG mid way through 3rd. Wow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah let's protect Coreau......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@askrohan another point for spare part Mantha as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Washed up Zetterberg scores again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlakeEMeakin this one seems apt. https://t.co/YQR4SJWFZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JPhoenix7 that was the least threatening 5 on 3 in the history of hockey.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wingedwheeler28 Not at the Joe however as bad as they are I refuse to boo my team.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is HSJ still pulling for the Wings to protect Coreau?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Isaac_Smith91 Equal worstest team and even that's debatable given how the Wings are performing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Isaac_Smith91 Small victories?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Wings are nothing if not consistent early in games.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DimitriA26 Oh look. An Athanasiou sitting and watching the game. Where have I seen this before......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SavedByLeBell26 Low key go Devils. Want to jump then in Lottery Standings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#DRWFirstGoal Kyle Quincey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WingsPride All good mate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WingsPride See my other response. I agree.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WingsPride Tazers aren't without their own issues. There have been deaths attributed to them. It's a tricky subject.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WingsPride Have neutralised the situation. 2/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WingsPride Typically not which circles back to the root of the issue. Also given a few very public deaths at the h… https://t.co/iTZCg1MwsM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WingsPride Our cops use them here and they tend to, on average kill less people than US cops with guns. I'll stop… https://t.co/FtyFs8nznC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WingsPride It was a much more generalised comment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WingsPride Of course, why have tazers when you can use hand guns instead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WingsPride So are they gonna tazer you as well?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WingsPride I'm assuming they sprayed you in your eyes. Should have requested they just spray your feet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nbauer10 @LGhail @JimMWeber @SamBauer11 It's bonza]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSportsJim Sure. Have at it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSportsJim Every. Sunday.*

*Unless we are overseas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSportsJim You will not defile this with tomato sauce. https://t.co/J1imZlDBLb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSportsJim Maaaate. Gonna hook you up a Sunday Lamb Roast when you come downunder. Do one every week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nbauer10 May be worth doing it now since they last 2 years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nbauer10 As someone said to me yesterday. "You're white, you should be fine"........I did read we may have to do p… https://t.co/NmPN5bf87u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nbauer10 I will forge the ground in September / October for you. I need to renew my ESTA though. Yay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamBauer11 @TheSportsJim @nbauer10 Lucky to survive tbh. I remember all those Government ads about them years ago… https://t.co/MD2VhRb4T8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSportsJim @nbauer10 @SamBauer11 who wants to explain the terror that is Drop Bears to Jim? https://t.co/Qn99J5fX9G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSportsJim Do you like snakes? How about spiders as big as your hand? Nowhere is safe Jim, it's a constant battl… https://t.co/n4oLxClatm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSportsJim Thankfully no. They are quick across the ground though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSportsJim They are not to be trifled with https://t.co/g3YuDwdPpg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSportsJim I'd be more concerned about Cassowaries]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSportsJim The government issues these to us at age 5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSportsJim The bar was very low.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>