<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatrickZircher Yeah you're right. It was luck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatrickZircher It's not the skill of the art, but the graphic simplification of an expression/emotion + the accompanying words. Shrug.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PatrickZircher Relatable emotion and empathy to connect with the audience in a scenario that is both familiar / identifiable with audience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nellucnhoj It's a play on Quite Frankly I believe, he lives somewhere in Glasgow I think? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RadFeenix Oh man, I'm sorry. I tweeted about this last night... hit the same thing D:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Animation AE Tip: Right Click frames &gt; Interpret Footage &gt; Main &gt; Assume this frame rate: Set to 24 Frames per second. (Rather than 30!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hennygoransson This turned out amazingly - great stylisation throughout, love it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sgtmus Enough sleep is such an umbrella term right now, I will nap though, maybe rise about midday and get back to it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sleep or colour more frames. Colour more frames or sleep. Probably not paint more backgrounds. Probably sleep?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ciaranlucas I dunno, I think he could at least handle an 'of'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Buttersphere @OldSwifty I'm told they'll see the light once the full animation is done. Not long til then :O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is seriously so gosh darn good https://t.co/c1UbmiZPOf -  #epic #working #soundtrack #undertale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OldSwifty Aside from all the distractions and giggles from my side of the room you mean? :DDD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just done colouring Arin frames 272 - 340 and compositing those into after effects, and Swifty has handed me 341 - 362 #animateagrump Phew.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@declanshalvey That's epic. Transformative and wonderfully done. Thanks for sharing :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricSmack This is lovely &lt;3 bwaaaaaahhhhh love the colours!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fish finger sandwich.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OldSwifty I thanked you in person for tweeting this but I realise I didn't on here! Thanks Swiftykins :3 So much fun working with you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hennygoransson envious of your colour tools there in toonage boomage - India is hogging her licence to animate.. soselfish. :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of @OldSwifty 's smear frames are truly terrifying. #animateagrump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ludolik @OldSwifty Haha yeah - he's gonna bust out a sweet sweet serenade solo... totes going to defeat that plant.. yup... defeat.. haha..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really want an #office #cat -  they could help in so many ways. https://t.co/yzYFAJKvcf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Current favourite google image search right now is '#cats typing at computer']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@moopdrea @OldSwifty Ohhhh, thank you! I'm Swift's support - I'm providing coloring, backgrounds, tea and cake. :3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A progress frame from @OldSwifty 's #animateagrump scene #spirals Hope all the other animators are doing okay, last… https://t.co/KVW3ePM2ml]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KuroUsagi_desu Looking great yo, I love the muted pastel colours you've gone for. :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Painting my favourite thing right now, a mossy tiled floor. I love mossy tiled floors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grump room I'm painting as a backdrop for @OldSwifty 's #animateagrump #animation https://t.co/0vlRC4CyD6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deathink Sweet work yo. Pink visor glow is a really great touch, liking the colour combo a lot. &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's @egoraptor 's #cutiesaturday so here's a sketch of the girl from North :) https://t.co/GRkEjSa3l4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just animated a sparkle, am I a princess now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does anyone know of some cool online resources for learning melodies? I've been using youtube vids. https://t.co/DjVBax7ehB via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/ZpZDze9nwx - Great podcast I was listening to earlier about working in collaborative teams - lot's of great advice and insight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jerzy @OldSwifty Great great podcast guys, really informative. Yeah, said it fine :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I liked a @YouTube video https://t.co/tdYppohEsy LIA Cast 173 - What You Add to the Team]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jerzy @OldSwifty @LeanIntoArt Oh wow, that's awesome! Not to worry my name is deceptive. I think it's like toy- with a g tagged on. :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I liked a @YouTube video https://t.co/HDiEbiZ6c4 His Theme (WARNING: SAD)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help support the Brain Research Trust, fund @TheSonsieBogle to run in April -  https://t.co/JMj1jYsEsp #charity #funding #london #marathon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@R0mbag @nellucnhoj I'm out of the loop on that, what did JonTron do that broke you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nellucnhoj @Treestumped I think with more creator owned funding pools, people are factoring in creators more into the equation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charactercube @tapas_app Yeah Kenneth - we've set up a store on big cartel, almost done linking accounts in order to accept payments.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OldSwifty That's great, lovely use of space. I love his cheeky smile / expression in the beginning. &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superb animation from @OldSwifty her character Jove from Girl and the Glim sneaking in some guitar jammin' https://t.co/BuZvoP5bWI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charactercube That's awesome dude!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As soon as I figure out how to get a #gif out of @Krita_Painting it's so on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New jump up Morning Jam 7 - Swift Love, Improvised jam on a little melody for @OldSwifty -  https://t.co/HH0uOLiDUZ via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's really cool to see the diversity being shown for #animateagrump Wow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OldSwifty @Jerzy I read the Pickles and Taft mini comic, they're so adorable together. Bwah &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[charliebowater's photo https://t.co/AOAD1h6D8b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[oldswifty's photo https://t.co/9PxZDkxxOm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FaithErinHicks Yeaahhh Colm Wilkinson as Valjean &lt;3 Such a tenderness to his quieter pieces - 10th anniversary features the original cast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FaithErinHicks Oh jeez, which version are you listening to? 10th anniversary version is my jam.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ComicPrintingUK 2019: Trump sounds like a Comic Title in the making]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oldswifty Can hunt and locate my imperfect fills in her frames from 40 yards. Somehow draws fingernails on the gloves of her animation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Morning Jam 6 - Swifty Intro: https://t.co/GqWqRjhi0d via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Treestumped @TheWarblazer Oh wow, this is the second color pass I've seen on this piece, it's giving me the itch... :D Lovely work!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had no idea that  #coloristappreciationday existed and stumbling upon at the end of it! New goal: make great work in time for next years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're most welcome @Jerzy :D https://t.co/fsG2rLq2N1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nathanfairbairn Stumbled here by related artists on twitter and realised I recognised and owned an issue of Lake of Fire. Your Colours &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using the paint bucket tool in #photoshop to #colour lineart #animation #frames be like - https://t.co/myvAvpYqlo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaulJayNicholso no worries Paul, stay awesome :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Zednek101 @OldSwifty @Krita_Painting Dude, India will be pleased to know you got the likeness :D i'm looking forward to seeing it too :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helping out @OldSwifty for #animateagrump by colouring her nifty lines in @Krita_Painting https://t.co/7DFy68ubOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Morning Jam vid up, watched a great video about art in #context from @1FantasticWeek - https://t.co/CRTcSDPZXB #morningjam #piano #music]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@magicianshouse @Donathin_Frye @ComicBookHour Thank you :3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, art sharing! well.. well I can show you some series over on our tapastic - https://t.co/fpzcvr667m #comicbookhour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@devanmusedesign you'll like this #comicbookhour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@devanmusedesign Thumbs up - I was given a stash of volumes 2-4 for christmas that I'm eagerly waiting to read. If you liked saga, i think]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Donathin_Frye @ComicBookHour My collaborator is @OldSwifty - her gorgeous lines, omgosh!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That looks phenomenal, gonna give this a read. Wow! https://t.co/CwvHfJ0HHT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Donathin_Frye @ComicBookHour Thanks dude! You're welcome to read the whole thing over on tapastic - https://t.co/117qXQOlRd #comicbookhour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@devanmusedesign saga is published by image, image have a looooot of great creator owned series. Black science is up there #ComicBookHour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ComicBookHour #comicbookhour webcomics are the way for indie creators to cut their teeth on the process of storytelling to a wide audience!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ComicBookHour Q1: I read a lot of indie comics published on the @tapas_app tapastic platform, great community over there. Lots of support.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ComicBookHour hey the name's Michael, I recently collaborated on the mini comic North. Aspiring colourist looking… https://t.co/3HfSg0f7AK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another attempt at the head and added some context for the figure. https://t.co/5HaN2eIV8I https://t.co/SpqeF9KOnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Progress so far, unsure about the head :S #lifedrawing #charcoal #willow https://t.co/7I5Umhwqsf https://t.co/wrn063lckq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 hour pose at The Lab #lifedrawing #session #willow #charcoal https://t.co/Y4jRtW04lJ https://t.co/iEC7U35gJr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Currently wrangling this - #shipping #physical #goods #learning https://t.co/HJQXlqWyPz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of my favourites. Glad I hadn't completely forgotten how to draw. Great getting back … https://t.co/X0d54BtJpd https://t.co/9pvGVQCs1o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gestures. Great getting back to #lifedrawing #willow #charcoal #dublin #evening https://t.co/j92c2wd0F2 https://t.co/IgQNNwU1Rr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great model tonight, lots of twist and character. #lifedrawing #willow #charcoal #dublin #… https://t.co/iO68k1Uynx https://t.co/Lp3RSZdbWz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bottom left is @oldswifty from across the room. Great getting back to #lifedrawing #willow… https://t.co/TEQGiuR6Ok https://t.co/YU044sNNcX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great getting back to #lifedrawing #willow #charcoal #dublin #evening https://t.co/kPBCC8Arym https://t.co/ozAwR2Uxf7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going at catch a bus to life #drawing, first time in over a month. #rusty https://t.co/cT5LYpoYrY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OldSwifty learned about thinking of your art and the #context in which it lives, so i'm tasked with going out to collect leaves. #staytuned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deezoid @ericxyz hnng.. no, thank you! sir! :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ericxyz @deezoid lovely storytelling heightened by the light / colour. Tasty &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raw #capture from the #webcam #footage above - edited #colour #balance below experiment fo… https://t.co/5qsTmh5p2u https://t.co/VOH6FiNG1i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New morning jam up on youtube - https://t.co/eRTt8U4ne7 -  #red #hues #piano #improvisation #morningjam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tommmoore Great admirer of your films Tomm, see you speak at Manchester Animation Festival, great stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Left Charlie in Scotland :O #cat #catsofinstagram #catstagram https://t.co/WMsNoes0DC https://t.co/GeGkui1Prf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doig &amp; Swift have been accepted onto the tipping feature over on @tapas_app It's a remarkable approach to supportin… https://t.co/j9ArVLul73]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The penguin, it will devour your soul. https://t.co/vl1vhD6QRb https://t.co/ldHRpbaR4l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bitmOO bringing things to life, isn't it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holding this feels awesome. #comic #north #print #comicprintinguk https://t.co/fgGCosTOv4 https://t.co/aClCLyU23m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Splashed some #colour on @oldswifty 's portrait of me. Colour &lt;3 https://t.co/FgCRainqh7 https://t.co/qpEqj6DZlS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Subtle gradients in the sky #color #study https://t.co/duKlUUX8pj https://t.co/JNdhFvXG6C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As visual artists we keep sketchbooks. What is the #musical equivalent of a #sketchbook? #tw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying to rewire my brain from thinking 'Does this look cool' to 'Does this look appropriate' while I'm artin'.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>