<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[At least we're back to calling it what it is: a ban. That's the only thing this tweet clarifies for me. https://t.co/P0llxmE4TS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An imagined rendition of the Bowling Green Massacre trial. @NewYorker https://t.co/RhMEPomlJ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the American people, an upside. https://t.co/TLGz5Xa9P3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Admin revoked all visas from the 7 affected countries without announcing it publicly. Let that sink in. https://t.co/uSoO6AdoFt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High stakes nail biter: Ruling is temporary. Administration could again block travelers if it wins a stay. https://t.co/s1OzEuwJMe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@D_ScottKerr Thanks. Meant @StateDept.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cooperating w/Arab partners (pretty much essential to dealing w/challenges in the region) just got harder. By a lot. https://t.co/AA0hREeHyC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What will the next Iraqi or Syrian interpreter say when his American colleagues ask him to risk his life? https://t.co/dlTm5W0Yl8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[90% of migrants to Europe now come through Libya to Italy. In 2016, over over 4.5K people drowned on the way. https://t.co/7aUlvstkmU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey Kellyanne, @State folks didn't "sign a petition." They filed a dissent memo. That IS discharging their duty. https://t.co/3XkPzNKg8s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@tcwittes has a thoughtful take on Tillerson's remarks at @State today. Worth reading the whole thread. https://t.co/vlVHsO1aL0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There’s a word for the sentiments underlying POTUS's order, and it’s not bravery. Read @BrookingsGov's @BillGalston: https://t.co/xRpAsCTXs3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bruce_katz @Bobby_McKenzie  Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're welcome China. https://t.co/nbQg1fHDaD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just to put a face (or voice, as the case may be) to the situation. https://t.co/CYIlKmX9nO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guess who else is affected by Trump's ban? White Helmets (Syrian volunteers), nominated for an Oscar. Can't attend. https://t.co/uKjFFRhUUG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of this information was and is available to the Trump administration. https://t.co/YM2CgaPhAv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I am American too." This just grabs you in the gut. https://t.co/o0JzrJj2c5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How hard do you have to try to mess up Holocaust Memorial Day and Black History Month?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's right. Plainly dangerous. https://t.co/XhkbJ30E1q https://t.co/UzE0RHfThD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The refugee ban makes it easier for organizations like ISIL to recruit. My thoughts: https://t.co/gqOZYFOA4T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The indirect consequences of Trump's #refugee ban are just as bad as those that are obvious. My thoughts: https://t.co/gqOZYFOA4T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cooperating w/Iraqis, which is pretty much essential to defeating ISIL, just got a lot harder: https://t.co/z3u4KrvDkf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whether or not its lawful -- and substantial evidence suggests its not -- the #refugee ban is counterproductive. https://t.co/gqOZYFOA4T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CajunAngela Cadence is pure Trump. A betrayal. Very weak!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AG firing does not bode well for: @StateDept dissenters, a legit election meddling probe, America.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I ask again, is this real life? https://t.co/qMQyf127fa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most disturbing thing about this? The Sessions connection. https://t.co/B0jxX2Hxpj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“For as long as I am the acting AG, the DOJ will not present arguments in defense of the executive order..." Amen. https://t.co/Q5aBXAlz6B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terrifying. And very much worth reading. https://t.co/Yr9bqQtGEw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just a reminder: Those diplomats took an oath -- not to a party or a president, but to the Constitution.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Administration warns diplomats unhappy with immigration moves to "get with the program" or "go." That bodes well. https://t.co/yHzknmKP8v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 separate background checks, 4 biometric security checks, 3 in-person interviews, 2 interagency security checks, to admit 1 #refugee.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This still matters, by the way. A lot. https://t.co/hn9qbNOCev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It begins: revolt at the @StateDept  over Trump's immigration ban: https://t.co/szE9eKNn7f @lawfareblog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most stunning tidbit from this piece? DHS Sec got his first full briefing on the ban as Trump was signing it. Geez. https://t.co/AIaOAyWOdd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How are ISIS sympathizers referring to Trump's travel blan? "Blessed."
https://t.co/tWtRfwCAut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This man was sent back to Jordan, which is not on the list of countries from which entry is banned. https://t.co/dkBEyuXtR1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd call this evidence of discriminatory intent. https://t.co/gHOBv7rmXu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amen @NormEisen: Arbitrary, discriminatory nature of the order is bad enough; if POTUS also considered payoffs to TrumpOrg, it’s much worse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moqtada al-Sadr: American nationals should leave Iraq, in retaliation for the travel curbs. https://t.co/LMnAErktHk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who said this would embolden the far fight in Europe? https://t.co/TDuAqbANAT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[French FM: "Terrorism knows no nationality. Discrimination is no response,"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[London Mayor: Ban is “shameful and cruel.” UK Foreign Secretary: "divisive and wrong."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merkel's spokesperson: she's convinced that the resolute fight against terror doesn't justify blanket suspicion on grounds of origin, belief]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And our relationships with allies, our national security, our standing in the world, and the lives of those most in… https://t.co/RBR6cxQCUn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heard at White House rally: There are so many things to protest, I just bought a white board. That way I'm all set for next weekend. Yep.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hmm, wonder why... https://t.co/nWeK2jNSr2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this real life? https://t.co/xYRM5gXjAM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tcwittes Talk about fake news...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Definitely. And @BrookingsInst's Rights &amp; Responsibilities series (re: Syrian refugees), which is a go-to:… https://t.co/8nalBmK3ZJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't go to law school, but I did go to high school. Feels like a good time to revisit this: https://t.co/ea467QLUhY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As police attempt to break up the protests outside Trump Hotel, the crowd chants: "Who do you serve?" https://t.co/qLlER4pk11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A few relevant, non-Alternative facts about the vetting process #refugees undergo before resettlent to the US. https://t.co/zllpfmoUAA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Merkel, unsurprisingly, comes out swinging against the EO (translation via @WSJ's Berlin correspondent @AntonWSJ): https://t.co/KZa1QbPsKQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the stunning incompetence - and malevolence - of POTUS's EO banning #refugees.
Read @benjaminwittes: https://t.co/y3rMNggAYH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well this feels relevant again. https://t.co/Q1KKAOffc4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When he said it, he meant it. https://t.co/fsMmjvm2sb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asylum and development policy are linked. Read @alexander_betts: https://t.co/1IG5A6Gp1k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best tidbit from this piece: "integration is like a bloody big motorway." Thank you Brits. https://t.co/KbdtWTekPA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JuddLegum's got a thing or two to say about today's epic news cycle. His tweetstorm is worth a gander.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile... https://t.co/Y2ewdyfQr4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Should a President hold himself to a lower standard than his own appointees?"  Watch @OfficeGovEthics head today: https://t.co/NSjNivXbLY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At @BrookingsInst, @OfficeGovEthics head says plan Trump laid out today "does not meet the standard" re conflicts https://t.co/NSjNivXbLY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Refugeecrisis outstrips capacity of natl govts to address it. Would #Tillerson engage local partners? https://t.co/xMDIhhC6ux @bruce_katz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The four questions members of the SFRC should ask Mr. Tillerson tomorrow: https://t.co/xMDIhhkvCZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've just discovered @NYTMinusContext. My world will never be the same.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remarkable turnaround from November 2015... https://t.co/T4UxlzYm9m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best tidbit from this piece? Russians responding to contact by a female air-traffic controller. “You have a nice voice, lady. Good evening.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. and Russian jets crowding the same airspace fighting parallel wars = an international incident waiting to happ… https://t.co/eoPbonSCV8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How @realDonaldTrump could move the US embassy to Jerusalem without setting off a disaster. @Martin_Indyk: https://t.co/qe9QAH87Jp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome to 2017. https://t.co/Segw4C8PQl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out @AnnaBNewby's useful round-up of views on 2016 and the year ahead. https://t.co/E4nwMtly6x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can the private sector play a role in addressing the #refugeecrisis? A few ideas: https://t.co/UvqWalmpoT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The returns on investing in #Syrian #refugee education are enormous, far-reaching, and long-lasting. https://t.co/UvqWalmpoT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Born #refugees. Read: https://t.co/cdqS86komp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who are the remaining 35%? https://t.co/IoRIUf1QSI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding refuge, seeking peace. #Syrians in Germany on the year that was: https://t.co/gXPUkYyaHw @bruce_katz @Bobby_McKenzie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well that could complicate things. Not least the effort to evacuate civilians still trapped there... https://t.co/sHD7KimpDv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sign of things to come? https://t.co/Jcwb6yARxt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We have not done enough. https://t.co/ILyIkXFerL @Bobby_McKenzie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For political reasons as well as humanitarian ones, assisting #SyrianRefugees *where they are* is imperative. How: https://t.co/UvqWal4O0j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think so. https://t.co/ujMR99k1iv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aiding #refugees who flee violence in #Syria = a substantial investment. Costs of doing otherwise are far higher. https://t.co/UvqWal4O0j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can he resolve it? Spoiler alert: with concessions to Russia. https://t.co/ElrZz1JxK1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing how much doing nothing can do, especially when it's we who do nothing. Wieseltier on #Aleppo: https://t.co/daNmn9NrFa @BrookingsInst]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We've got to help #Syrian #refugees where they are. That means increasing access to ed &amp; jobs in frontline states. https://t.co/UvqWal4O0j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Events in Aleppo remind us how impt it is that @realDonaldTrump not discontinue resettlement of #SyrianRefugees: https://t.co/UvqWalmpoT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What should the Trump admin do on behalf of Syrian refugees? Correct the record, to start. Few more ideas too: https://t.co/e1540bwH6A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What can the next admin do for Syrian refugees?@Bobby_McKenzie &amp; I have a few ideas: https://t.co/e1540bwH6A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It can only do so if America takes action itself. Here's how: https://t.co/HVkzYfwCch (2/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To make Syrian refugees more than a political slogan, @realDonaldTrump must challenge the interntat'l  community to take action (1/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can improve the wellbeing of #Syrian #refugees and advance US interests at the same time. Here's how:… https://t.co/S0f5tBF2Uq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now that the cast of characters is in place, worth revisiting what @BrookingsInst experts believe to be the consequ… https://t.co/peKgPYiMoR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least he tells us what he really thinks... https://t.co/zNs7qlgvDY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The number of people brought out of #Aleppo could reach 100,000. What happens when they reach Idlib? https://t.co/jmDtXLRZd2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well deserved recognition for a piece that was compelling, insightful, and deeply thought provoking. Thanks for wri… https://t.co/mixC30Cyal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This. A thousand times. https://t.co/qbxEq1g2cI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what barrel bombs do: https://t.co/Aw0Qqli9rL.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This morning 20 women committed suicide in order not to be raped." Shame on us. https://t.co/FHEDWsrGQg]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>