<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Richard_Schiff wow I got a retweet from 'Toby'! I can die a happy man :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's very 1st counter-terrorism raid resulted in a US combat death. Where's the outrage from the right? Can you imagine if it was Obama?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember when some lefties thought Hillary would be the hawk, not Trump. The very first public statement of his nat… https://t.co/dcBbV78RJ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Do you get a sense that the media in the West...is almost working under the precepts of sharia law...?" - Bannon
https://t.co/uugzCDHJ5d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To be brutally frank, I mean Christianity is dying in Europe, and Islam is on the rise" - Steve Bannon on his show 
https://t.co/uugzCDHJ5d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We’re clearly going into, I think, a major shooting war in the Middle East again." - Steve Bannon on his radio show
https://t.co/uugzCDHJ5d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“If we didn’t hit the pause button today...we’re going to be importing at least a couple of million Muslims whatever happens?” -Steve Bannon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Look, it’s pretty dark here in Europe right now, but there’s something...much darker. And that is Islam" - Bannon
https://t.co/uugzCDHJ5d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you only read one piece today, read this investigation of Steve Bannon's views on Islam and war by @USATODAY: 
https://t.co/uugzCDHJ5d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome, heart-warming story. https://t.co/UWIf86vpOQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, speaking about him in the present tense... https://t.co/3z5MN3i4se]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Kuwait issues Trump-like visa bans for five Muslim-majority countries" Argh.
https://t.co/TziGYseiNd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I would love to be a well-educated black, because I believe they do have an actual advantage" - @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/SDojUBxX1K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“I’ve got black accountants..I hate it..only kind of people I want counting my money are..guys that wear yarmulkes"
https://t.co/SDojUBxX1K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump now bragging about how he increased the black vote for the Republican party. It's always about him &amp; about ratings. #blackhistorymonth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump now turns #blackhistorymonth event into his usual attack on the media: I don't watch CNN, I don't watch fake news, etc, etc. Sigh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump holding event commemorating #blackhistorymonth in the White House right now flanked by Ben Carson and Omarosa.
https://t.co/O8aTlv0Vik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This x 100 https://t.co/ujXDuUwYy3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["8 Lessons From History for Resisting Donald Trump" by @pastpunditry  https://t.co/87zgSEY90k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['You couldn't make this stuff' up is the motto of journalists covering the Trump era. https://t.co/kfuKIG6jjI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SebGorka great TV. let me know if you want to come back on @AJUpFront anytime soon. We're not far from the White House, as you know...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did Trump just say 'I am a man of my word'? Lol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NatashaBertrand @ddale8 thanks both]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See it *is* possible for U.S. cable news to do proper journalism. Great stuff @jaketapper #mustwatch https://t.co/08dStjLkNK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the U.S., you're more likely to be killed by a vending machine than by a refugee-turned-terrorist. #justsaying
https://t.co/LrXLehQkP1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of #economicanxiety here...
https://t.co/vD411QzA7a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShelaghFogarty Not sure what you mean. But this is worth a read:
https://t.co/vD411QzA7a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @WajahatAli, he stole your line from CNN last night :-) https://t.co/b3FWS5D4Zm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShelaghFogarty @EdelmanPR @LBC hey, I'm all for engagement. Sadly a lot of Trump supporters don't want to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then it's game on for Trump and co because then it's a free-for-all in which their 'alternative facts' can be pushed with no accountability.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump wants to delegitimize the 'MSM'. I mean, if his followers don't trust the media, then what purpose do 'factchecks' serve? No referees.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 'only 15% of Trump voters trust the media' is a great stat for Trump and Bannon. Their aim is to get that number down to around zero.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When discussing media coverage, don't forget: only 15% of Trump voters trust the media (cf: 51% of Clinton voters)
https://t.co/KvDuDNxgK8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This is unfortunate..." Amusing to watch @OwenJones84 run rings around an unprepared @piersmorgan in this clip - w… https://t.co/BnNzb9uMUz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We shouldn’t welcome Trump when he cares so little for democracy," writes @PCollinsTimes 
https://t.co/ZJLXedpL58]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump live in White House just asked Dan Coats, national intel director nominee, I kid you not: "Do you have anything to say about cyber?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is a “blunt instrument for us,” Steve Bannon said last year. “I don’t know whether he really gets it or not.”
https://t.co/H9y1QQrkNh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#mustread from @alicesperi at @theintercept https://t.co/eZqzRL071m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big/important scoop from the folks at @theintercept https://t.co/DlT77P3kdQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adamjlent from millions of Americans watching at home, mourning over the loss of liberal democracy &amp; constitutional norms &amp; basic decency?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will Trump open an envelope live on TV to reveal his SC pick? Will 2 'finalists' be in front of him? Will there be tears? #realitypresidency]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CasMudde thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spicer just refused to confirm that Nora was killed at the weekend: 'We killed an estimated 14 members of AQ...as far as I am willing to go"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshuahersh Can i take that as a compliment?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To those lefties + Muslims (you know you are) who obsessed only over Clinton's hawkishness while ignoring Trump's, hang your heads in shame.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing this hasn't got more coverage, or more outrage. Obama killed the son; Trump in week 1 killed the daughter.… https://t.co/0JW6oH1Bi3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On @ajupfront I asked Hamas spokesman Osama Hamdan if he was embarrassed by the anti-Semitism in the Hamas charter
https://t.co/hQ2LMatpFm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Being Muslim in Trump's America" -powerful and personal by @hsmoghul  https://t.co/g7qV008TZu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Germany, woman "told to squeeze her breast at airport security to prove she was lactating" https://t.co/ldRxJ9iMEt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sadiq Khan: world leaders must speak out against Donald Trump travel ban | London Evening Standard https://t.co/k6LwGURcvq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This https://t.co/SWAdOt9ZkK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading the morning news headines on a daily basis these days is enough to make you go mad. And some of us have to do it for a living. Sigh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump fires acting AG Sally Yates after she declines to defend travel ban - https://t.co/7e2D2rVTDr https://t.co/KvE6q3KF4j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This! https://t.co/FkMWU36wF1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Says man who himself accused Trump of being "clearly out of his mind" &amp; of  "stupefying ignorance that makes him..u… https://t.co/M0brY2saEG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It wasn’t outright hate, rather part of this new nationalist conservative identity movement" https://t.co/GmjhTEazrz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, will Trump be banning Marine Le Pen then? https://t.co/GmjhTEazrz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember, according to the Islamophobes'/Trump fans' own logic, they now have to condemn/apologize for/take respons… https://t.co/u9RSrzsgI2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am starting to tire of @nytimes' repeated references to Bannon, accused of Islamophobia+anti-Semitism!, as 'provocative' or a 'provocateur']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeterBeinart @realDonaldTrump 1 study suggests 6th-grade level English, which I think is an insult to 6th graders:
https://t.co/9BIoiVU31Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 hours later: No correction. No amendment. No apology. No mention of *actual* suspect's allegedly pro-Trump, far-r… https://t.co/ccuH8byI8v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Republicans Alarmed Over Obama’s Executive Orders, Cheer Trump’s On"
https://t.co/nGn1OLTmMO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["How war on Islam became central to the Trump doctrine" - good stuff from @D_Shariatmadari 
https://t.co/e5JIXbq2O1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's only been a few hours but this tweet from a top Trump supporter hasn't dated so well... https://t.co/GUQCvqxOR1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine if it'd been a church in Canada attacked by a 'jihadist'? Can you imagine Trump's early morning tweet response? (2/2)
#pt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 tweets from @realDonaldTrump today, none giving condolences/offering solidarity to next-door Canada after #QuebecCityMosqueShooting. (1/2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's a white dude &amp; possibly not Muslim. So how long, as @hash_said asked me, till 'troubled lone wolf with history… https://t.co/jv3lrHz7m0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This might be kinda awkward for all those Trump fans screaming 'Muslims did it! Why aren't media covering Muslim an… https://t.co/Ws065HQAoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["the new president is doing the Islamic State’s propaganda for it, buoying the caliphate in its time of need"
https://t.co/WfRqpva25Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnRentoul For once, we agree. Trump has brought even us together...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The president has the right for his nominees to be taken up," says Spicer. Somewhere, Obama and Merrick Garland are having coughing fits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spicer just absurdly claimed that refugees would have 'flooded' into the U.S. if warning given. No one in the briefing challenges. Or laughs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ask pointed questions: 'Is it right for a 5-year-old boy to be detained at the airport?'. 'What's your evidence for Delta glitch?' etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching the WH Press Briefing is infuriating - journos, pls stop asking open-ended questions to Spicer 'what do you say to those...'. Argh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Is it crazy to express a preference for Christians [refugees] over Muslims? Of course not." https://t.co/yeUSDrIJfm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've said it before and I'll say it again: you. cannot. make. this. stuff. up. https://t.co/iy4KFd8eg8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 is white, 1 is brown. They *may* be Muslim. Neither is a Syrian refugee.
Wait for facts before jumping to conclus… https://t.co/hjGAvOfDsp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PfeifferDC @realDonaldTrump Would it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who in public life writes/speaks/tweets like? Seriously, who? https://t.co/k7DXxGM0gN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Opposition party'? He is literally now copying and pasting from Bannon. This is a Bannon presidency. https://t.co/NGTSFd4FHh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will @Number10gov be commenting on this today? @BorisJohnson? Will UK government stand up for its citizens or just… https://t.co/ywb8cip6wg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US embassy contradicts British government claim that ‘Muslim ban’ doesn’t apply to UK citizens | The Independent https://t.co/1OsCZkKf6z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's now become part of my daily morning routine: brush teeth, shower... check Trump's Twitter feed for the latest… https://t.co/rC8dhZZqY2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Anxiety About Muslim Refugees Is Stoked Online by the Far-Right Media" - depressing but a #mustread  https://t.co/Xh3TeFWmAi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lt General (retd) Mark Hertling just said on CNN that for ISIS, the #MuslimBan is the recruiting &amp; PR equivalent of Abu Ghraib for Al Qaeda.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@WajahatAli delivering fact after fact against the #MuslimBan on CNN right now, up against Jeffrey 'alternative facts' Lord.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Trump’s facile claim that his refugee policy is similar to Obama’s in 2011" #factcheck by @GlennKesslerWP  https://t.co/ItvceQuhmi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good for @MarthaRaddatz https://t.co/Rl5jsDwcWk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This https://t.co/dVUWwOm2PX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I don't think he should be coming on a state visit while the ban is in place" - strong from @SadiqKhan  https://t.co/VxTwCeZKwo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sadiq Khan demands Donald Trump's state visit is cancelled - Mirror Online  https://t.co/VxTwCeZKwo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1) Many more Muslims have been killed by ISIS than Christians 2) he's explicitly making it a religious #muslimban,… https://t.co/3tMRlaBM8H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The Times is a great, great American jewel - @realDonaldTrump, 22 Nov 2016
https://t.co/4yqB4mrKRt https://t.co/drCAIBnKLO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your daily morning Trump tweet https://t.co/tWRuVmAlQf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kashhill @alivitali is there a clip?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, DHS legal advice on green card holders overruled by the White House...well, by Bannon. https://t.co/NQvBi8y15F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the KEY point. This isn't just about Trump. He couldn't do all this if he didn't have the near-united suppo… https://t.co/jVdHTwpI4g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@woodruffbets Where is this? Do you have their names by any chance?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danielmarans Non-white judge? Oh that'll be on the WH radar.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 7 days Trump has probably done more to damage U.S. standing in the world &amp; promote radicalization than George W. Bush did in 8 years.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>