<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatchRagamuffin Beautiful work! I particularly love the animation on Arin when he does his 'haaaaaahh!'. Really nice timing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scheree Nice job, dude! I really like what you did with the continue screen!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Knicker_Bottoms This translates to "Exhale" :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Knicker_Bottoms This is serious business.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrittySugar Thanks! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dshanaur Yeah, it's pretty exciting! I hope we get to see it soonish!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dshanaur Sure thing! It looks rad! :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@faalinetweets That pause kills me. My need to inhale is mighty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dshanaur Yeah, it looks awesome! Nice job! I really love the way it looks, it's cool that you thought outside of the box.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@faalinetweets this is actually extremely therapeutic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Buttersphere a worthy trade.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CountZachulaaa okay. This looks incredible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I'm inking frames I feel like a sniper because I spend half of my time holding my breath to steady my hand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dshanaur wow! The technique here is super sweet! Are those scanned parts that you've rigged?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hennygoransson this is so great! Did you freehand those lines or use the pen tool, because they are so clean and smooth and lovely!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PattenPending this is gonna be so amazing. I want to be in pizza space.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrittySugar hahahahahaha!!!!! That end pose!! Stellar!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TopSpinTheFuzzy @planetrazzmataz also the timing of the plant smacking the wall is bloody masterful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@moopdrea these are so nice. The turnarounds in particular are really beautiful. The attention to details re the mouth shapes is ver cool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TopSpinTheFuzzy @planetrazzmataz gaaaah! AMAZING work! I adore the design of the characters and your posing is so STROOOONG!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love this so much. https://t.co/Yh6S2rnI2V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexa_doodles Thank you very very much!! :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@egoraptor Omigosh - thanks so much for the follow, dude! You're a hero! I love your art, music and comedy. Keep on being your awesome self!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaperbagTweet Dude! Thank you so much! And thank you for the follow - I love your work, so it means a lot. I'm a big admirer!.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaeldoigart Thanks for being my one man production studio, Doigleberg - you give me the time to focus on animating! Best support ever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Simon_Appel Thanks so much!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hennygoransson I'm there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TakoPancakes Thank you, dude!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_FreddyUlate Any and all Crush 40 songs are totally applicable in this situation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ludolik @michaeldoigart How sad that it will all end in tragedy! Though the episode has now been immortalised in remix form! ;D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@moopdrea @michaeldoigart Omigosh, thank you SO much! Mike's responsible for all the colours and bgs. Hold judgment till you see it, haha :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_FreddyUlate GUESS WHAT LIES AHEAD ONLY ONE WAY TO FIND OUUUUT!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AtroxChobatsu @michaeldoigart Thanks a million! That's like.... The animator's dream compliment! :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaeldoigart is making my animation look cool for #animateagrump ! https://t.co/SlkmeVGGmH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inking frames at the speed of sound! Got three days to go gotta FOLLOW MY RAINBOW! https://t.co/LYrqEwXNFO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KurvosVicky @DeviantArt @myanimelist Thanks, dude!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KurvosVicky @DeviantArt @myanimelist Feel free to add me on facebook or email me! I'm often busy, but I enjoy a good discussion!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KurvosVicky @DeviantArt @myanimelist Yeah - I agree. Equality goes both ways!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KurvosVicky @DeviantArt @myanimelist No, it's cool! I like hearing about these topics - I'm super interested! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KurvosVicky @DeviantArt @myanimelist I think mainstream western animation has a long way to go before it starts being truly progressive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KurvosVicky @DeviantArt @myanimelist I'll give that a read! I agree that this character type isn't explored much at all outside of anime.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KurvosVicky @DeviantArt I see what you're saying! How do you feel about sexualised anime male characters, as in 'Y… https://t.co/oqfNzgiybP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KurvosVicky @DeviantArt But you think male characters should be fair game to oversexualize too, is that what you're saying?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KurvosVicky @DeviantArt You don't think? There are quite a few lads in animation I think are quite sexy :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KurvosVicky @DeviantArt (Skimmed it just now and already nodding about your points on Moana - had a big rant about that the other day)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KurvosVicky @DeviantArt Thanks very much for the link - I'll give it a read, as I'm a big believer in expressive female designs!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stitchfeather Thank you, dude! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KurvosVicky Dude, I'm totally with you! That stuff drives me crazy, too. The gals from same story as this guy are also heavily stylised :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pancakeser @SovietGamesVNS Awesome! Beautiful background, really fun to work with! It's on Steam, too! I'll give it a play, thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's #cutiesaturday again! https://t.co/z9nA9bUBEm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pancakeser I was wondering what it was! I found it on google images but couldn't find the source. Is it a Visual Novel game or something?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shavostars it's okay, I am also a lie - a friend drew mine, too u_u  your work is fantastic though, so I think you can get away with it! :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimkoikoi ack! The curse of improvement - being able to see past mistakes! We'll never be happy! :D  It's such a beautiful piece, though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimkoikoi Aw man, that means a lot! It was a lot of fun to do!
Your Kiki animation - was the last section straight ahead? So much momentum!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PuccaNoodles Thanks a million! Your work is so cool! Gorgeous drawing skills!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elbormes It's a gunwand! :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimkoikoi @RubberNinja WOAH! Wooooooooaaaaah! WOOOOWAAAH! This is gorgeous! Amazing work. That run &amp; the timing on the antic is beautiful!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RubberNinja Duuuuude! Thanks so much for the follow! You're awesome! Can't wait to see more #Gameoverse ruffs. It looks incredible so far.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shanooloo Be all like 'It's meeeee!' and then wink twice and give me the thumbs up. I'll memorise the code! :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PattenPending Of course! Thanks so much. :) Everyone is really kind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@k7movingdoodles Thanks a million dude! Your work is awesome, so it means a lot!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shanooloo Omigosh! Is Sinead your RL name? Let's hang out! I'm sure I'll recognize you when I see you. I pass so many peeps on the stairs!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New followers! I appreciate each and every one of you - I wanted to thank you all individually, but there isn't tim… https://t.co/jD4GCJ4QVc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_MilaYin Thank you! I really appreciate the kind words, and I'm super happy you like it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@siskavard @RubberNinja You're so welcome! Just awesome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wontonssoup @RubberNinja dude, nice!! Lovely work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@siskavard @RubberNinja This is so amazing. Fantastic animation!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LandsharkRAWR @RubberNinja Those smears! They're sweeeeeeet!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sand_011897 thank you dude!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StudioYobi I'm really glad it did! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lemondaurora wow thank you so much. It means a lot!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@isaactorres290 thanks so much for the follow!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sprouteeh heya! Thank you very much for the follow !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matheushintate thank you very muchly for the follow, duuuude!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FOXAR_ thanks for the follow! Hail Miyazaki!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_HannaGeorge_ thanks for the follow! It's really cool of you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@curiousertea your art is so cool! I love it! Thank you for the follow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RubberNinja thanks so much for the retweet! I really love what you've started here!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@periiwnkle that's really awesome of you! :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jerzy @michaeldoigart @LeanIntoArt wow, thank you so much! We'll give it a listen when I get back! Hahaha, it's 'Doyg' but we don't mind!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scissorgoat so happy you like it! Thank you!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StudioYobi heya! Thank you for the follow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rosealune thanks very much for the follow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AstrophileArts hey!! Thank you so much for the follow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KierPix thank you so much for the follow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lemondaurora ooh your work is so cool! Thank you for the follow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jellial thank you for the follow - your art is mm mm!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@periiwnkle thanks for the follow very much!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@starcre8tor thank you for the folloooooow!! &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WTFSociety505 @RubberNinja oh, man! thank you so much! I'll keep working my butt off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@starcre8tor that means a lot! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shanooloo hey! Thank you for the follow - I see you're a dubliner too, who loves animation! We should hang out sometime. Your art is great!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stitchfeather thanks a million for the follow and the retweet! I really appreciate it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noitibmar heya! Thank you for the follow- that lightning animation is bonkers! So cool!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@motionandtime thank you very much for the follow and the retweet!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ethanirons8 hey, thanks very much for the follow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AhLaToad thank you for the follow! Your art is amazing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scissorgoat hey! Thank you for the follow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@planetrazzmataz heya! Thank you very much for the follow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@starcre8tor thank you! When you get into an empty room, don't you just want to jump all over everything!?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>