<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh i like #6.  @yvesbehar applicable in all sorts of solutions.  #ecm #eim vendors and pros should take a look at t… https://t.co/20Lf1emXTt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I rememeber Mac users saying the same thing lol.  #infogov #privacy #technology .....but could linux help? https://t.co/JAtn7ubOIw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Balance @grantrobertson1 lol good luck with that! https://t.co/J1mmczMx3h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#infogov pros get your copy now.  Very timely thanks @euanc we're discussing this next week ☺ https://t.co/ugzQRtszMf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yazidi MP and 'Isil's most-wanted woman' banned from entering US to collect award https://t.co/BODlb1zEQN via @TelegraphNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jkevinappleby @TheBishy imagine what we could accomplish if we enabled people to play to their strengths :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jkevinappleby @TheBishy whats fascinating is the traditional view of 'x level can talk to  customers' when the skills tell a difft story]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After the nonsense of the last few days this is the only civilised thing to do. Thanks steve @AvidaBar #bronte https://t.co/vCQXOoCdnG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its v interesting to complete this as a team.  @TheBishy facilitated this and it was amazing to see how our consult… https://t.co/qa4ZizJ0yS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Simply by following the protocol of the system, Brett had derailed and handicapped one of his best performers" #HR… https://t.co/LcxsYFYkNU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbrislen @russellclarke4 @rhysiedarby 😞 you boys scare me sometimes 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Phil_Mattingly @evanperez and then gets fired :( sad day for democracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@russellclarke4 @paulbrislen @rhysiedarby nah time for a ginger Dr who :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ValisWatson @realDonaldTrump sorry so you are saying you dont want an AG? He sacked her for disagreeing with his EO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unbelievable! So anyone who disagrees with #UnholyTrinity is "weak".  #StandUpToTrump https://t.co/1dUVG1wWe8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lets see if this gets on the offended list @paulbrislen lol. https://t.co/pCJoWkkdvs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnneWheaton how does he choose which ones to be offended by...there are so many 😆]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What an arse! Im with you @paulbrislen :) https://t.co/EbcIxgBqYM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So he has a very different definition of "out of his way" to the rest of the english speaking world!  #NoBanNoWall https://t.co/2iB3hX16Rm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice to see a balanced and honest piece. #digital is made harder when there is no vision and leadership https://t.co/rMbgJxVkPm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lldzne certainly an interesting time in politics :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is scary! https://t.co/8u6H4Symbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lldzne no and  the latest sentiments of 'criticise trump and leave' isnt going to enamour his administration to bureaucrats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lldzne will be interesting to see leg they bring to the floor.  With Rep majority hes expected to be push through whatever he wants..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lldzne but hoe many of those agencies allies and institutions have stood up?  Its like toddlers seeing how much they can get away with]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lldzne created a lot of friction and almost managed to hide his appointment to the NSC. Upside? Ummm...........]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lldzne #bannon on the other hand seems to be having a brilliant time! #StopPresidentBannon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NoBanNoWall #viber offerring free calls https://t.co/7FGzvmMHrh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The tweetjams are incredibky useful given the short format of twitter. Great access to some smart ppl so highly rec… https://t.co/BF3B0o3kII]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is pretty cool #mechanics #microsoft https://t.co/8HcOjTXzYA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbrislen @ScottBaio @AJemaineClement so proud of you @paulbrislen  :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#wellington people - recommendations for oriental duck pancakes with hoi sin sauce cucumber and onion.  Go and thanks xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If english isnt youre first #english heres a great help for you #wellington #immigrantsupport https://t.co/fsfEdtlFCa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mishacollins now thats a pleasant image to go to sleep to :) #lovewins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BCAppelbaum using actual facts isnt their strong suit either https://t.co/rHCzbzGzsg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only if you listen to what people need. #technology https://t.co/DBKyAZ64Im]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aka that ship called the mayflower :) @WillMcAvoyACN https://t.co/AcjAcr0SNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Alisonmau its a moral responsibility not a political one.  And #NZ has a strong moral compass - time to show it :) https://t.co/T9CllqXjju]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WgtnPhoenixFC @YellowFever_NZ "onfire" in more ways than one :) https://t.co/ynXh1pFIUF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thoughts with family and friends of those affected. And first responders :( https://t.co/K2fwZacOiF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZInlandRevenue any plans for that here? https://t.co/iK3mCyrTbu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WgtnCC fire service closed willis st at junction with l quay. Police on scene https://t.co/rj22wu4NlM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The integration of #erp #crm #eim. This is what delivers roi. https://t.co/EdJn6TUDK4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If they are mindful of posssible re-identification but qe need to acknowledge that the tools will improve faster th… https://t.co/HssXViy0rK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He shoots ...he scores! 😂 https://t.co/w7Ie5ifcwr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Clocky001 its saddening that we dont learn from our history and maddening that this puts our troops in greater danger :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkHubbard33 add coriander its allegedly good for you :) now where did i put the bacon 😉]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Clocky001 thx but also right u should call me on it - only way we learn is by talking. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Clocky001 my point was that you cant claim all muslims are terrorists in same way that you cant claim all christians/protestants are. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Clocky001 oh mate i do and have included british govt in previous posts. And i do understand the troubles. Sorry if it offended u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaddythePunter @HelenORahilly @mairiac31 the profile is based on race! Ergo racist #facepalm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaddythePunter @HelenORahilly @mairiac31 where is the threat? Wheres the intel? You dont have any so yes its indecent and racist!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can we put some smart machines in the whitehouse? #NoBanNoWall https://t.co/D9mTRhjeD3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaddythePunter @HelenORahilly @mairiac31 target security risks yes but thats not what this is. No prof security/ intel agency wanted this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaddythePunter @HelenORahilly @mairiac31 but he isnt flagged thats the point! And its not about inconvenience its about base human decency]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It comes to something when you find yourself agreeing with @Ed_Miliband but i do. #NoBanNoWall https://t.co/v1OVKRIHJp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least #PrinceCharles has conviction.  @KensingtonRoyal proud of him! #ClimateChangeIsReal https://t.co/VyLbmklTzL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The funpolice killed @WellySevens and the media helped.  Hope youre all happy! https://t.co/X8uw4WGDWJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pic of US if all immigrants had to leave. USA was founded and has grown strong bc of immigration. #NoBanNoWall… https://t.co/OSzCPTy6Cq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaddythePunter @bridwise @HelenORahilly and that my friend is EXACTLY how Nazi Germany was allowed to grow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaddythePunter @HelenORahilly @mairiac31 WTF is targeted about it? The guy is a reporter not a terrorist. Hes not on any watchlist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a gross #violation. Unless there is definitive evidence of criminality this is mass #privacy invasion. Id s… https://t.co/Nf79lm6f9N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lynnecazaly do u have a link for registration or are u full?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What an idiot that guy is - so #KKK arent terrorists? #IRA arent terrorists? Educate yourself man. And sorry u get… https://t.co/vGegsR2FTX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Move it to #dunedin or #christchurch.  Fun police have killed a great tournament that brought many visitors, laught… https://t.co/PKOWRzApQ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lynnecazaly its a great reminder. I was guilty of a few of those in the early days of my career :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another great resource from @lynnecazaly #strategy #ba https://t.co/F4H8Tamm1L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise level search tools can add massive benefits to #productivity and #experience but getting #cio to pay for… https://t.co/8gmbudHBFX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well said #wellington mayor @justin_lester now if we could get our @pmbillenglish to respond that would be great… https://t.co/75rG08EgoR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sophieridgesky @adamboulton The order wasnt supposed to apply to green card holders either but it has #NoBanNoWall https://t.co/RjCqcGjK50]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#wellington welcomes you!  Enjoy the wine, the company and ummm....maybe the weather :) https://t.co/ZYFWhBRnRC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are no words!  #StopPresidentBannon https://t.co/fbXqFaCC4c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The foreign office obviously has different instructions than the CBP #NoBanNoWall https://t.co/r49JF9nbnZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fight goes on - its still a morally repugnant and raciat action #NoBanNoWall https://t.co/a2gBY1xFyb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spectatorindex yeah when they do that let us know #NoBanNoWall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Irrespective of political affiliations this is just lunacy! #security #bannon https://t.co/1aOZNR0vao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ban applies to dual citizenship holders and is also just morally wrong! NZ has a strong moral compass - show th… https://t.co/m6uyfjPeK8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toddlers having tantrums seldom do #NoBanNoWall https://t.co/Vh87Wi855N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No shit sherlock! @MeetThePress https://t.co/JOyyuhTzkO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now this gives me faith in politicians! #NoBanNoWall https://t.co/1GAfoBjhEl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hurrah for wisdom! #NoBanNoWall https://t.co/BTEFQBtZy7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NZNationalParty are you watching #NoBanNoWall https://t.co/mTcvMrE5C8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NoBanNoWall people stand with you all over the world :) #humanityfirst https://t.co/Xme7VcwOjr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok lets start by asking native americans to publish a list. #NoBanNoWall we are all immigrants https://t.co/sOuM4unPu9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NoBanNoWall UK citizens make your voice heard https://t.co/kIQDqxhiSs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShaneWilliams11 @WelshRugbyUnion thats what we r missing. Speep and slick feet! #6nations https://t.co/gbg2qIzV18]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making the world smarter but also increasing our need for power.  #IoT #energy https://t.co/HSChfdGRf1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewshubNZ and did you ask @pmbillenglish for a statement?.....oh look more tumbleweeds #NoBanNoWall https://t.co/t7dyyiGPOf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woke up this morning hoping that yesterday was some kind of bad dream but no the lunatics are still running the asylum! #NoBanNoWall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wall of shame #NoBanNoWall https://t.co/ZgQWDudFX2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonGroves1 whats embarrassing is the leadership losing its spine. We have uninvited dictators before so put your big girls pants on PM!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BMHayward @pmbillenglish @NZNationalParty agreed. Though he did take the time to tell us he was at a movie #priorityfail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And thats why ive deleted uber #deleteuber https://t.co/Use7Kr2aRx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking at the pic i thought they were at the beach lol #wales #rugby https://t.co/55WpIeB6az]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brendongreen when those seeds are federer and nadal they're probably ok.  Ratings arent the only attraction]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WellySevens what were the official crowd figures for the weekend?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Neil5Powell  the boys played amazing rugby.  Great teamwork and some beautiful running lines! Well done @blitzboks https://t.co/Gwh0xlPH3N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grantrobertson1 hes a bit busy watching a movie apparently 🤔]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benjaminryan true but theres something about @fijirugby - i love watching those boys play!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WorldRugby7s and #Wales get Pool C with #france and #samoa.  Better get fitness training boys! @WelshRugbyUnion]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>