<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesFales2 Why do you think I'd know?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesFales2 Again, that doesn't seem like somebody with principles would say.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesFales2 So here is my point: it doesn't look like it's based on high principles, since no outrage at Islamic country bans of Israelis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesFales2 This tweet sounds overly defensive given that I was talking about leftist attitude in context of the article, not you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesFales2 @Yair_Rosenberg @The_Oilholic But if Arabs target Jews it's their business?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesFales2 @Yair_Rosenberg @The_Oilholic So you have no opinion on ISIS or Hitler?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesFales2 @Yair_Rosenberg @The_Oilholic Your outrage is reserved to the US only?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesFales2 @Yair_Rosenberg @The_Oilholic No outrage at Jew ban kind of cheapens outrage at Muslim ban. Looks like it's not principle-based]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simon_feenix @rickyred09 @joerogan If those zookeepers could actually shoot the man, they would. This is why punctuation is important.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PreppyAltRight @TheRickWilson @haaretzcom Sorry, the origin of white supremacy is an inferiority complex - cuckery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's either a Nazis or an SJW. So hard to tell these days. https://t.co/5hqzRv9N25]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@haaretzcom @EricYoffie psst. Not about you...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @wikileaks https://t.co/v8QcOvDeCf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IAmVerySilky @seanhannity @POTUS Because elephants never forget, you obese fool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsMelChen LOL, next you'll be telling me that Captain Crunch has never been at sea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsMelChen here is the dilemma: should you punch the Nazi?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsMelChen Trolley is hurtling towards 5 Nazis on the tracks. Trolley driver is a Nazi. If you punch him, trolley stops and he runs away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsMelChen This is wrong. Every ad does it cereal first. You're sick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TarekFatah @OmarYKhan @reggcohn What a ridiculous, horribly written article. "If you criticize, you dehumanize." Frankly it's offensive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not a normal moral state for a human being. https://t.co/ppshXiBOZu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessicaFemin @gregstevens Growers wont stop growing corn and plant avocados because they don't expect idiotic Econ policy to last.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The US collects $1.2 from Jose... https://t.co/stEFi0Y2YF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lucasjlynch That's the problem with identity politics. Preferred identity can be worn by people with agendas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*autistic screeching intensifies* https://t.co/0J53oTg2LW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Amendment suggestion: death penalty for corruption while president.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's gonna be all skin and bones by 2020 (sorry) https://t.co/A9OnpsESR0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder if Muslim teenagers create another hashtag like #FreeJahar https://t.co/fqAXqc5WCf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clairlemon I think Australian makes sense to discourage people from taking extremely risky trips by sea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian forces murdered civilians and @RT_com tried to conceal that fact.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If this is your symbol, then you're not really against fascism. https://t.co/KMAU5x7FjH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidAFuquaTX @RawStory Violence against the govt is an American tradition.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Dean was white, he would be a white supremacist. https://t.co/tcKinEhrEW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you don't think it through before counting bodies. https://t.co/uu4Htfv5AJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ask him if Arabs accept UN judgment for creation of Israel. https://t.co/Xh2CRdUUfD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone banned from 7 Muslim countries. 

• not you Jews
• not you Christians 
• not you polytheists

https://t.co/G6KgoaoOhQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wokieleaks1 @frackingzionist In the immortal words of Benny Hill: "I would not tell a lie, unless absolutely convenient."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next they came for US soldiers. What WERE they doing in Muslim countries for years? https://t.co/noU0AUMa9N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this the year Tommy stops pretending to care about liberal values? https://t.co/wndBHJZ0re]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Whitemale3113 @patrickjcapone I hope my sons grow up to be pussygrabbers, not some perverts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Superslaviswife @Whitemale3113 And of course there is the dirty matter of Nazi collaboration still buried in ex-Warsaw bloc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Superslaviswife @Whitemale3113 Jews were betrayed by people in almost every country Nazis invaded.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Superslaviswife @Whitemale3113 It's true that every life was precious, but there was a final solution only for one type.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Old_Shoe1 Indont think you understand what @uberfeminist is doing. Please refrain from commenting until you level up sarcasm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what I imagine every frog on the internet calling people cucks looks like. https://t.co/ylghnAEdiM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dumisani6 Shouldn't have to choose between anybody who wants to destroy our way of life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I liked @ScottAdamsSays before his head injury.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahKate26 @piersmorgan I commend him for breaking the stereotype that Brits are clever and funny.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tzaousios1453 @GordonRepinski Not all Trump supporters are right-wing killers, but the right-wing killers are all Trump supporters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maej43 @ddale8 Don't judge a man until you walk a mile in his shoes .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But enough about the future of the Trump administration. https://t.co/ByNXKgozzj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brigamongus Soros is a great man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimsciutto What clarity are they seeking? They were told "not just a Muslim ban."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beautifulwood The facts are that racists like you have been trying to spin the murder of people into their own fault. Deplorable scum.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MsMelChen @JeffreyGoldberg 

"My grandfather died in a concentration camp. He fell off a watchtower."

Except this is serious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beautifulwood @acoyne You are not the victim here or at all. Have some sense of decency, ugly Canadian.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rupasubramanya @TarekFatah Yeah, because white supremacists never killed anyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...but that's none of my business https://t.co/sFrwMAlnXv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hemantmehta @kurteichenwald Trump met the Jews half way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did the CNN also drop the bomb? https://t.co/wTwQX5400u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrmisanthrope2 How does it feel to know that will will undo everything Trump does the second he is gone?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unless you have friends and sex you're not worthy of respect. https://t.co/x3s0w87q6B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fr33domF0x What happens when I want magahats out of my country?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Magahats be like: we won't let Islam destroy the West. Cuz we gonna destroy it first. https://t.co/ihhZzWtuqU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is another extreme. I don't want to see praying crowds in public spaces. https://t.co/r8GYXuM8mi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CathyYoung63 @realDonaldTrump I think he means they were pre-approved by Barack Hussein and were in Syria completing shahid training.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And you'd be calling it a false flag https://t.co/ene9elM3py]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeorgKendrick @thehill When did whites ever commit racial crimes, this century?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShreeParadkar @TorontoStar Also, your argument is basically "so what if you're more likely to die from traffic than terrorism?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShreeParadkar @TorontoStar There is no need to continue splitting people into races just because 19th century European racists invented it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine my shock when James von Brunn had once eaten shawarma. https://t.co/BLisv67Z6i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unless we block 88-year-olds Islam will take over. https://t.co/mPeNSeYeLJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@saramayhew Who would play her best?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@christianjbdev Pretty sure it's Schiller.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ruppli @wokieleaks1 They haven't lived there and they're too stupid to open a book.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wokieleaks1 

What would Stalin do? 

• starved millions
• committed ethnic cleansing
• collaborated with Nazis
• murdered millions more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshtpm You know @JustinTrudeau did the same thing with a peep?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuliaDavisNews Fascists operate on fear and thus projection. What every They accuse others of is what they're thinking of.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bellecosy They seem nice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know, participating in Nazi circlejerk of hate will not save you from the pogrom. https://t.co/OwoQ7jgWuF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StrizzoX @horowitz39 Yeah, go fuck yourself, racist degenerate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TPSOperations Is possible to see which material was deemed hate speech?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#impeachment 
#inquiry 
#imprisonment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OnlySinner @ConfessionsExMu What do you mean "you people"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OnlySinner @ConfessionsExMu They're long dead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OnlySinner @ConfessionsExMu Not speaking for you. You wanna sit in that shithole, do it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OnlySinner @ConfessionsExMu No, you're saying you don't care if they get beheaded, because being born in a fascist shithole is a crime.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OnlySinner @ConfessionsExMu You can't fight darkness with darkness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If they are checking Muslims' social media, what level of Trump love are they looking for to approve entry? Like full-on ass kissing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[he lols best, who lols last https://t.co/HsZH6c63Wi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@uberfeminist @WideAsleepNima Did you receive an invitation by mail to tweet at her?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The biggest criminal empire in history. Cosa Nostra is child's play. https://t.co/lRbAXzOTbc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump further endangered every American in the Muslim world. https://t.co/Crcal9V343]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LOL 

@wikileaks
@Snowden 

How's the privacy battle going? https://t.co/qcIcYqwzcd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SohrabAhmari @NatashaBertrand @theintercept These two should be in jail for life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turns out it was illegal. https://t.co/A1FGoeqzui]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jfthomasser No mindreading required. In time you will fully understand the error of your ways. In truth you've already started. Bye now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There should be an IQ check before letting people vote.

For example: Which photo has a larger crowd? https://t.co/UnccYQ70Bn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aussie_Sailor Marched around a defeat at sea, into a defeat on land. Genius.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jfthomasser Now you sound like a leftist Islam apologist. But you're apologizing for Nazis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Aussie_Sailor He who dares, gets ambushed.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>