<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishTimes does she know that women who have abortion often have other children they need to afford? Not all teenagers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wolfiemann @JessicaValenti like staying in Trump Tower. Like Erics business trips. Like paying Trump Hotels for Secret service. Hypocrite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hockeycoug44 @NYDailyNews @ShaunKing thats not the point of the article. Read it again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaeIDevine @NYDailyNews @ShaunKing @dailykos think you are back to front on this one Michael.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maureenwagenaar @NYDailyNews @ShaunKing did you read the article? If you did you certainly didn't understand it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_Premise @NYDailyNews @ShaunKing he has no reason to be proud or ashamed. That is the point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cbiscuiti @NYDailyNews @ShaunKing it was of course. The whole world watches how the US media distinguishes between white crime and 'others']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NYDailyNews @ShaunKing great article. NYDN needs to try harder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Explained: Israel's new Palestinian land-grab law and why it matters https://t.co/ajUUY8SB50]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmandaMarcotte Check out @Khanoisseur's Tweet: https://t.co/RsMoNkhYnv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Check out @Khanoisseur's Tweet: https://t.co/RsMoNkhYnv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RawStory disgraceful. Incarceration Nation has killed its own soul.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leogwalter oh sorry. I've been getting a lot of abusive tweets so when "Why don't u get a  fucking life, loser " came up I snapped back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@canuckistan2010 @brendanmernin @MartysaurusRex nah. About 30%. And God knows she was spot on! American conservatives are vile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shannyk36 @kurteichenwald the books were written before his presidency. Neither did anything like paid speeches during the presidency.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBSNews he is such a fruitcake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@moosecustoms @YukonGale @jerf37 @CBSNews oh my god you've been watching Alex Jones. Admit it now and for your penance go say three rosaries]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBCWorld @BBCNews does Trump have business ventures in Pakistan. If not then its a possibility.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TooMuchMe @igorvolsky @Fusion the corruption in US politics really is remarkable and worse than ever since citisens united.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kurteichenwald he always did though. I've never once heard him disagree with his lord and masters. Not once.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cyclone_cowgirl @TJMcGibney @ROShier @VillageMagIRE its exceedingly cult like. He can do no wrong in their eyes. Blind to reality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump Is Signing Executive Orders That He Doesn't Read or Understand | GQ https://t.co/fdr0sBWAMV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump is angry he "was not briefed" on executive order giving powers to Steve Bannon: https://t.co/3gq0AEBFnM via @fusion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@New_Narrative @maggieNYT @NBCNews it's up to every liberal American to help family &amp; friends with paperwork/expense of getting registered.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WajahatAli @ShaunKing I agree. I don't like religion full stop but demonizing one and a half billion is asinine and cruel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ambiej @jeneps speaking of football. https://t.co/Kgzv4zyqxl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@budarydachas @ambiej @owillis @jeneps he punched his son in the face at school when he created him wearing normal clothes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tillwoman @ambiej @jeneps the way she clamps her arms to her sides! Poor creature is rigid with fear and loathing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leogwalter @T64Pamela @Kodie2038Donna @flahertykeely ah snowflake did I hurt yr feelings? Good to know a Pussy Grabber supporter has some.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cyclone_cowgirl @TJMcGibney @ROShier @VillageMagIRE the gullible. https://t.co/952KL4cl6o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kodie2038Donna you'll have to block me. See hard though it may be for you to comprehend, the internet is universal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@T64Pamela @Kodie2038Donna @flahertykeely Enjoy your game -  and the Budweisser ad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@T64Pamela @Kodie2038Donna @flahertykeely we elect the EU Ministers. Did you not know that? Bit like your states. Plus each country has veto]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@T64Pamela @Kodie2038Donna @flahertykeely ah but right wing in Europe is the equivalent of Democratic in the US.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@T64Pamela @Kodie2038Donna @flahertykeely you know nothing! Ireland has never even had a left wing government nevermind "socialist".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@T64Pamela @Kodie2038Donna @flahertykeely I'll concern myself about anything I choose. I'm not a parochial American conservative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@T64Pamela @Kodie2038Donna @flahertykeely Im Irish so can't vote. But did protest the US Embassy last Thursday. Not for the first time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@T64Pamela @Kodie2038Donna @flahertykeely which fact is delusional? It is you guys who are delusional. You're like a cult.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@T64Pamela @Kodie2038Donna @flahertykeely except he lies in every sentence, is corrupt to his core and has shifted Doomsday Clock forward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@T64Pamela @Kodie2038Donna @flahertykeely swamp draining? You mean like this https://t.co/yYV77b4sjZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TJMcGibney @ROShier @VillageMagIRE which point would that be?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@T64Pamela @Kodie2038Donna @flahertykeely cause for arrest? No. WW3 we are only a Trump fart away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kodie2038Donna @T64Pamela @flahertykeely possibly you missed them. Watching Fox News will do that. Here's a list https://t.co/2P7P8OMpO5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jaketapper @JeffreyGuterman maybe Trump is a truther. He likes infowars apparently.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CobesME4 @4Kenna99 would you have preferred he didn't fight ISIS?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kodie2038Donna @T64Pamela @flahertykeely Trump attacks everybody worldwide except for Putin. He's even trying to bring down the EU!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThatOneWIGuy @flahertykeely @LeaKThompson and now I sent you the wrong link! I need a drink! https://t.co/busAsrvp79]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThatOneWIGuy @flahertykeely @LeaKThompson sorry .Spelled wrong. Lord Haw Haw https://t.co/IaVKKeyt5g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiteralShaking @faiza_n_ali @ShaunKing if you are interesting in reading the story : https://t.co/IaVKKeyt5g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiteralShaking @faiza_n_ali @ShaunKing on his birth cert but not actually. That's not unusual.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiteralShaking @faiza_n_ali @ShaunKing have biological father was black so he is a pale skinned biracial man. Not that race is a 'thing'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiteralShaking @faiza_n_ali @ShaunKing oh don't be so childish.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelNoTrump @sharondigi @sarahkendzior @IBTimesUK @realDonaldTrump actually he looks  much better without the hair.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@THMizell @WendyStidd @seanspicer oh the stock market is up? Well that never let us down before. Oh wait. https://t.co/KvrGOYC5UU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tonydiaz777 @RNEspinoza @terryreed48 @CaseyHinds @CheriJacobus and up until the danger presented by Trump CNN US was pretty conservative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spectatorindex or in other words "Fox News viewers can't see further than the nose on their face."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mmfa I dunno. They work so well against themselves it seems a shame not to take advantage of it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@haaretzcom The American story is apparently now UnAmerican. Bizarroland.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRoot oh well in that case make him President.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OccPalGaza he's a nasty piece of work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Irish Climate Analysis and Research Units: On the Mail on Sunday article on Karl et al., 2015: https://t.co/ULOExEC99W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid yep. I've never seen bills to cut out the St Patricks Day parade or closed down Irish dancing lessons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NathanaelStCyr @BBCWorld @BBCNews she supported monster. Could have chosen to just give lip service like her morally superior sister.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dan__Gleeballs @BBCWorld @BBCNews Merkel demonstrates humanity. Trump demonstrates inhumanity - so comparing apples and oranges.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sumer_More @FanGirlLA when the husband is able to carry the baby to term fair enough. Until then women must control their own bodies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Independent that is one sick sick country. Remember when the US was an example to us all? Then we got internet and saw the reality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nine_FiftyFour @ShaunKing when we are a Trump fart away from WW3 Americas business is everyones business.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RNEspinoza @terryreed48 @CaseyHinds @CheriJacobus Also articles in The Guardian, Newsweek and Foreign Policy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RNEspinoza @terryreed48 @CaseyHinds @CheriJacobus make them watch CNN. I usually scorn your countries media but CNN is good at highlighting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoemacfA @CheriJacobus why US conservatives are mad as hatters and like no other conservatives in the western world. More like a cult.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoemacfA @CheriJacobus they've been that way for at least the decade I've watched US politics. They and radio are why US conservatives.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@debjwood1 @creativelytired @CheriJacobus CNN have been doing a terrific job of late and I usually have nothing but scorn for US media.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@frenchcheesey @CheriJacobus @reese_malmgren don't forget they supported Bush too until they became too embarrassed to support him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stych626 @ShaunKing your country locks up more of its citizens than any other country in the world. Land of the Free? Incarceration Nation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nine_FiftyFour @ShaunKing think about what that says about the Land of the Free. Think about how that impact down the generations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nine_FiftyFour @ShaunKing your country locks up more of its citisens than any other country in the world. Ten times the rate in EU countrys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eoghan was that uou on CNN just now? If so - fair play to you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eoghanmccabe was that you on CNN just now? If so - fair play to you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeojjKelly @IGD_News I dunno. They were already serfs in a corpocracy. The fight has been bred out of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brooklynwatch @kylegriffin1 @washingtonpost im not even American and Ive known about him too. People need to watch the "bad hombres".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As am I . "Why Not" not "Why Not?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kurteichenwald and since the magazine is Irish you should warn the thickos about the phone costs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kurteichenwald judging by the comments not one person bothered to check this out and so jumped to the wrong conclusion. Pearl clutching.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kurteichenwald kurt you clearly didnt get it. It is "Why NOT" as in why it would be unethical to kill Trump even though he is a monster.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VillageMagIRE @JKinast18 his supporters don't actually read past headlines I'm afraid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@internetalena too little, too late Alena. WW3 is a Trump fart away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theresphysics @BV that was predicted years ago. Resist until its too late and then  - "oops".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BreeNewsome I protested against Trump last night in Dublin. Protested against Iraq war and I protested against  Reagan. Power to the people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BreeNewsome Is there a mass movement in your country to help each other register and vote? The world needs decent Americans to vote.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeithOlbermann @NYDailyNews if he was that right wing at a tender age he clearly has sociopathic tendencies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmnestyIran Iran show the world you can be better than the Americans. Don't execute.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lupe3asco @Matt_Holck @mrdaveyd they are? Then show them this so they can rejoice in what your country supports
https://t.co/MFqt5I0kuY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Colmogorman I missed the beginning. Did the protest at the US Embassy today at 6 get a plug?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Colmogorman you had Seth for breakfast. Well researched and debated. US cons never seem to research further than Fox News talking points.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SethBTillman Colm O Gorman had you for breakfast. American conservatives never seem to research further than Fox News talking points.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TodaySOR Ireland appeased Hitler and never lived it down. Now we are doing the same with this centurys out of control psychopathic despot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ktumulty have American conservatives started to admit that they really fucked up yet? Curious Irish women here?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spectatorindex hope Le Pen crashes and burns. Both the UK and the US gone over to the dark side. I hope France (my fave) remains true.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcorubio can you really be such a hypocrite. People all over the world remember the GOP meeting on Obamas first auguration night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mappermick @morningireland one doesn't need to resent it when others want the same though. That is the message here.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>