<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Secretive anti-Trump protests to erupt Super Bowl weekend in Houston https://t.co/ueEMrqi1Mx via @USATODAY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘1984’ to Open on Broadway This Summer https://t.co/eXHuU3P6NS via @variety]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Filibuster Must Die https://t.co/TzMjDDDILN via @dailycaller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mattis threatens 'overwhelming' response if North Korea ever uses nukes https://t.co/jeEsxkT46b via @BI_Defense]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNN Guest: Berkeley Rioters Were Actually Secret Right-Wingers Affiliated With Breitbart https://t.co/YksJb9Cp3L via @mediaite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over 12,000 tweets are calling for Trump's assassination. Here's how the Secret Service handles it https://t.co/4ZGjeuXPK2 via @mashable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protesters storm NYU over conservative speaker's seminar https://t.co/5BTuEPNVAk via @nypmetro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Left Won't Stop Threatening Violence Against Trump https://t.co/ZSVITtaFh5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s Enemies Within https://t.co/GZ8h0u9O14]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Spokesman Sean Spicer Explains Planning Details Of Deadly Yemen Raid | Video | RealClearPolitics https://t.co/RGZxk9LeYa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The official @EAMaddenNFL #SB51 Prediction is here! Who are you picking to win? #MyMaddenPrediction = #PatriotsWin https://t.co/2FxOVvOcrt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@true_pundit  would be smarter to use as a down payment for the Wall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DHS Secretary: Travel Ban Not a Ban on Muslims https://t.co/TjJcn0nCOK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mary Matalin: I Dont Want To Sound Like A Trump Groupie, But Im Turning Into One | Video | RealClearPolitics https://t.co/VpH5ZMEYFP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spicer On Mainstream Media: "Theyre Not The Only Game In Town Anymore" | Video | RealClearPolitics https://t.co/NzwXNgtmvh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Special Report Panel: Democrats Delay Committee Votes For Trump Nominees | Video | RealClearPolitics https://t.co/O0rdCt9oOr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dick Durbin: "I Just Don't Remember" If I Voted To Confirm Gorsuch In 2006 (He Did) | Video | RealClearPolitics https://t.co/basrWu8zbP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump At 'Black History Month' Meeting: I Don't Watch CNN, "Don't Like Watching Fake News" | Video | RCP https://t.co/aqPJdHawGY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael Eric Dyson: Donald Trump Is The "Heinous Manifestation" Of White Selfishness | Video | RealClearPolitics https://t.co/STsHGMBIQR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chris Matthews: Gorsuch Vote Will Go To A Filibuster; Democrats Will Not Vote For Him, "Not A One" | Video | RCP https://t.co/7kVxyGPi6W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mother Of Son Killed By Illegal to Pelosi: Which One Of Your Children Is Expendable For An Illegal Life? | RCP https://t.co/vcGlQDFMER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Admin on Islam: "Not A Religious Problem, It Is A Radicalization Problem" | Video | RealClearPolitics https://t.co/WNFnt5Q9Va]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DNC Expels Chairman Candidate From Race for 'Disgusting' Criticism of Islam - Breitbart https://t.co/GtQ9dmTSfh via @BreitbartNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sen. Franken Loses his Cool During Hearing on Session for AG https://t.co/6A2kZ2oVlp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CrusaderTrump @DailyCaller  completely agree! Just leave. Take your debt &amp; your share of the US debt. Return our naval bases.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump  Superb choice!  Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flynn: 'We're Officially Putting Iran on Notice' After Missile Test https://t.co/zsMDGT5ToQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jews gave Muslims keys to synagogue after town mosque burnt town - Business Insider #SmartNews https://t.co/1LvsPp3JfF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArthurNathan  I had to adapt quite. Author unknown BUT great quote!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I don't know(or care) how many attended Trump's inauguration but I can tell you exactly how many attended Hillary's&amp;that is only impt #."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laura Ingraham: Gorsuch is a refreshing change https://t.co/A2VFRELHlK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge Napolitano: Gorsuch is most the Scalia-like pick https://t.co/TvyqQuDsQH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US official: Iran conducts another ballistic missile test https://t.co/YkQRpo1Hfu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tucker Carlson Tonight  1/31/17 | Fox News | January 31, 2017 https://t.co/xhmKIxsFTz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tucker takes on Dem lawmaker on Gorsuch, abortion https://t.co/u3tmEtxAXj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FLASHBACK: Joe Biden blockades George Bush appointment of Supreme Court ... https://t.co/1sX4dJIgGG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2007 SCHUMER CALLING TO BLOCK SUPREME COURT JUSTICE NOMINEE https://t.co/1pc6iKGgZ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The role of Supreme Court Justices under the Constitution https://t.co/K2Q19xgVXu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chris Wallace Confronts McConnell on SCOTUS: ‘Fair Amount of Hypocrisy’ ... Garland https://t.co/9pNVLkPFfY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biden in '92: Supreme Court Nominee Should Wait https://t.co/cghcH2gkaN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About 900 State Department officials sign protest memo: source https://t.co/WcTPCq8aBU via @YahooCanada. RESIGN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frank Sinatra - You Will Be My Music https://t.co/nhReH2XX0G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Krauthammer: Dems have their playbook against SCOTUS pick https://t.co/hCl5TWgzjt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Newt Gingrich Full Interview On Fox &amp; Friends (1/31/2017) https://t.co/uvN8Sxn5l6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WATCH President Donald Trumps Press Secretary Sean Spicer Press Briefing... https://t.co/KHQP6AHEDd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schumer 2015: "Refugee Ban Necessary" - Schumer 2017: "Trump Is Mean." CRYING! - YouTube https://t.co/L9jL3B62kc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/itJ0KrHxC9 via @youtube    Schumer speaking out of both sides of mouth on vetting of immigrants]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OliviaMesser @thedailybeast  Dear Senator thanks for your thoughts. We will approach this the way we planned.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TPInsidr deciding to filibuster before you even know the name of the nominee tells you a lot about the Dem's obstructionism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DLoesch @pw_cunningham one consequence is the Dems show us what we knew about them already]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TwitchyTeam  Just because she can sing does NOT mean she can think about what is in the best interests of the US.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DailyCaller  it isn't Islamaphobia when they really want to kill you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dapandico1 @Getaclue77 @DailySignal   They need to keep their word &amp; resign - we relied on their word!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's Supreme Court nomination willcome TOMORROW, not Thursday https://t.co/s9pFumHre9 via @MailOnline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hannity 1⁄30⁄17 ¦ Fox News ¦ January 30, 2017 https://t.co/dwGP605bXb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEWS ALERT , President Donald Trump Latest News Today 1/31/17 , White Ho... https://t.co/2aJJv6kjz3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimesofIsrael  How many terrorists came to the US from their group?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump fires acting AG for defying immigration ban https://t.co/1npjd9yvpA via @nypost COMPLETELY APPROPRIATE ACTION]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxNews @KellyannePolls  I guess we will need to change the filibuster rules!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimesofIsrael  She has been fired!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DailyCaller Amazon, have you been hiring many refugees from the 7 countries on the list?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump fires acting AG for defying immigration ban https://t.co/1npjd9yvpA via @nypost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Acting attorney general orders DOJ not to defend Trump's travel ban https://t.co/vmNNfeAsCF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DailyCaller totally insane]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump signs executive order to cut regulations on businesses - https://t.co/lnt3PrenK6 https://t.co/EtYaM0sZPC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graham: Trump Does Not Violate The Bible By Protecting Americans https://t.co/flcVOcdYGw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['People who were praying lost their lives': 6 killed in Quebec City mosque shooting https://t.co/VsScf9c0vi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High Court Precedent May Limit Trump’s ‘Sanctuary City’ Order  https://t.co/x4WeSrbYjr via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill de Blasio Has Trouble Differing Trump's Immigration Policy With Oba... https://t.co/OnzHkPqFbE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America's News HQ 1⁄29⁄17 ¦ Fox News ¦ January 29, 2017 https://t.co/rDON4RLtZA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Media Buzz with Howard Kurtz 1⁄29⁄17 ¦ Fox News ¦ January 29, 2017 https://t.co/Mf5NqrFn9O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The truth about feminism and Islam https://t.co/bV4YCKAEmv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump reveals new U.S. attitude to China https://t.co/Wyxd2Xiegx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FaceTheNation @keithellison Have any Mormons or 7th Day Adventists committed acts of terrorism in the last 15 years?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any Mormons or 7th Day Adventists committing acts of terrorism?

https://t.co/Z5IA3C1WBQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[⚡️ “White House weathers storm of criticism over immigration order”

https://t.co/Z5IA3C1WBQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MiaChandlerGOP greater chance of me jumping out my 32oor window&amp;flying to SuperBowl, playing QB &amp; winning game with 7TD passes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dcexaminer Considering Iran is the most significant state sponsor of terrorism, we really don't care what you think about this issue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watters' World 1⁄28⁄17 ¦ Fox News ¦ January 28, 2017 https://t.co/XeLC0tLV1x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fox &amp; Friends Weekend 1⁄28⁄17 ¦ Fox News ¦ January 28, 2017 https://t.co/ehnKbwzfb6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Greg Gutfeld Show 1⁄28⁄17 ¦ Fox News ¦ January 28, 2017 https://t.co/ENdCrPPmVK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justice With Judge Jeanine 1/28/17 | Fox News | January 28, 2017 https://t.co/xpgaXgdYIZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@true_pundit  Great idea! If you are here illegally then you should leave. What part of illegal do you not understand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WSJ  Merle's &amp; May -read Trump's order. You can take all of these people during the next 120 days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@true_pundit  why should we care about what Zuckerberg thinks?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Reuters it is a 120 day ban so we can develop a vetting plan that works to protect the US. Don't want to be like Germany!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jackie Mason Video Blog 19 on "Health &amp; Fitness" https://t.co/NqTeePeLcB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jake Tapper: "Muslims Biggest Victim Of Islamic Terrorism" | Video | RealClearPolitics https://t.co/xIt2pnwTWQ  SO WHAT?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maher: Liberals Must Examine Why We Keep Losing Elections; We Protect Feelings, Demand Apologies | RCP https://t.co/sDrzhriHLU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gingrich: Americans Much More Comfortable With Pences Speech Than Madonnas Speech | Video | RealClearPolitics https://t.co/Xfa6FxGzgO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Washington Posts Eugene Robinson: "I Dont Need Steve Bannons Permission To Do My Job" | Video | RCP https://t.co/DSMlpQzzUk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dem Sen. Al Franken: "We Have A Strategy" To Resist Trump, But Im Not Going To Share | Video | RealClearPolitics https://t.co/hnhqKRnYKz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Hannity Interview: Trump On "Dishonest" Media, Border, SCOTUS, RealClearPolitics https://t.co/7UDZwufcvR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Weekly Address: An Update On What We Have Accomplished | Video | RealClearPolitics https://t.co/B1RVsqdnlY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump signs memorandum to defeat ISIS, executive order to curtail ex-officials from lobbying |  https://t.co/hvyN2vb8Eg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federal judge grants stay to allow those with visas to remain, 10 still detained at JFK |  https://t.co/z6O54trQRx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[California campaign to secede gains momentum https://t.co/34tBqdTZ5G via @YahooNews BYE BYE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jackie Mason: Donald Trump is magic right now https://t.co/eHQvxC4v8W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Reuters   Why would a rational US person want to go to Iran?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/mfEME5e2Cy A BEAUTIFUL SIGHT - THE END OF A COLOSSAL ERROR]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>