<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Recording midi with construction behind me. No big deal... Step one of recording my next album is well underway… https://t.co/daG5NOhNAQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You in the crowd? Tag yourself. #summercity #wellington @wgtncc https://t.co/GWFBDekLCh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My last gig for a while is tonight in the Sound Shell in the Botanic Gardens @WgtnCC #summercity #wellington https://t.co/k8DeWgoZhm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's fucking @PJHarveyUK and @JohnParish50 - bow down #Wellington https://t.co/pbA2OuaXkX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Local Legends and rising music stars will grace the Soundshell stage" See you Saturday! https://t.co/6fd8EeLoOD @WellyEvents #summercity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#wellington #morning #wind #ugh https://t.co/uZ0PuJU1AC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#morning #wellington https://t.co/KcFPsOQlMt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just Announced: Wellington, New Zealand - Jan 28 at Meridian... https://t.co/QlPZBNHJM1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such a stage presence. This is to make up for the lack of audio on my last video. Don't know what happened… https://t.co/TgohZQ8ujs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was pretty close to #NickCave last night... Actually got much closer than this. I stole his mojo for my next albu… https://t.co/e9i5hbrsY2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today: Wellington, New Zealand - Jan 7 at MOON https://t.co/KpDvm0oooZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sound check for @birdeatsbaby @NewtownMoon 8:30 tonight. My last big gig for album time and Mishkin sounds fantasti… https://t.co/ep4Gsij34q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My last big gig (potentially) until after album is done. Saturday @NewtownMoon Tickets here:  https://t.co/KtsSz5SILs #Wellington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#wtf #wellington at least I have my swim suit with me... Not quite what I was hoping for. https://t.co/vfwe1zzMmH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posters are up for my next gig!! Happening this Saturday at @NewtownMoon #wellington #nzmusic @birdeatsbaby https://t.co/vanUF138lP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just Announced: Wellington, New Zealand - Jan 7 at MOON https://t.co/sKkBA9Eiph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#cardsagainsthumanity #newyears #2017 https://t.co/w3dJqYxnWX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My family knows what I want for Xmas #nailedit #IpreferOregonmadepoop #bigfoot https://t.co/y30uhP9LOZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tried to do a fun selfie. But my attempts to "eat" the mountains just looked like I was having a… https://t.co/6WeyNFWgNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Burning in the Southland sun on Christmas... #burning #yesitgetssunnyhere… https://t.co/USETywhRtE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what it looks like when you have Xmas drinks until late and then wake up at 5am for a… https://t.co/YWSpO79cIQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not playing many more gigs in the next little bit, so get your butt down to this one. Ruth… https://t.co/xdNVJlY3Cm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today: Wellington, New Zealand - Dec 18 at Red Moon Collective https://t.co/WmDkxSJ7FO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the "what is this fucking gig?" pose... Well, it's Red Moon Collective $10 doors at 7:30… https://t.co/8kidPt8fQ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What it feels like for a girl.... Listen to every word of this https://t.co/VmLTnQ9xez @Madonna #womeninmusic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Weekend: Wellington, New Zealand - Dec 18 at Red Moon C... https://t.co/B5auQKSzxy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've got the bean bag and a water gun in case anyone bothers me. They're setting up the rope… https://t.co/OMjkTJcNwA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flew to #nelsonnz for the day for our work Xmas party. Wined and dined on a yacht for the day,… https://t.co/4OBUVMe5CY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just Announced: Wellington, New Zealand - Dec 18 at Red Moon... https://t.co/AIQCBNgrkK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#elfontheshelf #Flatmate https://t.co/9DyMW0NcdJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because you watched Cabin in the Woods, you should watch The Never Ending Story!!! Oh, thank you… https://t.co/2QgLs3NWud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Came back to work on Monday to this on my work phone... This is what happens when the office… https://t.co/Klx4FSpFjH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Titan at Moon #now #wellington https://t.co/hPRxN1cXFo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Wellington being unappealing yet again #whyIputupwithyourshit https://t.co/W4axDbCLWP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happening now at Caroline ruthmundy https://t.co/BunulzQtyf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Music starts at Caroline in 20 min! With ruthmundy @abbywolfemusic #wellington https://t.co/iM0kvHUosA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The moment the construction workers in your back yard catch you taking a selfie of the first… https://t.co/D9vusidyP6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Omg, I'm home!! 4 gigs in like 24ish hours. Tour done... Now back to focusing on the album.… https://t.co/n8FarlQDO9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One more gig to go and this little tour is done.... playing on the ferry again on my way back to… https://t.co/qcS0cnNrZy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jhan Lindsay finishing up at East Street in #nelsonnz I'm on next with my new synthy songs.… https://t.co/4NxHx4EEuW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today: Nelson, New Zealand - Nov 26 at East Street https://t.co/WolPAmH2YE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jhan playing a little lunch jazz set in Picton lecafepicton before we head to Nelson. #nelsonnz https://t.co/ou80R9chrY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I look half naked in this photo... Almost to Picton! Jhan Lindsay is gonna play at lecafepicton… https://t.co/TpwQ6zsIuI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On our way to the #southisland for a gig in #nelsonnz tonight - 7:30pm at East Street Cafe. But… https://t.co/rirwUUA5DH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting ready for the last leg of my tour in #nelsonnz tomorrow at East Street, and hungry but… https://t.co/BmK0cH37ER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Weekend: Nelson, New Zealand - Nov 26 at East Street https://t.co/fNhu8x0bkG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just Announced: Nelson, New Zealand - Nov 26 at East Street https://t.co/dWB3LCvtBy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come to Moon! New music from my second album tonight! #newtown #wellington https://t.co/2MXNt27eWj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today: Wellington, New Zealand - Nov 20 at MOON https://t.co/PTanwCNUjY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just letting you know I'm all good here after the 7.8  earthquake that hit New Zealand this week - I was in Auckland that night. Take care.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Working, come to The Wine Cellar and say hi. #gigs #auckland https://t.co/hc9brLTe7K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sound guy: I want people to come to this gig so they can hear the prophet through the PA. The Wine Cellar #auckland https://t.co/YpnUPRVY2b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today: Auckland, New Zealand - Nov 13 at The Wine Cellar https://t.co/bq2oqbrQNq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another tour animal, giving me their vibes for my gig at The Wine Cellar tonight. #nzmusic… https://t.co/lMCuAG10iJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had an epic day exploring the North Shore, finding secret beaches. #auckland… https://t.co/4HsVn1VGOb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ha ha ha! I'm on tour officially! In Auckland for the weekend with a gig on Sunday at The Wine… https://t.co/FwH7zEpI7T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Weekend: Auckland, New Zealand - Nov 13 at The Wine Cellar https://t.co/7O89NZj2Er]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Newspaper in New Zealand. #nailedit https://t.co/UGBAheYKc3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Met a tough deadline. Drinks time, next I prep for the album recordings #MusicLife #ugh #teeth https://t.co/O8CFZGf8RN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's been a year since my review in @nzlistener #nzmusic #intheshallows https://t.co/hNY2FdsbtA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markcubey thank you! What email can I reach you on? Hard to go into detail on Twitter, but should be more about publicist work than RNZ.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@markcubey Cristine Angus recommended I get in touch about a music publicity matter. I'm a welly muso -would I be able to email you about it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just Announced: Auckland, New Zealand - Nov 13 at The Wine Cellar https://t.co/vlZKpFUjbm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got my #itfollows shirt #horrorgeek @itfollowsfilm https://t.co/lecDs4k0eo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My synth is being cared for by another being tonight. For a few weeks actually. I miss it already #prophet6 #custody https://t.co/lAJ7jpeqCY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love Tool. That is a fact. @mjkeenan 
https://t.co/pnm7NaMD6c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to @kererubrewingco for the gluten free beer!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am gluten free &amp; boring &amp; don't eat naughty food... But today I get beer and pizza. #Winner @HELLpizza666 https://t.co/xFs2pA5kD5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help! Have you listened to my album? Could  you write me a little review? I'm gathering feedback of what fans think of the album. Message me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We have an office #doggie! Don't have to raise it or clean up after it. All my dreams have come true! #winning https://t.co/8rN4HwkQNW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to meet up with @nameulkwoe for a coffee and some #music chat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A year ago today was the first day of my massive #intheshallows #albumrelease tour with Jhan Lindsay. Time flies. https://t.co/W3jM2VBSat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snarl face at @thecrosswgtn last night. Hard to look pretty and angry at the same time #sadsongs #Wellington https://t.co/k3ReMbyKhL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today: Wellington, New Zealand - Sep 28 at Southern Cross https://t.co/wBk1M8D5vr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Announcement! Recording my second album in a few months. Most written on #synth and less on piano. #Music evolution. https://t.co/u4Amyqa2gs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over a year since the release of my music video for Whisper. That was a solid block of hard work. https://t.co/NCLF6L59hT #music #wellington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I told you I have an #announcement coming... You'll have to wait till next week to find out! #secrets #NZmusic https://t.co/IdyxLX2czy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Fan #art!! I'm so honoured! Thanks so much Wayne Wolfson! Check out his other works here: https://t.co/gDlHvra5Cd https://t.co/cuF06hWg95]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[100% approval rate by the sound guy at all gigs with the synth... #soundguylove #wellington #synthlife https://t.co/CNhDbtycjX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm Number 98 out of all songs. Great review too from another Wellingtonian. #wellington https://t.co/rcaswSNdqT https://t.co/2iFPzImw2y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today: Wellington, New Zealand - Sep 10 at Cabaret L'amour Dinner Cabaret https://t.co/rfHPZE7M3H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Weekend: Wellington, New Zealand - Sep 10 at Cabaret L'amour Dinner Cabaret https://t.co/eZq9vFqSRc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Played a sneaky first synth gig tonight and didn't tell you. #sneaky #synthlove #wellington https://t.co/zfh24iA0DV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm in the newspaper. Gonna be playing music at a #burlesque show this weekend #wellington https://t.co/seQfoBjqbD https://t.co/ONtr99kb4J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posted a new photo: https://t.co/c4J5h3DOlq https://t.co/NXaoGMEc3h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posted a new photo: https://t.co/PUELVXuj4q https://t.co/NXaoGMEc3h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posted a new photo: https://t.co/eBcDGb2L4m https://t.co/NXaoGMEc3h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posted a new photo: https://t.co/OfiH3WkO8F https://t.co/NXaoGMEc3h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posted a new photo: https://t.co/XnORPazq6k https://t.co/NXaoGMEc3h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posted a new photo: https://t.co/jJwLCgRUn0 https://t.co/NXaoGMEc3h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posted a new photo: https://t.co/TCkA82P6FW https://t.co/NXaoGMEc3h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posted a new photo: https://t.co/XvOBxefbtC https://t.co/NXaoGMEc3h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posted a new photo: https://t.co/LxfAB4zTfz https://t.co/NXaoGMEc3h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posted a new photo: https://t.co/7g7f5xyxqJ https://t.co/NXaoGMEc3h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posted a new photo: https://t.co/jv6ma4WbYM https://t.co/NXaoGMEc3h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posted a new photo: https://t.co/0cxm74EsgQ https://t.co/NXaoGMEc3h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posted a new photo: https://t.co/BCsaVQClMO https://t.co/NXaoGMEc3h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posted a new photo: https://t.co/F1z0l5T139 https://t.co/NXaoGMEc3h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posted a new photo: https://t.co/juyJLDpnSp https://t.co/NXaoGMEc3h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posted a new photo: https://t.co/FTmS5nXCLX https://t.co/NXaoGMEc3h]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>