<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[2017 &amp; still no behaviour support after infamous blue cage affair - letter to Education Minister -... https://t.co/MzUz6nneR5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SOfASD reminding the ACT Government that when we ask questions, we'd like answers: https://t.co/Bvcbi7Gxud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulation to team for autistic women submission to UN https://t.co/DWIUMkORLg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fight back against false Centrelink debt threats https://t.co/gUN0i5Y17z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CPSUnion there are two issue - staffing and corrupt immoral policy. Better to talk about them separately.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Government fabricates welfare debt, demands payment in 28 days - but takes 50 days to process a review. How is... https://t.co/sNGaCkllQA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Government's fake welfare debt scam invokes mental health problems.... https://t.co/pz0vAH61ep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump improves access to comedy, everywhere ... including for the Dutch. https://t.co/xyEsGwOCcr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dan_Bourchier @ZedSeselja @GaiBrodtmannMP @abccanberra Just ensure Centrelink gets payment right in the first place - no debt scam needed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[just saw, on an old Spicks and Specks episode (with Finbar Fury), that in 2007 the Governor-General gave George... https://t.co/JqpdnlOgB4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Productivity Commission is reviewing the NDIS. https://t.co/UNIvCISQ6D https://t.co/DMevp9eGye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@welfare_rights @ACOSS scamming/defrauding our most vulnerable (&amp; illiterate) citizens is cruel and immoral. It's disability discrimination.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cporterwa @AlanTudgeMP @ScottMorrisonMP scamming/defraud nation's most vulnerable to balance your Budget. That's just cruel and immoral.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#notmydebt targeting autistic people, people with intellectual disability and/or anxiety is disability... https://t.co/6chDtw8Nop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@canberratimes fabricated debt scam affects intellectually disabled, clinically anxious and illiterate Aussies most. It's discrimination!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GetUp Centrelink must drop its use of "customers" and replace it with "victims". They are targeting the anxious and intellectually disabled]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do you get rid of foot fungus?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A4 media release and letter to the Minister - https://t.co/V3kSv0YpOC https://t.co/cmlD2s5ook]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[noticing that none (not a one) of my LinkedIn contacts endorses me as a musician. I'm unsure how I feel about that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the Centrelink debt fabrication scam is an utter disgrace. It is cruel and very dangerous. #notmydebt https://t.co/XxUEDnRu2j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[waiting on hold for Centrelink? Add your own debt fabrication story to the #notmydebt website -... https://t.co/uzUXEMdjik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@autismcrisis @DrBrocktagon is that what "inclusive" means?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[did the Government/Centrelink cut off your Pensioner Education Supplement (PES)? Here are some suggestions about... https://t.co/u1A1r1tAck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ask the NDIA a question, just do not expect an answer - https://t.co/EhaQof5PlD - NDIS ceased in ACT... https://t.co/EXc9pRuZ92]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[politician meets business at footy? Yet Minister not met autism peak body (A4) since 2013 election... https://t.co/HLOaD8qJcW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[politician meeting business - yet Minister not met autism peak body (A4) since 2013 election... https://t.co/poiQ5DKvnF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A4 asked government to cease its debt fabrication debacle. https://t.co/Jf62S8OAlZ https://t.co/kU7KNBvXXi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[surely asking for money you are not owed is fraud. How is Centrelink's attack on our most vulnerable citizen's... https://t.co/mSGHHEvuQ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@canberratimes well that's just who you want defending Ms Ley MP's use of privileged access to tax-payer dollars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noeltowell @theage DSS name is no longer appropriate; it must be renamed Dept of Insecurity and Centrelink Kruelty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cporterwa @JanePrentice_MP Your Department must be renamed - may Department of Insecurity, Centrelink and Kruelty. https://t.co/AiIQdKna3M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cporterwa jail for the not guilty! How many undiagnosed autistic people end up like this? https://t.co/49iATR6CiV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gerardthomas_1 @newscomauHQ census, NDIS portal not working &gt;6 months, NBN, etc. it's called "innovation".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LindaBurneyMP @GetUp and there's no sign that any person with disability has to step down from their role. #notmydebt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noeltowell @canberratimes @cporterwa possibly Centrelink could be sued for defamation as well. Citizens cannot trust Government. :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Heartless to the core': autistic man chased by Centrelink debt collector https://t.co/QiNol1Js3B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shameful! Centrelink demands money it isn't owed from autistic young man:  https://t.co/gEks7mCfnq https://t.co/xdzEvElMMj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CDA39 @WilkieMP if people with disability are represented disproportionately, this policy may also be disability discrimination.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SquigglyRick @Birmo Cwth Education Minister right to be sceptical about disability numbers in schools -... https://t.co/E4ljd0hdwg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnaSamways a false believe that religion is meant to help with morality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnaSamways the myth that democracy works. :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CDA39 @daruvic the report says if the standards were not used then the students data was omitted. There is no measure of compliance here :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas message from A4 to Minister for Social Security https://t.co/8PQVAdn5MT https://t.co/I5nhCE5heg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[free access to Autism journal until end-January https://t.co/na3wDojfPM
Are there any research... https://t.co/VxAYw0ErlS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AfdoOffice WTF - page 5 - if the school doesn't follow disability standard in education then omit the student's data. Data is not credible!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@birmo @SquigglyRick no surprise here. The NCCD was designed to fail students with disability - just as described. https://t.co/RAmMlx8FGD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesMerlinoMP @CatiaMalaquias @Milliganreports @birmo clearly safety and wellbeing is NOT number one priority. We are not fooled.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Autism language matters. Can we get lots of responses please? https://t.co/H4wl4NqauF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConversationEDU prove E=mc^2 was a question in my HSC physics exam - in 1967. They should still teach the basics today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBuckl3y and specific issues relating to autism (from the UK) https://t.co/SOyl6nsfNL - little autism awareness in Aussie health system]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[issues for people with disability in the health system:... https://t.co/r4F9RBYKGU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CDA39 @JanePrentice_MP Good! But many autistic people completely excluded from any employment at all. Better employment outcomes are needed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@admonkeystrator @ACOSS @LaLegale @cassandragoldie politicians promote this myth - so employers don't offer jobs for people with disability.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ACOSS @cassandragoldie growth in autism rates continues, but government call autistic people rorters, bludgers. leaners - hence no jobs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RossJoyce_CEO @AfdoOffice here a relevant report for autistic people: https://t.co/SOyl6nsfNL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SquigglyRick if they waited until it was all sorted, the NDIS would not have happened at all. Yes, it was rushed. But that's a good thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scimeetsbiz @AutismCRC HCWA data (use in AMA's analysis) massively underestimates ASD age-of-diagnosis in Australi… https://t.co/qUlI9J6Plk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HChristinaR Australia does not have a "justice system", it has a legal system - especially in relation to disability.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SOfASD and A4 are keen to hear how accessible advocacy support is for NDIS appeals for autistic children... https://t.co/r8arrPwinL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[a UK report on autism and their health system... https://t.co/gVdDE6I6iL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[increasing autism/ASD diagnoses not just in Australia -... https://t.co/nk3j7e53JW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A4 words on government support plan for carer supports - https://t.co/g6pHgmExoK - all image no substance. https://t.co/YxxSW3rui6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A4 comments on government plan for disability employment - https://t.co/ldBNtZNsuM - some practical suggestions. https://t.co/mXga3u9iRF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Refund Holly O'Sullivans Disability Funding - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/vURSJ4BKco]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sent in 2 submissions this morning - employment and carers - https://t.co/ffltk7AK6B https://t.co/4F67DZaZmV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@noeltowell Finding won't stop politicians and government officials basing disability policy on misinformation and prejudice. :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SquigglyRick Erratic decisions from the Information Commissioner. Won't let me see DSS autism data as I might know everyone with autism!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WA not in the NDIS - WA citizens have questions - https://t.co/6mHB0fpSyP https://t.co/VwH55GLv36]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[is it legal, or moral, for a politician to ask your name &amp; address ... and who you vote for?... https://t.co/wQjCKFbicK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evattaus @AusHumanRights If it meant it, it would have created the law that is required. Australia didn't, there it's not serious. :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alisonamountain @AusHumanRights @MagdaSzubanski In reality, HRC is there to convince the United Nations that Australia is doing gr8.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alisonamountain @AusHumanRights @MagdaSzubanski I doubt that Aussie politicians (of either major party) will let that happen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AusHumanRights @MickGooda @GuardianAus so-called Behaviour Management Unit without behaviour management professional in sight. No problem?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DisabilityEmplt @Ausattitude @Graemeinnes would business employ rorters, bludgers and "leaners" - how Govt describes people with disability]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DisabilityEmplt @Ausattitude @Graemeinnes electing governments that enhance competition - excluding people who don't compete so well :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this woman has balls. https://t.co/Iz3tYsqOW0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TriciaMalowney @nswcid Autism Aspergers Advocacy Australia (A4) has 50% neurodivergent (33% autistic); 83% living with autism/ASD.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EoinKillackey @PatMcGorry autism isn't even mentioned in burden estimates. What is that about?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@frankie_iorfino @PatMcGorry @susanley Autism is excluded from burden of disease and mental health reporting - see https://t.co/U2OEEH3uUZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Louise_Thornton that been entrenched for a long time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lenoretaylor there is evidence that consuming faeces treats some gut dysfunctions effectively. Fake news only benefits when it is funny.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AUMentalHealth hmmm. The @aihw says there is no (0, zero) autism in Australia - not reported here https://t.co/U2OEEH3uUZ or elsewhere :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AUMentalHealth AMA's media release -https://t.co/GU66ZTNZzH - sadly ASD diagnoses are much later than figures the… https://t.co/W1Q1rKSNOV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FB says I liked 141 things this year. My year was much better than that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VEOHRC @Graemeinnes governments call people with disability rorters, bludgers and "leaners". Not much incentive for inclusion. :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VEOHRC @Graemeinnes and employment rates for autistic people and people with intellectual disability are significantly worse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AMA's media release on ASD - https://t.co/kR0c0kyl6L https://t.co/owCBGNHb0z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks AMA. Better autism awareness helps. 
BTW, diagnosis is typically later than you think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amapresident @AutismAwareAus @couriermail @Sue_Dunlevy thanks for this. But only 50% of autistic children are diag… https://t.co/2uN8TjcUPT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DownSyndromeAu response does not address the issue raised. Government using my tax to pay public servants who aren't do a proper job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DownSyndromeAu your letter shows their senior staff do not know enough to design effective policy. Taxpayers want better value for money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[disability employment rate would determine politicians' pay if they were serious -... https://t.co/F9ibR89OvR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrBrocktagon @Macquarie_Uni been there, done that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuliaGillardGPE @Birmo Aussie law protects &amp; promotes disability discrimination - in education, employment ...  everywhere :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuliaGillardGPE @Birmo In Purvis vs NSW and Walker vs Vic children are denied education https://t.co/DBojy7nWF1 &amp; https://t.co/mJbfsHRmns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian Autism Alliance | Australia's Strong Voice For Autism https://t.co/oUWT3Gq9Yg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[new Australian Autism Alliance - https://t.co/BpGntMm2sU https://t.co/hRPgnC1Yxw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and the NDIS isn't really helping with this :( https://t.co/SOtiQhxNIO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OK, I've had a week to cool down (without effect). Is it just me, or is the attitude expressed from the... https://t.co/jKtcas9RQY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DisabilityO @The_NDL 18% of Aussies have disability. Immigration should ensure 18% of immigrants have varying levels of disability.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>