<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzfatmatt hopefully added to the atmosphere of the location]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interview on our southern world record, with @SusieFergusonNZ &amp; @radionz, from the southern ocean: https://t.co/nfpjshf4lz #RossSeaTrip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Karina_Joy you mean residents or their guests? Who would that be?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Karina_Joy we're going to see what the weather, time and track line into Chch gives us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vsvictory thanks. Btw, being interviewed by National Radio over satellite tmrw at 8.50am about our furtherest South ship record!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vsvictory we're a small team that creates private charters to polar regions under EYOS Expeditions. If you hv a private ship, we can help]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vsvictory me personally? Assistant expedition leader, lecturer and zodiac driver...?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ordered my zodiac passengers to abandon ship last week, they were very happy to comply! #RossSeaTrip, Antarctica https://t.co/yDvSUxPv6L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Karina_Joy yes it has been remarkable. Though the calm weather meant Cape Royds/Evans are still in fast ice &amp; we missed them unfortunately]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@farmerjase thanks. Just my iPhone ones too. Just sailing back from far side of Ross Sea tonight. We're closer to Argentina than NZ at mo!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would be the 1st humans to have ever walked here, Barlett Bay, Cape Colbeck, Antarctica #RossSeaTrip https://t.co/0IFZdjzuyB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freezing cold today at Barlett Bay, in a freezing cold corner of the Ross Sea #RossSeaTrip https://t.co/wctP82La8Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hottriggered I've seen a few seals in my time &amp; this has to rate as the most strikingly beautiful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WOW! Spotted my first Ross Seal today after 18 trips to Antarctica. Seen by so few people. So little known about it… https://t.co/bKKD5EoCK4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Setting off to cut an ice landing staircase into the southern most piece of coast in the world, Bay of Whales, Antarctica #RossSeaTrip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Standby for world record attempt at the southern most  vessel EVER, later today #RossSeaTrip https://t.co/G7bOQy8EZu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Into the Bay of Whales, always hoping to set a furtherest South record for a ship #RossSeaTrip https://t.co/H3J7AoCmUY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sitting having a brew, watching the Ross Ice-shelf slide past the window; the odd Emperor penguin too. #RossSeaTrip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shebaandkate has all the prerequisites for polar work, looks good on paper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pv_reynolds @pv_reynolds flippers back and striding out. Right foot down behind the bristle tail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lukeappleby not of that sorry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lukeappleby large colony nearby. Some just use us as a landing site, &amp; sometimes a refuge from predators. Happened 10x y'day. They hop out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unexpected passenger, Franklin Island, #RossSeaTrip, Antarctica https://t.co/naSZ2oHwbv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a terrible day to be Kayaking in Terra Nova Bay, Antarctica, around blue icebergs. #RossSeaTrip https://t.co/0QQlozj97k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vaughndavis sure is. Into Mario Zuccelli base tomorrow. Perhaps we'll get their signature stealthy low pass over the ship in a twin otter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drygalski Ice Tongue is a 92km long floating glacier in Antarctica. A 1/2km x 30m face collapsed before us today. I… https://t.co/IS1pxUcWnH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another day mucking around in boats. Bless. #RossSeaTrip Antarctica https://t.co/QM9bUhcuzK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brycepearce serious question? Background knowledge, experience, skill set &amp; any extra 'bonus' skills. Give me a call in a fortnight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brycepearce another blue sky day today. Soon to get my zodiac amongst the Drygalski ice tongue, one of world's longest floating glaciers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couldn't be happier than a boy with a boat amongst the pack ice. 2 emperor penguins found. Smoko time. #RossSeaTrip https://t.co/XekChotwNe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pushing pack ice. #RossSeaTrip Antarctica https://t.co/GsaJauLoO7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Driving my zodiac at midnight, under Mt Herschel, #RossSeaTrip Antarctica. Sir Ed climbed it in '67 I believe https://t.co/JvnfnHoPDK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah nah, good to be back in the Ross Sea. Adelies for Africa #RossSeaTrip https://t.co/xVVhtdhGkV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back at Cape Adare, Ross Sea, Antarctica. Home to the 1st dwelling on a continent. Can't wait to start driving zodi… https://t.co/e3iHR4dWM6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brenakiwi Yes. A path less travelled. I've been past a few times, but never seen them in the fog or snow storms before]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Balleny Islands, 2000km south of NZ. Midnight last night - our last sunset for a while #Antarctica. #RossSeaTrip https://t.co/T05PYDmXVm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dilemma - passing one of the most remote island chains in the world, stay up all night or get sleep? #RossSeaTrip https://t.co/vdoN3FXU2a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just arrived at the Balleny Islands, 2000km south of New Zealand #RossSeaTrip https://t.co/xhAHsYNKLy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@farmgeek I'm deep in the southern ocean, below 60 degrees, and we haven't even seen that much yet!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out our Southwards journey to the Ross Sea Antarctica https://t.co/amwBAv607x #RossSeaTrip https://t.co/EAPTArVwxQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like I'm going to have a go at underwater ROV piloting. Add that to my lever twiddling excavator &amp; drone flyi… https://t.co/D4bSzVhf6Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're heading out of Hobart, Ross Sea Antarctica next stop #RossSeaTrip https://t.co/SYS0kR3r04]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SusieFergusonNZ good to hear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been blowing its proverbials off in Hobart. Feels like home. #RossSeaTrip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@agwomanchelsea sorry I meant which ship/company. Who was your EL?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SusieFergusonNZ how did the camping go?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LilyLivingstone have you told her about social media hinges?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@agwomanchelsea who were you with? And more to the point, did you find Ramos Generales cafe/deli in Ushuaia?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty cool, I'm in Oz, but the wild rabbits at the farm keep emailing me #robsfarm https://t.co/SzRYNtvyWl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevDaly yip, and the ship's booking agent pays top $ for flights too I see. @airnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevDaly scrub that, jst found  bloody @airnz hv unilaterally decided to dishonor seamans books 4 months ago. +$120 to get a bag to Melb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kimi_collins what species of pickle is it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Toa5t obviously full of confidence fresh from their success in getting Mexico to pay for the wall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevDaly logs time at sea/position &amp; if you're travelling to or from a ship overseas you normally get 40kgs &amp; extra bag with it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Seaman's discharge book', perennial source of mirth for some #RossSeaTrip https://t.co/jnWbUT6ktT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last kiwi dunner before the Ross Sea journey, fush and chups on Petone Beach with an IPA. Perfect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pestproof @mecha_genki related to one of our incredible native versions we found in Taranaki once: https://t.co/POotfLZKhk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@warnersl 1) obligatory for visitors I think? 2) u can never take going to the Ross Sea too seriously no? Lkg forward seeing everyone again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@warnersl Hobart on Sunday I believe. How's Australia been treating you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlastairJNZ thanks. Bloody Instagram ruins a perfectly good in camera crop too though ;-&gt; @NZGeographic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JMulliganRNZ did I just hear there was a fire at Jesse Point on Rat Peak in Queenstown?! You writing the news too?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LachlanForsyth back on the Tele! That didn't take long]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PolarKimbo off to the Ross Sea with you I see next week. This is becoming way too regular, people might talk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brycepearce very thought provoking read and very challenging for some]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NZ, on the road to becoming the Detroit of agriculture?  Do some thinking about this: https://t.co/buNvFgMNQE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Singapore Airlines flight to Canberra out of Wellington sure makes itself known just now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out SmartStart, new Govt initiative to merge multi-dept contacts into a one stop shop. Smart work: https://t.co/4pxtg2XXve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarabeee I think my Elna does that and a few others ;-&gt;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hochylora not to mention copyright @petapixel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kiwinerd interesting to know, I use 'snell's window' regularly in photography: https://t.co/LuBE9vXCJo @FeyHag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brenakiwi boycott them. I have to pay staff for not even working &amp; then pay cafes' surcharges too. Should factor it into costs annually]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@blairdrysdale77 good to hear. Many seem to hv bought the media/SM story that 2016 was bad; #Lemmings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2016 wasn't a shit year. I had a flippin' top year, &amp; so did most of you I suspect. Have a top 2017 also. Kia ora tatou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrowFromHereNZ happened to a friend on the picton ferry once. Destroyed the leather inside of their Damlier. Only time she saw her dad cry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@macgibbons thanks. Don't think we'll even make it that far. Big day thru Molesworth &amp; Rainbow Road. Will be good to be home to bed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LilyLivingstone it's a sign]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@macgibbons we passed on the Strait I see. All the best for 2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off to the Ross Sea in a few weeks, but there looks like a lot of sea ice about still. Hmm https://t.co/yCLhd9N8sP #Antarctica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matteastnz I should've parked the jeep in front and gone for a peaceful tramp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matteastnz tempting. DOC nds to consider whether it's appropriate to hv jetskis in a pristine alpine lake enjoyed for wilderness values]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@teradar yes, my brother owns one, and he just happens to deliver the 9m old products of aforementioned organs too. All bases covered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Olivefarmer very true. Can't remember what Winston had to do with it, was he onboard?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hariata it's actually a kids titanic slide, but yeah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hariata all about him, to hell with the trampers and tourists enjoying the serenity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picton knows a good New Years party, complete with Wahine reenactment. Awkward https://t.co/FmWcjXoJ3Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turn up at remote beautiful wild Lake Tennyson this morning, &amp; some Audi driver decides to hell with peace &amp; tranqu… https://t.co/2w5wGkSEE9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@E2NZ check all the DOC science and research series papers online, they should be in there. I used to commission it. @DolphinEnc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@E2NZ plenty of tightly managed restrictions, including a daily no interaction period based on research relevant to area/species @DolphinEnc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Out looking for dolphins off #Kaikoura early this morning with @DolphinEnc. Open for business since #eqnz https://t.co/His58yu8qB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BR3NDA what would you expect after compulsory military indoctrination, free thinking? @LostArcNZ @nz_voter @SirWB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RexWiderstrom exactly. Organic milk powder $15k/tonne, ours $2-3k/t. Cld hv wealthy farmers healthy land @ShayneCurrieNZH @RFStew @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RexWiderstrom the real strategic error was not hdg for high value organic less intensive 10yrs ago. @ShayneCurrieNZH @RFStew @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brycepearce I don't think the EPA is compliant with the USA anymore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@babye can we send a couple of German girls your way? We had them hardcore camping on Molesworth last night so they… https://t.co/NLozlJJFnH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[100% pure NZ. Warming up the 2 stroke in pristine Nelson Lakes National Park, gassing the tourists enjoying the pea… https://t.co/OcJFsk7CDV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TeamTottie Was hoping to come up via Molesworth in a week or so but Awatere valley still blocked. Prob won't come yr way now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Olivefarmer was hoping to, bt doesn't seem Awatere valley Rd will be open for ages? Which means Rainbow Rd home @TeamTottie @DougAvery12]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrSeaRotmann she's great]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tockly you're onto it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simon_pleasants I wish it were that simple. We've been hvg problems for months, made worse by Xmas. We still hv to run a business. @nzpost]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>