<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seb_Zein its making my travel plans difficult.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But like why would Bosnia do this and completely split Croatia in two? https://t.co/CKy2HwACEt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently I'm now the only person in the family that knows how to use a computer??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My mom calls me "I need you to help me buy something on Amazon" I get downstairs and both of my brothers are sitting directly next to her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(It's just because I'm really thirsty and my water bottle is empty.... I think)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing stranger than being someone who literally never drinks and suddenly being like "I wouldn't mind some alcohol right now"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Managed to get the same spot that my brother and I shovelled this morning #success]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not many customers realize that what they're doing is a little bit dumb. I liked it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every few months there's a customer that really charms me. Today the guy said "There's no cure for the kind of stupidity I'm afflicted with"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I barely convinced myself to drive to IKEA today and I work here. Wtf are all these other people doing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My car is my actual prince charming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every once in a while I'll move in a certain way and my ribs will crack, is this normal?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson I probably won't have cause to anyway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson okay but I think I'll hold back on that one anyway :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson are we sure she's a reliable source of the current slang?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson so then you learned it from her?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson but is this just a friend of yours that you convinced to use it? :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson it might be because I'm on mobile but that link just takes me to https://t.co/UgIZuqVBPg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson and tbh I'm not convinced you didnt just make up filmé]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson sometimes my little brother tries to teach me things but I'm convinced he makes them up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson okay but being an old lady means you cant make fun of me about it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson oh I thought you were saying that was an actual film called filmé. I dont understand slang. I'm an old lady.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson oh but I definitely havent seen that. I think. :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson I did unexpectedly love that movie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson filmé? Is that even french? :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson oh right hahaha I wonder if I've forgotten any other ones.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson oh that's pretty cool. I havent been to the movies in months.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson so they just play it early?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson how are you watching it the night before it comes out?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson yeah the live action was pretty good! Are you looking forward to Beauty and the Beast?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson its just what I grew up with! I'm also like the only person who likes Cinderella and Snow White]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Life is meant to get boring when you get older so it's not so disappointing when you die" This show is too quotable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Topshop is selling velvet bathing suits and I didn't know that was a thing but I kind of want one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like I might be Ella from Please Like Me and I'm not unhappy about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every bathing suit I want at Anthropologie is like $300+ and like while I could technically afford it it just hurts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone knows the IKEA PS 2014 lamp looks like the death star. You are not clever, person on pinterest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe Netflix was the problem this whole time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well the internet is back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes lying sideways on your bed just feels more introspective than lying on it properly. Is that just me?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson I also just sensed tension but Akal said I was crazy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson i feel like she was being very professional and putting effort into a good show and he at one point came out smoking???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson I think maybe he gets himself too high]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson I'm convinced the guy isn't going to last in the band.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson the performance was good but I just couldn't fully enjoy music I didnt know haha it was my fault.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson Beach House opened for VW, Phantogram opened for Metric but I saw them again last year. My friend got their drummer's stick!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson It's the only song I knew when I saw them live so I enjoyed it haha I regret that now though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I once again completely forgot about Phantogram. Definitely more dancy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also that I do NOT know all the words to Threat of Joy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quickly learning that the danciest music on my Spotify is Future Present Past.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mearcstappa ugh you Americans and your affordable phone plans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TV/ internet is out. Thank god for 4gb of data.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Th end of crazy stupid love is the absolute best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you pronounce the second R in February?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember that time I bought a keyboard and used it like for one week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really need to get a hobby.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson did you expect a song by either of those people, let alone both, would be good?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mearcstappa what did I do now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mearcstappa a) Not a huge DC fan b) I am watching a show on Netflix, I'm watching TOO MUCH Netflix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so bored and Netflix has asked me if I wanted to keep watching like 5 times now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson It just ends on cliffhangers and that gets me every time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been watching Please Like Me all day and it is SO hard not to constantly tweet quotes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson The story's interesting!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson But also tbf none of the characters are really that interesting haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson I don't know I just don't think she's special at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson Not at all! Betty's story is so much more interesting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson See I like Betty so much more. I guess we don't agree on women either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson Is he hot though? That's debatable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson I want him to be more my type and sing and play a better song.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously what do people do with full days off??? I'm so restless and I can't even leave the house because of snow ugghhhh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hankgreen I feel like I just wasn't reading this question carefully enough. Almost like one of those trick questions from highschool...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mom: " go build a snowman! This is the perfect time" little bro: "No, I'm waiting to play" lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nevermind. My brother is apparently just waiting for the other people to finish playing now like this is too real.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The game where you text is redeeming itself. Look how pretty this is. https://t.co/1H6m8SOHb7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So apparently this was plowed twice this morning already so I called in sick to work https://t.co/srxQlbZOkH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please note that Tinder is the worst.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson yes but some people have work on Saturdays. Some people work 6-7 days a week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Super happy that they decided to plow our complex at 11:30 pm!! Everyone is doing a great job and no one needs to sleep on a Friday night!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson I imagine you would have to be to listen to it all day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson Yeah this is pretty good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson oh I get what happened here nevermind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson what is... what??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson I don't know what those are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson To listen to a full album or that album specifically?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson I'll just stick to listening to the entirety of IHADTYWM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson Never heard of him. But also how do you listen to the same song more than like twice in a row and not hate it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson Weeeell I don't drink and I'd rather not do therapy so I really hope I don't fuck up too badly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson I'm actually pretty scared that this is going to happen to me with my promotion. I dont know if I can handle responsibilities]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson That really sucks. I'm sorry. I don't even think my boss would let me do that if I wanted to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson Don't you like need a degree to be an accountant?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson :( What happened?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson holy shit what! Why??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson I'm sure that's not true haha so wait, are you working 4 hours overtime???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson oh okay. Is that just your shift or are you working late?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Literally every hotel in Santorini looks amazing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson oh okay. Where do you work?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson Exactly. Anyway, did you watch Riverdale yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson Yeah I noticed what I did as soon as I sent it but fuck it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson well I guess I died my hair pink so who am I to judge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson LOL what does this mean??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothyhudson So... is there any additional hair growth that wasn't there before? lol]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>