<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Can we all hold off on ruling on things we hear out of the White House until we get:

1.) readouts
2.) more proof
3.) actual recordings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charlescwcooke that makes more sense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charlescwcooke as that’s the hottest building on earth, those masks must have been mighty uncomfortable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonahNRO i’d say they’re pretty strong libertarians on most issues.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charlescwcooke was this at the Oxford Union?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@charlescwcooke i know this actually happened but I keep imagining that this was a protest against Roderick Spode.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SethAMandel under a red red sun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“According to my religion, pass interference in college football is a spot foul.” “Well, if you say so…"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcome to my church, the “OSU WAS SHORT” Life Temple.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a good point: this could get real weird if any belief is a religious belief. https://t.co/PG9ADwKFgZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mckaycoppins combination of the two, i’d guess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mckaycoppins same people who did “Catch an Illegal Immigrant Day"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mckaycoppins it gets attention, and a lot of those groups just want that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SethAMandel has anyone compared Trump’s advisors to the Gang of Four]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a federal RFRA, FYI.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would need more information but this sounds not good. https://t.co/DB1GLqcL2V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What in the https://t.co/TB3ikt5voc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Masters of None is even better on a second watch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NoahCRothman i do not wish to know the answer to this question.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This seems a smidgen shortsighted, but I’m just a black person, what do I know. https://t.co/5bJ85GdUHa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EsotericCD victim of its own success, one could argue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessesingal fake account.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pegobry he sounded like he was talking about a classmate whose name he couldn’t quite recall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That story was even wilder than anyone knew at the time. https://t.co/iO9V6urFQD  https://t.co/xVh0iizeWt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@petridishes and certainly don’t scratch her wittle fuzzy tummy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EsotericCD the Key and Peele sketch about college football player names was funny because it’s incredibly accurate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wrote this to coincide with the first day of #BlackHistoryMonth. It’s about a game we were never supposed to win. https://t.co/5lXx5UhDZe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sasimons @michaelbd NZ is also not as liberal as a lot of people think, FYI.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timothypmurphy @AdamSerwer Ollie’s at Queen of Sheba, eating tibs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelbd @sasimons @NewYorker having another country you’re thinking about is concerning, yes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sasimons @michaelbd i’m aware, but i’ve spent a fair amount of time there (wife is from there) and it’s… a normal place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sasimons @michaelbd New Zealand is notably full of civilization, though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SethAMandel allegedly the bobcat was seen on Mass Ave last night and definitely isn’t currently sitting in my apartment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daveweigel haven’t these people ever seen “M”?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AceAnbender can we talk about Harbaugh’s use of the term “youngster"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jpodhoretz @SonnyBunch @SethAMandel @bethanyshondark that Instant Pot is innocent, innocent i tell you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jpodhoretz @SethAMandel @SonnyBunch i am so worried about all of you what does cheesecake know about you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anthonytbroome everyone’s making 100K with full medical]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may laugh at Michigan’s #SigningOfTheStars event intro heavily featuring kicking but that was a VERY ANXIOUS TIME.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SonnyBunch @SethAMandel what the hell did that whipped cream to do deserve that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SethAMandel @SonnyBunch what do you think about sweet potato pie Seth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SethAMandel @SonnyBunch is this what being outraged feels like]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SethAMandel @SonnyBunch pumpkin pie is such elite pie Seth you are a genius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SonnyBunch @SethAMandel “here’s a hunk of sugary cheese” “no”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SethAMandel @SonnyBunch “hey you want some sweet cream cheese” “NO NO I DO NOT”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SethAMandel @SonnyBunch it’s so bad. it’s just so bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FYI: Eli Whitney was white. Apparently a lot of people learned otherwise. https://t.co/WbaP8uMIb7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That Black History Month speech also reveals that Trump has literally no one on his team who can write.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Michael Vick essay is fantastic, as is the idea of Vick and Matt Ryan having dinner together. https://t.co/VrkVkw5VCN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conservatives getting on board with federal intervention on a local scale would be an exciting prospect. https://t.co/2kA5RezNwp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somewhere in the great beyond, my grandmother just sighed deeply. https://t.co/BNrlpBdOZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@redsteeze the amount of money i would pay to see Trump give a ten minute monologue on who he thinks Harriet Tubman is is… large.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrewCHallett who in 2005?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aubrey Solomon and Rashan Gary playing next to each other is a meteorological phenomenon I am into. https://t.co/MfhI5OGaIZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello. I wrote about race, and how we’ve been playing a game we could have never won. https://t.co/5lXx5UhDZe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please, please, please let me ask him what he thinks Frederick Douglass did. https://t.co/ZNKPldJzjW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bomani_jones i would pay money to ask him what he thinks Frederick Douglass did.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A reminder that Angela Corey was perhaps the worst prosecutor alive. https://t.co/sqssSqCwru]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rembert @jbouie … we still got george washington carver though, right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Literally no one in this arena is more excited than Brent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brent Musberger may have just described Georgia-Kentucky as a “real donnybrook” or at least he did in my head.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you’re looking for something to watch, check out this documentary on the lies of the War of the Roses: https://t.co/sr6P1QGD8A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EsotericCD yeah. and his poor wife.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EsotericCD it’s a story that started out way more humorous than it ended. It went Hastert really quick (allegedly).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@josh_levin @BenMathisLilley “I AM CANCELLING MY OFFICIAL VISIT TO SCOTUS PLEASE RESPECT MY FAMILY AT THIS TIME"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EsotericCD i haven’t seen “Weiner” but man, that documentary went from “mildly amusing” to “worrying” very quickly, I’d guess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@byjoelanderson i flacked until like a year and a half ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@josh_levin @BenMathisLilley you just wait till LSU jumps in there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gorsuch really went after it during the dead period. https://t.co/y495ndVUhn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NiemanReports the sound on the livestream isn’t working!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@harvardnews sound isn’t working on the livestream!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The baseline on “Want More” is just exquisite. Listen to the “Live at the Roxy” performance. People lose their minds over it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rastaman Vibration. I will ride for that album. https://t.co/hsOqFw40f8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bomani_jones Survival and Uprising come after Kaya, and after (IIRC) he had become increasingly more religious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bomani_jones it was released after he was shot and escaped to London. I think of it more as “let’s all just calm down."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bomani_jones honestly even the songs that Bob didn’t intend to be political are political. The second half of Exodus, all of Kaya.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bomani_jones yeah, that would be a poor choice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bomani_jones also a good lens at a complicated history. “Rasta don’t work for no CIA."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally. https://t.co/EguhImFceV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smartfootball @ChrisVannini oh definitely, being anything below a coordinator is some BS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just remember that Kirk Ferentz has total and complete job security. That’s all you need to know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smartfootball also, again, Harbaugh is a lunatic. This works for him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smartfootball exactly. I could make an argument that the pressure is worse, but even then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smartfootball again, recruiting appeals to the insane, who are the only people who should be involved in this job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smartfootball and if you’re good enough — hell, even if you SEEM good enough — people will do such stupid things for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanRubenstein but seriously, Harbaugh could start demanding random goat sacrifices and someone would come up with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanRubenstein i am detecting a hint of sarcasm here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AceAnbender i would rather be a college coach pretty much anywhere besides Kansas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AceAnbender pros: uh cons: :: points at Jed York ::]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recruiting is great if you’re insane, and the perks are infinitely superior.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrewCHallett I’ll never forget the “PUT IN MALLETT” chants of 2007.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrewCHallett oh, most definitely, but it definitely lessened slightly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(This is all Mike DeBord’s fault.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret to Michigan fandom is that everyone hated whomever was starting at QB until like, 2011.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TWSStwins nah man, recruiting is great if you’re completely out of your damn mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not an unusual belief. https://t.co/tIZOKUUN74]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MGoFish there’s a theory that that was on Steinbrenner, yes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, Harbaugh picked college over the NFL because college football is infinitely better for coaches than the NFL.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kimo von Oelhoffen set back the Bengals franchise for a full decade. https://t.co/JjX6YQXDHK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@byjoelanderson “turns out, you CAN burn down a home without using fire."]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>