<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to see Lion this week. https://t.co/BLk5d6Bx42]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fionapettit71 also look at the pub med on banning of MMR in Japan: https://t.co/qzUg95gxoV I met Micheal Rutter, great fellow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fionapettit71 it's a great article from a highly respected academic. Rare for a muggle like me to be able to access published research]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dechamcork @fionapettit71 @lstwrd @cooper_m @greenparty_ie Here's the science explaining it https://t.co/XFXmxHJWGI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sharonf Hey Prickly ! Happy new year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RositaBoland excellent interviews on @SeanMoncrieff Have you heard of @loudfence movement? In Australia, silence is confronted with ribbons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daveGildedALM @billybragg @cookingvinyl @redessential @tomhappens @NewstalkFM Yes but us over 40's need a reminder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to Billy Brag should be prescribed daily for all adults over 40 https://t.co/BVYJTjycLX @tomhappens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WendyBrandes if only they made actual decent coffee. Still, will continue to buy their lemon &amp; poppyseed muffin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@luberachi loved him in Wilderpeople]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stuartclark66 could you find a better word? Intellectually disabled people suffered at the hands of Nazis. The conflation is superfluous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnGobanSaor @dbelle1992 not on the no fly list obviously]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KenSweeney I think it's gorgeous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IllSueYa @PA well none of them voted for her to be PM. Because no one elected her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Scary Love - Autisable https://t.co/EM7EXc87vT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch Winona Ryder make funny faces at the SAG Awards. https://t.co/5PBpcdqgdc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@karamina any chance I can read it ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@karamina @clairehennessy yep. I've got two teenage kids firmly on the spectrum.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@karamina @clairehennessy interesting. What's the research background ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonathanhealy yeah, Enda is really good at standing up to rich business men like......[redacted]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patquirke such great sportspersonship at the top ranks at the moment. My sister would have given me a deadleg if I beat her in a grand slam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The true brilliance of the #Williams sisters: me &amp; my sister couldn't play for 5 minutes without hitting each other with our rackets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daithigorman to paraphrase Orwell: "all undocumented migrants are equal; some undocumented migrants are more equal than others"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@James_Proclaims @YouTube now. GO TO THE LIGHT!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@missyasin @neuroconscience @NYDailyNews why are border staff doing this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colettebrowne @NWCI @Telegraph at least they're not wearing white.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They replied! https://t.co/nqGjyDpHbi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@damienmulley absolut mango. I'm never leaving the house again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia actually lead out in the whole Alt right thing (but got rid of him) https://t.co/jgqQ1unjcZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@damienmulley @babaduck71 are you on west coast time?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every day I like George dubya more and more. I still love @POTUS44 but Dub grows on ye. https://t.co/wt8NjcchER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone selling pussy hats in Dublin/Nth Wicklow? #represent #Nastywomeneverywhere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ireland and she gave him to the circus to be raised by clowns?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_RachelSloan @CarolPoveyNAS @LimpsfieldGrang don't we all have a big "A" on our foreheads? Just me?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just had to pull over at @tomhappens pronunciation of Bogun on https://t.co/5I18HL9BJ1 then I heard the new Choose @SeanMoncrieff ad. PMSL!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@c_oreilly @ireland I'd bat that on to @AdamPHarris and the team of youth mentors at @AsIAmIreland - making Ireland accomodating for autism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carolineclarke @annemccoy keep this in your handbag. I have craziest crazy lady hair and it works. Doesn't make it… https://t.co/45pbn5EgPr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's Ross and Rachel: https://t.co/gOPykXg6xo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BillyBaldwin @nickers1973 @robreiner I think he may be a robot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here I am eating Ferrero Roche for breakfast like a peasant... https://t.co/5Yc2iJ7RJl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@corkyfella @tomhappens if you click play on Listenback while you have 3G or wifi it downloads the whole thing. Keeps playing without wifi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billybragg @tomhappens @mkamurphy you may all have to forget retirement as the lights go out, walls come tumbling down (up?)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pussy of the year. https://t.co/OIAtzbSLQA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@roisiningle @DerekinBerlin @IrishTimesLife You should do a companion piece on the "Loud Fence" movement in Australia, particularly Ballarat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LESLEY KNOPE! https://t.co/qXh71uTdAM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Martina if you get time take a drive down Great Ocean Road to Apollo Bay. Tiny town with beautifully long beach for walking in bare feet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvanHandler I have 4,000 followers and I heart you xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MargaretEWard so insular to believe a US based organisation can organise marches in Sweden and Melbourne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MargaretEWard this woman commented twice on my Facebook page post thanking the marchers. Orwell was right. She rea… https://t.co/wSSs82TdtF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope she and Barron have a safe house. https://t.co/5nZIdXSdf2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Martina Mornington?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GriffinTech @iPhones4Autism Done! Even if your staff had old 5c cases they don't use it'd help. Griffin are the best for Legacy devices!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Twitters: I need to source 6 of these Griffin iPhone 5c cases for @iPhones4Autism for a cohort of non-speaking autistic kids HELP PLS?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi @GriffinTech my project @iPhones4Autism is has been donated some iPhone 5cs Can you help with a donation of All terrain Survivors?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HI @Meteor_Mobile Trying to select the internet deal on €5 top up for Gracie. Is that offer over?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@monicamalpas77 I've got kids firmly in the spectrum. So my only experience is specialised ed. I'm Not the right person to ask so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steveddaunt @tomhappens my Boo made me sing the the Vultures song for Mowgli tonight. The Beatlesque Vultures]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@josefoshea @Jezebel I'm genuinely afraid for her. Wealthy women are just as likely to be psychologically abused as the rest of us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm really starting to fear for #Melania .She reminds me of the society lady in @MarianKeyes "This Charming Man"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jesskellynt @NewstalkFM love my Fitbit Jess. It's continuous reinforcement for the behaviour analyst in me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vmarks went well. New Principal got behind us &amp; said "Make it so" whenever we asked for evidence based interventions. Thx for Moral support]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having an @OisinTweets cocktail while in the bath listening back to @tomhappens Sunday show = bliss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well F#% me! That fantastically retro @u2 song @tomhappens has played every night this week is actually Ed Harcourt! https://t.co/nrNZMCGdUz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tv3elaine you have your own show now? That's brill!! And much deserved. Over a decade since you came out to Greystones to film us xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichieMcCormack @Independent they're kind of right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@declanbuckley @barbarascully Lovely to have you both back. Mondays are marginally less shitty when you are on @SeanMoncrieff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mumbles_j oh god I love this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ciaraobrien hope Missy is on the mend soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ciaraobrien any lasting damage? Had an "escape of liquids" 2 years ago. All laminates ruined.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnGobanSaor @rosanna_davison so does vinegar reinforce them? Aioli?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ciaraobrien what happened with kitchen?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ciaraobrien a steamy bathroom works wonders. Put her in a high chair or buggy so she can't reach the taps but run it hot hot hot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnGobanSaor @rosanna_davison but lovely on nice carbie chips. Thick cut.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ciaraobrien oh no! How's the croup for starters? And you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Freeyourmindkid that's adorbs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DCZia @Marv_Vien all Dads should aspire to wear Dad jeans that well. And that jacket? Werk!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barneyfarmer @RichieMcCormack and @U2 at the Dandelion Market.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MazzyK *tilts head*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["White floor coverings" or "white bed coverings" aka white sheets. And those funny hats. https://t.co/ewTba0yool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ciarakellydoc "Make America Great Again" = Make Autism the Bogeyman again, I'm afraid. So glad we live in Ireland.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lexia @rickoshea @RTE2fm Actually Lennon. My sister came in and made me change the channel to news. I was watching The Muppets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*sings* "go west! Where the air is free, go west!" https://t.co/NB76c03pt5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@James_Proclaims @CNN why did he give 2 of them a dead arm before leaving the stage?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lexia @rickoshea @RTE2fm Challenger. Heard it on a clock radio as I woke up. Yes, I'm old.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guest Post from Sunway Holidays: BOOKING and Travelling with Autism - include and enjoy
 https://t.co/8FET8HiBww]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be gaslit. Don't let this become normalised. https://t.co/RWPBI04o0k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katebattrick @ElysianBrows They are amazing. Husband actually noticed &amp; complimented me after second visit. Free touch ups.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katebattrick yes. I'm on Carers' allowance. And I spend it on beautiful brows.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ireland The Fundamentals of Caring is super]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewsHour @jk_rowling are the crowd on the right wearing white sheets?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katebattrick ps. Fancy brow salon @ElysianBrows opened opposite the post office where I collect my pension. I'm a brow lady now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vmarks *high 5*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vmarks Show Me the Data! https://t.co/V94tfhjudP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vmarks this time last year I had two fabulously qualified &amp; interested teachers. The universe is paying me back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katebattrick I'm trying to stay out of jail. But if do I'll make everyone my bitch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katebattrick I'm fixing it https://t.co/TrfyyBOMHz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vmarks appreciated. I'll use my one phone call to tweet you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cloudsteph or this https://t.co/HVr5Owy10X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TrumpDay kitchen cocktail inspired by @OisinTweets on @tomhappens Wrap paper towel around the mixer to prevent blo… https://t.co/FPSnwlj555]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WendySparrow this works too. I'll take a polaramine later when I'm off duty. xx https://t.co/DpALjlAyTR]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>