<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The Raccoons of the Resistance in the time of Trump: 'Be fierce, furious and fight!' https://t.co/Aoo1zBFQiJ via @firstdogonmoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come do my job!  Head of Supporter Engagement role @SAFEnewzealand - deadline 7th Feb: https://t.co/5ft5ZiZTP5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Setlist from last week's amazing @nickcave gig.  Personal highlights: Tupelo, From Her to Eternity &amp; Mermaids. https://t.co/QZPZ6N9log]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Why the next four years will be a test for all of us' via Yaa Gyasi for @guardian  https://t.co/PMBU1RXQkk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NextChallenge yeah I've been there in -35C, but also in +47C - depends when and precisely where you go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ukcharityjobs @walkoflife1985 in that case, colour me interested!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Philosophy can teach children what Google can’t' - Charlotte Blease https://t.co/ON1ojHsXcX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Resignation letters handed in, one-way tickets to Singapore booked.  From there, train up into Malaysia.  Then - who knows?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@walkoflife1985 Sounds like an adventure - when were you thinking of doing it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn this really neat, practical #BJJ technique in just one minute - courtesy of @RenerGracie &amp; @RyronGracie  https://t.co/EtjsgQUidy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Why swimming in the sea is good for you' https://t.co/a7OeZzbile]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am leaving my amazing role @safenewzealand next year to travel and start the next chapter - so come do my job! https://t.co/5ft5ZiZTP5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great video showing just some of the things @SAFEnewzealand supporters have done for animals this year: https://t.co/HwoEWeHuYg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Why time management is ruining our lives' - insightful article via @gdnlongread  https://t.co/HmSBQQh1Xt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finalised the playlist for the office Christmas party tomorrow.  My colleagues are lucky, lucky people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['5 Misconceptions About Being Vegan' https://t.co/txFOBZdkUZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Garnkiny Ngarrangkarni' by Mabel Juli - one of my favourite pieces of contemporary Aboriginal art on display at… https://t.co/MDKqhEPDu4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Frightened by Donald Trump? You don’t know the half of it' via @GeorgeMonbiot  https://t.co/DljDxaWELf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good article raising some excellent points about how deeply entwined modern life and needless animal suffering are: https://t.co/POOconVk1n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Master Huang Xingxiang demonstrates five #taichi loosening exercises: https://t.co/NMrCUg527A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Like living on a waking dragon' - pretty apt description of life at the moment!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeling the aftershock in Wellington: https://t.co/W0JipFevAY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Early morning run
'Round the bays of Waiheke
Forgot about Trump
#Haiku https://t.co/E1PWzESpDo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a Waiheke Island vineyard for Natasha's birthday https://t.co/i9khl46aGH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pweeds Thanks - and yes, good article!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this selection of free online human rights courses: https://t.co/AVmVSnY93I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the @TimaruHerald last week https://t.co/WEOvhHMU60]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful images - brings back memories of drinking from bhar during my own visit to Kolkata in 2001: https://t.co/gTGlE0rjH6 via @AJEnglish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant Editorial from @NZStuff: 'Videos show bobby calves are still being mistreated' - https://t.co/84DqGM9urP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got my tickets for the Wellington show - exciting! https://t.co/Ckjs0Odhei]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Trump is no outsider: he mirrors our political culture' - useful analysis by @GeorgeMonbiot: https://t.co/9jXizn1Zy6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful region, with some great hiking - thoroughly enjoyed a day climbing Mt Taranaki itself back in March https://t.co/RsmyvVj8Sy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight on @CheckpointRNZ, @SAFEnewzealand &amp; @FarmwatchNZ revealed new footage of calf abuse in the dairy industry: https://t.co/p2XahyZJZ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taiji Qigong Shibashi demonstrated by Master Lin Housheng: https://t.co/wViwKljCQd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just started learning an awesome new #kungfu form - the beautiful, flowing 'The Essence of Spring/Plum Fist 2nd Branch']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mykki Blanco recites Zoe Leonard's ‘I Want A Dyke For President’ - more relevant than ever: https://t.co/bXa2CSES1L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interview with my fellow @JaiThaiBoxing trainee on reconciling training to be a paramedic with training Muay Thai: https://t.co/nI3UZifVRK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Biggest drawback to living over 11,000 miles from my freelance client?  Getting up at 2.15am for a two hour conference call]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indigenous Australians most ancient civilisation on Earth, DNA study confirms https://t.co/DO6gRqrZ22]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Forget the bucket list, forget the ego. If you want to be a hero, stop conquering' https://t.co/g4udJpaRZd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Skeleton Tree' - beautiful, tragic, ephemeral, mesmerising, other-worldly and as close to a masterpiece as any album produced this century]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['On a Plate' - The perfect explanation of privilege: https://t.co/LWMxZoIaoG via @TheWirelessNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some really interesting presentations at the #afforum today - particularly enjoyed @LeahEustace, Lettie Bright and Tom Dolan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If into BJJ and visiting Sydney, be sure to check out @pedro_sauer affiliated Higher Jiu Jitsu - great vibe and very welcoming to visitors!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fallen cities: how artists have captured ruins, from Kabul to Rome https://t.co/le6wqotq93]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How politics works these days: you buy the results you want - https://t.co/MblXXcvF2w via @GeorgeMonbiot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Marianne Elliott: Unravelling charities' ability to do good' - worrying trend for charities in NZ: https://t.co/EjI9Hgwit4 via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is better to be a warrior in a garden than to be a gardener in a war." https://t.co/LCwZCGrDKk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pweeds just a short trip across the Cook Strait - home on Saturday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[View from our home for the next 3 days - the beautiful Wheelhouse Inn in Nelson https://t.co/KlGfjxIRfO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Help or hazard? Why GPS may be leading us astray' - very important article via @Team_BMC https://t.co/lC1eSw4vhA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['The Moral Responsibilites of Jiu-Jitsu Pracitioners' - essential viewing for all martial artists v @GracieBrothers  https://t.co/Q3ghOCugfG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAFE - New Zealand's leading animal rights organisation - is looking for a new CEO to lead our staff team: https://t.co/rapoLwat7x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone participating in martial arts sparring - irrespective of art or seniority - can benefit from watching this: https://t.co/POJ3FjW8D0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Revealed: Cambodia's vast medieval cities hidden beneath the jungle' https://t.co/Dd2TnNfa0k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to heading to Palmerston North later today for chi gung followed by a kung fu sparring class - may be sore in the morning!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Change desperately needed in dairy industry' - great @nzherald opinion piece by my colleague @MandyCarter111: https://t.co/Mp9qzUIelG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting, well thought-out article on a topic I’ve been concerned about for some time: https://t.co/CcROtTuCY3 #fundraising]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oldest handwritten documents in UK unearthed in City dig - fascinating insight into the lives of the first Londoners https://t.co/92jP2ZMtGL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12-year-old Maja has started a petition asking countdown to stop selling cage-eggs in their stores - sign here: https://t.co/J8oznv6fuv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished the @campbellclaret political diaries. Riveting stuff - highly recommended for anyone interested in modern politics or comms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out #WinningGirl on @Vimeo - inspirational documentary about teen Judoka and Wrestler Teshya Alo: https://t.co/RJ9FDkn7r3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unlike Prof. Ballantyne, I think this is very exciting, but then I grew up with tales of  'Endeavour' https://t.co/Y7fxZh7w0s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aboriginal rock engravings of a large sea creature and a figure of a man - near Waverton https://t.co/BsoGfxLQNP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sandstone Aboriginal occupation shelter - Balls Head Reserve https://t.co/BrhKwmyPo9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aboriginal occupation site on Berry Island: water storage hole, stone tool grinding grooves and rock engravings https://t.co/O1YMPxJRi8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoying the small - but fascinating - 'Pacific Spirit' exhibition @austmus https://t.co/gY9kB1tfS6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you think adventure is dangerous, try routine; it's lethal." - @paulocoelho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Palmyra must not be fixed. History would never forgive us' - completely agree https://t.co/MPGEyX3LwT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colony cages: exposed. Watch the shocking footage and take action now: https://t.co/SNaF5eqAjk … https://t.co/EqD7mNiket v @SAFEnewzealand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch @TheStoryNZ tonight at 7pm and see the shocking truth behind the new 'humane' replacement for battery cages: https://t.co/YorRNAZvgT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Work for @SAFEnewzealand!  We're looking for a full time Campaigns Assistant / Auckland Volunteer Coordinator: https://t.co/m4K0aZeXqk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well how else was I going to celebrate passing Kung Fu grading? https://t.co/D6CvIAe14K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 minutes qigong in the Botanic Gardens - best way of spending the afternoon tea break and getting some energy for the rest of the day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Why UFC's Toughest Fighters Are Going Vegan' https://t.co/D6CLqRrJBc via @MensJournal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['The Archaeology of Kouphovouno' @LivUniAlumni memorial lecture for my old dissertation supervisor Prof. Chris Mee: https://t.co/WtnFBI0pCy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Latin joke in Wellington!  And it's funny! https://t.co/3eDQ6HlcVt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Second day in a row eating amazing vegan street food at #cubadupa - today's choice: burrito with extra jalapeños]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['The 8 Best Muscle-Building Foods For Vegans and Vegetarians' https://t.co/QA3axN1QUY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New trail running shoes! Looking forward to trying them out https://t.co/gTAWSkDTt1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Abolitionism versus Reformism' - classic article by Austrian animal rights activist Martin Balluch: https://t.co/sdxZp52JSC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the summit of Mount Taranaki (2,518m) towards Ruapehu and Ngauruhoe https://t.co/gRpJ68Yhxb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Conor McGregor's movement method: the missing link in MMA?' - surprised more don't take this approach - hardly new https://t.co/owoPUnuk3S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The view from the venue for today's workshops https://t.co/I4s6n6VAFv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to today's workshops on 'Three Secrets to Fundraising on Facebook' and 'Integrated #Fundraising' with @paretotweets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really felt that one... https://t.co/2zlse1PVkZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally reading Keri Hulme's 'The Bone People' - what an incredible, haunting, brilliant book - and what a vivid, evocative writing style...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kiwis: please take a couple of minutes to answer some quick questions on eating habits and motivations - thank you! https://t.co/EMaGXAkaOW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please support Holly (11) who is walking 30km along the #Wellington coast this Saturday to raise money for animals! https://t.co/5MJeLQDmub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Almost ready to go here in #Wellington #NZvAUS https://t.co/d4MIZFgcfd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kdn68 cheers mate - these things happen. Could have done without the hassle though!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had a great time exploring the Taupo / Rotorua region - now heading back to Wellington for #NZvAUS @WestpacStadium - looking sunny for it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Champagne Pool, Wai-O-Tapu @ Waiotapu Thermal Wonderland https://t.co/KZiBHwSNPr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Artist's Palette, Wai-O-Tapu @ Waiotapu Thermal Wonderland https://t.co/VUBmuIOlTx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First stop on the road trip: lunch on Peka Peka beach https://t.co/gxt53piu3m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One super stylish troll https://t.co/xMamHdNGOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['My meat addiction is over: I’ve gone vegan, and it’s brilliant' - great article by @MxJackMonroe  https://t.co/oLpj4OUyT1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Debunking The Myth Of The Modern-Day ‘Adventurer’' - an interesting perspective from @tom_r_allen https://t.co/hQ8UYqzIEP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sexual consent explained with tea - how brilliantly British: https://t.co/1ADKGY6Fbd #ConsentIsEverything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The petition calling on the NZ House of Representatives to ban rodeo has 42k signatures - help make it 50k!  https://t.co/lfbNGx1E64]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>