<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Gord Downie makes surprise appearance at Blue Rodeo show in Toronto https://t.co/ytpUA1av8Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TTC union head, 17 officers removed from positions by American-based union https://t.co/YLSnR76ge3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Second funeral for mosque victims to be held in Quebec City https://t.co/41pIscocqJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reporters' spy saga gives glimpse of UK surveillance culture https://t.co/TDtHMCk6n3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toronto mom furious after school bus driver forgot her 'traumatized' daughter https://t.co/XDsMSjt9X7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. officials confirm travel ban doesn't apply to Canadian passport-holders  https://t.co/08qLOarC3c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snow expected tonight in GTA: Environment Canada https://t.co/CahrIaSoRM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quebec mosque attack victims include professor, grocery store owner https://t.co/r4O9sJTbWE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quebec City mosque shooting: Suspect identified as Alexandre Bissonnette https://t.co/SctCFJpQ5p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow @ColinDMello for ongoing coverage of the demonstration at the U.S. Consulate in #Toronto this morning… https://t.co/yulQ6MNtCd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quebec City mosque shooting: 6 dead, 8 injured https://t.co/kEmShpUlye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dual citizens with Canadian passports not affected by Trump travel ban: PMO https://t.co/efH6liiqtB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thescissorboy Hi Grant, I'm with CTV News in Toronto.  Would you be able to give me a call at 416-384-7100?  Thanks, Ian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amber Alert:  15-year-old Alyssa Langille missing after possible abduction in Missisauga early Sunday afternoon.… https://t.co/OiQlK3CdwV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snowboarder credits inflatable backpack for saving him in BC avalanche https://t.co/tpSpvtFX6Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prince William visits bereaved children, says he was 'very angry' when mother Diana died  https://t.co/a1seKS31vx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Compelling video: shows how dangerous Saturday's pileups on Hwy. 401 were.. https://t.co/dLKUmgIjK7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Queen attends church following illness https://t.co/pcWLYUbXN9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hydro One IP address red flagged as suspicious 8 months ago. @blissblogs @CTVToronto https://t.co/Wa0wtFabcs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fire officials in Bradford says five houses were destroyed in early morning fire. Fire broke out at 5:00am.… https://t.co/9AOff8EkkA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Several homes under construction destroy by fire in Bradford, north of Toronto. @CTVToronto @CTVNews chopper on sce… https://t.co/saTxuN8Xaz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Compromised Hydro One computer shows difficulty of tracking hackers https://t.co/pB142bk8pp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive: Internet address at Hydro One linked to alleged Russian hacking https://t.co/8yPN9Umbjq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canadian dead after New Year's Eve party in Thailand: report https://t.co/Uz5OWC30Xs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a #winter #hockey classic from the early 70's. https://t.co/BDNRBwRFVZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another crash.  Hwy. 401 westbound, express.  Near McCowan . Up to 3 vehicles involved. @CTVToronto https://t.co/6fJAUjshMN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heavy tow trucks on scene now on Hwy. 401 eastbound at Lakeridge Road.  EB 401 remains closed after early morning c… https://t.co/KtVN4P3QYD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EB 401 closed at Lakeridge Road, traffic being routed off Hwy. 401 at Salem Rd. @CTVToronto https://t.co/hPmhMmrmqs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking: Dump truck hit bridge.  WB 401 Express near Jane Street.  @CTVToronto https://t.co/ZzZact8rDr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A slow drive in #Toronto and #GTA.  Winter travel advisory issued by Environment Canada. https://t.co/3RLB8gc51s… https://t.co/qs9pSW8mNo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the spectacular Christmas light displays in the GTA.  Ilona Park Road in Pickering.  @CTVToronto https://t.co/bAaIKsOXaU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['It's Taylor Swift!': Superstar surprises 96-year-old fan at family Christmas party in Missouri  https://t.co/Hc4HBmTSBW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iconic 'Star Wars' actress, author Carrie Fisher dead at 60 https://t.co/VRxdIv7zGW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Changes to Ontario energy bills, land transfer rebates kick in on Jan. 1 https://t.co/jhX5p0pqnr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada sails past Russia to open world juniors with 5-3 win https://t.co/OjIjfWo0C5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Royal Family attends Christmas Day service; Queen absent due to heavy cold https://t.co/Tx6Cgi5DPv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toronto to London flight diverted to Ireland; 10-year-old passenger dead https://t.co/HBhj5AZYgO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Behind the scenes for @ToyMountain. A big night coming up @CTVToronto https://t.co/TtpadBCf3K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[El Al #LY30 at Toronto Pearson after calling mayday and returning to Toronto last night.  @CTVNews @CTVToronto https://t.co/KC9UZHAF4k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunrise just before 8am.  Wed. Dec. 21, 2016.  First day of winter.  @CTVToronto @CTVNews https://t.co/mPsLvqwSSl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9 dead, suspect arrested as truck rams into Berlin Christmas market https://t.co/XrJR2sOMLm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aleppo ceasefire collapses, threatening evacuation plans https://t.co/amRQQBqZc9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One dead, 3 people unaccounted for after fire at home in Port Colborne https://t.co/63o5cOvJ6D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Nowhere safe to run': Desperate appeals as Syrian forces poised to take Aleppo https://t.co/E3GHM6Ebnb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['No one is helping us': Syrian girl says goodbye on social media as rebel-held Aleppo falls https://t.co/FsxIEwtep1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police investigating after video captures vehicle smashing into parked car in Mississauga https://t.co/XZagQAAZYF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snowfall warning issued for GTA, most of southern Ontario https://t.co/NKViZQxPgW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stealing from graves: valuables reportedly stolen from urns in two Burlington mausoleums  https://t.co/B7R4taXzQh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toronto police searching area where body of murdered doctor was found https://t.co/yMHJskewKQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Premier Wynne suggests Ontario won't block tolls on Toronto's Gardiner Expressway, DVP https://t.co/jX9LewJ4Y7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toronto Mayor John Tory vows to 'fight against' any proposal to bring tax rate in line with rest of GTA https://t.co/C5N84vopkd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One dead, six-year-old critically injured in multi-vehicle crash in Brampton  https://t.co/j4yo7NNWhe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police in Europe make 5 arrests in 'unprecedented' cybercrime takedown https://t.co/tGhJcWSFcP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live coverage on @cp24: sinkhole rescue in #Toronto @CTVToronto https://t.co/4DG8cD4hoq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CF-18 pilot killed in crash 'passed doing what he loved,' family says https://t.co/C6htdZ7PK7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suspect sought in Toronto after woman pulled off bike by her hair, robbed: police https://t.co/Gzi3b08t94]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toronto Police release photos of vehicle wanted in Scarborough hit-and-run https://t.co/zypbPA2W4z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Appreciate the insights on the threat of #ransomware https://t.co/SpPoIWyaKl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beach weather in #Toronto https://t.co/h9ajIhsQR9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No charges against Clinton after new email review: FBI https://t.co/WoApagjnHu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toronto home sales, prices soar again in October  https://t.co/QKPDr9ff9b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mississauga officials cry foul over assumption that they will help fund SmartTrack https://t.co/EVQm8ndtnZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Majority of Torontonians oppose long-term traffic closures for construction: poll https://t.co/m1WWYZUA1f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clinton urges FBI to explain newly uncovered emails https://t.co/gCMpuWucNE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Atlantic: We Built a Fake Web Toaster, and It Was Hacked in an Hour https://t.co/rjUKPFsACY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fall colours this morning in #Toronto #Brickworks https://t.co/4pRACD7K2b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanksgiving in #Algonquin. High falls, Kingscote Lake https://t.co/dlMrfkDrrM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hannorein I just added you as a contact.  Can call as soon as you  accept.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fall colour in #Toronto at the #Brickworks https://t.co/uUEWjq4scl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Canadian senator leaves $100,000 to widow, Senate owed $176,000 https://t.co/uT6BS72ixM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Holly__Williams Hi Holly, I'm with CTV News.  Wondering if you could give me a call?  416-384-7100.  Thanks, Ian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toronto Kite Flyers club at Woodbine Beach today. The Octopus kite is 88 feet long https://t.co/MIlQtFP9VL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surf is up today at Woodbine Beach #Toronto https://t.co/8I2K2GhCvQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['It was simply bad time, bad place,' says woman punched in Hwy. 401 road rage incident  https://t.co/By7euRgQch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Dear friend' of Stroumboulopoulos found dead inside his L.A. home @ctvtoronto https://t.co/WsicirTw8G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elaine Biddersingh gets life with no parole for 16 years after conviction in death of stepdaughter @ctvtoronto https://t.co/NGtE6oDC73]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arrests made in Brampton pizza place robbery that left student with 'life-altering' injuries https://t.co/Gtu60zMUzH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Granddaughter charged with stealing $12,000 of grandma's jewelry in Barrie https://t.co/c8Xa5W0l1p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Lowest of the low': Man in Michigan passes fake $50 to girl at charity lemonade stand https://t.co/OtEFwm85PQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surrey BC RCMP officer charged following Creep Catchers sting https://t.co/LOf6UDt8y6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suspension of St. Catharines vet was 'appropriate,' College of Veterinarians of Ontario says  https://t.co/VPgLLzOy5a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two tickets split Friday's $60 million Lotto Max jackpot https://t.co/XkKwaogCiE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[iPhone 7 crowds continue in #Toronto https://t.co/D0ZMZKIFt5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CTV News Exclusive: Veterinarian handed 10-month suspension for choking, punching animals https://t.co/AoBVdkRUsZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huge lineup down Wellington for #Snowden at Roy Thomson Hall #TIFF https://t.co/KkKUXWOTsp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teen shot in city's Swansea neighbourhood https://t.co/Wx7opYmula]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rec program registration help in Toronto: Frustrated dad creates app to easily sign kids up https://t.co/PGUMWGkWdE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Naked man in Toronto takes bath, steals tomatoes from backyard of west end home: Police https://t.co/Ah4npckGth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada's athletes at Rio games to be celebrated at Beach parade in Toronto. Live @cp24 https://t.co/CYTiRjstAw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toronto Police identify suspect after three killed by crossbow in Scarborough Village https://t.co/iD61hRyUQb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rio police seize passports of Irish Olympic delegation staff https://t.co/hRRZ05z5dN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Hip mix songs old and new in final Kingston show https://t.co/e7iFyXNShd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Busy newscast: behind the scenes @CTVToronto @CTVNews https://t.co/KbrPOuUner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great view this morning from the @CTVToronto chopper flying north above Kennedy Road in #Toronto https://t.co/4m2FvF3IqF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rob Ford crack video released after Crown drops charge against Sandro Lisi https://t.co/RsexaVEGiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RCMP say FBI tip alerted them to 'imminent threat' posed by Aaron Driver https://t.co/KcbuXrtP7F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RCMP reveal video of masked terror suspect Aaron Driver railing against 'enemies of Islam'  https://t.co/HrWdQaJEyU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CTV News Exclusive: Lone suspect killed in anti-terrorism operation in southern Ontario https://t.co/zr0wZozie2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And here's a Pokemon evolving into a stronger Pokemon https://t.co/jZHBc1NoIW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's all the game activity that keeps Pokemon players coming back to this area https://t.co/tC8zDsvhAU]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>