<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Just let a dog with no hips.
Due to the lower bone/floof ratio it is even cuter than fully-hipped puppers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have no idea how Macs work.

They instill fear in me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Throwing money at problems always works best.
That's why rich people never have shit kids.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Revolutions start with rabble rousing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chennanigans has anyone told him it's fine for dudes to wear makeup?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[International law is only becoming effective because this generation of educated is being told it's effective.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The Bill of Rights as a Defence: The Last Refuge of a Scoundrel"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SofaRobb genuinely considering the caravan lifestyle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SofaRobb I just want someone to blame and the Americans seem a good target.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SofaRobb I'm just super pissy because it's hard enough to find flats and I'm goin to be homeless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Met a guy organising flats for 20 friends who are abandoning the US After the election.
Wonder how they feel about refugees.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TedTedwin @jessicaavery_ you want to be fellated by Nixon?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessicaavery_ it was a simpler time. Failing to Lick Dicks and Watering one's Gate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The recycling centre is the place to make friends
Guy talked about how he committed insurance fraud for a new TV on the way to the e-waste.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These world championship darts players look like extras off Coronation Street.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is your name on any Forbes lists? Then don't tell me how to get rich.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With the diet I'm on, two bottles of red wine is my daily recommended calorie intake.
Guess I don't eat anymore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you hadn't read the books, the plot in the movies about Voldy-mate stashing his soul in sundry chattels is a bit of a snarl up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much does a nice hermit cave set you back these days?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeorgiaOG2 welcome back OG2. If only OG1 were here to share this moment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was jealous of immortality, but remembered jellyfish are immortal and as a species have achieved very little with it
#jellythoughts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This invertebrate jellyfish has more spine, charisma and likeability than some people I've had to deal with
#jellythoughts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jellyfish in the water look delicate and majestic. On land they look like hangover vomit in a showercap.
#jellythoughts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nana with the prime MDMA https://t.co/R308wneJhM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Tell you what, I've just never had a good home made babaganoush"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am neither conventional nor usual]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sonniewonnie hope they will be unrelentless and vehement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["My lasagne is your lasagne bro" - true friendship]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im retaining water like a dehydrated camel lately. Makes buying new shirts nearly untenable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessicaavery_ who tipped you offf about that Matè?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@garethmorgannz "let's light a fuse under [parliament]"

Are you Guy Fawkes and his band of pyro-enthusiast Catholics? If so good timing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessicaavery_ don't forget mushrooms and blue cheese]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexa_ruthless it's almost as if we don't have a global digital network which allows for the instantaneous transmission of information.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexa_ruthless I'm with you. More accessible, better turnout. And not relying on the postal system can't be a bad thing (damn local body)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessicaavery_ I was never going to share so there was no need to broadcast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexa_ruthless wait, are we not to believe that electronic voting spells the end of our fragile democracies?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turns out one can very much over-caramelise mushroom and blue cheese sauce.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fork count in this house has dropped to zero.
Did the Catholic Church of the Middle Ages come through?
#EatWithYourGodGivenFingers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Plymouth is getting a cheeky Nandos. 
Biggest development since that building made of mirrors turned up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeorgeEGe I don't believe myself to be either. Maybe a large purple number with a feather?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd like to start wearing hats but every hat either seems to be for fuckboys or neck beards.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one dresses really scary for Halloween.
Didn't see a single 'my uncertain future' costume.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessicaavery_ @Kat_Rad you're so weird]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessicaavery_ we reached the use independently. Also it's in the dictionary m9.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessicaavery_ it's seasonal. Like when everyone changes their colours to black for rugby stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it too late to retrain as a doctor and go do some brief good in the world?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lindauerpapi someone behind me opened their paper and just whispered "fuck". Think we're all on the same page.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Halfway through a fact problem about 'Fat Mobile' I started calling it Fat Bird.
#ThirstyProle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Saturday exams, because we don't shit them up enough already" - some fuckspanner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His voluminous, superfluous chins enveloped his moon-face like a fleshy ruff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just because your Marxist Utopia is classless doesn't mean you have to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessicaavery_ @Kat_Rad I swear we were talking about competence not appearance thanks Regina]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessicaavery_ It's true.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things customers call me:
Good - George, mate.
Bad - Boss, Chief, Sir, Mister, fuckhead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eating spicy shit makes that cheap wine taste like the most delicate sweetness known to either God or man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're going to leave me passive aggressive notes at least leave a contact number so I can tell you exactly how to go fuck yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrissybrown @anya_maule @VUWSA context is extremely important]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't wanna work, wanna make money while I sleep.
So I prudently invested in a balance portfolio of equities and bonds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was a fucking day and a half.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today the waterfront bore witness to tensions involving four grown men and a security guard over a cauliflower.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once we had about 36 forks in this house. Every single one is gone now and Kmart is calling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll do me. You do you. We can compare how we end up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrissybrown @jessicaavery_ it was funny though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrissybrown @jessicaavery_ I had a very near miss with a bus on my bike, it scared the shit out of me and I thought I was going to die.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessicaavery_ different kind of organ donation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Become an organ doner today: cycle in Wellington.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daylight savings really messes up my "no hard liquor before sundown" rule.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been a long time since I've had "faggot" yelled at me out of a moving car.
Has New Plymouth come to Wellington?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This day is so beige.
I just.... Wanna burn it all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I'm cycling I change gear more often than an experimental junkie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realVUWSAwatch who are you person of the anonymous twitters?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Move over Fresher Five I just put on the Election Eight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chennanigans she was telling us about her love shed she lived in as a student when she was at Kelburn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessicaavery_ there's also some banger quotes in the exec column I wrote this week]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's way too hard to find an empty tute room to have a bit of a kip in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheeky Dick pic. https://t.co/8ekfP2j5Fp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Do you think he's into Winston Peters pegging role play?" - @JessMcBurney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexa_ruthless in favour but only on Hawaiian.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jackestpersona are you VUWSA's conscience? Your spot on questioning make me feel things deep down inside. #vuwsavotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TedTedwin if that's what the people want I am happy to investigate and initiate this new initiative. #VuwsaVotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anya_maule The slush fund is a lie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chennanigans @hyphenating @VUWSA fair point, we don't want to be the Council Whipping Boy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chennanigans @hyphenating @VUWSA good point. Definitely more in favour of partnership]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chennanigans @VUWSA funding arrangements aren't inherently erosions of independence. We would be extremely careful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hyphenating @chennanigans @VUWSA on this one that is perfect. We shouldn't rule out other arrangements though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chennanigans @VUWSA ideally yes but that level of independence is a few years off. For now we have to do what we can.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chennanigans @VUWSA definitely! It would depend on what the council wanted us to do. Independence is crucial, isolationism isn't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does the council wanna make some donations to @VUWSA to educate students about some things? #StudentsVote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gnomespeacock straight after this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoelRowan I did not know that. Not sure if the candidates do either...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off peak reductions? Sorry do students not travel at peak times there Andy? #StudentsVote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Media in danger Helene? You're the only one going after them in here. #StudentsVote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Students don't vote because there's nothing voluntarily offered to us. @VUWSA had to fight for anything at all this year #StudentsVote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nickoleggett greasing the wheels of democracy with support for e-voting. Good. #StudentsVote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How many students live in Manhattan Jo? Pretty expensy I hear #StudentsVote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boy from Porirua not afraid of firing shots #StudentsVote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can any of the candidates get local infrastructure working better than our sound setup? #StudentsVote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrissybrown @clayton_bryar @lithoboly was that the initial meeting I heard upstairs this arvo?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That late afternoon salmon sushi is not good for my health.
#Sub-PrimeSalmonCrisis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TedTedwin everything is property. Welcome to the capitalism hellscape.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>