<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[whenever I feel an earthquake I rush out of bed and make sure I'm wearing clothes I could survive the apocalypse in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gydelne don't worry. We can see uni from our house. U can live in a Hamilton east sized bubble here x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realstephnieb oooh I will investigate thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Wellington, pls advise if there are any byo spots near parliament end?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I made falafel &amp; hummus from scratch for the first time and hot damn @me https://t.co/4ZUxiUG2U0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[getting paid is nice. would recommend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reedfleming @Catherine_andy Yes, I am aware of how party membership works. There's a fine line between leading change and complicity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Catherine_andy sorry you struggle with being a member of a party that allows its mps to promote racist polices but that's kinda ur problem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it makes me feel so uncomfortable thinking about voting for the green party but like labour are racists so what's a girl to do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's an uncomfortable fact (but still a fact) that the member for Palmerston North is a xenophobic weasel of a man https://t.co/50WoMq9rXU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best case scenario for 2017 is that we keep fascism at bay and Andrew Little becomes New Zealand's new Prime Minister. Let that sink in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They've got the unsold premium seated tickets for Guns N Roses on Groupon for $69 \m/ https://t.co/J4Hwufr5s9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rosalindaymes if it helps, I'm on the verge of like 3 fillings so I have to stop drinking fizzy n shit 👎]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went to the dentist for the first time in 8 years and god bless the tooth fairy coz I don't need a damn thing done]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WgtnCC @annemjw yes dw was going to anyway 😊]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annemjw @WgtnCC all down Devon. If they're still there by week's end I'm gonna add some of my own creative flair.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today marks a year since I packed up my gran's old putty car in Hamilton and moved back home to my out of touch lindaeur-socialist bubble.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I got one good thing from my time in politics, it was the ability to design and maintain a swish af war room white board.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ired0mi concert vibes are very high up on the scale of vibes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_wild_world how else do u achieve those ~concert vibes~]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I do not mean to make light of real cultural appropriation pls appreciate me and my witty repartee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will not stand for this sickening appropriation of my heritage https://t.co/kY2UKRTmN9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[shout out to last week's chelsea who left a perfectly ripened avo and vogels in the department fridge for this week's chelsea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sokeroida @g_townnz yes! I had a vege burger from the fish &amp; chip shop too for peak Aro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@C_F_Darling @g_townnz gurl! Come join us on the deck sometime soon!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[mood: drinking a beer called lack of faith in a park with @g_townnz https://t.co/reSfTArWDE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't wait till she gets home from working at the cattery so I can call her. I need some Gran wisdom in my life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WELCOMETHRILHO that sounds perfectly reasonable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WELCOMETHRILHO I am very sorry, RIP. Was just visiting fam for christmas. Anything above 30 is toooooo much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WELCOMETHRILHO tysm. i had to turn into a beach goth to survive adelaide. i don't know how u deal with australian… https://t.co/aXG9ogNs2q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it weren't for immigration, y'all would never get to read my Drunk Gran tweets https://t.co/kajoTg7kIa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The view from my new room is 🔥🔥🔥 but also, working from home is really ominous when uni/work is on the hill staring… https://t.co/bOfYjrg2nf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First time putting my British citizenship to good use https://t.co/t6MHyN9xyv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck all this pragmatic lukewarm double the quota noise. It's not enough. Stop saying it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm feeling really homesick but I can't figure out if it's for Waikato, Upper Hutt, London or Adelaide.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This dog is giving me life this morning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When u follow someone back &amp; then they go RT bomber onto the TL https://t.co/11lbPEoswG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TuskCulture I would rate our current discourse as a solid 0.5/10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@renee_jg I'm not a liberal feminist, and it's how I feel about you, not all of feminism (you're not that special sorry)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[thanks 2 Facebook for throwing me back to 2013 when a boy in young labour literally bit me at summer school]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I stole this from Cool Dog Group and I feel bad but also you have to see this fam turn the volume up https://t.co/Hdrr3eleXG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know that the seeds of a new wave of fascism have been planted, and the world is ending etc, but how annoying is loud gum chewing amirite?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alixhigby I have like four more &amp; I honestly don't think I'll get through them before they expire! My aunt just lo… https://t.co/HtJZhTxPf3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@King_Soph I opted for the "run away to work and pretend it never happened" option]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just walked out and left it there. Drunk Friday night Chelsea is not going be happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A visual representation of what happens when I get out of bed before 10 https://t.co/hNeeWCfmgM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@King_Soph @superleeni if you ever need to talk natural/organic hair care, I've used &amp; sold most of them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CrikaRika same but also tegan and sara are a thing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am from Upper Hutt so I have punched quite a lot of people but I'd like to put it on the record that I would also punch any and all nazis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[fuck you felix the huddersfield station cat, i thought we were friends https://t.co/P9gHsKHb04]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeirLeslie they better not bloody hike up the prices of there $2 bubbles (formerly $1) too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[estab are charging $50 a head for a max key o-week gig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mood: PJ Harvey was great but I hate men]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solid intel from the engineering department's women's bathroom https://t.co/TM9a0dNz2A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instead of building houses on protected heritage land, let's rezone all of Auckland's golf courses and build on them https://t.co/ucqvvjrqmw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This weather is worse than the actual winter I just had in London]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gydelne @g_townnz she makes a good tea if she applies herself. you've got yourself a bargain. i wish you both happiness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gydelne @g_townnz oh yeah that but also her clothes are for retired wine moms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@g_townnz @gydelne you can question my methods, but they worked!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@g_townnz @gydelne this is a lie (alternative fact, if you will) and you know it x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gydelne yes! Let's go when you're settled and flush. Don't listen to Georgina. She thinks Trelise Cooper is hip &amp; cool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gydelne yes and national library but they are special places and they are exempt from my scorn as is the train station and ezibuy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johubris Oh no! I hope they do well in the new location. They're next to 2 halls so I suspect they might.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best thing about block chains is that I don't even know who the bad ppl are anymore coz they blocked hashtag li… https://t.co/689m9SKmH2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johubris WHAT I'M SO SORRY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only good thing about the Parliament end of town is Nudel orange beef, but there's one on Ghuznee now so I never have to go there again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it was coyotes never mind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[what was the bar that used to be the bangalore polo club called?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[he was real chill about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just spilled my iced long black (😖 why are they a thing) all down my boobs as a man wearing a robe tried to give me a meditation booklet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wellington I don't like the Bowie mural it's too bright]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johubris labour will commit to a review of a review of a review of a review of the law]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's been 4+ years since I worked weekdays &amp; wasn't studying. Weekends are the shit. Long weekends are ever better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stay in your lane 2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so much vagina centric lukewarm white feminist placards on my feed 🤢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raging night in because flatmate @steviejnz found The Batman Game circa 1966 at the Newtown vintage market ! https://t.co/OW6VpxeORB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[substandard latkes from five boroughs. Wellington Jewish ppl where u at let's open a deli.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[went for latkes instead of going to the women's march because America and lukewarm activism is dumb and I only care… https://t.co/NDYDQ2N2gk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kate Shepherd was a conservative old bat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[fukn outrageous if true https://t.co/lAV7RxISD3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[generations of my poor family shed blood, sweat, &amp; tears so that i could go to uni &amp; get a job where i could stay home &amp; work in my jammies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DawgBelly that can be arranged]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DawgBelly yes please!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DawgBelly seriously? If you don't want them I'd happily buy them off you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kiwipaula yeah. It sold out so quick - just before I got paid too 😢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[two men called mark and colin have pushed the price up of two pj harvey tickets to $330 on trademe &amp; there's still an hour to go. bastards.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steviejnz @g_townnz @realDonaldTrump block her]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[gran is on the wines again https://t.co/L4JFbRwrST]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[all is not lost https://t.co/0dn7kgVfgH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@genuinelygreat I haven't read Cohen's take, but I've read the original. So good!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TuskCulture I really like this one by @willpooley https://t.co/V20lPo0P6u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[can you even say "more accessibly"? i don't know. my job is to edit things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[dear internet, if you have any good pieces on how academics can write more accessibly (simple, creative, without pretension), please hmu.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[everyday is a good day when it's donut day https://t.co/DtxULfXDtQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@King_Soph death]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to rip the heart and soul out of a true Wellingtonian, reply to their lukewarm tweets by cc'ing the capital chatter account.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get it together lil pups]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really love German Shepherds but they have a lot to answer for. They need to find more ethical employment &amp; stop humanising the police.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[jesus mary and joseph https://t.co/AT2Qhly5a1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2. The weird sense of superiority New Zealanders get about "women getting the vote first" is so cringey.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>