<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The Secret Teachings Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/HnEpgsKwDT I'm on facebook too if you want to f… https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closet Couture Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/zf6NaSnSdt I'm on facebook too if you want to follow … https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook and Google join forces to wage war against fake news https://t.co/tKJvvFcdeT via @mashable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seth Haapu Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/LStvnNMtrh I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fitspo Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/C3iw69dpya I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trifekta Ent Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/iiX9daoTu5 I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lisa  George Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/XBhQNitHCE I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Josh Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/sppdYcHzu4 I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ben Landis Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/6JYSzX6nlS I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maxine Miller Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/NtbGvXZNZd I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Miss Miranda Glamour Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/CFndImgqo0 I'm on facebook too if you want to f… https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marek Kośniowski Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/ac1KvjdYp7 I'm on facebook too if you want to follo… https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Linda Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/425J7n4jrY I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nicole Johnson Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/IB4Edcf1bc I'm on facebook too if you want to follow … https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sierra Seip Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/K4wibrn0Bp I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sarah stirgill Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/edkntN9Eel I'm on facebook too if you want to follow … https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MelJo JoJo Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/Vc5dahEBtO I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BurlyLife Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/WE8ErfWxxQ I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Polecats Fitness Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/UEGv3fkmD0 I'm on facebook too if you want to follo… https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WLG Free the Nipple event tomrrw: Be aware that if u take pics without consent this will be reciprocated &amp; posted in a vigilante group]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Cumpston Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/Vf5IawAGjS I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tad Liles Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/wwKEy7Rf62 I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fetish Film Factory Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/d7KTmdqJDd I'm on facebook too if you want to fo… https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those eyes! It's the same look when he lies. There is something there #JohnKeyResigns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there a scoop? NZ media: ponytailgate2???? #JohnKeyResigns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Either it's the truth and the story will be consistent or it will change #JohnKeyResigns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Princess Leenka Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/3lAxHKD6BI I'm on facebook too if you want to follow… https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TuraSatanaProduction Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/kjCwneNDE1 I'm on facebook too if you want to f… https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lisa Lee Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/4foCEhTp88 I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ralph Mcguire Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/oW0mJV2hTe I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/cpBRbFHaoG Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/14jBcdc4dP I'm on facebook too if you want to… https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rebecca Mackenzie Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/jeqwvnoGDY I'm on facebook too if you want to foll… https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Faye Feline Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/9qx5u9LYoV I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spiritually Sexy Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/U25eN7ccd2 I'm on facebook too if you want to follo… https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ca████████ Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/bjqCkj1Rmm I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael Mamas Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/wYLVSnmuV4 I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[shana l Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/MENEJ2gdiD I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Swing Cats Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/qb8Uxiy1q7 I'm on facebook too if you want to follow … https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SPORTVIDEORUGBY Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/vn4JFjL1FH I'm on facebook too if you want to follow… https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robin Hopkins Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/l0c0kucM9B I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Film Fatale Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/Z5fXPt9uvc I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mark Goulston, M.D. Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/EFYLV4U8Rc I'm on facebook too if you want to fo… https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Voss Events Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/VoB0sySBt8 I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the new info on Undieground Burlesque's page https://t.co/X7wEAvXAOK https://t.co/YwT3mruNpd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the new info on Undieground Burlesque's page https://t.co/X7wEAvFZXc https://t.co/41mdwfIBIC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the new info on Underground Burlesque's page https://t.co/X7wEAvFZXc https://t.co/qV9J0dSJVt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Killean Duthie Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/W7rnjsYmfL I'm on facebook too if you want to follow … https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[test one, two, testies one two]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Palace Productions Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/GS8rwyViSv I'm on facebook too if you want to fol… https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Texas Burlesque Fest Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/UycOg66LFl I'm on facebook too if you want to f… https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Josephoreliebrenda Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/D2pBh6S3oT I'm on facebook too if you want to fol… https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SOTB Burlesque Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/WBH0iq1mml I'm on facebook too if you want to follow … https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Michels Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/8Vp87Z7WQv I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vintage Dames Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/IVLjGRAedA I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chandra Gilliom Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/Lsf5BfydU8 I'm on facebook too if you want to follow… https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wayne Kirkwood Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/jP8CULmmgP I'm on facebook too if you want to follow … https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[bookthefilm Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/r23vcQGkHw I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Livestream Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/ZO69gV3u2Q I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nooooooooooooo! NZ sevens coach announces his next move at a NZ Rugby press conference
https://t.co/PvrASutvG2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sarah Hodges Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/7TI7Kpvuuj I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ephrimvael Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/wCpVQM4b3g I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NoScrum-NoWin Rugby Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/l6SNpGOrLX I'm on facebook too if you want to fo… https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keshia Martin Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/wDerDwauZI I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UCLASemelFriends Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/HuuYzEP1o4 I'm on facebook too if you want to follo… https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mindfulness Wellness Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/yPBG6kth2f I'm on facebook too if you want to f… https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live Your Now Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/KlPwpd9PcY I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beaudenbarrett this is brilliant  https://t.co/vN4vxuRbfA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking news: 500 cattle stolen, and the puns are hilarious. You're welcome.   https://t.co/lyeHxtsv2M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KT_Ten10 right! I see Tix are on sale now. Squeaaaa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@izzy_dagg you had the funniest expression on your face at the post match. I couldn't stop laughing, so I had to focus on the journo's]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a post show tradition and is now a post test-match tradition. Nommm. #BledisloeCup https://t.co/5Dx6KeUoMK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beaudenbarrett nice shot, but you dribbled!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I so didn't know that the ball boys dried the balls with towels. Fancy that is. #BledisloeCup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KT_Ten10 looking dapper there KT. It's toasty and warm up here in W Media. Not the same without you and the 7's commentators]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Angada Kick Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/DO7N3eF9RT I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Titmore &amp; Asspley Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/qx4hcs0Y9z I'm on facebook too if you want to foll… https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loxie Arcane Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/Z37HKZ75Od I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NzQ3J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RareVintageBurlesque Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/bsJJHxGEce I'm on facebook too if you want to f… https://t.co/8wu84NzQ3J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IoaneAkira @nz7s yes it's devastating, but keep your chin up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Burlypicks Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/FlUtzch7Hw I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rosebud Burlesque Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/3vXgpv4Jcm I'm on facebook too if you want to foll… https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justadandak when you mentioned teaser tracks I sat there nodding. It's one of the things I do for an up coming Undieground Burlesque.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TEDxWellington Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/2csTVyV3aY I'm on facebook too if you want to follow … https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just had an informative &amp; entertaining work shop with @justadandak on Social Media FUNdamentals. DK put the fun back in social media 4 me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brooke Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/zFLznNrbEG I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nautica McKinney Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/IVwSprU7li I'm on facebook too if you want to follo… https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Al Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/XaNjkE2ChL I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deanna Danger Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/SOXb9HK1jw I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vixen Valentine Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/rUV0HPSh8z I'm on facebook too if you want to follow… https://t.co/8wu84NzQ3J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dalton Miles Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/E83S6HTzz5 I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh dear, I've found the MTV channel and catfish programme. I still have no clue what I'm watching]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talking to my bestie makes my heart sing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I did something really unusual today: I stayed home. Infact I have that planned for the whole weekend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elson Sim Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/8aUoTgiwmg I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Velvet Kensington Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/h3dygyHyLj I'm on facebook too if you want to foll… https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aki Technologies Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/Dx9TGuFTKT I'm on facebook too if you want to follo… https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bonnie Stein Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/rVmxmMLeC1 I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maria Wesley Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/cP003dvWNu I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lolly Bam Bam Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/umuphoqm0t I'm on facebook too if you want to follow me https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Devorah Costanzi Thank you for the Twitter love. https://t.co/srlYVJJTUS I'm on facebook too if you want to follo… https://t.co/8wu84NRrsj]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>