<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[150 billion to Iran and then they break the rules of the deal.....@BarackObama did the worst deal ever. @realDonaldTrump fix this please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These signs exist. #wewelcomealllegally #trump #maga #BuildTheWall https://t.co/WHsz1QTVJy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AshleyJudd what an idiot you are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He should sue for them allowing his life to become in danger. https://t.co/TYkviolAuh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He should get an apology https://t.co/TYkviolAuh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[u could have reported that 60% of voters do not to wish to impeach @realDonaldTrump but u went negative again.… https://t.co/2HgESYIhRT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow this madness needs to end. https://t.co/EADOguu8y3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hundreds of migrants have reportedly set up camp on Lake Como, close to George Clooney's mansion. He's mad about it.. too close to his home]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They get lots of clicks for reporting partial truths #fakenews https://t.co/ZuxdxGSmsm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do we know how her ratings were ? @tamronhall https://t.co/cO5WjIG1My]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can we organize a rally to protest all these rallies.  Too many.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarackObama turned a blind eye for 8 years and now @realDonaldTrump has to come in like a bat outta hell and fix his mess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaraSetmayer always acts like a lady even when faced with opposing views. https://t.co/OvWIe8L8Kv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very interesting read https://t.co/pHj1Nx8oVs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But the people don't necessarily want to go back to work. https://t.co/VM1s1tTsQP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does anyone work ? How do they have this much time. Damn I can hardly find time to Pee during the day let alone pro… https://t.co/QQytrqfVpE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aplusk very disappointed in your speech and u. 109 detained out of 350000. 42 Muslim countries not on list.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seanhannity AWESOME EXPLANATION OF TRAVEL BAN. THANK YOU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For safety of travelers they should ban non-ticketed passengers from entering airports]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think @POTUS should #TearUpTheIranDeal! https://t.co/HDsROkyGyN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where are you getting these numbers ? CNN ?? https://t.co/gZJYgarfvo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I couldn't tell you any of their names https://t.co/F1J7k2gqJ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We've been taking in the tired and poor,,, we're tired of paying for the tired and poor. They need to get a job or… https://t.co/4BsUsKhXv3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm predicting she's been snorting Oxy or doing Meth #SaveWynona #WynonaRyder @wynonarider https://t.co/Ilc2KzFrGB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was @BarackObama in2015 who started it. https://t.co/Jfw8oCRVfA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MagicJohnson what about the medicine you were able to get from Europe while millions of Americans who couldn't aff… https://t.co/1tS3xtM5fI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While you received medicine from Europe, millions died in US who could not afford the same medicine. https://t.co/sB5MIDZehG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very simply. You touch one palm to the other in a repetitive forceful motion... https://t.co/Jgj11iDVGM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I lock my doors every night. I don't lock them because I hate the people outside, I lock them because I LOVE the pe… https://t.co/5BAZWFm0zb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good! help fund them get legal citizenship. https://t.co/Wyfid7bJSV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I lock my doors every night. I don't lock them bc I hate the people outside,I lock them bc I LOVE the people inside @realDonaldTrump #repost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I lock my doors every night. I don't lock them because I hate the people outside, I lock them because I LOVE the people inside #MAGA #repost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally https://t.co/pM5KN4Hjg0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#boycottHollywood https://t.co/4x3LFI2FgZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I lock my door at night not because I fear my neighbor, but because I love the people living in my home. #homelandsecurity @realDonaldTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Visa Waiver Program Improvement &amp; Terrorist Travel Prevention Act of 2015  @realDonaldTrump wasn't president @BarackObama was! #factcheck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And how about that shooting in Canada or you still just interested in bad mouthing president. https://t.co/81fWwcQLsa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Immigrants coming to USA legally are ALWAYS welcome. #mada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If this doesn't make sense to you then you should maybe join the armed forces to see for yourself. https://t.co/lmgPfuDggY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[makes sense to temporarily ban areas till the new admin can settle in and implement new travel rules for areas host… https://t.co/R7nX9YtoaU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG the airport is horrible enough without listening to her on top of it. No one would put you on their show to dis… https://t.co/RVPKUknV16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't forget the gays that have been murdered and thrown off tops of their buildings while hog-tied only to be ston… https://t.co/xI4matKsFd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where were you then? Watching it on TV https://t.co/y9xxU0RVfQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She isn't a dummy. https://t.co/WPX8xEttpP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So now we are giving human bodily functions to statues,  hmmmmm https://t.co/3xnh6esxxZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But she doesn't protest the killing of gay people by way of stoning and throwing them off buildings while being hog… https://t.co/ga4NNDhmM6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They'll figure it out https://t.co/Ko4wFlsLqW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can a paper that reports partial truths be regarded as reliable.  I think not.  #fakenews https://t.co/DilTVQqPd2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who did this?? Lol. #MAGA https://t.co/QC7JRzYj2i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ummmm hi, just thoufgt I'd mention The Doomsday Clock isnt a real clock so therefore the hands didnt really move… https://t.co/JkypHOIeqo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN is #FAKENEWS https://t.co/S0p9FQ0F48]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think someone is trying to make a name for himself https://t.co/tGmQjFM0AT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ridiculous. @CNN  is like a witch hunt https://t.co/0ZcwvfKkb1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What about all the American citizens living on the streets, the homeless, the veterans ? Create safe zones in Syria https://t.co/8r4jmNZ9Uk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He should meet with her. https://t.co/vg4o5Adv9n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @FedEx https://t.co/gNhtYobPi8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought Arizona reportedly had a very high amount of illegals ? https://t.co/gdpbrIKO53]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do they keep leaving out the word "illegal" ? https://t.co/arp7Zg5NZF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scientist using a fake clock in and of itself is not very scientific. https://t.co/S9vgPd0YAX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If this is true, the person should be prosecuted. https://t.co/yQf32pMuIh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems like exactly what @CNN tries to do to @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/AfhEX1R8HP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At some point maybe we should just allow females to vote on abortion. https://t.co/DaUvwoGbTC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just let us know so we can continue that wall on up- #maga https://t.co/ebJdmgZdG1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ronnie, Robbie, Ricky &amp; Mike if I love the girl who cares what u like.... https://t.co/td7CKdbZlr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You call it madness, we call it progress https://t.co/hAM4mKjm60]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fire her https://t.co/EdJ9LXmrdU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What are they saying ? https://t.co/aJsdouhy73]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exactly @Cameron_gray https://t.co/O2I786ud51]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He not only schools him, he reads, writes and erases him !!! #MAGA @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/YE1VlPU1w6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG.  This just made me LOL seriously. https://t.co/bku3cVjgSk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting point   Thank you for putting it into perspective. https://t.co/b1fGqHp5ay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN mixing words again creating chaos https://t.co/E1VIOhktOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarlHigbie one of my favorites https://t.co/05miYpV9pG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow the law. Bucket up buttercup. I have no problem with immigrants that follow procedure to become citizens leg… https://t.co/TEAADyLPc7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was a mutual agreement to cancel meeting. Good thing Trump tweeted his decision hours ago. Please Start reportin… https://t.co/xwUJv46cKq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Probably was asked to resign because of his poor performance over past years https://t.co/qCTUHKH7rV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yea all these protests and who knows what they are protesting https://t.co/QQmmMiuaXc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Preach ! #truth https://t.co/GUKau257eu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe @BarackObama should have sent them the 221 mill instead of Palestine #MAGA https://t.co/XUUSisbWRT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then they should be able to prove they weren't involved and they'll be cleared.  But maybe just maybe some were inv… https://t.co/w6H78USRW4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who ? https://t.co/WspRg8MjFs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By far the best I've seen.  LMAO https://t.co/ZS5oxb04yM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FoxNews thank you https://t.co/ivdZTdFE4z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You really need to get out and volunteer more if that's the most disturbing thing you e seen on TV.  Plenty of horr… https://t.co/so35rixHjz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes I know so thank God his term ended and @realDonaldTrump begins https://t.co/tzYUaDHvMv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is this fear based photo?  @CNN constantly planting seeds of anger https://t.co/0rE4lfMwoX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sounds like an excuse to me https://t.co/Au5ZHonCbL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No your constant negative comments about @realDonaldTrump are dividing this county. #takeAChillPill https://t.co/gqF2jdV56i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell that to Chicago Cook County. #MAGA https://t.co/xypBSfYoUD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What about the people who actually go through legal process to get citizenship? https://t.co/eahUMSCOkN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidMuir hope you are fair to @realDonaldTrump and not one sided like the rest of media]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnKerry stop giving our money away.  We all don't have a net worth of 198.5 million dollars like you !!! #MAGA #TRUMPTRAIN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepKayGranger @RepEdRoyce great job stopping the 221 mill that was quietly going to Palestinians by @JohnKerry and @BarackObama]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope this is true https://t.co/5spvI6OWHR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are trying to say that there was no voter fraud.  Illegals voting is voter fraud.  People registered in 2 state… https://t.co/WHpG7lLWdv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's stupid.  Probably books that were paid for by tax payers https://t.co/oZhohuqSrd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you for reporting US GLOBAL HEALTH ASSITANCE" other media outlets are purposely leaving GLOBAL out to inspire… https://t.co/M30pm2LZ6a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarackObama gave away 221 million But media concentrates on inaugural audience #s &amp; fails to report 221 million going to the Palestinians.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can you Believe 221 million going to the Palestinians?!  Let's see how you twist this or not report on it at all @andersoncooper @CNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This about sums it up @HillaryClinton @BarackObama @realDonaldTrump @KellyannePolls #AmericaFirst #MAGA https://t.co/6K0Isgp90G]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>