<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean, it worked and this is prime D Ogilvy but giving your spokesman a model in order to draw people in is gauche https://t.co/D5mGw90LBE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CuckooEvents @mark_breen Love his glasses]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nominations for the 2017 @thesmeawards are now free until Feb 14th. https://t.co/mB6tSw8q0P #LoveSMEs #weLoveSMEs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CorkLovesMusic Feb 22nd https://t.co/f4OHt1mt0F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forget fake news, real news can destroy your reputation too. You have fire insurance, got crisis comms insurance? https://t.co/FOwupfi0n8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sure you'll not be surprised but massively disappointed at way some tech companies don't care about #MuslimBan https://t.co/vETbzkgAZr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh God, the machines can now lip read us from space https://t.co/317nC7fZo4 https://t.co/h6EujwWDgw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is like first aid training. Hopefully you never use it. Crisis Comms Strategy. March 9th Crisis Comms Workshop https://t.co/FOwupfi0n8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[21 documentaries from the 21st century worth seeing https://t.co/Y2S3jSRpNC https://t.co/VMWzlldv0g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jan workshop filled. Full day digital strategy workshop on Feb 28th + 45 min one to one follow up with me. 8 ppl max https://t.co/z5Ocx6ZZed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to know which companies are tracking you on Facebook to throw ads at you? https://t.co/XTBKiwTfRV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So is Trump doing secret orders as well as the public EOs?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Morning all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2017 Nominations for the @thesmeawards are now open and are free until Feb 14th. https://t.co/mB6tSw8q0P #LoveSMEs #weLoveSMEs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[G'night t'land]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Locations from the various Star Wars films you can visit. How many have you been to? https://t.co/eYMIWy7wNQ https://t.co/oPxvCJnPQT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remove all the writing and production staff or just cancel it for  few years. Public sick of it. obv writers are to… https://t.co/NLohZrqnnZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally she's been diagnosed with a medical condition, proving everyone wrong with their doubts. The 71 year wait was worth it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For those praising McDowell, a reminder of his own ban on foreigners coming to Ireland https://t.co/KZTYNhW7sw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TanneryDungarva Thanks boss!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TanneryDungarva @Audisbakehouse @AltitudeIreland Thanks for that. Next Cork one is Feb 16th https://t.co/pUl1kBjkDK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jan workshop filled. Two left for Feb 28th Digital strategy workshop. 45 min one to one follow up with me. 8 ppl max https://t.co/z5Ocx6ZZed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keithbohanna "I've locked the door, there's one knife and four of you"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forget fake news, real news can destroy your reputation too. You have fire insurance, got crisis comms insurance? https://t.co/FOwupfi0n8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Digital Strategy Workshop in Cork has also sold out. Next one is on May 10th now. Still 8 spaces max. https://t.co/DBv0uU7LyI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iandioch Beauty and the Beast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leedalyire @bright_side_me Yeah I put new stuff out 2-3 times in a 2 week window]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Vid https://t.co/Hv5z276wd0 Christmas music! (Follow my Instagram https://t.co/kbdD7iqJLi) https://t.co/SvaM7xhQ3d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gavreilly @brenflakes always in our hearts https://t.co/OgXKNUKKwh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aoifemcelwain rock your bodddyyy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will it impact on our Paddy's Day junkets? No? Carry on. https://t.co/KngkvZMrVY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That'll do Pig, that'll do https://t.co/flJOkV3iZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Simplest and Most Perfect Explanation of Privilege I’ve Ever Seen https://t.co/v1qErZZk1i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swearimnotpaul I really can't explain myself to me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Head of Comms job for Alcohol Action Ireland - https://t.co/zLNAoOv8xo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Use Snapchat for your Irish business or org? We’re compiling a list that we’ll share of who in Ireland is on it. https://t.co/c44CV0Fak8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swearimnotpaul certainly if like them we lack humour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Newstalk talking to yanks holidaying in Dublin, supporting Trump's ban. Deport them now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing how a single movement of a pen can turn border security into fascists. They were fine before this, right? https://t.co/qHSJa7SuL4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dermotcasey touch her jewels, she'll cut off yours]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrangeWeb @verondaly It was nice knowing you lad!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The millennials are the brainiest, best-educated generation ever  - Generation Uphill  https://t.co/XO2OGs62L6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fionakearney Christmas is a girl's best friend, no, not the same buzz to it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@derektroy Yeah, it's just PR bull to boost a company]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Diamond engagement rings are a made up tradition designed by De Beers to sell more diamonds, diamonds are a con too… https://t.co/jOyPEnH2m8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is hating on you. Your boss is being grilled on Liveline. Pray to superman? March 9th Crisis Comms Workshop… https://t.co/2VOYrXBo4C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@twentymajor "Speedy McTweetReply"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uhm so you can hack in to Oculus and spy on people over the web? https://t.co/32bVvOU9vk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cork Feb 16th. Win back against Fb. Full day on Facebook and Facebook Content creation. W Nice lunch. Sign up here: https://t.co/pUl1kB1JMc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["My English is, how you say, inelegant. " https://t.co/4nnsbgGqrk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full time social media manager in Ireland? We’re making a list of who and where we are. Want on? https://t.co/VWTqaslMI9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really like giving training courses and running course with great speakers. Want to know about em? Interest list: https://t.co/FSWydhJ9Vq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've ended the professional relationship with @blacknight around sponsorship of my events inc @TheSMEAwards The awards are still happening]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I have a mailing list. I try and give you good information in it while selling you useful crap. Useful to me... https://t.co/YALYw3n607]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google's 5 messaging apps. 5! https://t.co/Q21EgGLpA3 (via Google gets around paywall) via @BenedictEvans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Timing eh. "Minister Breen leads Enterprise Ireland Trade Visit to Arab Health, Dubai."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surprise heavy leg day in the gym. Oh I just love those.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is it a data breach and not a hack? Cos you have a good Crisis Comms Strategy. March 9th Crisis Comms Workshop https://t.co/FOwupfi0n8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 places left. Full day digital strategy workshop Feb 28th + 45 min 1 to 1 follow up. Limited to 8 ppl.… https://t.co/Ft36aIsZgU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to sponsor some fun events in 2017 inc   @webawards  @ecommerceweekie @socmediaawards  @thesmeawards damien@mulley.ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is like first aid training. Hopefully you never use it. Crisis Comms Strategy. March 9th Crisis Comms Workshop https://t.co/FOwupfi0n8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iandioch No lecturers going with the "Lecture 0" thing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 places left. Cork Feb 16th. Facebook Content Creation. Start winning on FB. Full day. Nice lunch. Sign up here… https://t.co/r6B2vWeE2z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember when yer man used to kiss up to the Cato Institute and was online besties with the Neoliberals? More traffic to be anti-trump tho.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edavieswork Ah now. Though I know a social expert that "Doesn't do Facebook"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hughcurran or can't stop using them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jan Workshop full. 4 places left at Digital strategy workshop Feb 28th + 45 min 1 to 1 follow up with me. 8 ppl max. https://t.co/z5Ocx6ZZed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarrenGale_1 ah yeah all is grand, usual really]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarrenGale_1 howdy, where in the world are you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Morning all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I have a mailing list. It has things in it you might have use for. And I won't talk about you if you join. Deal? https://t.co/YALYw3n607]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patphelan or buy you a plantation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@travors @lexia @YouTube I just saw that pop up on YTS!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HateChrisGreene https://t.co/5WuiVt0kO5 can mute in timeline based on keywords, think this then applies to mobile app]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@killawallachris and they're bought]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No seriously though, how the fuck can you be a business coach or a startup advisor when you never ran or owned anything bar your delusions?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HateChrisGreene will mess with web version later]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HateChrisGreene yeah filter option in Settings now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MiriamOCal @TeresaMannion she could power a small country!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People are asking" https://t.co/5smxtsnem8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting a lot of UL ads in my FB timeline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emmetbroaders that or they just screenshot another tweet so again they get the damned RTs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The tweet was not deleted but hey someone just wanted engagement on their own account so said so https://t.co/bQW4II9FMk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trailer for Billy Lynn's Long Halftime Walk is nothing like the movie.  The trailer is pretty much one 3 min scene in the movie. 5/10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A kitchen is being delivered to a refugee centre so apparently my point of decades of abuse of refugees is moot. Oh do fuck off you cock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's not a PR op though for the refugees you keep locked up but tweeting about Trump gets you praise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Says Minister in Govt that keeps refugees locked up for a decade, won't allow them to cook, won't give work permits https://t.co/gDuyz6lqw6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we do the same in Ireland, is it actually logged? https://t.co/E6Tns4LMli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AaronMartinxxx the Sunrise and Sunset would kill me, cold is fine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StevieGrainger @despod He's replied to dozens and getting shitty with them saying they're on a bandwagon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to email all our TDs and Senators, here are their emails in one handy page: https://t.co/IHxSSoutYD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of companies got nice finders fees, be great to see how many of those jobs still exist https://t.co/UTUDiOe26j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gnelis rightly so]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goebbels is from Cork, sure that's something]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Morning all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[G'night t'land]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More people (esp white women) would vote for anyone else bar her. And they did.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["if Hillary Clinton had won" https://t.co/d9IopxxahT 1000s of results of people thinking she had a chance. She lost to an OrangeFacedPissMan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OrlaLinehan Oh nice one!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Minister for Badges, the one who kept refugees locked up trying to lecture the Govt about Trump. Pensioned, spineless fuck.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>