<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Se_Railway would be good to announce that at London bridge. Why does this impact services all day long? Happened pre 6am]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Se_Railway so why can't I get home now? No information provided at all. Awful yesterday and awful today, couldn't get in nor out !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Se_Railway why keep saying another is coming  if there was no chance! Would have got a slow train 40mins ago if proper communication]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Third world transport system]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frozen. 50 mins on the Orpington frozen platform. Apparently trains delayed by 6 min, gets to 1 min then cancelled. Why say 6mins !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Se_Railway a single broken down train and nothing can get to London??? This isn't 1817]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tprstly not sure the Motorola flip mobile phone was 1973!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@se_railway well done today, 6 coaches ... Greatly appreciated by all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Se_Railway sending just 3 coaches for the 05.51 to charring x is just stupid. Should be 6 the amount of passengers standing every morning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the hell is happening to democracy. Vote. Majority wins. Done. Don't dispute it if not what you wanted. #brexit #trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@businessinsider @Daniel_Rubino Microsoft has been massively more innovative than Apple for the past few years.The gap is just getting wider]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[lots articles on MacBook pro interactive strip, looks pointless. Yet Surface Studio, a game changer, nothing. Tech journos are pointless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So today, didn't see any daylight! Train at 05.51, dark, work in the basement then home at 19.30, dark. I miss the sun!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Standing room only, all because you send just 4 carriages on the 05.51 from Orpington to Charring X. Send 6! @Se_Railway #billyBasic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes it's hard to see the light at the end of the tunnel, but when you do, you know the hard work was worth it. Getting there!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/AOm1zsH4R2 come on Apple, a joke is a joke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/ZOsdhk4eIj today some basic economics are finally recognised!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Third world train infrastructure and trains. Too hot for signals and no air con. Utter joke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoying SCRUM planning, in our SCRUM of SCRUMS .... #agile #productivity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems history has forgotten chemical allie? All those who died by the WMDs in Iraq. Maybe they never found any, as they were all used?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Sad we forget #history so quickly. Remember 7/7? What about 9/11 and the events that lead to Iraq? The Somme and our battle for democracy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is it so hard to get a train to run to time. Happened just once now this week! #southeasterntrains]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come on wales! Talent, drive, pride!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glad Osborne seems to be staying on as chancellor. Need some continuity, and rightfully his focus is the economy, not #brexit negotiations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People have spoken, lets not debate it, lets get on with living with it and making the best. #democracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vote for #Brexit is a vote for democracy https://t.co/BQyoyTt5XT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we Brexit, UK overnight becomes the EU biggest customer. Finally,  power to negotiate and make our own way. Let's not waste June 23]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In business, in sport and in life, your destiny in your own hands is what you strive for. Brexit is control and destiny in our own hands]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catching up on top gear. Should just have Jenson Button present everything!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had a wonderful bank holiday weekend. Nothing more important than family!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loved another #GoT episode, best show on T.V.!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a spurs supporter, have to say we'll done to Leicester]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Takeaway from yesterdays #FinTech talks. None of founders speaking understand actual tech, innovation or how its built. No clue. #sadFacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brilliant, Google safe browsing tools label https://t.co/iC4dHofnSY unsafe. Glad I'm sticking with Bing. Maybe a Yahoo come back?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Following on, yesterday fintech talk claimed no IT developer in a bank is innovative! Utter drivel comment Giles #Zopa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fintech conference today, disappointed with comments from Zopa founder on actual tech. Should know Microsoft is massively innovative atm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving this in my drive...It has been a good weekend https://t.co/5J0QXSREWA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@surface have a surface pro 3, might go for the pro 4 shortly... Shall see]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@surface really impressed with them. Great bit of kit, excellent with Azure Active Directory, and excellent as a tablet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nutter on the train this morning, not what you want at 6.30am]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems a lot of financial based companies want to play on the fact they "not a bank". That's not good, means my money isn't protected #fscs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thatscricket @jamestaylor20 Shocked and so sad to hear the news :( England will miss Taylor, no doubt!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think the exec team will be happy with these. Have to say, simply stunning kit #SurfaceBook https://t.co/AHpiFjqynz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hkanji @nuzzel @rishad clear from day one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I turned the golf off just as Jordan got to the 12th. Ooppss. Missed all the drama, and shocked this morning. #EnglishMaster]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am I the only one who thinks the PayPal new money TV adds are simply awful?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think Microsofts AI bot on twitter is unfortunately now a reflection of many users on twitter. Have to teach it who are just t**** &amp; ignore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see his point, but little harsh on people who are not savy, Granny for example https://t.co/HNt9RVVEjq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An exciting week so far. So much done, well done the team, sure we all need this bank holiday weekend!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am I shocked? No. Not the first or last CEO to act like this #Powa #Administration https://t.co/bWK60sfemp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Commentary in the icc cricket world cup can be funny. Well placed! It was a wild slash that just went that way!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Uni_of_essex looking forward to meeting this years IT graduates at project presentation day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really wish people with colds and flu didnt come into work, sharing all that on the train and underground now means i feel ropey!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have to say Chris Harris on Cars is exceptional. Guy really knows his stuff!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have to say, I LOVE the new Aston Martin DB11...I want one...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always great when you get back to the office and look through whats been developed in the past few weeks, and you're chuffed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First day back in the office after the South Africa break. Feels like a long old working day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Africa is hot hot, though not to leave the hotel for a walk. Ahh. Lucky we have sub, swimming pool and everything we need]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two weeks away from the office. A needed break, but once I'm back, I know i will wish i hadnt had two weeks away due to the mountain!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A win is a win, but wasn't impressed with England, good start, so hopefully can build on that performance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trains are getting busier and busier! Thanks 😞]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full day of business processes today. Loving VISO it seems, oh and spreadsheets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Managed to watch Legend yesterday. Good film, like the way the story was told, Hardy was exceptional]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pleasent spin off from the weekend though, listening to Michael Jackson while working away, forgot how good his music was.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still frustrated with incompetence of some individuals making me work longer on a weekend. #NotThatComplex!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mixed bag of a weekend. Some great time with by little boy, but still a working weekend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watched the bbc4 doco on Donald Campbell last night, what an inspirational man. Need more people like that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great article today by Simon Sebag in @standardnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@standardnews the tech firm IT shortage is due to firms not looking at the talent in UK UNIs. Simple as that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just read tech firms want visa relaxed to grab IT workers from outside the UK. Utter joke, so much IT talent at our UNIs, actually look!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love SCRUM day. Intense sprint coming up, but they are all going to be like that. #build]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stock market falls, petrol set to be sub 90p by April, just a matter of time before house market drops, or bursts!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watched a lot of football for the first time in years and years today. Prem standard has dropped massively!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazed at Broad today. Top stuff! #StunningEngland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/jnrb9NZGvY that's very interesting. Some people need to take note, work time is work, nothing is private]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Corbyn politics upsetting the Labour MPs yet again...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our propriatary built Adaptive Case Management platform for handling a lot of business processes is going very well. Worth the investment!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Windows 10 universal app, yes we will thankyou...First class experience across all win 10 devices, no matter form factor. Looking forward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full on first day bk. Lots of doco, lots of exciting developments.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Office move today. No more silicone roundabout, fair thee well Shoreditch....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do/can southeastern trains ever run to time? I've not experienced it once!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4.8m use London tube on one day. Gives context to any number based statements in politics I think]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@azurecoder catch you when bk in Blighty 😊 have fun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blimey, October saw msoft sell more tablets online than apple! #surface https://t.co/iSiVRS0OBU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fed up with train services, so so so bad!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is it with national rail journey planner, simply inventing trains that don't exist. Keep trying to catch trains that aren't real!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even at a point that some staff really only need a Lumia mobile phone device, continuum, monitor and keyboard, that's them sorted!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our office moving more to convertible devices with dock stations and multi monitors. Keeps costs down, raises productivity and flexibility]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I truly believe convertible devices, like surface pro, like surface book and even new Lumia phones are changing the workplace landscape]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Visually can see the ball move off of the bat! How is that given not out? On review even! #blind #England#cricket]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very much looking forward to this evenings CROWDIT launch event. Great work by these guys.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surface Book sells out in all flavours. Good sign that Microsoft blending tablets with traditional laptops and desktops is the way forward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Death of the PC? You don’t have a clue what one is https://t.co/amU6MWjcwa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five from five circle line journey failures. Does that line ever run properly?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Circle line is awful. Ribs about every ten mins, at best, then just sits at Aldgate for an additional five! Should be running every 2 mins!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Windows phone as a PC via a neat dock, almost full PC. enough for, mail, web and universal apps. That's innovation, business should love it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hkanji we need cycle lanes. That's rather a narrow view of London life and public spending]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VW boss tries to lay blame with a few software engineers! Utter disgrace, they develop what they are specified too! Utter lies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After the Google and Apple events, have to say Microsoft is showing they are the innovators right now. #impressed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Corby wants Royal Mail returned to public control. He doesn't live in the real world does he... #fail]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>