<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Spoke at @AllHealthReform event on health care reform this morning. No live tweeting allowed. Did it really happen?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ddiamond True. You can cover 'more' with 'more' for 'less.' But you don't want to be one of the 'less' who get 'le… https://t.co/Ui54o2m5LD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The hard part was not gawking at the Chrysler Building next door. My son built a 6 ft replica of it in our backyard. https://t.co/0aftXVUR3P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicholas_bagley @onceuponA The other key question is which of these would hit Plan Year '17 and which would hit Plan Year '18.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Must read from @nicholas_bagley and @onceuponA and must ask if the goal is orderly transition or disruption.

https://t.co/PmAUOeMo6x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@squelchedalot 11 generations all in VA in my family. Can't speak to all the branches though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Obamacare Executive Order is not a specific action. It is a declaration of administrative war. Orderly transition or massive disruption?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The President goes by. #InaugurationDay. https://t.co/RDQSx1VWq4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Motorcade in the parade. #InaugurationDay. And the protesters chanted. It's America out there. Really, really. https://t.co/x4M1roXnzC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The motorcade heads by. #InaugurationDay. https://t.co/9eg8Dd2FFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And we have protesters too. Many slices of America here at 701 Penn. #InaugurationDay. https://t.co/2iRqnX66lw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is must read work from @axios. There are no solutions; only trade offs.    https://t.co/XxqUZRFq4d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The view of the queue on 7th St from my office. Chanting and singing. It's quite the scene. #InaugurationDay . https://t.co/7DS8eKTTp0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Start spreading the news. Bringing my act to NYC on Tuesday. #FDA2017 https://t.co/s11QcnSGvr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A few quick thoughts when asked. How I see it from my view on the ground. https://t.co/uYWKUjieqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the poster referenced in my interview with @ddiamond for the @politico podcast. https://t.co/AcadPnSSKD It… https://t.co/A1A6ZMwpWK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grassley Continues To Press CMS on Medicaid Drug Rebate Classifications: What Will Be the Fallout? #drugpricing https://t.co/KmER7ddeSo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happiness is speaking to @TheRealANCOR and seeing my Iowa peeps Chris Sparks and Marilyn Althoff. Teaching GOP spea… https://t.co/fW9wprU4CC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To Get Dems On Board With ACA Replacement, Republicans Should Take Medicare Off The Table https://t.co/SYeohntrZa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatMayne Ugh! Is the scandal the behavior or the incentives? #FollowtheMoney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For donations to @ACSCAN, I'd sing Sitting on the Dock of the Bay, rap, or chicken dance. Thanks @MatthewTSimpson and @MintzLevin DC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forty-Five Days and Counting for Current HHS Leadership: Implications for Rulemaking https://t.co/XSayspHENB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Future of the Medicare Part B Payment Demo under a Republican-held Congress https://t.co/rU3adRjs8k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a moment I truly miss my old job. Writing questions for Chuck Grassley to ask her at a hearing is a staffer… https://t.co/e81S9D2IqW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Paths to Deregulation During the Trump Administration | Mintz Levin | ML Strategies https://t.co/4uJiNXo3Ou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talking drug pricing at Bloomberg's #PowerofDifference event. The issue is not going away. I really do talk with my… https://t.co/vMLd5ifVIf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making the Sausage: Medicaid Block Grants in the 115th Congress - Health Law &amp; Policy Matters https://t.co/RLjCCI1FA6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Fate of the Children’s Health Insurance Program Under the 115th Congress - Health Law &amp; Policy Matters https://t.co/DqPucVAEx9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Promise to Repeal the ACA Poses Threat to MACRA Implementation - Health Law &amp; Policy Matters https://t.co/e8g8LO3JA0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will Republicans Embrace CMMI’s Authority? - Health Law &amp; Policy Matters https://t.co/7QCO6iUPg2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Speaking to @NJACP08628. NJ Community Providers. Staying positive about the future of disability policy. https://t.co/GfQOY4lN2l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transitioning the ACA: Republicans Must Make Hard Choices - Health Law &amp; Policy Matters.  https://t.co/Pc3vi5tPOk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transitioning the ACA: Republicans Must Avoid Disruption - Health Law &amp; Policy Matters https://t.co/x1vGMchDVy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transitioning the Affordable Care Act: Republicans Must Talk to Insurers - Health Law &amp; Policy Matters https://t.co/3gKsOUaA0p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s Not Really ”Repeal and Replace”; It’s Transition. Our take on the new world. More to follow. https://t.co/8Q1yInp6TC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Departing @DCA as an #HonorFlight arrived. Amazing. Overwhelming. Totally choked up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Veteran's Day reflection is about my grandfathers, teenagers from Salem, VA stuffed into ball turrets in WWII. https://t.co/jGob6RAOlN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yours truly at CQ Roll Call event on what next in health care with Mark McClellan and Cindy Mann. https://t.co/bFwBNAYicz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rocking it #PCPCC2016. I had walk up music and a faux Michael Jordan intro (@AlanParsons Sirius). So much fun and s… https://t.co/2qXGJQUydf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is why @TheFix is a must read and will continue to be even after tomorrow. https://t.co/K9eWgTbILX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do me a favor; send an old friend a note. I did last week, and just learned he's gone. RIP Brother Don. https://t.co/UciMTbnHps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was a lot more fun moderating than being the one on the spot. And speaking of spots, how 'bout that gigantic bal… https://t.co/l9sstSJPxY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Town Halls in all 99 counties every year for 36 years. He stands before his constituents and engages through good a… https://t.co/BSoF9BmODw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent folks here at #FNCE. Making eatright more than a slogan. It's hard work and professional support making a real difference.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Speaking at #FNCE in a few moments. A room full of nutritionists. Was it wrong to bring donuts?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thoughts on the Mylan 'Settlement' with my colleague Ellyn Sternfield. There's more here than meets the eye. https://t.co/buljIJyXSf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honored to share the stage with @neeratanden @celindalake @FurchtgottRoth for @politico &amp; @AARP to talk… https://t.co/9BPmWz3D00]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My upcoming Saturday: me, my son, Matthew, #SeagullCentury, @Nationals playoff game, and #HurricaneMatthew. Crystal ball, anyone?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, yes we do. @JoeLipchitz  Happy to do so for the folks @bidneedham. https://t.co/cyA3xIrPq5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And a shout out to @johnsonphotog for her work @bidneedham event last night. Not easy to shoot a moving target, https://t.co/whtyV2vbnw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honored to address the Board of @bidneedham last night. Inspiring to be with people who care so much about their co… https://t.co/7fSjjmjIjI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@contirena1 Curious what you think of my iPhone and Pinto metaphors.  https://t.co/4Wv8Wpy1j9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheFix Pintos and iPhones.  See my quote here.  https://t.co/4Wv8WpPCaH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With CSRxP (@RxPricing), I'm talking about drug pricing. Transparency. Competition. Value. https://t.co/UMsyXvgmC2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think this is a big deal for the ACA especially given reports about the current pools. https://t.co/2TmORXySDd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research Opens a Door for Disability Policy.  A few more thoughts on the @nberpubs work.  https://t.co/nPH8BlcazZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is very geeky stuff, but the conclusions are a big deal for disability policy. https://t.co/V0ohnZzI03]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Done here at #MLPharma. A great day capped off with me &amp; @jrovner. She is absolutely the best. Now to begin planning for MLPharma 2017 ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got transparent with Chris Stomberg and Sandra Wilkniss #MLPharma.  Next up, the one and only @jrovner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Under way at #MLPharma event. Industry panel with @PhRMA @AHIPCoverage @pcmanet and @pharmacists was a great start. https://t.co/iccnYXRufa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Selfie with the audience at #ancor2016. Disability providers are my heroes. https://t.co/vFcP3vopxT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just arrived in Chicago for #ancor2016. Looking forward to talking disability policy tomorrow with my old friends like Chris Sparks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#AHAmtg I also worked in Aja, Dikembe Mutombo, Meghan Trainor and the X-Files. All to promote #ruralhealth. https://t.co/GDnxKWcBxN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just spoke at #AHAmtg where I worked unicorn and underwear into my speech. I love #ruralhealth. https://t.co/aYzMh0VCXd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CMS Increases Oversight of Medicaid Managed Care Contracts - CMS Takes Control https://t.co/uoLLYZm2H1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The IMD Exclusion: Changes Now and Changes to Come - Health Law &amp; Policy Matters https://t.co/N9lfS0DDtZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My favorite #Prince jam will always be the long version of I Wanna Be Your Lover. #RIPPrince]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jrovner Coke Zero is black. Diet Coke is silver. The green one is Coke Life (I've never tried that one).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of CMS's new primary care model. I wonder what CBO would have said if a Hill office presented this for score. https://t.co/3n0tzg6B5C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Health Care Geek uses BABIP and VORP in a sentence.  Film at 11.  https://t.co/PpL7n5GGRG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I spoke at @NatQualityForum’s Conference #nqf16 right before the @Athletics Billy Beane. You best believe I broke out the baseball metaphors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Legislation begets regulation. Enforcement of regulations begets scary monsters. Phase 2 HIPAA Audits https://t.co/jfFQ5JdyIv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Part B drug rule discussed. Grab some popcorn and pull up a chair. This one is going to be entertaining. https://t.co/G2QLe6Utsd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you'd like to know more about the CMS Call Letter than plans are generally happy, give this a read https://t.co/skX1X6x5UA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Comparing doctors the same way you compare shoes, cars, and cell phones. It's one step closer. https://t.co/72a5I2msPa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congress Is Coming Back.  Here's our sketch of the next work period.  https://t.co/yjI2W7ACuf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Valentines Day happiness is being married to a health care geek who gets all these goofy tweets. Peace out! #HealthPolicyValentines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our review of the #Medicare 60-day rule.  Good stuff from folks way smarter than me. https://t.co/GWlsln3fRe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your love and durable medical equipment.  Some things just don't need to be competitively bid.  #HealthPolicyValentines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Valentine, I love you more than the extenders.  Well, I mean except for CHIP and therapy caps and ... #HealthPolicyValentines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Now you see it, now you don't" notice is the the REAL action on drug pricing #Medicare.  https://t.co/VXq7bpywSx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Valentine, no counter detailing will ever get me to leave your brand.  #HealthPolicyValentines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Valentine, my love for you is no demonstration project. #HealthPolicyValentines.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mamurrayflemimg My love for you is like Medicaid eligibility should be: continuous!  #MicDrop #HealthPolicyValentines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Valentine, I love you like rurals love add-ons.  And I love me some rural add-ons!  @ruralhealth #HealthPolicyValentines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Valentine, my love will always pass utilization review because it is certainly medically necessary.  #HealthPolicyValentines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our love is compliant with interoperability standards.  #HealthPolicyValentines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Valentine, I want to be your Sole Community Provider EACH and every day. #HealthPolicyValentines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like Medicaid, I am AMP'ed for you love.  #HealthPolicyValentines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your love is the only EHB in my non-grandfathered qualified plan.  #HealthPolicyValentines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You want me to pay on AAC but I am set on WAC – can our Medicaid reimbursement rates find harmony? SuperGeek!  #HealthPolicyValentines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like @PhRMA and @IAmBiotech dream of patents, our love is forever.  #HealthPolicyValentines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My love for you is 100% of AV.  #HealthPolicyValentines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will you 340B my valentine?  #HealthPolicyValentines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess you say, what can make me feel this way ... health care policy.  #HealthPolicyValentines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like a Cadillac Plan, my love for you has no spending limits.  #HealthPolicyValentines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Valentine, you are my biosimilar.  There's just no one quite like you.  #HealthPolicyValentines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's grow old together.  You, me &amp; Medicare.  #HealthPolicyValentines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A long time ago in a place not so far away, I worked on Medicaid AMP. Here's our take on the new CMS rule.  https://t.co/caITsENNNK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Martin Shkreli was NOT the most important story on Capitol Hill Thursday.  https://t.co/UBua8rIBz2  #biosimilars #nosmirkzone]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>