<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[$3 billion child support system the latest federal government tech-wreck https://t.co/V6HiCz8n06]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swardley permanent ban on lobbying for foreign governments as well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Martyrmade imagine the butthurt to come]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimdownie50 I may be in the Spring. Would be good to catch up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimdownie50 we will need to because the world is not waiting for us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimdownie50 and put in a proper industrial policy beyond supporting a rentier economy based on selling things plucked out of the dirt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimdownie50 and along with "shift the rhetoric" we need to change our competition policy to actually encourage competition...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimdownie50 grown in a darwinian world, red in tooth and claw.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimdownie50 because otherwise I don't see how we will survive the onslaught of hyper-competitive firms entering the marker, who are...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimdownie50 "entrepreneur" talk about competing and winning. so I think it's time to shift the rhetoric a bit in the other direction...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimdownie50 I've only ever heard praise for "collaboration" here and can't recall the last time I heard even a self-proclaimed...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimdownie50 and the ones who did "innovate" are the ones who survive...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimdownie50 in a market economy, people innovate because they're in a competitive situation and if they don't, they go out of business...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimdownie50 distinguish sometimes from simple collusion...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimdownie50 there is an unhealthy emphasis on "collaboration" in the very oligarchically structured Australian economy that is hard to...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FedEx excellent decision and I'm very glad to know this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What we need:
Competition not oligarchic collusion
Change not "change management" 

https://t.co/6DqHNZCICf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Competition not oligarchic collusion; change not change management needed in Australia now 

https://t.co/6DqHNZCICf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@craigthomler YES! this is the kind of thing that I used to think about as a chemistry nerd. now I can die happy 😀]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@egadsthefuzz in this case in particular]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aussielunix @DTA *shock*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I spoke with @jennywiggins at AFR abt my experience in gov and what Oz needs to do to compete in the digital economy
https://t.co/6DqHNZCICf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Info_Aus @jennywiggins @FinancialReview @myGovau watching videos of people trying to get things done is really eye-opening]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1jh @aussielunix that's crazy 😕]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lansing follow me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kathyovoorhees @Lathrop_18 @pjf why should i believe an accusation with zero evidence?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shia destroyed in days by a few 4chan anons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Livestreaming assaulting people on camera probably wasn't such a great idea https://t.co/LIehFfS3ER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very good to see Brennan out of the CIA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ABC @primroseriordan lol except for the wall Mexico itself built to block Central American migrants... https://t.co/sfFzrdArZ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@primroseriordan @ABC imposts on remittances]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SuperManfred fully agreed. i'm delighted @POTUS has killed it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SuperManfred @elonmusk @Gizmodo nice interview. sad that the interviewer insists in having the uninteresting last word on each question!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AI system as good as experts at recognising skin cancers, say researchers // smartphone implementation please  https://t.co/VIsoUNI9d3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TPP is dead https://t.co/uQ26OhfC5j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamestaranto @dandrezner kind of like the investigations into "Russian hacking" by a Democrat administration after Clinton lost?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lathrop_18 @pjf untrue. he owns no stock in either. all divested last year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["THIS IS FINE" https://t.co/jTDBG36IcF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence has arrived, but Australian businesses are not ready for it  https://t.co/r799QkVRga]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the Centrelink debt debacle failure rate is much worse than we all thought https://t.co/XjSVedbbOQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NicoleWill100 @FT @FinancialTimes quite right. which is why it's funny.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NicoleWill100 @FT @FinancialTimes lol. From CNN or Buzzfeed?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ckilpatrick it's pure tribalism in the service of no principle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OZloop @knausc can you send a link direct to the story? I can't open it in apple news.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomas_quinlan real well here mate. hope all with you and yours too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TPP is buried. NAFTA next. Excellent news.  https://t.co/kzwi9SHDjt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theresa May and Donald Trump to hold talks on deal to cut tariffs and allow workers to move between the US and UK https://t.co/6MNzGHDFrQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Post-Brexit, UK can now have its own industrial policy. Excellent. https://t.co/h093WksEMh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Confusion in Centrelink about removal of six-year expiry date on debts | The Mandarin https://t.co/M224ITeSo1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@varadmehta @angadc it's the language of civil war]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@martinsw "transformation" by itself is just an empty rhetoric. what is being transformed, for whom and why?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lacan was right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hillary sadly, the answer is pure fantasy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@craigthomler given the political nature of most appointees that wouldn't surprise me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@craigthomler @ShaunCoffey @Independent it's a very good move in my opinion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@craigthomler it's hardly without precedent nor is it a big drama]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@craigthomler "The Obama administration has notified all politically-appointed ambassadors that they must vacate their posts as of Jan. 20,"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@craigthomler @ShaunCoffey @Independent nothing owed to political appointees by the taxpayers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@craigthomler @ShaunCoffey @Independent they had a couple months to pack and move]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@craigthomler @ShaunCoffey @Independent no reason whatsoever to accommodate political appointees' "specific needs".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StefanMolyneux so much for "love trumps hate" and the other noises they make to distract their victims before they assault them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MariaMacNamara1 @splunk2 @AlexScandurra @RadioNational twitter won't be able to be sold]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[a great example of the brilliant design approach that the NZ gov is bringing to digital services https://t.co/yZ2uqBvj5Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KateNixon77 thanks kate! that is brilliant. exactly the kind of thing i was referring to and where NZ leads the way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This sounds familiar https://t.co/SYQP1y2gBJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aussielunix @DTA much respect and gratitude for the work you and Lindsay did for all delivery teams - could not have done it otherwise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is an excellent piece about what we were trying to do and why it is important https://t.co/CcJWjGpOhc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jpwarren @paulwallbank thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chieftech the problem goes deeper too - the back office is a mess as well and the user journeys fragmented]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chieftech @paulwallbank I remember that post! Those were optimistic days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swardley it was essential. GDS encouraged good things and stopped bad things. Can't do that without spend control.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“You can’t Kumbaya your way through this": I spoke with @paulwallbank about  digital government in UK, Aus and USA 

https://t.co/wK819sSXXQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This must be the wonderful online experience I keep hearing about  https://t.co/j6Usk93LZx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I spoke with @jpwarren at Forbes about #centrelink and other service failures and what we need to do to fix them  https://t.co/GF3vlOq7F3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulwallbank https://t.co/OgkfcgOW6F it took trump to make it obvious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Henry_Belot I was surprised to see that it was a ministerial role here - in UK a civil servant as well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sz_duras those nevertrumpers just don't give up do they?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great insights from NSW minister Dominello and Stephen Conroy - this is not a partisan issue https://t.co/2wCq9kTiUg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulwallbank follow me 😀]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PublicTech great interview thanks!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Public Technology interviewed my last week about what needs to be done to fix government IT. https://t.co/pmsr9fApT7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IOW, obfuscated by design https://t.co/d2hdypbsWD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndyGorfman not all gov IT is outsourced though far too much is. what's in-house is too often done with low skills or poor service design.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hear, hear! https://t.co/Jwqaop0hF7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Info_Aus @TheMandarinAU hear hear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sz_duras ...predicted when he said that something worse than Christianity was already on the way. Now, here it is."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sz_duras he was right when he said ""This priesthood of bad conscience, this nest of pious guilt-mongers, is exactly what Nietzsche...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sz_duras the butthurt is strong with that one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sz_duras she was right!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sz_duras isn't moving to Canada an option?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very sad news. RIP Mark. https://t.co/snFIYTgf5w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mtracey she's a senile old cow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@slowburnweb @dominiccampbell @simoncooper74 but that idea of "transformation by consensus", when has it ever happened?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@slowburnweb @dominiccampbell @simoncooper74 essentially just giving finance a veto over everything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShaneBryan_Aus pdf is the spawn of satan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShaneBryan_Aus thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShaneBryan_Aus thanks for that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hughstephens haha. that could be easily put together in a couple weeks by the @DTA or any other decent digital team.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShaneBryan_Aus @TurnbullMalcolm I don't know where to go to get that info easily online]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK MP Expenses Reporting Site referenced by @TurnbullMalcolm - a good example to follow 

https://t.co/o1eUuvXWRw]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>