<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Limited edition T-Shirts available at gigs while stocks last. 

$30 https://t.co/eQwFBzoJM1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Humanity strikes back at @realDonaldTrump. Join the #WorldToTrump open letter that’s sweeping the planet! #Trump https://t.co/CUI1EZ1jIn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's weird looking back at stuff you did and said many, many years ago and knowing that it's all there in public.... https://t.co/d6vj13gE6S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[KAPITI! Get your tickets for the goodtime blues event of the year!... https://t.co/E2vpxmAtV4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PALMERSTON NORTH! GET YOUR TICKETS TO THE BLUES EVENT OF THE YEAR!... https://t.co/dQibIxBEaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook https://t.co/ASgKpMD5P4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going to be doing a wee video chat for everyone once a month from now on. 

Here's the first one. 

Be great... https://t.co/UgElJ9uoHe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tickets to DW and the band's show in Palmerston North are selling steadily but there's always room for more to... https://t.co/JAvLf711at]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@norightturnnz It's an utterly idiotic move. I hope the LEC revolts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How would you like to WIN FREE TICKETS to see ex-Chicago Smoke Shop frontman Darren Watson and his amazing new,... https://t.co/zGwEzTbcxm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm playing a couple of rare out of town shows with my full band in Feb. Tickets selling fast. Get on it. https://t.co/iTZTev47JA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tickets are on-sale today from 9am for my first gigs of the year in Paekakariki and Palmerston North.... https://t.co/20IHqdiUPl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Darren Watson &amp; The Dangerous Experts Play Manawatu!

Ex-Chicago Smoke Shop front-man Darren Watson and his... https://t.co/S0gsKEpMs5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's the finial 2010 demo for my tune Love Is An Ocean from Saint Hilda's Faithless Boy. Close to the finished... https://t.co/wqNrQ4DVpi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Darren Watson | Love Is An Ocean Demo 2010: https://t.co/y5Vr1OGjaW via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really? I'm a New Zealander last time I looked.... I only cringe when idiot politicians don't seem to get it. https://t.co/TIdCTykCmW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Darren Watson | Tribute To Earl Hooker: https://t.co/aMG50VQ3DZ via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only $1 download! https://t.co/2QrwkqjKfU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please share this widely and let your Kapiti and Manawatu friends know about these two shows in Mid February... https://t.co/2EbQt9hDG0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Darren Watson &amp; The Dangerous Experts - Live in February 2017!: https://t.co/e0ABdw63od via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free download! https://t.co/yTB4vk7S18]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free to download for another six hours. Get on it. 

https://t.co/CxR1YlWBxT https://t.co/kwmqUeSWck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Play music by Darren Watson - https://t.co/vzsJdDXTJi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free download. Merry grimble y'all! https://t.co/ExPpzwxHf7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Xmas everyone! For today &amp; Xmas eve only you can download my 2005 album South Pacific Soul for FREE from... https://t.co/AdiIWebtWX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new video to Facebook https://t.co/xY9QjPgLVL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Almost 4,000 views! Thanks for sharing if you have. It's working! :-)

If you enjoy the song how about... https://t.co/fcOm6KdouN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Radio shows, podcasts, blues-focused websites.

Hit me up if you want promotional download of my latest single 'I... https://t.co/ev7fVU3a7P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My new tune and video 'I Still Feel The Same'. Lovingly created at Lamington Recording Services. Music written,... https://t.co/dd4F5HWAnU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Darren Watson - I Still Feel The Same: https://t.co/9G1Hz9mBsG via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like I'll be playing the Mercury Music Festival in beautiful Whitianga next Queen's Birthday Weekend.... https://t.co/FhSzfALiEr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My alter ego has been busy uploading again....

https://t.co/yzxrIfweOy https://t.co/Im0cumAFqF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lesson vouchers available now! The perfect Xmas gift. 

PM me for details.... https://t.co/N0prrcnvWs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guitar Lessons With Darren Watson | Book NOW: https://t.co/pAWsUIkEEv via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jackcraw57 Was going for Toussaint so..... ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This time of year used to be really, really full-on once upon a lifetime ago..... ;-)

Xmas/New Year 1988/89 https://t.co/iquHIoQb3L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A serious message on the resignation of John Key. 
https://t.co/0vRzg9nuVY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2017 marks 30 years since my first 'real' band Chicago Smoke Shop started touring around these isles. 

Most... https://t.co/hJofTxLpe7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So looking forward to playing in Paekakariki again next year. It's been too long, folks ... so this time I'm... https://t.co/9npDneUzTx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unsubscribe from unwanted emails and combine the rest into a single daily digest with @Unrollme https://t.co/gG6V0V9GYU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One take wonder from 2011. I recorded this song on Saint Hilda's Faithless Boy. It's my solo take on a great tune... https://t.co/EPfVBqMDwM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A wee taste of Toast. Last Sunday.

Okie Dokie..... https://t.co/agVBDQUXtF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had a chat with the good folks at Wellington City Libraries. 

Check it out.... https://t.co/SUXuu1KEoo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This one has been kicking 'round in the head and various demo versions since about 2006. Here's the final demo... https://t.co/3F4McejRAP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Given the amount of crap happening under Jonah Key's watch plus suggestions it's a new fault line can I suggest they call it's Key's Fault?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stereo remix of Money now available with the Planet Key EP. If you  previously downloaded the EP you should be... https://t.co/4ER22X9JeR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you got your copy of the Planet Key EP yet? It's free or pay what you feel. :-) https://t.co/fACS8IbfVT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free or pay what you will. https://t.co/yCZqupedeU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a promotional video for Darren Watson &amp; The Dangerous Experts. Shot live of an evening at Wellington's... https://t.co/dA2rt4EmwW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For bookings contact:
Delia Shanly
info@darrenwatson.com https://t.co/PmGigtQG1o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@avancenz And about bloody time too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. Never thought I'd agree with Peter on ANYTHING. https://t.co/zjYKzfIURY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Media Release
20 October 2016
For immediate release

COURT OF APPEAL UPHOLDS PLANET KEY RULING

The Court of... https://t.co/sotbUheXGE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaxpayersUnion So you guys will now be wanting to know how much the ECs insane witch hunt over my song Planet Key has cost taxpayers, eh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Court Of Appeal ruling confirmed today that my song and music video Planet Key was not illegal. Thanks to everyone who supported me &amp; JJ.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to everyone who came along to Hashigo Zake last night! Turning 50 wasn't too painful thanks to y'all.... https://t.co/JBxipmgCYA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow night's gig/party starts at 9pm. Not 9.30pm as previously advertised.... https://t.co/AIAucjBaf7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Saturday night I'm gonna be doing a normal gig with my amazing new band. It also happens to be my 50th... https://t.co/GU6y8YGKnW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow night! Free to get in. Have a feed and a drink and listen to some blues. https://t.co/AeH0G6cNPZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where else can you hear Booker T &amp; The MGs' 'Time Is Tight' followed by 'Planet Key'? Nowhere else. that's where!... https://t.co/oTEh5uNJ7H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saturday night! No Cover. 

Debuting a new original tune and an old Blue Smitty favourite. Plus all the usual... https://t.co/jrOtBYZnlS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're in Wellington this Saturday night why not head down to the Lido and check out DW's amazing new band?!... https://t.co/AjWX8ZAx5p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going to write the following sentence in the only context it would EVER make sense or be true. Colin Craig is appealing. #jordanwilliams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Darren Watson | FREE BLUES GUITAR LESSON | A Swinging Intro: https://t.co/2pPl0EQmqw via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone just asked me why I keep going on about offices in this video...... which made me take another look at it... https://t.co/TNmQY98TFy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fiddy! :p https://t.co/8G3W8uGc37]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blues, rhythm &amp; blues, soul. Classics and originals. 

See you there! https://t.co/2CYkN4f5Qx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last night at The Lido. https://t.co/sgcF6ZfKQ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Darren Watson &amp; The Dangerous Experts - Live At The Lido 17|9|16: https://t.co/G4BysEvJFc via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After you come to my gig tonight you'll be looking for a cruisy Sunday arvo gig. 

Go to this!... https://t.co/z4hT3uUlo8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So looking forward to playing with Steve Moodie, Dayle Raymond Jellyman, and Rick Cranson again this Saturday... https://t.co/nc6BHJNtAE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Much fun to be had this Saturday night. 

See you there. https://t.co/dYOodUPFSm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saturday night!

If you're in Wellington send yourself along for a goodtime! https://t.co/zQle8drkvF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4000 Youtube subscribers! https://t.co/ZtGjOSAgSs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Throwback Thursday huh? M'kay.

Here's me playing a perhaps over-familiar tune in the original key of F#. That's... https://t.co/KAETc7CTzv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have two awesome MIM Teles for sale:

1 x Fender Baja Telecaster (Modded)
This has had all the (imo) bs... https://t.co/f3oV5yVFKq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posted a new photo: https://t.co/gl95rYDft3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posted a new photo: https://t.co/gl95rYDft3 https://t.co/QQuMwDzagQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posted a new photo: https://t.co/16HGTHMw4w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posted a new photo: https://t.co/16HGTHMw4w https://t.co/QQuMwDzagQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posted a new photo: https://t.co/ySdmEYIewQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posted a new photo: https://t.co/ySdmEYZPoo https://t.co/QQuMwDzagQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posted a new photo: https://t.co/Wsn3k9W9vr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posted a new photo: https://t.co/Wsn3k9Ey6R https://t.co/QQuMwDzagQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be playing at Ata Rangi Estate with The Dangerous Experts as part of Toast Martinborough again this year.... https://t.co/EGHlq3dpsW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posted a new photo: https://t.co/p8ae6GAksf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posted a new photo: https://t.co/p8ae6GiJ3F https://t.co/QQuMwDzagQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where else in Wellington region would you like to see my wicked new band playing? Venue suggestions?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posted a new song: "Money" https://t.co/5spJdHasr8 https://t.co/4fVPsm4Ruk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posted a new song: "Money" https://t.co/5spJdGSR2y #music https://t.co/QQuMwDzagQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[49 to go to 4,000 subscribers! https://t.co/2q1NcPfUNc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Throwback Thursday. 1993 TV3 Telethon for Starship Children's Hospital. 

Darren Watson &amp; The Little Kings Of... https://t.co/AhcqC0CXS2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posted a new photo: https://t.co/izdF73FcAu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saint Hilda's Faithless Boy is available on CD again for a limited time. https://t.co/LGo3wqwdGb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As of 31.8.2016 I will own the rights to ALL of my music again. 

This means you will not be able to find any of... https://t.co/91n714qDb4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posted a new photo: https://t.co/oYJiCNmqgT https://t.co/AttBip51DV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posted a new photo: https://t.co/dZWAmwsei2 https://t.co/gYrXIRYg9D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posted a new photo: https://t.co/xLZRBY756Y https://t.co/DKQPgG1syA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our distributor has sent the last 7 (seven) copies of Darren's 2002 Tui-nominated album King size on CD. There... https://t.co/ZY40VOyglQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great gig at the Lido last night. Thanks to everyone who came out to check us out. The band is going from strength to strength.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>