<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Good luck with that. https://t.co/WPogNCVZXh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty sure he's trying to Jedi Mind trick the fireplace. https://t.co/u03yQsOUvl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think it's time to pull the unpresidented lever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last name?
Patti. P-A-T-T-I 
That's the last name?
*head desk*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please make the shark look like Trump. https://t.co/47mFLXE7Lf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've taken zicam, Airborne, my inhaler. Please let that be enough. I do not have time to be sick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best thing I've seen all day. Watch. And watch it again. https://t.co/9hhpk4xsC1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@entangledpub A tiny figurine of a cat sitting on a toilet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am so grateful to my parents for giving me books, lots and lots of books.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RebelMur That's quite the talent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kate_mckean Security at Empire State Building once offered to walk me around the X-ray security point. I was not pregnant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Resistance. https://t.co/7JC3DX2R7M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loathed him as governor of CA. Will happily take him as president. https://t.co/UnF9EkT11O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahdessen This is why I have anxiety about returning things to stores. They ask why and I start to worry that my reason isn't good enough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What an asshole. https://t.co/XvEyrKriHx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wakes up. Checks twitter. https://t.co/gGems6bWYu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jennifercarolyn Computer labs were new when I went to college. I forgot to log off. And someone signed me up for a dating site.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Throwback Thursday! An author never forgets their first launch party. https://t.co/TGgVPItblR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Throwback Thursday! An author never forgets their first launch party. ❤

#writer #writers… https://t.co/QGi9bXU07e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrianCBaer Yes. Yes I am. Because they are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything sucks. So I went shoe shopping.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrianCBaer So true! I do this whenever I've received good customer service. Always call or ask for manager to leave compliments.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm really tired.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm asking in all seriousness: Why do people engage with eggs? Why give voice/power to an egg with 8 followers? Ignore them, please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Book mail from yesterday. I'm hearing a lot of great things! 

#booklover #bookstagram #bookworm… https://t.co/eMs6M86B6e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is so true. https://t.co/sn25hTTaaS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AngryBlackLady Fingers crossed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Evan_McMullin What's the likelihood that an investigation will take place?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why doesn't Trump call the fake news? MLK bust tweet was corrected but he's still talking about it. https://t.co/mO3A4AkCYx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SqueeTV It's super creepy to go back through the tweets. How horrible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There isn't. He's not a grown man by any stretch. https://t.co/bfae1qStd4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kurteichenwald @Newsweek Yes. Yes it is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I read it. You should too. ALL THE WAY THROUGH. https://t.co/Bab8vcS7Ou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're cow towing to a man who called you Little Marco Rubio for a year. We see you. https://t.co/ekAncktcej]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And Putin cries happy tears. https://t.co/Zk6et2WJ15]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ooooh. I'm going to have to think about this. https://t.co/rF85HLLNeB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GROUP HUG! #LCFZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bright spot in my day. @zoeinthecities https://t.co/vVwChXQP23]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't like Trump because I don't associate with FAKE PRESIDENTS. https://t.co/Gr5XnwewFw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahDarerLitt My dad tried to school me with "Politicians aren't the only people who can govern." I respectfully disagree.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TINALORK Super weird. I'll be right there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aishacs Thank you. ❤]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel defeated today. Republicans are better at this. They have no conscience. So they win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so fucking sick of Republicans. https://t.co/qcHKtSaIgd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I LOVED this book. Have you read it?

#writersofinstagram #writer #writers #january #wednesday… https://t.co/u7KtscaL6S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally https://t.co/63lKY65xO1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Contemporary Novels by and about Muslims. https://t.co/lq5DGYn7SS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Copperfields @lithub Thanks for the list!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Books are always the answer. https://t.co/aFp5McIzO0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be watching a lot more CNN. https://t.co/YVgoBJZCF7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elledoo Naturally. The liberal media is the true source of evil.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elledoo Clearly!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will never make fun of Canada.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why, in 2017, are we still pandering to Right Wing Christians? 

WHY? WHY? WHY?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then we will vote you out. https://t.co/JC00mNP6NO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT this forever. https://t.co/HUy9K60tBE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I fucking hate this guy. https://t.co/C6lhxdIzmT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This man is a hypocrite. Nothing but a lowly, power-hungry hypocrite. https://t.co/lOd2kKw10C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jennifercarolyn You are a superhero! This made my day. And I'm sure hers as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jennifercarolyn Holy crap! You're Felicity Smoak!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a world of Umbridges, be a Weasley.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone know President Bannon's approval rating?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are Dumbledore's army. https://t.co/OeFKxYjCJ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PVDTW1 I completely read that headline wrong. I thought it was about CA succeeding. Sorry!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In all fairness, do POTUS or Spicer actually know what an AG does? Because they seem confused.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NO. Do not give this power. https://t.co/9YnBpam5nI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course they will. Now imagine their reaction if Dems had done that for Garland. GOP=Hypocrisy https://t.co/d9REOkqlZJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teachers &amp; Dems know DeVos is a disaster. This isn't about party lines. She's UNQUALIFIED!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOP supports the GOP. Film at 11. https://t.co/5i66v0ruw2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's true. And it makes me sick. https://t.co/hwYg3vgsVi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear @SenateDems &amp; @SenateGOP - 
What are you going to do about this? What will you do when he belittles a foreign… https://t.co/MDOV9DMBQO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This headline is better. https://t.co/q9r576dlTX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do I feel like this headline is misleading? https://t.co/Na5Z0xnguq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OddballPaladin I always forget that loophole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Betsy DeVos plagiarized her work? Students get expelled for that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LSavedow @JoyAnnReid Exactly! Excellent analogy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would rather talk about books, writing, and reading all the time. I just can't right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of book birthdays today! I will be tweeting about those today because we deserve to celebrate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyAnnReid I've been saying this for years. Trump is simply the byproduct of a party based on racism and misogyny.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you! https://t.co/1zWMbNJW6p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol! This is CA too. https://t.co/4X4xorieCW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So the Benghazi outrage, that holds for Yemen, right? DT should call those families and personally apologies, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is important to have shelf awareness. I am fully aware that my shelves are a mess. https://t.co/A9SECOh9zb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shelf awareness. My shelves are a mess. A mess! They are two rows deep. The outer rows consist… https://t.co/CPRLyGPjlS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please. Help. https://t.co/21CPaVW0pS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#blocksessions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poorly edited. No structure. No plot. Writing is immature. Author needs a thesaurus, bigly. #DNFTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@carlywatters I have a recurring hand injury from holding books. Good to know I'm not alone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TLT16 @laurenduca Not mine! Borrowing from a friend. But it's perfect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seanhannity @newtgingrich You two. So cute. So obsolete.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait. I could've gotten paid! Son of a ... https://t.co/KmVZbpPbnP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insubordinate. Insubordinate! These idtiots want to be ruled by a dictator. https://t.co/iy93snCvAl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't fuck with Silicon Valley. https://t.co/ZBH12tSWIF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SallyQYates Thank you. We stand by you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you, #SallyYates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ask your buddies about Merrik Garland. Then STFU. https://t.co/ECtb6QWn36]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm such a lapsed Catholic I don't consider myself one anymore, but I'm proud of the Pope and the bishops for their words against the ban.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes. The answer is yes. https://t.co/6SH20abZ5Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first book is wrought with flaws. There won't be a sequel. #DNFtrump]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>