<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Destination: The Rim via Australia, Spain and Argentina 
#GoSpursGo https://t.co/w48SwKwHID]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having a crack at listening to a #MidnightOil album for the first time. Probably about time, I guess?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does Dow 20,000 Mean It's Time to Get Out? https://t.co/rcidfrmmaY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dow 20,000: Your Gift for Living Through Brexit and the Election https://t.co/S1sURoohYg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it just me or is Rafael Nadal really starting to thin on top?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdmondBurton If you want to read about what he's done.

https://t.co/ju4hjuuLjO via]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdmondBurton Hahahaha!! Just looked it up and it appears he's done a lot of positive work as a youth worker in the ACT. Good on him!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdmondBurton I think I might know why... https://t.co/xJsUY8gRpm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdmondBurton Amazing!!! Umm, what's he done...?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdmondBurton wait, is he actually nominated?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flip your flagship menu item upside down and nothing more? You gotta seriously try harder than that @maccas! https://t.co/kiHCDmgWjs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spotted a guy in a Shannon Noll shirt in Wynyard this morning. Whether worn ironically or not, not something one sees very often!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tmf_mike The Uncle Ben's brand grains are impossibly tender! You know you've made it in life when you can cook brown rice like him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tmf_mike Well no. You wouldn't be eating until about 11pm otherwise ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tmf_mike And that's why I always cook it in large batches on weekends and then reheat. Could you imagine cooking it after a day at work?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tmf_mike Haha! I find a rice cooker helps but you're still a way off getting it to taste like those Uncle Ben's microwaveable rice packets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would just leave accidents and homicide, wouldn't it? https://t.co/HSx7B9f3tx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tmf_mike Yeah, whatever it is it's certainly not what's written on the packet! Went with 3:1 and it came out so-so. A bit sludgey.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tmf_mike I cook a big batch on weekends to microwave and have with dinner during the week. Can I ever remember water-to-rice ratios? Never!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does cooking brown rice have to be such a major pain in the arse?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdmondBurton really interesting findings from some studies https://t.co/JI908quqJL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coffee + Stephen King Sunday morning Mk II.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantastic hometown show by @welostthesea tonight at @Newtown_Social! Europe: you've no idea what awaits you later in the year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@classicaleague @newscomauHQ sure this wasn't taken from the @BetootaAdvocate?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tmf_mike And by "band room", I mean artist dressing room.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tmf_mike Definitely not bigger but one with a band room would be nice! Alan's gonna love putting on his make-up in the public bathroom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tmf_mike And the venue will be so befitting of Alan Averill's stage presence...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My ears usually can't tell shit with remasters but lordy the 2013 edition of @lambofgod - ATPB cuts through so much mud of the original mix!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I genuinely thought I was going to get Rick-rolled when I clicked on the link but NO #CasinoMike is definitely goin… https://t.co/3hlm2PhSjv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've done my share of stupidly hot Sydney summers but this gets-hotter-through-the-night bullshit is really throwing me! 32°c at 6am? GFY!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tmf_mike Half of which would be made up of superfluous remixes as appears to be the trend in the electronica space.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tmf_mike You left out "Breathe" ;) They definitely peaked at that point in the late 90s but a handful of neat tunes have followed since.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone else think the use of steel drums over the opening credits of Schwarzenegger's #Commando strikes as an odd choice of instrument?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying Prodigy #TheDayIsMyEnemy on for size. Their relevance has diminished considerably since late 90s but always curious re their output.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All this moving around of sports franchises is making me dizzy. https://t.co/Hb52l0NGXQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stubbed finger first game of the year. Basketball season(s) 2017 has begun!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tmf_mike Yeah, I think I jumped ship about 20 eps in. Felt he was just trying to cover far too much in the allotted time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tmf_mike Yeah, sounds about right. Fairly short-burst episodes around the 10-15 minute mark?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tmf_mike Covering the entire history was too ambitious for the podcast I listened to. Better to have given focus to a single figure/event.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tmf_mike I tried a Rome podcast a few years back. Lost me a few episodes in as there were far too many figures and events to keep up with.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tmf_mike I tried non-fiction and found it heavy going. Got a John Le Carré book lined up to see how it fares fiction-wise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tmf_mike I'll have to give Audible another try. Wasn't sold on my first experience but suspect it was due to subject matter and narrator.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tmf_mike Absolutely right! Got books on Mexican drug cartels, political figures, etc, all half-read because the narrative was poorly told.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tmf_mike It's reminding me that reading doesn't have to feel like a chore (sorry Uncle Ho).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tmf_mike Enjoying it so far. First time in a long time I've read two fiction books in succession. Feeling like I need the escapism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tmf_mike 11.22.63. Holding off on Dark  Tower after  (hopefully) finishing this one fairly quickly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coffee + Stephen King book. Sunday morning set.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picnic at Hanging Rock was cool. Read like a high school English text, only without the teacher making you finish a chapter every night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The aircon unit at home works!! GFY #SydneyHeatwave! https://t.co/nNFiorklLv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tmf_mike Truer words never spoken. Think I caught maybe three sets in there the whole weekend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tmf_mike Just seemed like no one was getting into that room in a timely fashion to see anyone over those four days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tmf_mike Did you manage to catch him at RB? Specifically, was there room at Patronaat during his performance?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tmf_mike "I've got a desirable 17 minutes of drone, now to change it up for the next segment."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can anyone honestly differentiate between Steven Seagal's "Marked for Death", "Hard to Kill", "Above the Law" and "Out for Justice" films?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tmf_mike Definitely taking to it more with repeated listens. Curious how he'd have gone about conceptualising and executing it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reacquainting myself with the meditative drone of CHVE - "Rasa" a year on from seeing him mesmerise and captivate Pauluskerk in Tilburg.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welkom bij Sydney FC en Australië @JordyBuijs23 - looking forward to having you with us for the rest of the 2016-17 season!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walk past a guitar + bagpipes busking duo in Martin Place on the way to work this morning and now I've got Finntroll stuck in my head. Urgh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdmondBurton Actually, I think we need to give a free pass to Indigenous wearers/purchasers of the Indigenous All-Stars RL jersey.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdmondBurton Ver happy that there are no arbitrary exceptions to the rule!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdmondBurton what's our stance on those who buy/wear NBA East/West All-Star singlets?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdmondBurton I remember being told as a kid by the "bigger kids" that it was worn when a player personally believed his team would lose(?!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdmondBurton I'm curious as to its decline specifically in RL given that its use is still prevalent in American football and baseball.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdmondBurton Yep, they concluded that it can enhance a player's ability to track moving objects in sunny environments.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#RugbyLeague enthusiasts: is there a reason for the decline in use of "eye black" (black paint rubbed below eyes) in the sport these days?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bazillion degrees in Sydney today, why not a steaming bowl of home-made #pho to top it off? Closest I'll be getting to VN for a while.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And while I'm on this #karatekid trip!

https://t.co/izL4YHXSVV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What #SydneyHeatwave? 
Training for #Bbbrun in Rhodes next month continues. https://t.co/3dtXkSkeWM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Cabra Kai Academy" martial arts school in Lansvale - a name so awful yet so genius at the same time! #karatekid #sweeptheleg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've followed pro-wrestling on and off for nigh on 25 years now. #TheUndertaker is simply ageless! https://t.co/8iQAIOc8pC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring on Andorra, Liechtenstein and Monaco - European Principality Group of Death at #WorldCup2026 then. https://t.co/yRO6GsBhtU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pointless fixtures? Confederation wheeling-dealing? Bullshit football politics? You've got it! #worldcup2026 

https://t.co/mjQwmVWI68]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Given the MM/DD/YYYY date notation generally used in the U.S., shouldn't it be called "Born on July 4th"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tmf_mike I quite enjoyed the listen. Production showing its age but otherwise struck as a more organic Godflesh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to Fudge Tunnel for the first time. Know nothing about them aside from being one half of Nailbomb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@nevermoreband Inside Four Walls and @systemofadown Prison Song thematically the same song, only delivered in drastically differing ways!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdmondBurton Definitely. Was trying to think of a gun, perennial playoffs PG, e.g Westbrook, but still not enough seasons to challenge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdmondBurton Just thought his place would be occupied by another PG but then struggled to think of anyone else who'd have the numbers...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdmondBurton Andre Miller, Top 10 all-time assists? Not super surprising but kind of is at the same time?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdmondBurton Seriously, though: for such a dorky, unassuming guy, god he was good!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdmondBurton And the takeaway is small white guys are really good at getting the ball to the big black guys on the team to score!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdmondBurton given he's not known for being as prolific a scorer as others on that list, nice seeing Kawhi perform… https://t.co/9ab5PMyCXs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Gyradiko Bexley - top shelf pita gyros! Source it if you're ever in the St George!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If anything's gonna make a trip to @Bunnings on a weekend more bearable it's seeing all those dogs pushed around on trolleys there!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tmf_mike Constantly having to pick myself up off my arse. It's embarrassing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those kid shoes with wheels in the heels - bloody annoying!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdmondBurton I hear South East St Louis and North West Virginia Beach are both pining for a professional basketball team...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdmondBurton But can you move them to a SE, NE, SW or NW region of a city...?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdmondBurton YES! Didn't want to throw around "identity" so used "character" instead, but now you're with me and see what I'm getting at...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdmondBurton I should clarify: I was citing CC as an example of being a dull, lifeless sporting franchise. Me and my ambiguous tweets!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdmondBurton But struggling to think of a more dull franchise in the league taking into account city, logo, colours, roster and honours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdmondBurton Haha, yeah, looking back at my tweet it could be construed as being rather ambiguous!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdmondBurto To any city or does the game limit the locations to which a franchise can be moved to?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdmondBurton Sweet highlights. What I was driving at is the Bucks franchise as a whole lacks any dynamic nature e.g. Columbus Crew in MLS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdmondBurton @Forbes noting Kings are #18, wonder how Clips would be valued if they were still in San Diego (comparable to Sacramento)?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdmondBurton you'll need to enlighten me...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdmondBurton No. 1 through 4 no surprise, but Clippers at 5? They were virtually unmarketable in the 90s and 00s.

https://t.co/IW3fzvApFr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Milwaukee Bucks are the most character-less franchise in the #NBA

Discuss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or Sydney and Melbourne for that matter. https://t.co/jb2U6d5MAf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ipohonyork - source it if you're in Sydney and looking for no-fuss Malaysian hawker food. Top-shelf stuff!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>