<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Alexa and Google Assistant have a problem: People aren’t sticking with voice apps they try https://t.co/dytMF6es5a via @Recode]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A distinct possibility I'd say... https://t.co/ynaQvII0MM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hotting up....Google Flights Gets Aggressive by Intercepting Airline Trademarks https://t.co/N9EkFqF2Oz via @Skift]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting, but won't score highly on "recurring revenue"... The ‘Uber of funerals’ is turning heads in Russia https://t.co/LZOUOXrpOl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why artificial intelligence is the future of travel https://t.co/IYjX3AW0Mk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What, why and how: chatbots for brands https://t.co/rZW4KhOXts via @thedrum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber’s new tool gives cities a mind-bogglingly detailed view of traffic patterns https://t.co/foZYw7YDhc via @Verge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snake on a plane cancels Emirates flight to Dubai https://t.co/mIP0CZfkyN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How easyJet transformed customer data into emotional anniversary stories https://t.co/6mHnw3cfMN via @campaignmag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Travellers ready for Messenger-type communications, especially with incentives  https://t.co/vmZl2OmycI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Deadly snake imitates tinsel on Australian Christmas tree"..or alternatively, "Snakes like trees &amp; it's Christmas" https://t.co/lpB8T1JXxp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter Reportedly Developed Its Own Instant Messaging App But Decided To Can It https://t.co/TB23SRzu2H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's hoping - next year is shaping up to be another good one for airlines — and travelers https://t.co/isyc7qrtgG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I'm a dolphin apparently... https://t.co/all4iBcL0I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Almost like installing a standard home router... https://t.co/xejB4Y5V9C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting stuff....Virtual Reality’s biggest names just joined forces to make VR even better https://t.co/L87EILNLFz via @thenextweb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you get stuck with literally the only middle seat that exists on the Swords Express coach home]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Myth debunked: bird crapping on head is not good luck sign. Got parking ticket after receiving the massive payload from fully loaded pigeon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A slippery slope....Facebook Said to Create Censorship Tool to Get Back Into China https://t.co/4SykN9vjVr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Airbnb has no plans for an API to integrate with its new trip platform…yet https://t.co/NfL3ojQV4a via]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nmcgivney yeah, could be a some short term curiosity factor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toblerone, what have you done! https://t.co/SVOm9Ccpmm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoy this @TheRDS https://t.co/x7nK5OQCWP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google's Travel Business Is Already Twice the Size of Expedia's https://t.co/rVvRkr44qp via @Skift]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm pretty adventurous food-wise but not feeling this #reykjavik https://t.co/59KVguZO9J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A gloomy day but still looking pretty Reykjavik https://t.co/UUQSxy4z2H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Legend - Worst thief ever? Suspect 'hides stolen blind in trousers' https://t.co/qAtVqH2a9P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing - Danny MacAskill releases brilliant new mountain bike tricks video https://t.co/IfDFLkdhpH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glenvillemorris you chose the middle one obviously?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Made by Google: 4 reasons Google threatens Apple’s hardware crown https://t.co/7A9wGTcIPU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook launches Marketplace to let you buy and sell items with nearby users https://t.co/GPem16EX4d via @Verge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google’s October 4 hardware event: What to expect https://t.co/EmzYPv17ti via @Recode]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Marriott learned from its faulty Facebook Messenger chatbot https://t.co/CYka3zUtwW via]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Facebook and Google should leave their secret gardens https://t.co/SUbthNaFpi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is interesting - Spotify eyes SoundCloud purchase as Apple challenge intensifies https://t.co/jHOfN0i5gJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's arrived at last - Apple Starts Selling App Store Search Ads on 5th October https://t.co/SjlglO15mV https://t.co/SjlglO15mV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think you suffer bad luck - read this, feel better  -BBC News - Spider bites Australian man on penis again https://t.co/w0NkYgrKY2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Germany will not get the "better" ads FB promised- Facebook told, stop collecting data on German WhatsApp users https://t.co/I9JD4JbkgE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WhatsApp is testing a new group chat invite feature that uses shareable links https://t.co/jLtDIbS8OB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 things to know about Snapchat Spectacles https://t.co/sdDZ1T4pJm via @digiday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bloomberg: Apple moving forward with smart speaker to rival Echo https://t.co/9PrZlUuucO via @engadget]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not exactly shocked by this -  Facebook overestimated key video metric for two years https://t.co/rtLTCIHsov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really hope this was true https://t.co/NCo6PWUS4F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clinton’s App Is Trouncing Trump’s in Pretty Much Every Way https://t.co/3iKW7QpWMw via @WIRED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Early days but exciting nontheless - Allo brings Google's 'Assistant' to your phone today https://t.co/tHto8Cty2x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well this is pretty good - Retailers Can Now Buy Facebook Ads That Only Run If the Right Products Are in Stock https://t.co/pwqahCtW1M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real life code warriors - WhatsApp devs (possibly) troll Apple with hidden ‘f*ck you’ in source code  https://t.co/GVdtV2iug1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catch me speaking today at 12.20 in the  AirXperience stream at the #AviationFest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to 2 days at #AviationFest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What The Guardian has learned from chatbots  -  when bots are too "human" it freaks people out! https://t.co/EnbGKkytr4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glenvillemorris just landed. Thank God]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryanair FR3007 from AMS clearly running late as inbound aircraft not here. Any chance of an update?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glenvillemorris ha yes indeed. And fair play to them for notifying me before airport screens. App 1 Schiphol 0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not what I need to see after 11 hour flight from Mexico and 4 hour wait for connection https://t.co/31gXfGAMb2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unfortunate that during my first visit to #Mexico City Trump decides to drop in too....at least he made a mug of himself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good news - Jumio secures $15 million for further growth  https://t.co/dZAIHsKYWl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mmm..."better ads" ...WhatsApp will share your phone number with Facebook for better ads https://t.co/VvcKeLUlyU via @thenextweb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expedia, Travelocity, Orbitz, and Wotif quietly add natural language search to their homepages  https://t.co/gJYeloPNvr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Faster Apple Watch 1 Models Said to Launch Alongside Apple Watch 2 Later This Year https://t.co/UOCch34Lch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook opens a giant hardware lab to build its future https://t.co/0inlDneJIG via @engadget]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CocuKitchen hi. Do you still serve food at 6pm in Baggot St.? Is it your lunch menu? Cheers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clever promo from Lufthansa - selling seats on Airbnb https://t.co/TBiXIiLQeB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @netflix take a bow. #StrangerThings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Airbnb wants to make bots to cash in on all the stuff you do while you travel https://t.co/fag72USgW4 via @Recode]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting from TripAdvisor  - adds airline user reviews https://t.co/UQOZ9JGHFc via @TWtravelnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What you need to know about messaging app Line in 6 charts https://t.co/IxEO4lLO4K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google's relentless march on travel continues -  adds airfare tracking, hotel deal spotting, filters to metasearch  https://t.co/tDTQQev6AX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kenearlys disaster for the game really]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Literally not a fan of the team, but very much a fan of Man City's approach to innovation https://t.co/VqbkBMz0Im]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cracking article -REDEF ORIGINAL: No One's Better at Investing in Attention than Facebook (@liamboluk - @MediaREDEF) https://t.co/kmY2HILrj1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great read - Be prepared: We're entering the post-device era 
https://t.co/B7I8JExm74]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook Adds Raft of Chatbot-Enhancing Features to Messenger Platform https://t.co/UqcPRepvLg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This!....Google: time for the travel industry to see through its do-no-evil mantra via @bhealy_ireland https://t.co/J7XGcLIOzb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah to be a fly on the wall......Google convenes meeting of travel brands to ease tensions https://t.co/9n6S3MNSaU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As "Ns" go it's not the worst I've seen - Netflix just changed its icon [Updated] https://t.co/uvtDXOLBMx via @thenextweb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harsh,  but some truth in this.....Apple doesn’t understand photography https://t.co/1mQLBemKsU via @thenextweb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great long read - Light at the End of the Funnel: Why the Marketing Revolution is About to Arrive via @tweettal https://t.co/QzYlUw79Y4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting - but Rich Notifications may kill this ...Politico is hacking Apple Wallet for news push notifications https://t.co/50qu99DL8B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheapflights launches on Facebook Messenger with an interesting quote "54% of revenue now comes from mobile" ...https://t.co/tj9ZsBiOsH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ultimateaunty congrats! Very impressed and you'll have a 100% career win record!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ultimateaunty fair play to you. How did you get on?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chatbots take the pitch for Euro 2016 https://t.co/dP1mgBB0ys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spotify Says App Store Changes Don't 'Get to the Core of the Problem' https://t.co/95u0xu6aBc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future of Apple’s App Store is subscriptions https://t.co/dpFsif7P86 via @verge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[German publishers are pooling data to compete with Google and Facebook https://t.co/aHDm11fe2d via]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@j0eclifford @davidmulligano good man! It was a spectacular balls up. Next year! Maybe...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@j0eclifford @davidmulligano you've been biding your time with that Joe. Was a nightmare in fairness!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidmulligano sorry forgot to say enjoy Thursday night football!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidmulligano I actually enjoyed seeing Spurs kick lumps out of Chelsea despite the total bottle job!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davidmulligano ha! Yes it is. No idea when that was taken. I look very interested in something!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Etihad claims Hollywood first as Nicole Kidman stars in virtual reality ad campaign https://t.co/77NE18nnyP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WestJet Goes Mobile with TSA PreCheck Program https://t.co/BgrZ6OYuJd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobiles provide the most emotionally engaging screen for marketers, according to Yahoo research https://t.co/BIDmrsa0bN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice - Skyscanner launches Facebook Messenger bot https://t.co/tAJsATIOEf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chromebooks outsold Macs for the first time in the US https://t.co/bcffl4KSDh via @verge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intrigued by #GoogleSpaces - not sure yet if it competes with Pinterest, messaging or is something totally new. Let's see]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ryanair reveals strategy to be a digital business with an airline bolted on  https://t.co/OCcpefKFeR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting - Marriott and Trivago Sign on to New Ad Product for Facebook and Instagram https://t.co/nuZrbGhbDR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why telling ourselves we’re ‘too busy’ is bullshit https://t.co/s6M7Fk6uIE?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously. What a hero. #Attenborough90]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>