<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[A night cap of remembrance. Something I've been saving. A 25 years aged Balvenie bottled the very hour Erich died. https://t.co/6UBrL68Ej9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnJCampbell just a snippet really. So many great stories. His 48-hour joke telling competition with Barry Crump, for example.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hilstace he tried to sue Porirua. They lost but exposed some terrible things that were going on there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarabeee he was a great dad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ChrisCalviFree @markcubey @JohnJCampbell this one got framed https://t.co/PHUr9AgBF0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisCalviFree @markcubey I got to hear the later ones on the radio, and all were resung around the house.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FitKiwi I believe they were not friends. Opposite sides of the abortion debate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnJCampbell thanks John. I would fall asleep to his shows with a transistor hidden under the sheets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is lots more I have missed. Political campaigns, garden plays, radio shows and songs, travel, his many friends, and his family.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Erich was diagnosed with multiple myeloma. He outlived the initial prognoses by several years but succumbed in 1995.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The final campaign took up most of his later years: in particular, his work for IPPNW and founding and fighting the World Court Project.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[abortion law reform, humane treatment of psychiatric patients, proper health funding, zero population growth, and nuclear disarmament.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This led to a life of campaigning. He fought for: sex education, cervical smears, a 2nd medical school, the contraceptive pill,...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He founded the NZ Medical Association as a rival to the NZ branch of the British Medical Association, &amp; started publishing his own journal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He did not like the conservatism of the NZ medical community and he set out to change it and to fight for better medical services.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He left Otago and went to work in general practice in the Wellington region. My mother and he built a practice together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While lecturing at Otago University, he also fell in love with one of his students, my mother.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He fell in love with New Zealand. He particularly loved the people here, their generosity and their spirit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While in that role, Erich saw an advert for a medical research/lecturing job in NZ. He took a boat to NZ not knowing what to expect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When his mother became sick, Erich left his research career to work in the hospital treating her. When she died he became a ship's surgeon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Erich worked for while as a researcher at the forefront of medical science, particularly the science of ageing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Erich was a Fulbright Scholar and spent some time travelling and studying in the USA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He was naturalised as a citizen of the UK in Edinburgh in 1944. He developed a love of all things Scots including whisky and Burns.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He told me he enrolled to do a third doctorate at the Sorbonne in French literature, but that might have just been a joke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During those 10 years, he published at least 16 publications in a wide variety of topics, not only medicine but also old French.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a student of Edinburgh University, Erich completed a doctorate in medicine and then a second doctorate in pharmacology.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Erich lived in Edinburgh for 10 yrs. He completed his undergraduate medical degree then transferred to be a student of Edinburgh University.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Erich was granted a place in London School of medicine which, because of the Blitz, had moved to Edinburgh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Erich taught biology in a private boys school while searching for a place in med school. It was there that he learned the rules of cricket.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Erich said the internment camp was wonderful, full of artists &amp; intelligentsia, including the Amadeus Quartet who would perform.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the war started, Erich was interred as an enemy alien for ~6 months.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The other sister went to the USA where she married the man who later invented the remote control. Erich and his mother went to the UK.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sadly, it appears Martha was betrayed by her lover's husband. She was arrested &amp; transported to Auschwitz where she was gassed on arrival.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Martha later travelled to the Philippians, then Spain and Italy, before returning to be with her lover in occupied Ghent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alfred arranged permission to enter the UK. But one sister, Martha, wanted to stay in Ghent. She had fallen in love with a married woman.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Erich &amp; his two sisters made it to Belgium. They lived there for ~9 months. At some point their mother joined them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Erich took a train to Berlin figuring that no one would look for a Jew fleeing in that direction. The next day, Hitler annexed Austria.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the UK, Alfred tried to help the rest of his family escape.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alfred’s work led to the Nazi’s calling for his murder. He was smuggled by Reuters over the Alps and to the UK.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Erich’s brother Alfred worked for Reuters. He went on to found Reuter’s business division. Alfred reported on the Nazi atrocities in Vienna.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Erich started his medical studies at the University of Vienna before all Jews were barred from the University.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Erich became a polyglot, learning most European languages, ancient and modern.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Erich developed a deep love of music &amp; language. He told me stories of sneaking into Italian operas or listening to American music radio.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Erich grew up in his family’s café surrounded by discussions of the political issues of the day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Erich’s father fought in the Austrian Imperial Guard in WWI &amp; received an injury from which he never fully recovered until his death in 1930]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Erich was born in Vienna. He was of Jewish decent. His father was socialists (so non-religious), but he grew up in the Jewish community.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About my father, Erich Geiringer, born this day 100 years ago (in ~40 tweets): https://t.co/IBi4NTELIQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OK, I am planning a rather large thread about my father. If you don't want to read it, you should mute me for a while.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is the 100th birthday of my father, Dr Erich Geiringer (1917-1995).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The last point was my reason for this tale. See Doug Linder’s site for more details on the Judges’ Trial - https://t.co/8wQTK5U0Qq (11/11)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schlegelberger’s decision to remain in office as long as he did lent his good name, &amp; thereby gave credibility, to the Nazi regime. (10/11)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schlegelberger was sentenced to life for his "hesitant injustices" because of the inherent injustice of the system he applied and… (9/11)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schlegelberger said he believed that if he resigned someone worse would take his place. This turned out to be right. (8/11)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schlegelberger resigned in 1942 because "the cruelties of the system were too much for him.” (7/11)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schlegelberger applied those laws with some leniency, although Hitler had the power to overrule lenient sentences which he exercised. (6/11)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schlegelberger tried to resist, eg arguing that half-Jews shouldn’t be sent to the camps (if they would agree to sterilisation). (5/11)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The laws Schlegelberger applied were the laws in force as passed by the national authority of the time, the Nazi Party. (4/11)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schlegelberger refused to join the Nazi Party until he was ordered to do so in 1938 by Hitler. (3/11)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schlegelberger was a respected jurist, an author, a law professor, and a judge. He rose to Director of the Reich Ministry of Justice. (2/11)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This seems like a good time to tell again the story of Franz Schlegelberger, one of those tried in Nuremberg after WWII. (1/11)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Won't mention Jews in commemorating the Holocaust; Chooses "America First" slogan; Appoints Bannon. Anyone still in doubt please wake up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Acting AG merely stated there is no credible argument EO is constitutional that would have been more proper &amp; more useful for opponents.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Acting AG's reference in reasoning to such things as the wisdom of the EO is unhelpful. It clearly strays into issues of policy not law.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrbarnabyb I think it will be mostly symbolic. New AG's confirmation hearing is today. Courts were already granting stays.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrbarnabyb what does what mean? Tweet not linked at my end.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, the #DoJ won't defend the EO in court, the #DHS won't obey the court's orders, &amp; the SD won't talk to Congress about the EO. #USinCrises]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok, this tweet was a misfire. I thought it was pretty funny. https://t.co/J8pmvO4m8p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poll results: 458 votes. A late surge brings "Yes" to 9%. However, the result is still an emphatic win for "No". https://t.co/hwuTPXre1Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New US regulation: the Bank's Farm Credit Administration Meetings &amp; Early Child Care Centre Fence Height Requirement Regulations 2017.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReaverBait @StephanieMarija Wellington CLC has a drop in employment law advice session on Wed evening, Hutt on Tue https://t.co/stxdibN68s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man of the match must be Stoinis. #NZvAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@susu_george @ayssoora I've headed home to cook dinner. But Old George's flat whites are always welcome in our Chambers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is kind of the point of international treaties. The duties are owed to the other contracting states, not the i… https://t.co/zVC8aljjMG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course it is the role of NZ &amp; UK to complain when USA breaches obligations under international treaties to which we are parties.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@susu_george @ayssoora personally, I favour large cups of free coffee, but that might be the lack of sleep talking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grateful for the ACLU lawyers, but not sure how to show it? Just do something nice for any random lawyer tomorrow. We're fungible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrumpyYetAmusin @sarabeee how was the protest today?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump booted the GSA’s designee for his own choice within eight hours. https://t.co/NKXn69QWUY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats To GSA: Trump Is Now In Violation Of His DC Hotel Lease https://t.co/caMJkGJkMO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This thread. Let's not completely lose focus on the deficiencies of our own stance towards refugees. https://t.co/v900XsqN7i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@DylanReeve yes, he claimed to have a secret plan to defeat ISIS. It turns out his "plan" was to tell the military to draft one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Watchmanz @Pno_nwa @Fishtiks @Twitter how about someone with a Nazi handle triumphantly tweeting a video of someone being murdered?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@LachlanForsyth @Twitter like this, which took less than a 10-second search to find: https://t.co/vtAlrnU3zm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Watchmanz @Pno_nwa @Twitter you are confusing free expression with a corporation helping to spread hate propaganda for profit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Watchmanz @Pno_nwa neither, supposedly, do @Twitter's T&amp;C's. But the application of those T&amp;C's appears lacking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Watchmanz @Pno_nwa eg I don't think @Twitter should generate ad revenue by giving Nazis free access to its platform to spread their views.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Suzyiam @HomeAndHoused I think "no" covers that. It doesn't imply agreement with past supply only acknowledgment of its existence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rachaelking70 @GemWilder not that I have heard. I expect it will take months.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm told these are mostly US citizens protesting in Wellington, but they are keen for some support from locals. Ple… https://t.co/k1FlefWu9Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protesters gathered outside the US Embassy in Wellington. https://t.co/LNCgx7VM9o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's nice. How come there are active Twitter accounts openly promoting discrimination against immigrants? https://t.co/aEaNzdk2pY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attending the 2017 Rua Rautau Waitangi Lecture with talks from Dame Tariana &amp; @garethmorgannz. #RuaRautau2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus tells story to explain who a neighbour is. Not someone from injured traveller's tribe, not his priests, but his enemy willing to help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People remember Samaritan was good, but forget point of parable. Samaritans were enemies, but one helped where fellow Jew &amp; priest refused.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarristerNZ That's 250 votes. It would be nice to get 500.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GRRMspeaking @LiveJournal It seems the Goebbels quote might not be authentic: https://t.co/0yaQfWFPN9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Trump wants to stop these migrants he will have to make that wall very tall: https://t.co/pcu5SQ7hrM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnnyRedLives I think that counts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NikkyD77 @Dovil absolutely not a serious question, or we absolutely should not share intelligence?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think this is a serious and interesting question, perhaps worthy of a more scientific poll: https://t.co/hwuTPX9Dai]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>