<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, no "red line" of congestion across the Burrard Inlet for the SeaBus, from @CTVVancouver 
@martynschmoll… https://t.co/3RtedB8pxP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is strong evidence that congestion pricing is not a war on the car but about our health, especially children

https://t.co/NgSY7aWRVH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not quite the same but similarly this is why we highlight more clearly our "All Ages &amp; Abiliites" AAA Network in an… https://t.co/4AbJcZL9Kg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to also see @CityofVancouver 'brining' our All Ages &amp; Abilities bikeways in advance of any snow event https://t.co/d8bQcCj6Ah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["City officials can’t take a backseat &amp; watch... as private operators selectively dictate which facts can be used"

https://t.co/rJIFqaOAs8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@humantransit Yes, we're even closer to Broadway rapid transit. I was encouraged last night by how many asked, why… https://t.co/6UwuxQwwgF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This dapper planner works as part of my Transportation Planning team - looking stylish as always in this nice artic… https://t.co/FO99EMNPnf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And if you missed yesterday &amp; can't make it to the final open house today, here is the link to the survey:… https://t.co/YadRMWGuK2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bike theft was down for the 1st time in a decade in #Vancouver - our @CityofVancouver partnership with… https://t.co/6A8k0SLgdi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Quick Facts if you can't attend:
More capacity, fewer transfers, lower costs, more flexible, more efficient for… https://t.co/CZ981TzdCy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The... project brought dramatic change to the area.. over time people have adjusted to the new shape of the street"
https://t.co/lqYxe8pOud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, half way through our morning &amp; great team work planning - what a great venue &amp; space to think strategically ab… https://t.co/wtb08MW7jW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“People think this is a luxury, but there are a lot of public benefits in the long term"

https://t.co/yvBxdmlUJ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Started the upgrade study for this #Seawall section 5 years - So excited to see it get separated walk &amp; bike paths!

https://t.co/CGOYby45TT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The overarching problem... is that it's not part of a longer-term vision &amp; transportation plan for Metro Vancouver"
https://t.co/cwbOh2tjF7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things to miss? The Chevron clock as I bike to work.

Things I won't? Multiple car driveways across the bike lane 

https://t.co/IwWAauLgus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Example of a transport inequity - that we 'invest' in highways but 'subsidize' transit by @Scot_Spencer… https://t.co/Qjq9VsAJuu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Florida, please help me get home safely from the #SafeStreetsSummit &amp; commit to action to not being top state… https://t.co/LcphcXlLh4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great morning start of day at #SafeStreetsSummit with Emiko @completestreets &amp; Charles @thehappycity https://t.co/YCyGsSE4Kq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's not the Doritos that are killing you but the place" @thehappycity on why solo zone land use has -'ve system effects #SafeStreetsSummit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here is the 2016 transit ridership as compared to previous years 

via @NorDelReporter https://t.co/3nF6GKcSNz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada, we aren't doing much better than the US so let's do our part in #Vancouver to significantly improve this na… https://t.co/PUmFyrOGcT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4.5% is awesome!  Look forward to the 1st year of the Mayors’ 10-year Vision transit increases contribute to anothe… https://t.co/RE4zMsKjnl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Walk 10 Blocks' pushes adults to walk about a kilometre every day.
"It really is just dead-simple to use, and it's… https://t.co/K0Te53ZGKR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited to be sharing our #Vancouver policy experience to encourage Broward, Miami-Dade &amp; Palm Beach to bolder sust… https://t.co/6uiwxTbh5m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But not quite the tactical urbanism you hope for as we needed Police enforcing the safety the coned-off travel lane… https://t.co/t5Yc9lHxDu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Impressed by the concept of the Quick-Build Protected Bike Lane, leg #1 on our #SafeStreetsSummit mobile workshop -… https://t.co/p1jyHpPdPf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrowardBcycle Thx for the ride this morning on our #SafeStreetsSummit mobile workshop. Had a great 10 mile+ tour o… https://t.co/sOyNzjwSrG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One day out of the office &amp; more on my 2017 work plan:
"the planning work would also look into street design and a… https://t.co/sVB7u2kfi1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grescoe When we designed this, we recognized it's almost an 'Active Transportation' scramble as only people biking &amp; walking cross Burrard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["100% of respondents felt the IllumiLane pilot made Vancouver a more joyful place" 

Thx @CityStudioVan for 'illumi… https://t.co/dggS5USyel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Shocking" pedestrian graphic pulled after outrage - 

More shocking is that it was created to try &amp; be helpful… https://t.co/pVmTva8yDS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great idea - could also track the # of TAPS &amp; when often &amp; frequent, revise the signal timing permanently &amp; move TA… https://t.co/q2LfNEIrUA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[En route to Florida to talk vision, policy &amp; implementing #CompleteStreets

Will feel a bit at home with… https://t.co/EbivjyRnUO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["BCAA’s Cambie Village location is easily accessible by both transit, on foot or by car" AND is on a major bikeway!… https://t.co/8pVAnq5ahS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Way to go #Montreal!
"The new additions... brings the city’s total number of car-free street network to 45 segments… https://t.co/zAn72wSc57]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JSadikKhan Helmet law? Hills? Rain? A protected bike lane network to support bike share BEFORE launch? 
#Seattle 3… https://t.co/nNNS8dGymq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mobi_bikes @CityofVancouver This map is missing all of the protected bike lanes recently built downtown in 2016. C… https://t.co/HLDL38ULX6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From @CityofVancouver in '16: 

2 separate research studies show multiple health benefits.. Comox-Helmcken Greenway… https://t.co/MvXdhIgdmv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or: 

We redeem CAPACITY to be # of people &amp; LEVEL OF SERVICE to be equity for all - now we have a true IMPROVEMENT

https://t.co/gB5Reiq6c0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Provide input on some of Vancouver's biggest transportation &amp; city building projects during our two-week transport… https://t.co/ZYHB16nWp0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This is in addition to the five B-Line routes already approved by the Mayors’ Council last November" https://t.co/TbBobYhP41]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Game on! Here we go!

"The City's... Arbutus Corridor is a game-changing expansion of our seawall-greenway network"… https://t.co/NOUl4YenhR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["protected bike lanes will need to become something that street engineers assume... - and omit only if necessary"

https://t.co/JWX8cPVZVT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So exciting - more Canada Line capacity, more Skytrain service hours, &amp; a significant increase in SeaBus - all to i… https://t.co/9mdaCtZ9tJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@renewablecities Glad to know you're visiting #Vancouver. Let me know if you want someone on my Transport Planning team to give a tour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had a great time with @modacitylife sharing a potential faster way to Transportation 2040 mobility &amp; safety outcome… https://t.co/1HdkKKzddK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bit cold, certainly wet, &amp; still dark this morning but a delightful return to commuting by bike (leaving more roo… https://t.co/9XEqJ8aCCe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimusser No Georgia is posted at 50 kph - not sure where the @CAA authors got that from]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just a sample of some the biggest transport planning moments of #Vancouver - have we learned well from history &amp; ou… https://t.co/OYi6vPIaoQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This chronology has so many key #Vancouver transport planning moments - nerd out &amp; enjoy this timeline!

https://t.co/2TAtmXfivn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then again @CAA, Georgia St is a #bottleneck - with PEOPLE crowding its wide sidewalks.  We consider that success.… https://t.co/Xe61SWfRsS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A National #bottleneck ? 
But @Caa is showing us just how reliable Georgia is for drivers (&amp; transit) &amp; safe for al… https://t.co/UbQosZuSxW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As per the open house photo from of our last change to the Adanac bikeway, we also want to do meaningful walking &amp;… https://t.co/pS6RrFilXe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice results in #Toronto

@CycleToronto @TO_Cycling https://t.co/IupxESL43E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look forward to fare changes by 2018. 
70% support distance-travelled fare system in TransLink fare policy survey… https://t.co/YVcKC0GIpd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Better coordination could... help governments make the most out of existing roads instead of building new ones"

https://t.co/xsKo71CtDS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Better yet, start with a true urban freeway that moves 13,000 people/hour on rapid transit AND turn its underpass i… https://t.co/0kSs7NS8Ir]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 ugly urban underpasses now functioning as public parks https://t.co/BZyOotjphg via @Curbed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Success will be measured by how fast people are moving: a bus... will count 50 times more than a car with one"

https://t.co/BIXcXYtjx4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also for 2017:

Look twice before you WIDEN the street.

#VisionZero https://t.co/mbA9Zsnh50]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opportunity to improve our Union-Adanac corridor for people walking &amp; cycling - improvements for the "jog" &amp; more… https://t.co/WeX6tiHZph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love our Healthy City Strategy -where else does a transport engineer get to learn the value of 'social connectednes… https://t.co/9Xj0ISg37Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our #Vancouver story is also that our protected bike lanes significantly increased the % of women using our Downtow… https://t.co/epLNLDixi1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@CityofVancouver does extraordinarily well in encouraging people to use other means of transportation than the car… https://t.co/yd4GhMtjFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["the best option... is to build an all-ages biking network on both small &amp; large streets"

https://t.co/sLyIqUBhQ8 https://t.co/evSUeadpsc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MitchellReardon Did you hear that today 300+ @CityofVancouver staff were redirected to ice efforts?… https://t.co/2ey3IlpsQH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The less people need to drive in our cities, the less we all pay, in more ways than one"

https://t.co/Zw9RZ6uLnw via @MetroNewsCanada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seeing 4x4 trucks desiring to use our #Vancouver protected bike lane network was a sign of success in 2016, more to… https://t.co/MX8IWCGtfY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy 2017! Are you ready for another busy year here in #Vancouver?

2 of 3 @vancouvermetro big stories relate to t… https://t.co/XvBVM0drBN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TransLink Thanks, with the snow falling, this is even more appreciated as a great travel option for #NewYearsEve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NewYearsResolution for all

"shift the focus from just moving people &amp; goods faster, &amp; make safety a top priority"

https://t.co/p6PxCnTF4T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It never ever makes sense for a major rapid transit line to end just short of... another major line"… https://t.co/TqsrBK0vDh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We really valued having Andreas Røhl share his Copenhagen experience back in 2012 here in #Vancouver when we create… https://t.co/oby1fonNvx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a new Legion of Boom in #Seattle - parklets &amp; streateries increase business activity and vibrancy along ci… https://t.co/Yvi2NXJArN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["automakers are trying to rebrand themselves" (yet) "they’re still in the old-fashioned business of moving iron"

https://t.co/gnjWoBCUsT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We might not always acknowledge it, but the reality is, when we build infrastructure we’re also building communiti… https://t.co/jFPScor9M6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, construction (most often) doesn't have to block #bikelanes. Here is my photo of @CityofVancouver showing it car… https://t.co/RipT6ySYMP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And I encourage my #Plangineers to champion our AT Promotion &amp; Enabling Plan into all @CityofVancouver departments… https://t.co/VDPLmkWOxF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["people who move out to the suburbs can end up spending far more on transportation than their Vancouver neighbours"

https://t.co/OzYxjCmwbw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a nice protected bike lane! Wide for delivery bikes going both ways.
@modacitylife @shift_delivery 

By chance… https://t.co/3q0Dby637r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From @mobi_bikes: 
For a limited time only we are offering Free Day Passes! Visit https://t.co/bmn0GlkfKy … for more details  #mobishawgo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need a digital Christmas stocking stuffer for your Millennial friend?
Maybe someone who wants trying Mobi as their… https://t.co/H1JSk3ubMk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Uber &amp; Transit best serve different audiences at different times"
Great facts from @TransitCenter &amp; @humantransit… https://t.co/MaXb3DnqDE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["one of the most dangerous paths the country can take because of the... potential for magnifying driver error"… https://t.co/2hdFTU67OK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantastic @Ayan604 snapshots capture the illusion of how suburbia appears to cost less unless transport $ considere… https://t.co/VKAwTLawdm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Our transportation corridors... are going to have to be shared to a greater extent.”

https://t.co/w7pbOVufqC via @MetroNewsCanada]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agree with @BrentToderian:
"What it should be is a conversation about how to make the city work better for everyone… https://t.co/OoMmb3RDkA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Concerns are mounting about how the cars behave in dense urban environments" - so keep a focus on sustainable modes
https://t.co/Zs6J5nk5nJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With Hornby, @CityofVancouver finished a Downtown protected bike lane network - history indeed as our daily cycling… https://t.co/hf5c0scNb1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exciting nerd days ahead! While population #'s come out in early 2017, we have to wait almost an entire year for Jo… https://t.co/VuqEIpD4EB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@martynschmoll Totally agree which is why @CityofVancouver includes our most used bike routes &amp; walkways as priorit… https://t.co/zAVNpiNWwG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just in time for the holidays - the new #Vancouver 95 B-Line express bus service connecting destinations along Hast… https://t.co/TcHhsUc6Hn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoyed something similar here in North #Vancouver, including a most pleasant walk up these stairs back home on thi… https://t.co/Qd0k8A0LLd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Putting some boundaries on the process of testing autonomous cars makes sense given the potential liability..."

https://t.co/oslCOUIdIU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Twas a great way to start an exciting Council day. Thx @_PIBC for recognizing our @CityofVancouver safety efforts https://t.co/FvchO5fDj3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TransLink is also making some changes to bus routes in the downtown Vancouver area — emerging from recommendations… https://t.co/VFMuJdf3aM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today we showed reimagining our #Vancouver streets as AVs become real by reallocating car space for other City goal… https://t.co/DdSxyorVr1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Make it easier to drive less" &amp; "Manage the road network efficiently" are our Transportation 2040 directions - we… https://t.co/BpNbkNr84r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And because ALL cars take up space, even autonomous ones, we need to keep building better #walk, #bike, &amp; #transit… https://t.co/kUr4lhqF1n]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>