<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[770: In the West Byzantium still ruled Sardinia; Sicily: governor at Syracuse; just the foot and heel of Italy; Venice; ports in Dalmatia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[770s: Byzantine Sicily produced several iconodule martyrs. The emperor had Methodius of Syracuse scourged +confined underground for 7 years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C8th: The Roman (Byzantine) Empire minted coins at Syracuse, Ravenna, Rome. Gold coins continued after 751 when Ravenna fell 2 the Lombards.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[740: Large campaign by Muslims of Ifriqiya [Tunisia] ag. Byzantine Syracuse. Countryside ravaged; but called back bc of a revolt at home.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[726-727: Willibald, an Anglo-Saxon pilgrim, sailed home via to Syracuse: on a ship carrying envoys of the Pope w letters from the Emperor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[c.723: Willibald, an Anglo-Saxon pilgrim to Constantinople &amp; t East, stopped at Byzantine Syracuse. Not the most direct route. Trading ship?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sicily 718: The Byzantine governor rebels &amp; declares a counter-emperor in Syracuse. T revolt is put down by a flotilla from Constantinople.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[704: Muslim flotilla from "Ifriqiya" [Tunisia] raids the Empire’s outer islands: Balearics, Sicily, Sardinia. Syracuse sacked? (unclear).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Late C7th: Civilian sea trade moribund. Coins struck in Byzantine Carthage, Rome &amp; Syracuse found in the Danube delta wd be due to the navy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arabic sources point to a date of AD 668-69, but the contemporary Liber Pontificalis says in the time of pope Adeodatus, acc. 672.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SE Sicily 669: Arab sea-raiders from Egypt led by ‘Abd’Allah b.Qays briefly take &amp; devastate Byzantine Syracuse. (Tunisia still Byzantine.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[668: Did the teenage Constantine IV, son &amp; heir to t assassinated Constans II, gather a fleet and personally proceed to Syracuse? Disputed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[668: The army of Byzantine Italy ("exercitus Italiae") seized Syracuse &amp; killed the usurper Mezezius. His head was taken 2 Constantinople.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Syracuse 668: Roman (Byzantine) emperor assassinated. His military commander, Mizizios, perhaps unwillingly or reluctantly, is proclaimed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Byzantium 668: emperor Constans II was assassinated at Syracuse. His son brought the seat of government back to New Rome (Constantinople).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[660s: Neither Greek, nor Syriac, nor Arabic writers speak abt the Emperor's sojourn in Syracuse. Information only from the West (Latin).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AD 663: Emperor Constans temporarily transfers his HQ to Syracuse, presumably 2 shore up the crumbling structure of imperial rule in t West.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 'End of Antiquity': After AD 600 only one city in Western Europe shows evidence of an abundant copper coinage, namely Byzantine Rome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Close friend of Obama". In The Age, left-liberal Aus newspaper. Next: the sky is blue.
 https://t.co/YGQUfkjWBA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Crude bid [by Trump] to be strong leader." Even The @australian blurs or removes the vital separation of reporting from commentary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Macedonian invasion of Persia. Fought near Persepolis in south-central Iran. Invasion leader: Alexander 'the Great': https://t.co/1MTE7pyyWS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Regrettably, Australia is leading the pace in becoming a full-on Nanny State: https://t.co/9FBKNu9C13]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In Germany, lawmakers are .. proposing criminalising ..fake news." Which is to say:  censoring unfavoured views. https://t.co/S6ZzGDBpQi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did US diplomats under Obama ever send "dissent cables"? To ask the question is already to know the answer:  https://t.co/Zqrx5Jmw4L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Eever123 thanks. But i am neither an academic nor a conservative. Aspiring intellectual perhaps. Member of Leyonhj… https://t.co/OC7BxWIB6K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Milo Yiannopoulos, scourge of SJWs, has them hopping. Vastly satisfying to see him twist their knickers: https://t.co/jUJHTZRUdF via @WSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Martin17773 thanks. Feser's discussion is complex but thoughtful. 
 @catoletters 
Topic: torture in Christian morality. Cites Aquinas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@byantium yes. Literally unimaginable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zzzzz. Wake me up after they go-go: https://t.co/N0sf68wlNL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Eever123 'My dear girl': The Bard is not my area. But I cd probably help with Byzantium...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Eever123 I am a conservative-friendly libertarian. Many of our values overlap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@catoletters No: https://t.co/AwxlVybJKq
@Martin17773 Did Aquinas deal explicitly with torture?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Eever123 Often remarked how diff Shakespearian is from Modern English. I wanted to convey that Richard's was older. Great Vowel Shift etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[News? 
My own retirement in 2011 was ignored by this rag. :) https://t.co/8b0Ze1733X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MoiraR Original in ancient Armenian: History of Sebeos. The English cd be J B Bury's, via the French of Drapeyon?? Cf French insensé.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MoiraR I found the phrase 'vile insensate slave' too delicious not to quote. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Richard III was born in 1452, 112 years before Shakespeare (1564).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is about 80% intelligible to my Australian ear. Nearer some NW dialects in modern England? https://t.co/ijw76QY8nT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picture of his hat: https://t.co/fg8B6oVD3B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Akakia: a cylinder w jewelled ends containing dust, held by Byzantine emperors at ceremonies. Symbolising mortality, hence his own humility.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[949: N Italian king's ambassador 2 Constantinople records jewelled organs; a mechanical throne; and a tree of gold w singing metal birds...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AD 917 Byzantine embassy 2 the East. The Arabs laid out massive amounts of precious objects, jewels, “22,000” carpets, “38,000” tapestries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C9th: The Kievan Rus' sold slaves &amp; furs above all; also amber, honey, wax; 2 buy Byzantine silk, jewellery, brocades, fruits, wine, spices.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Byzantine imperial triumph 831: a white charger w jewelled harness; his cuirass under a gold tunic embroidered w a design of roses &amp; grapes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John VIII, 1430s: In t jewel-studded bulbous-domed crown &amp; pendilia (side pearls) of Late Byzantium. Or large high-crowned mitre-like hat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1376: Byzantium sold the island of Tenedos 2 the Venetians for 30,000 ducats plus return of the Byzantine crown jewels. Not carried thru.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MoiraR Roman (Byzantine) emperor Herakleios was failing militarily. The Shah taunted him that soon Constantinople wd fall. Chosroes fell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1346-47: Rich Serbia, shabby Byzantium: Dushan crowned in bejewelled gold. Kantakouzenos wore one of coloured glass set in gilded leather.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1343: Byzantine crown jewels pawned to Venice, never to return. They may have been melted down when Napoleon conquered Venice in 1797.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Constantinople 1331: Byzantine wife of Kipchak khan arrives. Her brother under a jewelled parasol; his men in jewelled helmets. Ibn Battuta.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ACT [australian capital territory] is an enclave wholly surrounded by New South Wales (nsw). By implication NSW… https://t.co/Pwb8IDAaWt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kon__K i wd have thought the wording chosen by @JulieBishopMP was designed precisely to -avoid- endorsing Trump's 7-country ban.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[c.623: "Chosroes [of Persia] 2 Heraclius his vile and insensate slave: ...Have I not destroyed u Romans ...you trust in God; why then(etc)".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[780: Byzantine emp. Leo IV dies, aged only 31. Illness supposedly contracted from his wearing the jewelled church crown from Hagia Sophia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Constantinople 17.vii.1203: Franco-Venetian assault on 2 sides. Alexios III flees to Thrace taking the state treasury &amp; crown jewels w him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Byzantine emp. Manuel 1159: jewelled purple robe over golden [gilded] mail armour, &amp; a jewelled diadem “dripping w pearls [i.e. pendilia]”.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Published five minutes after the order was signed:  https://t.co/WXGubm6L4Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cry or laugh? What is the difference bet. a D-class "celeb" and a private citizen?  https://t.co/9alPNCeFhM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Evidently no apology by Mr Farah: "Relief for Sir Mo Farah as dual nationality Britons are exempt". Express:
https://t.co/qYruOVhdQ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is never wise for a Gen ?Y to debate grammar with a Boomer. https://t.co/1lI0Zn53JC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The "forgotten" Aboriginal XI, Australia's first touring cricket team. In fact "rediscovered" about twice each year. https://t.co/hdgV81yA0P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was always going 2b amusing w the new Don breaking. Today: managing a visit to UK w/o him &amp; future King of Canada mutually embarrassing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As always, column by @HenryErgas in The @australian v good. Today: the mob vs the people vs parliaments plural. C21st mob more dangerous?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tennis: correct question is: who was the more dominant *in her era*? Number of majors won not important. On balance: SWilliams &gt; MCourt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pétard, his, hoist, own, by. Facebook's Mark Zuckerberg drops case to acquire Hawaiian land:  https://t.co/dPtGtvdQv6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@infoanrchy Link: exec powers do derive from US Constit. AFAIK courts could validate, bc immigration is a Fed power. https://t.co/uhzbQIHeXT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@infoanrchy Discussion here of legalities of Trump executive order: note reference to statute law. https://t.co/MWbZ666Liy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does not wait to hear US response: "Mo Farah: British champion criticises US travel ban." Not a Somali citizen. https://t.co/en7ovK099w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Farah does not have dual nationality or hold a Somali passport.. trying to clarify ..with the US authorities." But Trump wrong beforehand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@infoanrchy precisely the point I made in my 1st tweet 9 hours ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@infoanrchy or r u now agreeing w my first tweet 9 hrs ago? said there Supreme Court final.
 @pixalkiller31 @alllibertynews @margokingston1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@infoanrchy @pixalkiller31 @alllibertynews @margokingston1 I was discussing "standing" ie whether non-citizens can be heard by courts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CivilSocietyOz  @HistoryNSW used 2 call itself the "peak body for all interested in history". A mere ?million in NSW. Claim no longer made.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CivilSocietyOz it was t hubris of your organisation that concerned me. Asserting jurisdiction or 'peak-ness'  over 24 million Australians!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CivilSocietyOz G.  No. Since Hegel, civil society means "market society as opposed to institutions of modern nation state". CS = not-State.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CivilSocietyOz which ones do u think are the worst offenders?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CivilSocietyOz And while I am on it, 'civil society' does not exclude the market. Even or rather: esp. Marx understood the market is core.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CivilSocietyOz "Peak body for civil society". Hubris on an almost cosmic level! Who appointed you to sit over all of Australia? Get real.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SincDavidson tks. didn't get that from other tweets. Surely wd get visa for US, but, like me n you :) cd be judged unsafe at interview.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SincDavidson possible, if dual citizen. (as you and I know, but many will not, in Aus one cannot be an MP if dual.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Evidently readers of BuzzFeed think Australia is small and heavily populated. If "think" is not too strong. https://t.co/qYXxBUdAyr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@honesthistory1 how did he tell which was which? Truth testable: but intention? Cf Groucho: 'if u can fake sincerity u can fake anything'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helmet looks Late Republic period of Old Rome. Middle Byzantine depicted as simple, unadorned "hemispherical prolat… https://t.co/i6kAgf4yBi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saw this interview. I am anti-ALP; but she did perform effectively. Tone of reasonableness. All the more dangerous… https://t.co/Bo9NdnaV7K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kon__K US is not bombing "Libya"; they were bombing ISIS bases/units there. And I can find no report of action later than Oct 2016.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikefagan_ibc but the "battle of Brisbane" is well known today. Search the phrase in Google Books. (btw: is yr link the right one?)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrayConnolly in canberra similar demographics taxi drivers vs Uber. But Uber never have body odour; always know way to the Nat Library. -]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iosefmann New England is not a swing seat. Or in Australian English, not 'marginal'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FXMC1957 Reminds of 1933: Oxford Union (student guild) resolved after debate "not to fight for King &amp; Country": https://t.co/bMdPBYhdav]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pop/soul. Everything else they did was v average but "Go Now" [before u c me cry] quite brilliant. Remake of, but b… https://t.co/leKFHdftQU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lies: untruths told with foreknowledge of falsity. Bullshit: truths one American professor doesn't like. And tellin… https://t.co/563Z79ar1b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Depends who you ask." https://t.co/4TYttCj329]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikefagan_ibc Wd you not say 'restored to history'?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Auspol Centrelink debts: minister Porter on Skynews TV: The "52" cases raised by the ALP have been looked at. No serious concerns.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pixalkiller31 on yr argt no non-citizen wd ever bring a case to a US court. They do, every day. I presume jurisdiction is geographical.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pixalkiller3 "locus standi" discussed here. The US Constit mentioned, but seems mostly common law. Note UK posn:
https://t.co/58u3h0Ojow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Qldaah exactly. Which makes your original tweet wrong. Fisher federal labor 1910 came *before* Ryan state labor 1915. Ryan not 1st. -]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Qldaah yes, so Ryan NOT the first.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pixalkiller31 then why did the US Federal judge hear the case?  Constit not relevant AFAIK. @alllibertynews @infoanrchy @margokingston1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@infoanrchy "really? You don't say!" /sarc/
@margokingston1 @justinamash]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>