<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Trainspotting two did not disappointed! Just as good as the firstðŸ‘Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lollipop lady on traffic lights...
Wow, good to know where my taxes are going to..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 seasons of @CW_Arrow in just over a week...
What a great way you spend ChristmasðŸ‘ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gracedunne72 @samenglish95 sams a cry baby..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samenglish95 why don't ye drink some cement to harden ye up, you little bitch!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gracedunne72 chauffeur of the yearðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the peasants complaining about the bus and I'm just driving alongðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ stinker!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every chance there is I miss @MarcKinchen ðŸ˜‚ even in ibiza I got in an awful state and missed the whole nightðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's with everybody thinking there kanye, gettin pictures with there mouth closed.. for the love of god, just crack a smile you vain fucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I say ikea are making a fortune in franceðŸ˜‚ selling chairs to beat the bandðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My name is Dean and I live in a country that panics when they see a roundabout..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sick I'm not going to Bruce springsteen!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's supposed to be sunny me holeðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gracedunne72 don't be saying that youðŸ˜‘ðŸ˜‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yet another flight in the space of a year were my bag gets checked for drugs.. is it my face??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Study is a load of wank!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bought a Samsung tv 13 months ago and its covered in burn marks! now @SamsungTV are telling me I have to pay to have it fixed! Not impressed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gracedunne72 still won the bet..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caught up on flash and walking dead.. next on the list is arrow, sons and agents of shield!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everybody is 20 and pregnant now and there happy about it? FoolsðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The person in front of me on the bus just read out his name, card number, expiration date and security code on the phone... #BrainsForDays]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dying to see deadpool ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just started arrow... V good!ðŸ‘Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally stressed over this phase 4.. FFS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What tick cunt opens the window on the bus, close to freezing over down here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No wonder people hate the bus when you're forced to sit beside somebody that smells like they didn't shower in weeks, it's vile!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always wear your hood up on a bus, nobody wants to sit beside somebody with a hood up #busLogic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nate dogg and Warren G had to regulate ðŸŽ¶ðŸŽ¶]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FM104 I'd be happy with even the cuddle mug #unluckyMe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gracedunne72 it's a movie you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bit of Thor on this boring night! ðŸ”¨ðŸ”¨âš¡âš¡]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was there a sale on for Amsterdam for this month cause every cunt and their ma is getting a pictures with the dick ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really need to be back in ibiza right now #ShowMeToAHigherPlace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First day in DIT Kevin St &amp; I already contemplated on bating the life out of granny for walking that slow in front of me! Hate fucking town!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never drinking that much again! #BlackoutsToBeatTheBand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After plenty of pints and jamesons, I don't even have a hangover #SuccessfulPubCrawl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothin annoys me more than an instagram slut!Yous relax putting up pics of people grindin eachother!Wouldnt even climb up on ye in a floodðŸ˜ ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just want to be back in bedðŸ˜´ðŸ˜´]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gonna be some handy weekendðŸ‘Œ #onlyFourMoreDays]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder if aliexpress sell money trees cause I'm a broke motherfucka!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some craving for a spice bag!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hate doing over time but fuck me, it's definitely worth it when it's payday!  ðŸ’°ðŸ’°ðŸ’°]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[20 hour shift done ðŸ˜¦ðŸ”« #deadt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FM104 Charlie sheen was in ferris buellers day offðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobody knows it but you've got a secret smile and you use it only for me #oldiebutgoodie  ðŸŽ¶ðŸŽ¶]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may not be happy with my body,  but I am happy with the food I eat. And that's all that matters in this worldðŸ˜€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really need to get into some sort of shape,  I'm one lazy fuckðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd love a Starbucks hot chocolate now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So drunk last night, I lost me phone and tried to ring it off me wallet.
Dean 0-1 vodka]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wanna be a.... baller
Shot callerðŸŽ¶]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take  over all them refugees and get them to build another 5 lanes on the #m50 sick of all this poxy #traffic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not actually sitting here planning on booking ibiza for next monthðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These hoes ain't loyalðŸŽ¶]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh she is the freak of the week!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm the kind of guy who laughs at a funeral.. can't understand what I mean? You soon willðŸ‘ #OneWeek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[300 seconds snap chat story? I remember my first gargle..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friday by the cure is such a tune.. even though  being in love is off the cardsðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FM104 any tickets left for route 94? Please!! #ibizablues here!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another night in the blacker where I'm left in the toilet getting sick... #standard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Show me to a higher place,  take me to  outer space!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its the weekend and got paid... How can it get any better!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you be my bodyguard, I can be your long lost paaal!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To all the ladies in the place with style and graceðŸŽ¶]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus I'm as rough as a dog today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going to fucking snap, somebody just get me out of work right now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing wrecks me head more than when people start talking about football in front of me, just fuck off! Haven't a clue what your on about!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Out every weekend and nothing saved for Ibiza.. Fuck it, roll on next weekend!ðŸºðŸºðŸº]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ain't no mountain high, ain't not valley low, ain't no river wide enough baby!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nadinebradyxx just go out ye bottler!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Craving some cinema nachos and cheese!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do I have to be so skinny! Its the worst thing ever! No matter what I eat I just stay like a fucking twig!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice long day of working in Belfast!ðŸ˜Ÿ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know what to tweet..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just wish I could turn this stupid brain off! It's just not good for me!!ðŸ˜ ðŸ˜ ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shellymaughan cutie! #oneYear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On call tomorrow and I already have a fuckjng job to do.. Great!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shellymaughan I'll burst yiu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shellymaughan I'm really iron man..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishNates be up to you knowðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its a #freeForAll on the m50 today.. Nobody letting anybody in front of themðŸ˜¬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electrical exam next week and then back on site... Those 6 months do flew in!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[only watching #community now... @ChevyChaseToGo is gone now @donaldglover ... What has life come to! #ThisIsMeNow http://t.co/B1ZB0rTDVz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sleeping after fas is a bad idea, definitely won't sleep tonight! #apprentice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The songs from the 70s 80s and 90s are much better then music out now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The effort of making lunch at night:(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus there are some ugly fucking runners out there!ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proper hate working Monday to Friday, should be a break somewhere in the middle!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One more day of this poxy training!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shellymaughan Yeah it looks alright:)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really need to learn to calm down, feel like fucking my head through a wall!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First time starting in the gym at 6:30am today, tough but worth itðŸ‘ðŸ‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shellymaughan gonna get you this;) http://t.co/izEO2Y2Njh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shellymaughan your just with me for the prezzies;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't believe me sparks exams are on Wednesday!! Goodbye job...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shellymaughan Still burst ye!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full weeks wages gone and only one presentðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@LadHumour: When your parents go to sleep at your 13th birthday party... https://t.co/Qc0PWdq1s1" @Sprouts143 hahaha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Fran should of listened to mother nature.. #lovehate  #love #hate #finale #shower #rte http://t.co/LDe104vB8I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't wait to stsrt  Fas Tomorrow ... Gonna be dead handy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hate them weekend when ye don't even get the chance to sit down!ðŸ˜¡]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>