<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@XabiRabbit yea true, hope not!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomasORuanaidh heard it at the time, great stuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomasORuanaidh Yep it needs to be made part of Irish culture]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ahboythekid yea bang on, Schmidt mentioned the lions too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@XabiRabbit of course he wouldn't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asked Schmidt last week about option of sabbatical for Sexton if injuries continue (with rwc'19 in mind). Said just focusing on this season.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All change in 24 hours. Watch Simon Easterby on the injury blows to Ireland and no Ian Madigan on The 5.30.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter O'Mahony ruled out of Scotland game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Johnny Sexton ruled out of this weekend's game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warren Gatland at Ireland training this morning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Johnny Sexton "is on track to train tomorrow". Rob Kearney said Paddy Jackson has "been running the plays" all last week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greatest of all time but also most Gracious of all time #federer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KieranFinn13 truly epic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is something else #nadalvsfederer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BernardOToole @ImGerTreacy Hope he wasn't cracking onto you Ger!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PadraigMcKeon what photo?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fahy_caroline definitely not Caroline! Fun times alright!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkDow97133063 no idea to be honest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidMatthews2 absolutely, this should have happened decades ago]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteedFiona @IrishRugby oh dear, at least when there were loads of people there for athletics events there was some body heat at least!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AilisMc ha yea. It was a place where running was the only way to actually keep warm. Good times!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New indoor track. Fond memories of competing in indoor track in Nenagh but used to be colder inside than outside https://t.co/58fPJdmUvt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RuthGorman_UTV @RealCFrampton Have a great week Ruth 🥊]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joe Schmidt &amp; Eddie Jones on The 5.30 this evening.

Cheers to @ConanDoyle12 for shooting a load of interviews. https://t.co/A6wecaa8BB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 6N head coaches. Jones with bandage above his eye after an accident. He told me it looks worse than it is. https://t.co/TJJV9aAG7o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the 6 Nations carousel in London https://t.co/Vfn9Ju7K3b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the Hurlingham Club in London this morning for launch of 6 Nations https://t.co/7qSzOOj5MJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caught up with Joy Neville in Limerick, a ref who's breaking new ground. On The 5.30. https://t.co/uZx0Ftk6Zz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is excruciatingly close for Connacht and making history #TOUvCON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DiarmuidOHallor @Independent_ie thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well said, O'Gara. Look forward to the day when* he returns to coach Munster someday.
*yes, when]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clear the decks for the first weekend in April. Over to Connacht to make it three provinces in last 8.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great work rate, solid defensively and under high ball, Conway looks like Joe Schmidt's kind of winger. Should be named in Ireland 6N squad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mallorie_Ronan thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lemonsrbitter thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@niamhieobrien Thanks Niamh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonoghueODavid thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stackeroo thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wrote about Peter O'Mahony and how he shouldered Munster through transition and tragedy https://t.co/fshbzei4hx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My dad texted me this pic from the black valley today.. kerry, in the winter https://t.co/06yi7C8D8I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leecaluan Who's complaining? It's a fact. Murray himself said today he has to learn to deal with it. No moaning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@niamhieobrien not sure if sport is on 3player. Try record or tv3+1!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also spoke to Murray about being targeted. More on The 5.30.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rassie Erasmus says munster would never jeopardise the welfare of a player re Conor Murray incident.  More on The 5.30.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conor Murray said he "didn't lose consciousness" in Glasgow. Said he came through all tests &amp; doesn't think munster will have case to answer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keith Earls rated "50-50" for Munster's game v Racing. O'Mahony, O'Donnell &amp; Zebo all trained today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caught up with Joe Sheridan to talk about his new goalkeeper role with Meath. On The 5.30. https://t.co/NNuAYXHtpt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missed those edge-of-seat end-games from Munster. Get a home quarter and anything can happen...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conway has been superb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's sharper than a knife-edge? #GLAvMUN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnfitzp1967  will be biggest test of season so far]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cumoski Point proved again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tmoroney4697 now you're talking!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnfitzp1967 Draw not made yet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go on 2017, give us a Leinster v Munster European semi-final. 
It's been too long.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantasy rugby from Leinster tonight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New players Crosbie, Farrell &amp; McCabe among those training with Connacht today https://t.co/sXXz2YYAXZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crosbie is Cup-tied so can't play in champions cup games. Connacht say Craig Ronaldson could be fit for this weekend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good news re Ultan Dillane - he doesn't require surgery on ankle. Expected back in 3-4 weeks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Connacht confirm that outhalf Steve Crosbie &amp; centre Tom Farrell have joined province for rest of season. Prop Peter McCabe joins on loan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeneNaoupu Thank you for your time!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loved this celebration from the Munster captain. https://t.co/VdbAoSx6QR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wrote about Sene Naoupu and how her second coming in rugby has been Ireland's gain  https://t.co/AKMSSsHbeC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interview with 17 yo pro tennis player Simon Carr, son of Tommy, coming up on The 5.30 https://t.co/vLS9LHahpv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Johnny Sexton back for Leinster - he will captain the team v Zebre tomorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mick O'Connell takes no shit. Brilliant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We talk about Axel every day of the week" - watch Peter O'Mahony on Munster's return journey to Paris on The 5.30]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Munster prepare for the trip back to Paris this weekend https://t.co/8lVMA5phSl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Darren Sweetnam sidelined for six weeks. No definitive news on Tommy O'Donnell injury.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jaco Taute's loan deal until end of season confirmed by Munster]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spinxy82 so the public should rule? Of course not. Disciplinary panels need to make players more accountable for their acts on the pitch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What an incredibly solid &amp; conscientious head coach Rassie Erasmus is. Has guided Munster through the toughest months imaginable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marlamamo @Independent_ie thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cumoski @dk3lly with bovril]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@liamster91 Yea, it's disappointing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No heart, no passion - @StephenFerris6 sums it up at ht]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice move from Leinster. Seems Ulster need a shot of Andy Farrell's defensive ferocity and passion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tmoroney4697 @BHHooker @Independent_ie Take your point. But when it was said with such definitiveness re MF incident I just don't buy it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ocean_handrail thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TTerryoha Cheers, yep good point re expediency]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Riordan_Matt thank you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeorgeSavage2 Thanks George. Agree. Happy new year to ye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KieranMHughes but Steve Hansen says they're not a dirty team!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eoinmc07 Ha for sure, thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BHHooker thanks for sharing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConMurphySport Cheers Con]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forget resolutions, rugby needs real reform in the new year https://t.co/639xgy5pYK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hoogenband0110 in record]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PMul73 not today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jjyoss83 no that's way over to the left]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slea Head https://t.co/MhUdK4PWXq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Soft day for the Banna Christmas swim https://t.co/mBEgERuXUX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Found one of the first sports books i ever read https://t.co/4GpoR2q2DM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's all about the size of the shoe @billykeane15 @RealBrentPope https://t.co/5z6pcoPyJh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was like being at the best wedding table #indosportsawards https://t.co/vBHmbWFlPZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not bad company before Irish Independent Sports Star Awards https://t.co/SD3DWiZCtH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FairGameCast Cheers ladies! Great catching up with ye on Friday x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ManelWatchIre @Shane_RossTD Thanks, will do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrogsNavan A few valid points, yes, but a lot more derogatory ones in an overall patronising piece]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thecailinrua thank you]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>