<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@rhysam @politico I'm not sure that this is constitutional. Not that that counts for anything now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every LGBTIQ person has had to fight for who they are. We aren't going to lose to the insecure orange Nazi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's scary that young people in Australia still culturally know who the KKK are. https://t.co/3By1OxL0Vs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rob_Stott Some don't grow out of it. Some obvious examples across the parliament.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a rule, I prefer to buy from smaller stores. The money circulates better and creates more activity and jobs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uh oh, thinking about the #futureofwork again. One way ticket to severe anxiety for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Westfield going to do when Kmart and Target merge, Big W winds up, JB buys Good Guys, and Myer or DJs give up?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mpesce The last thing we need is more concentration in retail. The big shops deserve to die, but Amazon sucks as a replacement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't achieve extraordinary things as part of your normal routine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@liamvhogan And management. Most of my problems start and end with them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't the minister defer to actual professionals about which teaching methods are best? https://t.co/D7u9kLtnRB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump should read the Constitution sometime. He might learn something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bannon's trying to ignite a live civil war in order to create a fascist empire. https://t.co/Iwbw8HGbKY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The government refusing to comply with court orders is an insult to the Constitution and the rule of law. Profoundly dangerous territory.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be silent is to be complicit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrMStuchbery I hope the staff release their detainees peacefully. "Just following orders" doesn't cut it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wendy_harmer @smh How many classrooms could be air conditioned if Westconnex wasn't being built?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Racism, corruption, and fascism aren't how you make America great again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What good have merchant bankers ever done for humanity?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marick I guess precision makes things both better and worse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marick They're excellent once you get them set up. Keeping the rotor straight is the trick, and you need special tools for that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Tupolev Tu-204 is the obvious choice. https://t.co/EvklPHcEl8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SenJohnMcCain For a little more fun, they should throw Rafale and Gripen in as international benchmarks. Not for the US to buy, obviously.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sounds like my current employer... https://t.co/LGNwmJ2HBf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marick I have the same problem with modern disc brakes. Very hard to get right due to the microscopic tolerances.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rhysam An insecure fascist? The guy clearly has no self esteem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the media are the opposition, how fucking useless/complicit does that make the Democrats? https://t.co/R5U4iZBQTB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saying that @realDonaldTrump's 20% import duty on Mexican products will be paid only by Americans shows a gross ignorance of basic economics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marick Which bits are you having trouble with?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BernardKeane There's a difference between environmentalist social democracy and communism, and Lee Rhiannon has always been the latter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1) Is Trump's 20% Mexico tax constitutional? 2) Does that matter any more? 3) Will any major business actually be forced to pay it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's still going to be more transparent than Australia. https://t.co/uEnYANv5rA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phbarratt @gjfitzgerald @MariamVeiszadeh Conservatives will delay it to oblivion, as they have with the republic, marriage, etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worked for me too. @Twitter gets shut down in 3, 2,... NO CARRIER https://t.co/TalxodIunY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phbarratt I seem to recall that some countries did little more than that. My understanding is that USA required an entry visa for transfers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought Trump was merely going to try and rebuild America's rust belt through protectionism. I never expected this level of fascism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Ministry of Truth is open for business. https://t.co/oLuqVQjx9t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phbarratt Fortunately there are now some direct Australia Canada flights.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phbarratt America doesn't accept the idea of people being "in transit", so they'd be subject to the same rules.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SwiftOnSecurity You can sell killer products if you can shift the blame to the victims. Drink driving, speeding, inattention, etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look, I love @JuliaGillard. She was a superb PM and lawyer, and her work with GPE deserves much credit. But Austral… https://t.co/KLoaeyYwnv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wemcharl @JaneCaro It wouldn't have mattered. The American system is gerrymandered to oblivion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chris Bowen must go. https://t.co/Fv3GJGmsXR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow @Interior to see stunning photos of America's incredible natural beauty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobskiNew @TheKouk I live in a one bedroom unit, on above median income. It's still a very marginal proposition.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This doesn't happen in democratic countries. https://t.co/4G5bNdkTfA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesmassola @GladysB @RNBreakfast How many investment properties does she own?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just keep inflating the bubble. What could go wrong when it explodes? https://t.co/VPXyGurafE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natecochrane @cnntech Yup. And it's going to break after about 5 minutes on any rough path...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't get a home loan with a gig income. https://t.co/eQW0ydrm6I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Amazing_Maps Misleading for Australia. Many workers are not entitled to any paid leave at all, not even Christmas etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CC Australian Public Service Commission... https://t.co/TQyYBNjzqw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I dread to think what happens when you're returning home and the recognition system fucks up. Because it will, repe… https://t.co/k0L8ZQyPO9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coyle_robyn @abcnews Saving money probably isn't the point. The government hates employing people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lance Armstrong didn't cheat. PERIOD. #SpicerFacts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NASAWatch "SLS is an efficient program. Period."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adambspencer The denial of reality really evokes the North Korean regime.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump has a Kim Jong-il level of separation from reality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump clearly lacks eyes. Nobody could have that poor sense of taste. https://t.co/oghB9pS7rc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hmm, I unfollowed @POTUS before the #Inauguration, but had to re-unfollow afterwards. Curious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cheryl_kernot @ReclaimAnglesea It's coming, but the system would have to be roughly as complex as current welfare system to be equitable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulg Only if he respects the term limit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GaryGolledge @phileevo We'll fit them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GaryGolledge @phileevo Can I suggest that we send them to the old West Belconnen tip where the Mr Fluffy asbestos is going?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrRimmer Leia over Jyn, but it's a hard decision to make.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GeorgeNegus We've seen this before, but last time the fascists were on the other side.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@liamvhogan As a software engineering student, I came to realise that the soft subjects were far harder and more complex than the hard ones.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeCarlton01 "The system is working exactly as intended."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@roseannebyrne @DrRachie @DianneCostin Mental illness can sometimes explain behaviour like this. But it doesn't excuse it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like @iinet NBN has a big outage. Nothing on their status page. What's going on?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomCBallard Says a lot about tennis's core fan base: overprivileged snobs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmacmullin @abccanberra What about peaks and troughs in demand? More efficient to park them when nobody wants to use them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's the best way to stop fascism in a post-democratic world? https://t.co/0vv5W0QxWK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fakeedbutler Adjusted for number of MPs would be more interesting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People who decried all her opponents as sexist are the reason Hillary was never forced to address her flaws as a ca… https://t.co/SMjNOLsEE2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superb journalism. Should be considered for a Walkley. https://t.co/gDEvbFv3TB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelkoziol Or that our sensors aren't fine enough to find small pieces in a big and deep ocean. Or that they move while we're searching.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't "budget repair" if it's a one-off gain. #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fakeedbutler Increasingly, it's how anyone gets work. Demand for labour is low and supply is nearly infinite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MelbUrbanist @NewYorker Rings extremely true for Australia too. Sydney CBD light rail, and every new rail station.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the Australian economy has just collapsed... https://t.co/qJmz4YUT14]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm glad I have no financial data to match. Never been on a payment, no investments, just PAYE wages. One redundancy away from destitution.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnieOdyne I'm watching a lot less news. It makes it easier.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reddishraven Yup. Thinking a lot about getting out of IT and retraining in something lower wage, but more hands-on and less automatable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #futureofwork keeps me awake at night, and is triggering some suicidality. It's not fun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@afterprohibends @AlexWodak Not many. A couple of government MPs or their kids would do it. But they wouldn't change policy for anyone else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mpesce @GhostWhoVotes ALP need to do something about that primary vote.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikeCarlton01 @serviceNSW Conway's Law. The system matches the structure of the organisation that created it. Reflects badly on the creator]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every single story on Nine's Today Show is an ad. How the hell is this legal?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There would be very few public servants who haven't written an email up the chain warning against a bad course of action. Usually ignored v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every single government fuckup has a trail of emails warning against it from people at lower levels of the organisa… https://t.co/xC6jzSKvVe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phbarratt I'd tip the yanks. Many more force multipliers like carriers, ELINT jets, tankers, and pilot exercises like Red Flag.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mpesce @RevRichardColes You're probably right. It is amusingly close to the price of Sussan Ley's impulse apartment though...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mpesce @RevRichardColes A small house in Sydney.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bruce_haigh @SkiPoss And it's only six months since the election. The rest of the term is going to feel very long indeed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a place in hell for people who tighten bolts on bikes as tight as they can. You're doing it wrong in ways that might not be fixable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not sufficient to refuse to perform a task for legal or ethical reasons. You have to prevent anyone else doing it in your place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natecochrane It's surprisingly good for keeping in touch with friends you went to school with. No more, no less.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SwannyQLD @australian Bumping the GST would probably trigger a recession at this point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The best way to be sure that 2017 is not 1934 is to act as though it were." https://t.co/49WKyfdWAQ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>