<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Print the Legend.  https://t.co/cXTy5KtIyF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Covlin Also bad karma: that's the night Muldoon got pissed, called a snap election.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@liamdann @avancenz @CTrevettNZH @toby_etc @LachlanForsyth See also 'Ming the Merciless']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattNippert Like Nixon having tapes, only much more bigly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MoataTamaira shady owner?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With Bannon as a Malevolent Baldrick? Let's hope so. https://t.co/stAoGz0CxB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JosephRomanos With Bannon as a kind of Malevolent Baldrick? Could be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toby_etc @avancenz O that's good. I've used Orange Peron, and a Bloviating Monarch Butterfly of Chaos.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kumararepublic @ZippyGonzales @StephenStra Post is a dying business. Billions' gone into rail since '08 - not sure its seen a return.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@avancenz @toby_etc Is that some sort of confectionary?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toby_etc @avancenz 'Totalitarian Twistie'  also has a certain ring.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reckonsemoji It's dropped through a time wormhole from Election 2020.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@avancenz Ah. I thought it was a memory lapse. [I call him President Lucozade, but it hasn't really caught on]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@publicaddress @JulieAnneGenter @jacindaardern @scoutriver You might have a third door knocker soon. I'd hide any cats you have, though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StephenStra @ZippyGonzales Yep, and those who bought it can better grow the business in new markets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZippyGonzales Short of nationalisation, you can't. And we don't live in that sort of world any more, which is, on balance, a good thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fastercamels  John Key's at a bit of a loose end. He'd be good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS @_hehir_ Field promotion/wartime commission. You'll be busted back to the ranks at the end of hostilities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Xas_ 'the louder you scream...'  I have a copy, from a compilation CD of some years ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MorganGodfery Yes I did click! And recognised it straight away. I still have a copy from Public Law &amp; my train wreck of a law school career]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beckeleven @secondzeit 'Some peoplke call me Donald [wah wahhhh] 'Cos I speak of the bigliness of Trump...']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MorganGodfery Hmm...do I click on llink? This sounds similar in theme to something I'm writing....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarristerNZ I remember him on the telly, debating abortion with a visiting Jerry Falwell. late '70s or early '80s.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Unimatrix_0 Better things to do, apparently. Can't say I blame him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzdodo @publicaddress @LewSOS @Dovil Ah, well you're not trying to grab the wrong end of the rubber mallet, and that is appreciated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This guy kinda knows what he's talking about. https://t.co/I4br4elt3g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PouTepou @huihoppa The electorate or the party?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteveBraunias Bloody well right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CJ_NZ @liamdann  Oh, I know. I'm a bit aware of their business, as well as being a sensibly enthusiastic consumer of their lager.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CJ_NZ @liamdann  OK, that *is* good. Love me a good Tuatara Helles, and its not available in enough pubs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@azizonomics Gifs are kind of a semaphore thing. https://t.co/8js8Xw3YZh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This kinda works. https://t.co/9AxpFwohb7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CTrevettNZH @Mihi_Forbes @emmawehipeihana @jcpihama shouting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@annetterongotai @TheNBR  I'm *always* positive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatthewHootonNZ @audreyNZH Loved that, too. I dips me lid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emmawehipeihana Prolly closest to Gareth, though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me too. We could be running out. https://t.co/SPBfIM8JZI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DawgBelly twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@edmuzik @BeeFaerie I shall write an endorsement of @GregPresland  in @TheNBR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maggietait @BenThomasNZ that would be more in keeping with the city's vibe than the Sevens (or the car race which Sevens kinda replaced)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewisHoldenNZ congratulations!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some lawyer, psychologist or probation officer wanted to show their other degree in English wasn't a total waste of… https://t.co/hAaIIYRx2v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@southernscoop @NZcourttweets Bob Jones did this, praising fine weather, when govt changed in 1975. It's an old gag.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/F9yYEQEmLI 'Labour and the Greens declared themselves in favour of nice things, and firmly against not-nice things. [paid]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@felixmarwick @CTrevettNZH @isaac_davison @jmodoh  You've changed, man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gtiso @ShakingStick @BenThomasNZ I have *never* belittled the gravity of Trump's order. Never would, either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenThomasNZ @LewSOS Ah, but they're the real right, according to @ShakingStick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gtiso @ShakingStick @BenThomasNZ 2/2..response like NZ had agreed to Trump annexing the Sudentenland or something? I'll stand by that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gtiso @ShakingStick @BenThomasNZ as a description of folk demanding an instant tweet from the PM and treating waiting for a considered..1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gtiso @ShakingStick @BenThomasNZ I'd settle for people reading what I wrote, not what they wish I'd written.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShakingStick @BenThomasNZ ... and, mostly, I only know what's on 'em when you post about 'em here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShakingStick @BenThomasNZ Riiight. So you want me to monitor KiwiBlog &amp; WO &amp; say where I think they're wrong. Awesome use of my time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShakingStick @BenThomasNZ @LewSOS Well, you've been getting a woodie for a Kiwi Trump for at least 6 months. Don't think it'll happen tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShakingStick @BenThomasNZ 'Cos its served the left so well, you mean?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS @AndreAlessi @ShakingStick I said he was right to make a measured not a rushed response, &amp; took a swing at the spasming on Twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShakingStick @BenThomasNZ @LewSOS @AndreAlessi Why bother? Only readers are a few drooling meatheads &amp; Lefties wanting to feel virtuous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS @AndreAlessi @ShakingStick ..2/2.. there's been some extraordinary bad faith misinterpretation gone on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS @AndreAlessi @ShakingStick  No, just here, for now anyway. But I haven't 'praised' anyone, not have I said they should say nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS @AndreAlessi @ShakingStick I didn't do that, if you actually have a look.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS @AndreAlessi @ShakingStick different to what?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndreAlessi @ShakingStick After all the talk about values yesterday, I'm sure Labour &amp; the Greens will be rushing to condemn this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pptsapper And a genius. And wisdom &amp; genius seldom reside in the same cranium.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattNippert @realDonaldTrump  I figured Clint Eastwood.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labour &amp; Green parties declared themselves in favour of nice things, &amp; firmly against not-nice things. https://t.co/VaEM5AKHm9 [paid]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[..with full link this time https://t.co/VaEM5AKHm9 [paid]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@moar_moar Dang. Clipped character off end. https://t.co/VaEM5AKHm9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/S44SN7tUuC 'The Labour and the Green parties declared themselves in favour of nice things, and firmly against not-nice things.']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the immortal words of Daffy Duck, 'I demand that you shoot me now'  https://t.co/T9r9ostP5g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChrisKeall Yep. It's what sank Nixon and McCarthy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_nber @LewSOS @EricCrampton Yes. You think that's a good thing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh dear. This is kind of Dan Quayle routed via David Irving. https://t.co/VqVSUisYtt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS @EricCrampton No, just thinking our govt should have a measured response rather than policymaking via emotional spasm on Twitter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricCrampton @LewSOS So would I. But yesterday's outrage was more about domestic partisan point scoring than anything else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@publicaddress @nzdodo @LewSOS @Dovil  Yes, so would I.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS o @Dovil @publicaddress I'm not, at the moment, saying he should debate anything. Only not do a kneejerk reaction.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS @Dovil @publicaddress Who's doing that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hebehu Yeah. Ah well. Some folk had some enjoyable thoughtless outrage, so its not a total loss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a bull, actually. https://t.co/f2ROUmKM0Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeeFaerie The Greens pulled their woman MP off. The Nats made their's a minister.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dovil @publicaddress call me old fashioned, but I'd rather a head of govt doesn't make policy positions via knee jerk on the twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@publicaddress @hebehu  PMs have to worry about more than branding.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hebehu nah, it's sensible.  Also, the tantrum throwers seem to assume Twitter is the world.  Which...nah.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Umm.  Yeah.  That's one way of putting it, I suppose. https://t.co/3RH9ynHsNH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I  rekkin Thatcher would have biffed him one if he'd tried that with her. https://t.co/mQTrmEjs5Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZippyGonzales Muldoon liked it, from memory.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fibbyccino @TheNBR what's this 'even' thing all about?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS oh I'm not a fan either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reckonsemoji @Zagzigger2 @LewSOS she has. And she's stuck me for some years as an unusually mature politician in the US.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS yeah. Warts n all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Zagzigger2 @LewSOS according to the radio, Hillary said something on the Twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewSOS He may be right, but 'no one goes so far as he who knows where he is going' (from Cromwell, who knew of what he spoke)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulbrislen Yeah. Orwell on language and politics, though...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have been thinking a lot of 'Amusing Ourselves to Death' the last year. https://t.co/bQ1aIH2VUJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HadleyDonaldson Go into coalition with Winston? Yeah, well....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FrancesCook Up at the west wind farm?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_hehir_ @Tim_Watkin should be more twitter exchanges like this (not getting ready for kirk, but reading this https://t.co/6IgobfryxT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OliverKamm @johnpagani @BeeFaerie Some things *feel* wrong. #altgrammar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@buzzandhum @beckeleven @Ghetsuhm Suits the colour scheme too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tim_Watkin @BenThomasNZ @GraemeEdgeler @philiplyth   Hmm... don't know at the moment, but will cue y'all in when it happens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeepingMum Fake. There's a couple of others I'm not so sure about, though...]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>