<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@sawngswjakec @adam_lewis But I dealt with it and then came to like it. Now pulp-free OJ does leave an odd taste in the mouth for me too...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adam_lewis @sawngswjakec I once only liked pulp-free OJ. One day I bought pulpy OJ accidentally. I was weirded out by the pulp texture.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barrysaunders @adam_lewis Don't know them! What were they like?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davecarter That's right - they have Barnesy/INXS doing 'Good Times' and The Wrights doing 'Evie', not the originals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davecarter The UK/US rock canon is mostly 65-75 but it's more 76-86 in the Oz rock canon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davecarter Which is interesting cos The Easybeats and Thorpey at Sunbury are held up as epochal by a doco like Long Way To The Top.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davecarter Boys In Town is their highest at #127...it's very very blokey.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davecarter But also no Billy Thorpe or Easybeats in the entire list - very little 60s/early 70s stuff in that list (not enough sheen?)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davecarter Of the top 100, the only post-1990 Aussie stuff is Baby Animals, Screaming Jets, Spiderbait's Black Betty, and Gotye/Kimbra.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davecarter I reckon this 2014 MMM countdown is instructive as to the Oz Rock canon: https://t.co/expftdIyQ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@barrysaunders @adam_lewis There's also heaps not on Spotify etc for licensing reasons or cos the record company has forgotten it exists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davecarter @staffo_sez And the production style of Mark Opitz, looking at his credits here: https://t.co/gGN9wgV5iW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adam_lewis Mostly I was imagining a world where there's an established route for e.g. a Vic Simms or Screamfeeder reissue to get attention.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davecarter @staffo_sez And it's basically mainstream music, or aiming to be, that could get into the charts (so add Powderfinger, Jet, etc)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davecarter @staffo_sez Standard rock instruments, pop song structure, distinctive singer, ethos of masculine perhaps-larrikin mateship...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@awardtour What's the story there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_jbradley @staffo_sez The juxtaposition between who's on the rock Long Way To The Top doco and who's on the pop Love Is In The Air doco?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@staffo_sez I mean, the stereotype of Oz Rock in my head is ACDC, Angels, Chisel, Hunnas, Hoodoo Gurus, Mentals, Paul Kelly, etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_jbradley @heckelfonic Side question: Who/what created the Oz rock canon? Is there anything more to it than 'what Triple M plays'?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_jbradley @heckelfonic ...but I totally agree that their focus on dad-rock is almost comical these days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_jbradley @heckelfonic Oh, those mags very much push the 'this stuff you heard on the radio growing up is actually quite deep!' thing...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adam_lewis But I do think Australia is missing a local Uncut/Mojo/Rolling Stone equivalent to push such claims to new generations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adam_lewis Honestly, I think critical consensus is that Don Walker, Paul Kelly, etc are geniuses, but maybe the public isn't there yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gisellenguyen Yep: if yr body is adjusting to missing some mood-altering chemicals it got used to, odd moods are an obvious side effect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matt_levinson Also makes me wonder when Turnbull &amp; co will follow suit with similar blanket policies to appease the hard right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matt_levinson Well, no. It does put a lie to the fig leaf of them doing it because they really care about stopping deaths at sea though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@loadie All the way with DJT...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty obvious that the price for the Oz government's support of this was Trump reaffirming America would take the… https://t.co/k1riOIdMQB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wasps are kind of evil, and evil wasps that eat other evil wasps from the inside are particularly so: https://t.co/YXFKxh3CJd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Modern rock is a niche now, where bands like Japandroids don't expect anything more than playing at middling venues: https://t.co/ksVl52lMdS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I felt more attuned to JJJ listener choices this year than the last few, but do largely agree with @BernardZuel : https://t.co/06CMLZfxgo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SBS's First Australians doco, on what happened on this day (and the aftermath) 229 years ago: https://t.co/g7Rt7IEi6l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Flume's trademark drop became a cliche worldwide: https://t.co/3YPkpw4HCh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sawngswjakec I liked this article explaining why they are so: https://t.co/8JCdB7N1K0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That very last computer-game sample thingy on Neil Cicierega's Shit ....what IS that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@penelly @goldfishlaugh Like they've been pushing the bounds of civility and dominating meme culture. The meme encapsulates all that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@penelly @goldfishlaugh imo the glee at the punch meme is cos it's such a perfect case of alt-right tools being used against them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicilind That would have been awesome!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicilind I love the way that language holds the calcified remains of history.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicilind Thus Yuletide!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great interview with Prince's 80s recording engineer Susan Rogers who went on to become a music psychologist! https://t.co/FEoYBc3F1s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adam_lewis So I think calls of 'overrated' function like satire - works better when you're punching up &amp; when your knowledge is first-hand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adam_lewis ..and lots of 34 year olds with fond memories of being 18 when Since I Left You came out who are now music reviewers *cough*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adam_lewis And ofc it's easier for a record to have cultural capital when there's a major label (and a huge tech company) pushing it...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adam_lewis In contrast, I think @heckelfonic was right to push back against Wildflower - she very clearly *got* what the record was about.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adam_lewis So yr serious music bros saying, e.g., 'Lemonade is overrated' are usually really saying 'stuff not aimed at me is overrated'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adam_lewis IMO 'overrated' is an argument about what music we should pay attention to, &amp; is often (but not always) about cultural capital.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gisellenguyen So I wouldn't be surprised if they've spent their career trying to look like the Tenenbaums...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gisellenguyen Angus Stone told me he called his home studios Belafonte Studios after the boat in The Life Aquatic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sawngswjakec And to calling every pop star who's maybe altered a lyric here or there a singer-songwriter. Very poptimist of them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@staffo_sez It was meant to be! Clearly in the morning I am not capable of better descriptors than 'very nice'...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Laura Marling track is inevitably very nice: https://t.co/bJNdxo2i6F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_jbradley I find all this stuff really fascinating - the history of words can be very informative about how people lived!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_jbradley But I reckon that there wasn't much impetus to define them until domestication - before that they'd have just been 'wild fowl'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_jbradley There have definitely been wild ducks swimming around in ponds since forever, and humans trying to eat them...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_jbradley I figure in medieval Spain, the person asking you to serve duck for dinner is more likely to call it 'patt' rather than 'ente'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_jbradley This suggests ducks were widely domesticated in Europe only from the later middle ages: https://t.co/2o1R9sIQWZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_jbradley I wonder if Muslim Spain had a similar thing to the English thing with cow being Old English and beef being Norman French?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_jbradley The English are very literal - famously everyone else in Europe calls pineapples something like 'ananas'!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonnoseidler I feel like the Quietuses of the world definitely aim at 30somethings keen to confirm their musical good taste as teens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonnoseidler Yeah, you linked to it! The academic in me was just curious where that fact might have come from.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_jbradley Whereas 'duck' replaced a word like 'ente' because the English called them, basically, birds that duck in the water?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_jbradley Looks like the German/Italian words come from Latin, and the Spanish/Portuguese word comes from Arabic?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonnoseidler &amp; this Liz Fraser/Jeff Buckleycollaboration that's floating around on the web is fab: https://t.co/RCyf24TM0i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonnoseidler She dicusses it in this Guardian interview: https://t.co/LVcMfxezky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1st year psychology textbooks often treat topics in biased ways and sometimes repeat myths: https://t.co/fzmu5vSN6o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mlle_elle In 2016 terms, they'd be like if the Chainsmokers were as weird as Shia LaBeouf but still got Shania Twain to do a guest vocal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My friend @drvickyw lists lots of interesting music psychology papers from 2016 (and congrats Vicky!): https://t.co/RirJZTr6Hs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent look at the difference between good science and good TED-talk-about-science material. https://t.co/0GhQWMWL0A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In my lifetime, we've opened up to talking about mental illness, and Carrie Fisher was at the forefront of that: https://t.co/z78wWgzsYc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gisellenguyen It's one of his very  best too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@penelly Was a pleasure to talk to your other two favourites! Both were unsurprisingly quite eloquent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wrote about some Aussie Christmas songs for the SMH, and talked to @timminchin and @darrenhanlon: https://t.co/363cbtAUAE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Richaod Cat Power, probably? Like 'Cross Bones Style' circa 1998?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HRobertsonEsq I mean, for Black Sheep, the Brian Wilson pastiche, they got in the actual Van Dyke Parks to columnate those ruins.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HRobertsonEsq The soundtrack is also possibly the best thing about the movie apart from all the other best things. Let's Duet!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HRobertsonEsq The Temptaaaations!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sawngswjakec Is half of this just than individuals are more interesting than the average of individuals?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Katering Show's advice column on how to deal with annoying Christmas things: https://t.co/zvT4EBwrfc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@quiteawful Ha, that millennial whoop thing shat me as well! I remember thinking it was very out of date + mountains/molehills.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I talked to Vice for a bit about pop and music psychology: https://t.co/B6ayltLiQC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An analysis of the 'pop-drop' that's now pretty close to being a cliche in pop: https://t.co/0BKrGqNYLR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting closer to understanding the evolution of whales: https://t.co/dMHAB5Uab9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Sherlock Holmes of birds: https://t.co/qopmX1puE4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@obliviousgeek Haha, yeah, I'm starting to wonder if people are mostly replacing lost copies now...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wrote this last year about the inescapability of Xmas Buble, and apparently it's just sold a million in AU, so:   https://t.co/Ul9sE4Rkll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome to see @RollingStoneAus giving @MarcusTeague a good amount of space to profile A.B. Original: https://t.co/Pse18qscBR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So many good Prince stories in this GQ article (including the truth about the Prince/Eddie Murphy basketball game): https://t.co/RzHy4EsZcb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anwen Crawford eloquently muses on Dylan's Nobel Prize and the difference between poetry and pop lyrics: https://t.co/AYdbg7KuDN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Onion headline: Exhausted Noam Chomsky Just Going To Try And Enjoy The Day For Once https://t.co/ISTkrPmTN2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Impulsiveness and selfishness are, neurally, two sides of the same coin: https://t.co/8vg4KD6zTx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ohmiso Yep, the way that screwing workers/creating a monopoly is a basic business model these days is very troubling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ohmiso And all the stuff in @staffo_sez's explanation of why he quit taxis: https://t.co/IDRs4XqNol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ohmiso It's cheap, gives the impression of being safer cos of driver ratings, and the app means you can see how far away the driver is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber's business model is fairly obviously to drive taxis out of business and then jack up prices: https://t.co/eyZ8EVxaBu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber are not profitable, and their rides are so cheap because they're being subsidised by venture capital: https://t.co/eyZ8EVxaBu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davecarter Yes, it's a very unorganic way to do it, and we humans are by definition organic!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davecarter I have too many thoughts for a tweet or ten - I'll email - but in general he's pushing a point of view amongst many.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andy Beta on the Tropicalia movement in Brazil and the way it disturbed the far right politics of the time: https://t.co/opvAjpn6un]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What that duck-rabbit says about the way our brains work: https://t.co/wKburTYe36]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>