<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Prime Minister Malcolm Turnbull's cowardly stance on Donald Trump shames us all https://t.co/dOlVY1GPg3 via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHen you've lost The Spectator, you're battling. Stung! https://t.co/27M2BhzCJK #notmydebt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah, that's a bit more like it. https://t.co/B7nhsZ2mSk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great moments in Australian history, #679 https://t.co/hJAqVVvJOw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man is hilarious. https://t.co/E12GTyLC2O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's What Happens When A Liberal Donor's Business Got Caught Dumping People's Private Information https://t.co/fTKot2Fjco via @MarkDiStef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But @TomMcIlroy ain't backing down on this one. No-how, no-way. #auspol 
https://t.co/RGWWBEZ9W8 via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@knausc Oh the pleasure was mine. You've spawned your share of imitators these past few weeks, after all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scumbags. Get the law onto them .@ShaneRattenbury https://t.co/UJTyUqn1il]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jaysus .@knausc , sure I couldn't have put that better meself. #notmydebt
https://t.co/JYXgjD1XE2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taking on the hard targets. Gutsy effort from .@theheraldsun https://t.co/slXGikLqDL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robo debt: Centrelink staff step-up the resistance #notmydebt https://t.co/aKeb24cVxm via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter Martin: The TPP was never that good for jobs, never that good for growth https://t.co/FFYNW1FckK via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10,000 emails terminated this morning! Ha!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesrob @adamgartrell @MarkDiStef Gawd. They trotting this one out again? We've all been hard-up for a story, but FFS...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The chilling tale of the Origin Energy whistleblower https://t.co/Mq9UwgliJC via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NotMyDebt The Centrelink debt debacle failure rate is much worse than we all thought https://t.co/1wD51x3Q8H via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automated Centrelink a fast track to Turnbull's demise #notmydebt https://t.co/M3Jjx62WEo via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Public service bosses missing on Centrelink's robo-debt https://t.co/VwljtEn606 via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GhostOfPJK @workmanalice who asked that , Alice?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thought Charlie Sheen was on crack... https://t.co/TOFzC4E1GN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelkoziol I caught Rebecca's latest piece in the Oz. She be post-truth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mohamed Hussain, he's a scrapper, applies to Supreme Court to have ACT election declared invalid https://t.co/hmLWru5phV via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junk food industry shaping health policies at public's expense: study https://t.co/LZFYPiWnni via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, that should go well. https://t.co/35DC3HWssu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jose Mourinho's remarks on Wayne Rooney are utterly classless... he deserves better https://t.co/HE5wsQ7z30]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Centrelink scandal: department declines to say how much debt retrieved by system https://t.co/zXPj7Sid6w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Malcolm Turnbull's year is not cactus ... yet https://t.co/0Rd3JEKemV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice, by @_Biancah Homeless in Melbourne: Where, pray tell lord mayor, do you suggest they go? https://t.co/88DI3QWR9u via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can I have some love for the stock-shot please? #notmydebt 
https://t.co/1iF697JAy0 via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sad thing about Leak these days is he was once such a talent. https://t.co/zoAPZBBy4z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Centrelink cooking the books on violence against public servants, union says #notmydebt https://t.co/8ogUvsRiRj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the Tele. Nice, Joel. https://t.co/1ATlUTcc6j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice, by @adamgartrell What is the point of this government? #auspol
 https://t.co/8LPztlihL9 via @smh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good luck with that, Nick. Nick Xenophon pushes to decriminalise public service leaks after Centrelink scandal https://t.co/CXP5S43kqB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nick Xenophon pushes to decriminalise public service leaks after Centrelink scandal https://t.co/2bpdOqoFAE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The faceless men who are supposedly 'public' servants https://t.co/6hBXgTP80M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Public service high flyers must wait for their money   https://t.co/9g0kVJcDCG via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Mike Baird's departure is bad news for Malcolm Turnbull https://t.co/CvOSXtiPsi via @theage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually Asher, I'm a long-term and very proud contributor to the old S&amp;L. Nation's finest, in my opinion.… https://t.co/IqDlOZqRy4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Journalist criticises Mamamia and Mail over lifting of investigative article into child abuse https://t.co/JHKVDkAniS via @MumbrellaNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's what we tune in for. #Skynews Give Bronny a show of her own, I say. https://t.co/lD4pjY9aKK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@9NewsMelb Wow, so THAT'S why she had to work as an agony aunt. Always wondered. #9News]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now, you can read the full text of the Centrelink whistleblower's allegations. 1/2 #notmydebt https://t.co/el7BX4RcmZ via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was just thinking the same thing the other day, looking at the latest poll. https://t.co/X8F09tzEzk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['I can't see me doing Liberal fundraisers in the foreseeable future,' @billshortenmp reckons. Never say never, Bill. #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn, I thought it couldn't get any worse for #Centrelink #notmydebt
Centrelink caught with pants down https://t.co/3hEqBEFM8c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How long has @GChristensenMP given @RichardDiNatale to comply? #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally. #notmydebt https://t.co/el7BX4RcmZ via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jpwarren We're leaving those in. Adds authenticity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Biancah The longer this month goes on, the more I agree. https://t.co/SN1R3gpalr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@not_my_debt Sorry everybody, we had to remove this content because it was breaking an embargo (our bad). It will… https://t.co/sxuAURObJl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Normal (not funny) service has been resumed. https://t.co/cKjGv4Z1Wy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlanTudgeMP @theage but not on present scale and not without human oversight. #notmydebt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shut it, or else, Centrelink public servants told. #notmydebt 
https://t.co/zsNjkeg7Zr via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robo-debt: Centrelink workers threatened with prosecution as bosses try to stem the leaks https://t.co/zsNjkeg7Zr via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Independent_ie Hmmm, reckon it might be t'other way 'round if she keeps this up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DHS used social media to con public, sacked internal critic after he told the truth. #notmydebt 
https://t.co/HQuU3uy7BJ via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The hunt: how Centrelink tracks tracks down internal critics #notmydebt  https://t.co/HQuU3uy7BJ via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fintan O’Toole: DUP must be punished for its Brexit folly https://t.co/6RwGwN0eg9 via @IrishTimesOpEd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nevermind Tony and Eric, there'll be another re-shuffle along in a couple of months. #asupol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah, the lost art of taking a hint. #auspol https://t.co/GBLaZAqlRY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lyndalcurtis No Tasmanian called Eric Abetz.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Henry_Belot Early vote for this bloke! #auspol
https://t.co/a9ZNxJOXE9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill's bordering on the funny this morning. Promising sign, that. https://t.co/FVoeWw5Xkn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Asher_Wolf @cheryl_kernot @MarkusMannheim , are you aware of this, Markus?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adamjohnsonNYC @fakeedbutler Mate, I think there's still a war in Iraq...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm cool with the idea of robo-public servants, just as long as they're not put on the #notmydebt case.… https://t.co/VJVrIBS4Qw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The price of hate... https://t.co/i83udU9r8m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JorianGardner @canberratimes Still got the eye, JG? when all else fails...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm wanting some love for the stock-shot. Introducing the robo-public servant https://t.co/a9ZNxJOXE9 via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introducing Centrelink's robo-public servant #notmydebt  https://t.co/a9ZNxJOXE9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DHS' new front-line will be virtual assistants https://t.co/Govl4WpNRV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labor suffers High Court setback in bid to claim crucial Senate seat https://t.co/qXugQ1E6Jy via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going after pensioners = political kamikaze for Coalition IMHO #auspol #notmydebt
https://t.co/nRaKFzRvPP via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mpesce You don't go to work the next day, in the recent experience of, um, somebody I know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Centrelink says somebody else is making "misleading claims" about online compliance. #notmydebt
https://t.co/pF1NtyRjeN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@9NewsAUS @9NewsMelb @LaurenGianoli Damn, it's easy to get attention in Australian politics these days. #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pensioners and disabled next in line in Centrelink robo-debt campaign https://t.co/nRaKFzRvPP via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The view from the top. #APS #canberraPerks of office: public service boss's $9000 office makeover https://t.co/CBNByzNJsI via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katie_b_burgess You'll get no sympathy from those who've just endured a Canberra silly season without you. (But welcome back)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's why nobody should get too excited about Ombudsman probing #notmydebt
https://t.co/L9Ox2aenK5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hmmmmm. ACT Chief Minister Andrew Barr a regular at AFL matches on taxpayer-funded trips https://t.co/aZDl70bPYF via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robo-debt: MP says public servants 'managed out' for asking too many questions #notmydebt https://t.co/APDhTIQfPN via @canberratimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@psychofairy I think there's one every year,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Standing up for Australian jobs. My opposite number's focus is just fighting for his own job.' @billshortenmp starts with a zinger #auspol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harassment of women by men at Summernats cannot be excused or ignored https://t.co/w7w2Vqwt3i via @DailyLifeAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gonna write something about #ambersherlock today, see if I can get it past @canberratimes Op-Ed boss. No, really.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@metrotrains so maybe you could help me with what I should 'announce' to my 2-year-old who's still waiting for me at childcare...?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@metrotrains unless it was the 4.33 upfield one, didn't see that scheduled. Would an announcement on delays/cancellations/platform kill you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@metrotrains a 'supposed' upfield train 4.16, Southern Cross, appeared on departures board on 2 diff platforms, then disappeared 1/2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey .@metrotrains , you're a joke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Raf_Epstein As a first offender and if she paid the money back, with a decent lawyer...no. #auspol #notmydebt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@australian fark, you lot were slow off the mark on that one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're fake news, all of yiz.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rwh3 @finbaromallon @canberratimes We won't be able to say (legally) until the cases hit the Federal Court.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing will ever be the same again, not after this. https://t.co/aUhHwJf4QB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['It's foreign, and (wait for it) I don't like it.' https://t.co/coIOenNKBF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia will no longer get a single government website https://t.co/Ay51Eimpp1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jpwarren @Asher_Wolf Political blowback considered less likely? (just a theory)]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>