<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[And love him or hate him he has earned his spot in HoF. Changed the landscape of the NFL. https://t.co/RuWIQgikW8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He shoulda known he was destined for the @CharlesHaleyHoF path https://t.co/JnyXysm6Ab]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will unfortunately have to follow the @CharlesHaleyHoF path. Mediots have memory of an elephant when it comes t… https://t.co/qEiZKdStWs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Knew it should be, douhted it would. Well deserved/earned RedBull, hooah! https://t.co/NKcVskNqnL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Law enforcement lies in the hands of the Judicial Branch of government. Not executive,  did you fail your req US Go… https://t.co/YLgUez631z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amen brother, glad to see you're finally woke to this demagogue fascist autocrat https://t.co/GFJG7bzzQE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please, be real. 90% of owners if not all voted trump (wallet) &amp; id bet 75% of QB1s. come up w/better excuse to hat… https://t.co/yeVhcX4j4j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need this on a shirt lol https://t.co/mPYb80jKXG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ive always said extreme christians are just as bad as extreme islamists.  It's the extreme part that carries the da… https://t.co/kAYfJlxwgh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well said and written, I'm sorry you ever have to go thru this, ignorance breeds hate. Teach your children well https://t.co/IbxP1PhjzQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber primarily operates in the cities, the cities overwhelmingly voted against trump. Poor business decision for Ub… https://t.co/K3UsfGzw3m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All while bannon runs the presidency https://t.co/XG2e2xOqiw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abhorable! w/that said, protests must remain civil, violence plays right into their hands &amp; throws the cause back d… https://t.co/FKA32uPJpG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The donald mistakenly believes prez is supreme being of the land. Thus what he says is final word. Sadly Congress j… https://t.co/30cpPNyysr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thwy have better health care anyway https://t.co/0pfgytKiL3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She is likely a battered wife, she chose power and money when she married him, she made her bed of gold leaf so she… https://t.co/j8204GFp72]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good for them, Pence is a lap dog so no big loss for cnn. https://t.co/DkHx0arM8u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dude has ethics which trumpski has none of https://t.co/BZkG6BFubX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We did not, they did and most are aholes https://t.co/sTNfDifuRE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They're to good for that,  that's grunt work https://t.co/XJaGUXFMOw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If u were rockin stance, maybe. Otherwise no, and those aren't sandals, they're shower shoes lol https://t.co/amrUCI42Qp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure why anyone would expect him to do otherwise or GOP, they are Wallstreet https://t.co/4ejXG2v5z8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thats gonna piss some1 off, they captured his essence, love the orange face. Gonna have to try and find this issue https://t.co/Skmvz5TXAM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's that pesky little prob of separation of church and state. Take away their tax free non profit status https://t.co/xpzUhmNqoq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im in no way excusing Briles, assts or Baylor but shouldnt these "bad dudes" names be just as publicized? i couldnt… https://t.co/EmNZdyXeQx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But giving up draft capitol is https://t.co/kr7zKpCHaL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think prob lies in fact rod wants his players to mv all around the line, position flex.I dislike cause it makes a… https://t.co/rBmx28MvGL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do they make that size? https://t.co/LLRKOn8D5L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the same time he lifts them for the country that infiltrated our democracy. Shameful https://t.co/T8VQyXhV7w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because they helped elect a mad man https://t.co/0yDplk5deu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But if someone is willing to pay me lol I'll take that moolah, send him my way https://t.co/6sAzO2iHKz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there anything in there on how i get my Soros paycheck? https://t.co/aWMDWsFdAg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lucky them, i wouldnt put my life on line for trumpski.  In trumps world his private security is so much better. Le… https://t.co/9OYqctgkKR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just more of her #alternativefacts,  i refuse to watch her, if you have her on I'll change the channel quick, #FACT https://t.co/XFJVqiqCNI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You get what you pay for https://t.co/yL7f9yRkmC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aww cmon now, i always liked dennis as a kid, he was never a bully just very rambunctious https://t.co/fPsag2fExZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For shame https://t.co/IEyp0HfJtn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wise words by a wiser man https://t.co/S5vXPD8ZEN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta call a spade a spade, he has referenced himself that way so why wouldnt the rest of us do likewose https://t.co/0rl6HWUvgn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Win Win imho lol, a girl can dream right? https://t.co/YYnpaI8KH2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retire, then coach, should dak suffer injury he unretires lol. Thats my dream scenario https://t.co/bzCngDoX6u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yet #alternativefacts say you are suffering greatly &amp; on verge of going under lol https://t.co/prnE0yyiiN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FBI, fully funded? WTH Comey and FBI should be investigated regarding their role in it, Comey did something no othe… https://t.co/M3YckjTNrZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thought the was already well underway,  if not why not? https://t.co/SYxQ5rdCmV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where was follow up question? He did not answer the question or he has no clue what home grown means, it means US b… https://t.co/AqTr5vioi7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He is so shallow https://t.co/OBvjOfG1Ci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[is what i said going into wk 17, 2 worst games came after bye &amp; mini bye, i feared it would happen in playoffs espe… https://t.co/sTNtLg9Nxp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sounds like they're borrowing a page from  GOP book of obstruction https://t.co/w91Mq1f2Nr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haste makes waste. DJT affinity 4 speed 1st unfortunately will see alot more deaths.Seal team 6 is successful cause… https://t.co/GVEHAN1BNr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've serious skepticism of any1 who accepted position by trumpkin, they basically shot their career in ft &amp; their j… https://t.co/8rsjRy9sSa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hmm looks very familiar, French voters, you're up, dont allow this to happen to your country say hell no to Le Pen https://t.co/JFsF44EiO5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fat chance https://t.co/oxkL1bxUFd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great, tired of our news outlets being used as propaganda machines,  if i never have to see kellyannes lying face a… https://t.co/rTfraTg886]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cause we all know trumpski has no qualms using nuclear options https://t.co/UVm6gPpIrE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He wont be in office long enough https://t.co/UL6OCj1rHe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Diff btw Sorros and Koch brothers, koch brothers have paid way more for GOP pacs and that pesky lil religion thing https://t.co/od3P23g9nu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not until they were publicly called out on it, trumpers are still out there claiming it was a Moroccan terrorist https://t.co/mMeyIHf5cr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Touche lol. Need more of this. Had media done this during election we wouldnt be in this situ today, better late th… https://t.co/8zHA4w4qnb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He can plan all he wants, impeached prez cant get much done https://t.co/GKb9iKfzhv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They have 2 yrs, things will be vastly diff, trump wont make it a yr https://t.co/GKb9iKfzhv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We aren't allowed to care bout this cause putin owns trump https://t.co/3Mk6Wm922Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kudos to @elizabethforma stand tall, stand tough, Dig those heels in. #NoGorsuch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So by ur logic when ginsburg dies, prez MUST nominate a liberal judge? Lol ur a laugh riot. Garland is as independe… https://t.co/MfBzwwhYMg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no requirement to replace a scj with like minded so i dont care what scalia was https://t.co/XD0exyAjAN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And truth be told i could care less, the pick was Garland and until a fair hearing is held, i expect no other heari… https://t.co/AqBr2IBvis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And who in hell wanted another Scalia, only neo cons https://t.co/u0PtsPY4S0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Garland in no terms can be labeled a liberal, modetate thru and thru, but 4 u neo cons all but neos are liberals https://t.co/u0PtsPY4S0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOP is in big trouble mid terms, there will be big scrambling a yr from now to distance self from trump, thing bout… https://t.co/85agM5Dimo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then gorsuch gets no approval, GOP says dems should look at qualifications and approve, those same standards have g… https://t.co/EdOFcFF3s7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or a military coup https://t.co/bord0BkFDb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely not, no one gets hearing til M.Garland gets his https://t.co/mrVpAFLWTd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one is confirmed til M.Garland has his hearing, the seat belongs to Garland.  #heelsdugin https://t.co/XQvfeZOXmr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woulda never guessed free was largest,  height? https://t.co/TKeQ0L4Xfu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hell to the NO. SCOTUS can not be up for negotiations,  the pick is Garland. https://t.co/U2CKx3a7PR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its M.Garlands seat https://t.co/JvQHemSO3A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[W.Va. must rise up, this guy must be gone in 2yrs https://t.co/oDixSjwMeT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can it be diff, untill Garland gets hearing no one gets hearing, period. I DEMAND NOTHING LESS https://t.co/mEwuitHzvK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best tweet of night,  but im still holding out for a 2 yr delay https://t.co/A0SCHioXF0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hmm, think ill turn on cnn now, good idea https://t.co/HcGBSR6Uc3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you no shame? We know the answer and it's a resounding no. https://t.co/vSwF8eoJFE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That seals it, cowboys pick him in 2nd rnd https://t.co/s6c8R6ZwZO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcuban and shame on those who buried head in sand,  it took conviction to vote 4 one u didnt care 4 vs the devil u knew was poison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gorsuch absolutely does not, there shouldnt be an opening yet knock on wood https://t.co/TF6jnfopBg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You neglected the fine print only neo nazis see, "only if anglo saxon protestant" https://t.co/BBny4eauOx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And retweet if ur from small town and dont approve of trumpocracy https://t.co/CnnEgybIuP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally a media outlet gonna show some spine https://t.co/IBwPF5WdUx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lets build pipeline thru Arlington National Cemetery &amp; see how that flies. Sick of CEOs only looking at bottem line… https://t.co/dGEQQ3Wtly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one Should get a hearing until after Garland, PLAIN AND SIMPLE, no ifs ands or buts https://t.co/hJ2Fi4i0wN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NO, No one deserves a hearing until Garland gets one. THIS I DEMAND https://t.co/TF6jnfopBg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why? GOP thought unimportant 2 have 9 4 a yr now. pick belongs 2 Obama &amp; dems, hold out 4 two yrs i demand. Russia… https://t.co/nz9wbsyfMW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DCBlueStar unfortunately depending on industry you're in you may have to weigh the benefits vs risk in doing anything "formal"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too not mention Jews on Holocaust Remembrance day is not nit-picking, especially when you know it was drafted by an… https://t.co/LptG7w8jPb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No reason every state cant do this. You can not earn a livable wage with only a HS diploma https://t.co/nlMcLK9FCU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lol hindsight is 20/20 https://t.co/bz4FvJCEeC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Touche https://t.co/NRCmWHuyN4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump can count on 2 hands the # of times he's been to church https://t.co/tb1DqA4M3V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He did but thats when he thought it was a Moroccan Muslim terrorist, silent since real facts uncovered https://t.co/sCkJO5q6hv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolute power absolutely corrupts, case in point, look no further than your GOP leadership https://t.co/c0SZak2JYN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this the list posted in the Holocaust Museum?  Looks like it, scarey shit coming https://t.co/tZHa2sedwm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clock is ticking,  wonder if trumpski knows this lil tidbit lol https://t.co/FnEHx0QKmO]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>