<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[A "comma meeting"?! Not quite. A "comms meeting". #oops]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had a #comma meeting about a staff competition to name our new meeting rooms. Had to introduce the comms team to #boatymcboatface]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cats registered with the vet &amp; chip numbers updated! Thanks @SPCAWgtn! #chip&amp;snip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's grounded today &amp; only given her a wee bit of food to give her stomach a rest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tuesday morning! Cat's sick. Not a great start to to the day. Poor wee thing hasn't been right for a day or so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Drumpf’s Rush to Enact an Immigration Ban Unleashed Global Chaos https://t.co/6CFpihudLT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeyPBrenner aye, better hold off on that US road trip for a bit. ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The entire #TrumpBan story blows my mind. Launched on #HolocaustMemorialDay too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giving "power back to you, the people"? - Trump executive order: White House stands firm over travel ban https://t.co/5IBBL9OULf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fun but tricky job as everyone wants to share their successes but no one likes being filmed or photographed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Monday morning. Back to the office. Today I'm shooting &amp; editing a short film clip for staff about one of our team's hard work. #comms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@c1aran that's why I've changed them. ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrJonesTalks it's awesome! Middle of summer now. Got my diving kit &amp; all my other stuff. Life's good. 😎How's life in the capital?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Sunday in a photo. #rewiring https://t.co/RpZxdqp64s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need to go through the rest of my setup &amp;check its all working. My regs need a service but I hope my BCD is ok. #FingersCrossed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to get my drysuit back again after 4 years. Stood in the sun waxing the zip &amp; talcing the seals while looking out over the sea. :)))]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spent yesterday loaded with the cold unpacking our stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OUR STUFF ARRIVED FROM THE UK!!!! YASSSSSSSS!!!! https://t.co/CDH4YfECsI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Up early &amp; out to the gym. I'm sure there's a beautiful sunset out here, if I could open my eyes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drinking an 433 by @garage_project @ Westpac Stadium — https://t.co/vsMNMagTVV #photo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Accidentally at the launch of @Garage_Project 433! Delicious!! #craftbeer https://t.co/YAJD045Hj1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cold &amp; rainy in Wellington. A stout kinda day. #craftnotcrap https://t.co/AYJm7YyRuC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best response on a #comms survey:

Q- How would you prefer to get info
A- Written down &amp; put inside a raspberry cupcake so we can enjoy it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prepare To Laugh At Some Of The Darkest Humor On The Internet https://t.co/UGIuzUExGY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crazy storm last night. Calmed down a bit now. A good day to stay indoors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been offline for a bit but now returning to Twitter again. So, what did I miss?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Be Calm Under Pressure: 3 Secrets From A Bomb Disposal Expert https://t.co/lYn99miLrI via @bakadesuyo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevielucas Haha! Merry Christmas to you too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're looking for a job in the NZ health sector check out our vacancies page. #Newzealand #health #jobs https://t.co/B0hPFo6hmG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdinReporter hello!! Viz? I'll check it out. Slides would be great. NZ is great! How's Auld Reekie?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take a peek inside the Wondrous #WellingtonAdvent Calendar https://t.co/oaEeqDhbx8 via @Wellington_NZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@great_defector everyone is well. What they say about animals knowing is bollocks though. Ours didn't wake up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@siobhh yeah, all good in Mornington. Hope your neck of the woods was the same. Scary stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaun_running yes, thanks. Scary stuff but we're good thanks. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well that's the first earthquake I've ever felt. Scary! #welcometonewzealand https://t.co/C6Wa3njZFw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bottled @Jamiedlynch &amp; I's Dunk Dog clone of @brewdog's Punk IPA. #craftbeer #homebrew Thanks @occasionalbrewr! https://t.co/KPbKFYVCQp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Morning! Today I'm harnessing the power of Georgia espresso. #cafiend https://t.co/RkJlFiNBMd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great chance to join a really nice group of people.

Disclosure: I work there. ;) https://t.co/B0hPFonSLg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PacificBeerExpo it's in the calendar already!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next up: making infographics for our finance section.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Afternoon. Fully recovered from @PacificBeerExpo. Spent today throwing together a plain English guide for work #pedant #grammarnazi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaun_running will do. Pleasant dreams.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Afternoon all. Out &amp;I about in Welly today. Buying some essentials; aftershave. #excitingtimesahead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New project for work: social branding for recruitment. Going to be adding LinkedIn to the list of #socialmedia I've used for work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PacificBeerExpo can't wait. And I've even got the Monday off to recover. ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Morning! Fire Friday!! Long weekend, first pay check &amp; @PacificBeerExpo!!! :))) #craftbeer #excitingtimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stories of loss supported by the Waikato - https://t.co/LQtDes8g4K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things you relearn about yourself: many of my pet hates revolve around fonts &amp; font sizes. #comms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Morning! My new boss starts today. And I've got a new work mobile to break in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@great_defector ALL THE PULSES!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KB_Shampain yeah, gonna wait till they really drop in May.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Midweek (?) beer to celebrate my first NZ pay check. Another cracker from @LibertyBrewer. #craftbeer https://t.co/E7tQ3tKwnC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FranSassy21 I find a great way to get a discount on goods is to do that &amp; then slowly but loudly count them out when paying. #toptip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FranSassy21 been so broke that the Salvation Army knocked on our door the other day &amp; surrendered.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not a full pay cycle but still the first income I've had since leaving Korea two months ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Morning! Got my first pay check today!!!! Woohooo!!!! #excitingtimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got texted my NZ income tax number. Thanks @NZInlandRevenue! Now I can get paid next week. :))) #excitingtimesahead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids! What time is it?! #NewZealand https://t.co/AvvGNJXlUc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First leg day in about 3 months. Couldn't walk down the stairs to the changing room. #hurting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeyPBrenner @LukeCage can't wait to get stuck into it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@trixylibrarian @piktochart great, thanks! Everything's good. Just need to get my first paycheck &amp; I'll be sorted. Hope you're well. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Morning lads &amp; lassies!! Any good tips for sites to make free infographics? Thanks! :) #comms #pr #socmed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going to hammer my Netflix account tonight!!! Not being able to check out @LukeCage has been torture!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You forget just how much of a modern necessity internet access is until you don't have it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got word that the man from @vodafoneNZ has arrived at the house to install our internet! #excitingtimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Morning! Just did my intro at the big staff meeting. Been a while since I've stood up &amp; spoken in front of so many adults.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Morning! Today's excitement: booking in to get internet installed in the flat tomorrow. #excitingtimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've a massive amount to learn about the business, all the services it provides &amp; its clients/stakeholders first though. #learningcurve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So far ppl here are far more comfortable with the idea that they should celebrate their successes than those in some of my previous roles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also very interesting to hear what type of Comms support they want &amp; where they think we could do better at promoting the business.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Second meeting of the day is an intro to one of the service areas which the business provides. Interesting stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First meeting of the day. Gist: "We want to be on social media &amp; generate content that people enjoy". What a start! #excitingTimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Morning! First full week of work coming up &amp; first Monday. #excitingTimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not having wifi yet makes following the #SCOLTU game even more stressful. #comeonscotland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quick sharpener at @Garage_Project. For the purposes of science I'm trying Death From Above on keg &amp; Cask. Cheers! https://t.co/bcYLk8ZIzE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've not used Sharepoint before so I need to learn what it can do &amp; how I do it. #web #comms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, my first project of my new job is updating the intranet. Any #Comms or #web ppl recommend good intro to Sharepoint sites?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Morning! Weather update: it's freezing!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@siobhh thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To the natives the after work pint was a sacred animal... @TuataraBrew https://t.co/W5C8v8fLJF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Morning! Suited and booted for my first day at my new job. Very excited. And up faaar to early. :) #excitingtimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@c1aran that could have been anyone's ass! ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ASBBank thanks! I will do. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TuataraBrew shame about the lack of tunes that night. But the beer will more than make up for it. ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's major achievement: opened a bank account! Went with @ASBBank. Their staff were great! #excitingtimesahead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TuataraBrew anything musical on tomorrow evening? My first day of my new job so want to come over for my first after work pint. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeerKel @ForkandBrewer nice! Especially interested in the saison. Haven't seen many in Welly so far.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@TheSoundNZ is rapidly becoming part of my daily routine. As good music should.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mornin'! Last nights krazy fog has lifted &amp; today looks like it could be another good one. #weatherchat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrJonesTalks @hackneycouncil good but The Dear Leader does it best. https://t.co/UwojjQ15Tc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, no looks like visa today then. :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wellington is awesome but I feel I'm in limbo until these things happen. So today I'm constantly refreshing my Gmail.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Until I get my visa confirmed I can't start my job, get internet in the apartment or get a NZ bank account.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been told to expect a decision on my visa today or at the latest tomorrow. Can't stress how impatient I am for this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quick coffee stop now. Then off to investigate the state of gentlemen work fashions. Not a bad place for a cuppa. https://t.co/TmsZJPJwzn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On my way I dropped into @lesmills on Taranaki St. Cracking facilities. Definitely signing up with them ASAP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Afternoon! Today's major achievement so far: join @wcl_library. Also downloaded their app which is pretty neat too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From yesterday's #zwanzeday - Drinking a Kriek 100% Lambic @ Garage Project Taproom - https://t.co/g9qEebvrpV #photo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From yesterday's #zwanzeday - Drinking a Single Barrel 1-Year Lambic @ Garage Project Taproom - https://t.co/3EbItPIG1R #photo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ZwanzeDay was ace! My first time attending the event &amp; first time at @Garage_Project's tap room. Will definitely b… https://t.co/fhywkHN1Wz]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>