<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@_marya_k the 'New England Bradys'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Mr Shanahan - please don't use all your awesome at once. San Fran needs a lot of it. Thanks; an overly-hopeful 49er fan. #SuperBowl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@_marya_k how's the heart rate?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesmassola how does this not convince conservative LNP MPs to change course is beyond me. Free SSM vote = ridiculous poll boost.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OnTheForecheck especially when Willy gets so excited everytime the opposition goaltender makes a save...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OnTheForecheck youth movement! #alternativefact]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey .@sydneyswans, how long until we can cheer cheer a red &amp; white women's team? I can't have my daughter dressed l… https://t.co/KnXQJvB0uk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_marya_k anything you say after 'Arvy' is wonderful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THIS. NOW IS THE TIME. #Preds #NHL. https://t.co/rdumdVC0O3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamVingan this is why you get asked about Saros.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlexConant it's certainly possible; but is usually reliant on supporting the 'wrong' sporting team - irrespective of the sport itself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_marya_k 1x handful of thumb tacs, 1x human image (magazine cutout can suffice), + harmless work-like image on PC to throw ppl off scent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_marya_k no.

Voodoo on the other hand...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OnTheForecheck unless it was 'Ribei-Ro'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_marya_k absolute trainwreck in real time and HD. Political TV show writers couldn't concoct any better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesmassola Whilst you are completely wrong (said with all due respect etc.) at least you aren't alone - https://t.co/4JwLgEjfXQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OnTheForecheck Carolina waterslide fun factor: 5/10. Calgary waterslide fun factor: 14/10.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neal passing to a guy heading to the bench is peak this season. #CBJvsNSH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OnTheForecheck as always, thankyou George McPhee.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_marya_k I traded foligno away in my fantasy league. I have regrets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_marya_k see: 'alternative fact'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@_marya_k REVERSE JINX THIS NOW.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Offensive dynamo Matt Irwin we need you. #NSHvsEDM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If my D-corp consisted of 'high flyers' like Larsson and Russell...I'd boo Subban too. Clowns. #NSHvsEDM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SHOOT THE F---ING PUCK RIBEIRO #NSHvsEDM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn it Watson. (But still...suck it Lucic). #NSHvsEDM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no way Arvy doesn't practise those wipe outs. No way. #NSHvsEDM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent goaltending by Ellis. #NSHvsEDM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_marya_k with 2113 PIM (total career), how long do you think Stu was on the ice to learn the rules?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_marya_k only if you can demonstrate intent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This just in: .@CBRBrave playing entire season away from home according to well placed #AIHL sources. #facepalm… https://t.co/aix3cSwE5S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I "intend" to show someone at the #NHL the finger. You clowns. #NSHvsVAN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caps/Pens: "...and that's how you put on a show."
Stars/Rangers: "hold our drinks."
#DALvsNYR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Henry_Belot Team #conservative: united.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Both coaches went 'fuck it' and pulled their goalies right? #WSHvsPIT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_marya_k fine*

(*as long as Ovi carries me to a fantasy league title first)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Henry_Belot Hi Henry. The article's electorate info seems a little odd. Broken Hill is in Div. Parkes. Pre-redistribution info?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_marya_k you can come back now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OnTheForecheck blue shell hopefully. Red or green shells never did anything useful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_marya_k now if he could just find his form...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@OnTheForecheck called it. https://t.co/lUi4ZhRigM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unless it was this obvious...the goal should stand (but it's the NHL so anything goes...) #NSHvsTBL https://t.co/KGgMPn0BQv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pessimistic prediction: Radulov scores an OT winner and then chugs out of his helmet in front of the Predators bench. #MTLvsNSH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OnTheForecheck @carolianne_ sporting arguments with dads are the best. I'm still arguing about finals losses from years past.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 smegging goals at #TORvsWSH and Matthews + Ovi contribute exactly 0 of them. Fantasy league hockey sucks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@_marya_k any anti-predictions for today's game? (If you say Weber gets a hattrick...I'm totally ok with that.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_marya_k why are you advocating tactics that will win games?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carolina's broadcast showing both teams in red. Clearly on board with the 'Chicago vs Chicago offcasts' theme of tonight. #CHIvsCAR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even Arvidsson's screens are typically full tilt. #CHIvsNSH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OnTheForecheck "the sum of Chicago's TOI not otherwise occupied by Duncan Keith."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_marya_k just great. Niners coming last here too. Thanks...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey .@BlueJacketsNHL - any room left on the bandwagon? Asking for a friend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@OnTheForecheck i have a baby photo for tonight's game at the ready. Spoiler alert: she ain't happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coreypronman only from beyond the 3pt line. Double if after an infield shift.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What i take from this, is that there is still hope for me. https://t.co/0mNH0QdAir]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because .@OnTheForecheck hasn't posted a dog .gif...here's my kid's reaction to the .@PredsNHL win https://t.co/aOun8gnD4S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_marya_k devotees to the Stu Grimson doctrine of 'everything arse-about'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OnTheForecheck hoping "Fiddler vs Watson with a surprise Gaustad tag-in cameo" is also there. #tradition]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy flipping line changes Batman. #NSHvsNJD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NSHvsPHI https://t.co/sjO2wDfOUl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@_marya_k OT L or SO L? #antiprediction]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best outcome for this PP: 1x shot on goal. Related: I am rapidly reaching peak cynic. #NSHvsPHI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OnTheForecheck only if provided by epic forward Austin Watson and no one else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_marya_k that + i just rant about mascot superiority until she leaves the room.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_marya_k how can i take the high ground when arguing with my other half (Stars fan) now? You ruined Xmas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_marya_k that hurt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reliable attacker and point-getter Austin Watson leading our SOG. #headdesk #NSHvsPHI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_marya_k cat pee = likely better at 3v3 and SO.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More like 'Minnesota Wild-at-anything-except-the-game-of-hockey'. #MINvsNSH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hutton needs to be pulled so he can do a late 3rd period interview. Because tradition.#HeyThanksForHavingMeGuys #STLvsNSH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why couldnt the people who replaced Mike Smith with a sieve have done it for the Nashville game too?? #ARIvsPIT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OnTheForecheck about the same as Colorado's locker room after the Montreal debacle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_marya_k "Duchene traded to Nashville for a 2017 1st rounder and the Predators broadcast team". That's the dream.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for stepping up Mr Subban. Crouse you are a mouthbreather. #NSHvsARI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_marya_k check for a 'cruel and unusual punishment' exception clause.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_marya_k interesting. I'd hope we could avoid another prospect + pick combo (a la Toronto), but with limited options that seems likely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_marya_k what trade (in your opinion) makes that happen?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's it. Arvy jersey. Sign me up. #NSHvsDAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roussel: wasting a Stars roster spot since 2012. #NSHvsDAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_marya_k this better be another of your anti-predictions...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The .@mkeadmirals .gif game today has been particularly strong. https://t.co/p4yMmoaRTU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need someone to reassure me (again) that Arvy won't be stolen by the expansion draft. My future jersey relies on this. #COLvsNSH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Grizzly_CBR this is why i prefer regulation losses. https://t.co/4f6Rrl2jb3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Grizzly_CBR at least you had the decency to do it in th regulation 60 minutes. Dragging the agony out into OT is cruel and unusual.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nashville: "...and that's how you blow a lead."
Detroit: "hold my beer."
#nhl #DETvsPIT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_marya_k 2/2. This is becoming a thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_marya_k any pessimistic pre-game predictions? Y'know, so the opposite happens. #stickwithwhatworks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@belinda_merhab @adamgartrell goes best with a suppository of wisdom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TomMcIlroy Amusing. Denies climate change exists...yet happily utilises 'the sky is falling' metaphors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_marya_k i think they heard you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_marya_k 1. But it was probably accidental.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoa. https://t.co/e6cvOlnz6Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where's the assist for Stuart? Reward the effort people...sheesh... #WPGvsNSH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_marya_k ...you're 2/2. Well played!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_marya_k i like this prediction more than your previous one :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How did a $500 million buy-in not result in the Las Vegas Craps? https://t.co/WoaPjMBJzs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_marya_k cool. Was curious; Oz sports tend to use team doctors with league oversight in case of drama.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_marya_k are they team or NHL appointed?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waaa-ambulance inbound. Hang in there. https://t.co/TGJiGyuNOe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd like to comment about his whinging... https://t.co/iUkLyxHvqw]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>