<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@timritchie yet again, I'm reminded just how amazing and inspiring your photos are. Thanks for sharing them with us all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK international Uni student applications down; US visa angst. Will 2017 be a bumper year for overseas students to Australia?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pipms I use a WordPress blog - on Azure, if you like the cloud ;) - or LinkedIn Posts for a ready-made audience but less control]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katinacurtis think ESTA visa waiver is different to Interview Waiver Program (which is for the old-style stamped visa), and unaffected]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intelligent Assistants/Voice Control: Starting with lower expectations leads to longer use https://t.co/0S2iJaCSwf [ie don't believe hype?]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crothwell lots of exciteable shouting at the TV down here!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 2017 global market for coffee pods is $17,000,000,000. Yep, seventeen billion dollars. That explains Cluney in ads]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This afternoon had a 1 hr meeting cancelled. So I built a university enquiry bot and chatted to it in Skype… https://t.co/5eG6SlkK95]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnqgoh Surely there should be a "Teacher's Entitlement" scheme alongside the "MPs Entitlement" one!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnqgoh 2014 report said NSW teachers were spending nearly $2,000 of their own money for classroom supplies https://t.co/xROwAx9XCl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Anthony_Caruana @myer I thought it was just me that has that experience (all the time). Nice to know it's common :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're into data visualisations, then take a look at https://t.co/7yu9UrSZQQ who have some really nice money-related charts and maps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katstheone in the locker at school. You'll never find me until you've made up a complete backup PE kit instead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How about this for a #raspberryPI project - a smart mirror that recognises you and shares info with you?… https://t.co/xSXltPPXmj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Out of office message ON. Only 25 urgent things to finish before the plane door closes in a few hours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This #STEM #Education project has everything - space, rockets, coding and student scientists https://t.co/10HXjQJekX Your school in 2017?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Q&amp;A: Great 1st Q to @CUBERIDER_AU "What's next". A: Ten times as many Aussie students taking part to develop STEM s… https://t.co/RSgmLErcgr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hearing live from the rocket launch site in Japan. 100 Aussie students' experiments getting ready for lift off with… https://t.co/MXeRaiyQml]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feels like the @CUBERIDER_AU launch is halfway into the stratosphere already https://t.co/Za7fB1kCe7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's nearly time for lift off. Until then we've got virtual space cadets at @CUBERIDER_AU launch with @dan_bowen https://t.co/chCKZjUon0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm unreasonably excited about the first real "launch" I've see at a product launch @CUBERIDER_AU… https://t.co/wL7bwFHbA2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a really nice website - all #Azure services on a single, neat web page https://t.co/f9CO3RuBaR  Well done @RicardoNiepel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The going-paperless journey for Bear Creek Middle School - some lessons here for all schools https://t.co/3U6W8VaRZG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first Australian space mission is carrying experiments from Australian students @cuberider_au https://t.co/tpk21M2p6H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT-evangelist teacher in Victoria looking for a change next year? Want "Ambassador' in your job title?… https://t.co/tqFGciNsgV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obvious that the infographic designers were given the #PISA2015 results well ahead of the education community #wrongpriorities]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want the job title "Microsoft Teacher Ambassador" next year? Based in Melbourne? Come and be a colleague! #edtech https://t.co/tifNBXtjSx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tablet and PC together, running #Windows10 and with a digital stylus, and still under $400 in Australia #edtech https://t.co/7cP0K3Ecut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the UK, students think universities should spend less on buildings, sports and social https://t.co/zu2q3S9aQc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wardy @wardyit Have you got one coming to Sydney soon? (A lunch &amp; learn, not just a pizza)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Important lesson to remember as we have the national discussion about Australian universities' research and focus o… https://t.co/gMXyZb2t96]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting watching the reaction to #TIMMS2015 as the different time zones wake up and react about what's said about their region]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AM I the last person to discover the 3D maps in the #Windows10 Maps app? 6 Australian cities, and some amazing Euro… https://t.co/jTiM2THzP5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That small feeling of satisfaction when somebody notices you've done something good.… https://t.co/4bvKlytv4W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do #Microsoft staff learn about changing tech internally? Here's the #MachineLearning &amp; #analytics story: https://t.co/6v61XK7zu8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My big win: Outlook rule that filtered &gt;10% of my emails. Every email containing 'unsubscribe', moved to a folder,… https://t.co/IGlng8mJDk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best Outlook email hack ever! Create a rule that moves incoming emails with the word 'unsubscribe' in the body to a sub-folder. Magic impact]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a discount for Education customers to attend Microsoft Ignite Australia in Feb 2017 https://t.co/9TBdsVg1W9 thanks to @MSAUedu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Australia Health Tracker has amazing, accessible data https://t.co/QWjdhMpgrR Anybody mapped it to fast food outlet density?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess we're going to #EduTechAU - my mailbox has suddenly started to fill with "Dear Ray, can we build your EduTech stand?" emails]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hartnellyoung @SandraMilligan3 So many scenarios for the future of assessment and certifications. Disruptive micro certifications?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does #DigitalTransformation mean for Australia’s education institutions?Thoughts on @MicrosoftAU's new report https://t.co/l0XcPBH8uc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SAlexander_UTS Thanks Shirley - typing too fast and not checking properly :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["From motivated to empowered: digital transformation in education" https://t.co/Ii9odh2s45 by @RayFleming on @LinkedIn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want an inspiring #edtech startup story and STEM Australian curriculum idea? That'll be @cuberider_au https://t.co/gQSrswNvvp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@terryfish And look at head teacher stat: Nearly 9 out of 10 had difficulty or failed to recruit a head teacher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MissDCox I think Gifts:No  Party:Yes  same as most companies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@0x4445565A @Asher_Wolf According to the legislation, it's still illegal if it can be accessed in NSW. I think law was written before web!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile QLD EDU publish lots of school performance #opendata  https://t.co/KsM2IE1eXO inc 3 years NAPLAN by school https://t.co/YDDJ8HRFWY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just discovered it's illegal in NSW to publish a list of schools by performance. $50,000 fine https://t.co/yQYRGrPMpq So much for #opendata]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Earlier in the week I went to #Hack4Good @UNSW. An amazing festival of tech and accessibility app ideas. More here: https://t.co/DHNy0SMK8y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Know a uni student? Microsoft is #5 in the Top Australian Intern programs list https://t.co/aalI6FzVBj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GFThommo Honestly, the most controversial thing I've read this week. I had no idea this was a thing. Makes me sad - have I read it wrong?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Microsoft Azure Bot Service makes it easier to develop and deploy chatbots. Will be big for EDU https://t.co/cT9GDMlijB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching Satya live feed from Sydney https://t.co/bmN7gB6j6b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice: two of these startups with Satya yesterday https://t.co/yYcmS3AVrJ came from Imagine Cup student competition  https://t.co/MmOa2bEeyK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the few times when we Aussies don't have to get up in the middle of the night to watch Satya Nadella live. 1… https://t.co/Z7P6PDV3Zy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Less than 50% of Aus uni offers are made to school leavers currently #changinghighereducation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#hack4good at @UNSW creating accessible web services using AI &amp; cognitive tech. Worth watching hashtag this PM as they race to finish line]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Partially sighted? Office Lens now has amazing Frame Guide from Seeing AI video (https://t.co/xPwYMQRraP) added https://t.co/pFGuE0YobE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Office Lens has some awesome new features on iOS for accessibility https://t.co/pFGuE0GNk6 Point iPhone at a doc, and it will read it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is one of those moments of change in education: Dyson to create university https://t.co/Q1o70hWFYo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andrew Hill, #Microsoft Director of Mechanical Design for  #SurfaceBook, is talking in Sydney next Wed @UNSW… https://t.co/Km9c2cgpG6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's now been 180 days without printing a single page (but I did today ask a colleague to print 3 pages for me)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That moment when you need to read the sign to know whether it's a school or a prison https://t.co/SAjjxrqYkT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What I learnt today: The Australian Privacy Act doesn't cover public schools and universities https://t.co/DrIITef4pS [Anybody know why?]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian headlines that make me smile: "Is this the greatest PC of all time?" from AFR has got to be up there https://t.co/BonEumXuWa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Hololens, AR and the future of Business Intelligence" evening with Lakeba - Nov 17, Manly https://t.co/zxn5olH3rK [Just cleared my diary]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. Surface Studio https://t.co/Hs38dXYrPF [Need to work out what I can sell to release the funds...]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such awesomeness for Australian teachers - get your student projects up into space. And get a cool mission patch… https://t.co/Yu92VfaJPc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free eBook - Data Science with #Microsoft #SQL2016 https://t.co/5wJ78be4eY (Creating intelligent apps using #SQL and #R)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #R Script showcase for #PowerBI is quite a treasure trove for data analytics people https://t.co/jsbO3P2SjA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian Office 365 Education customers have 7 days to ask for their tenant to be moved to Australia https://t.co/Wz1Vh3ufb1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jobs that didn't exist five years ago #21stCenturyJobs #socialmediafoodstylist #edtech https://t.co/N9leXIjC0M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @getproductive: New Learning Tools Help Educators Create More Inclusive Classrooms https://t.co/BWtfNdVrCI [From Peter, NSW EDU Acct mgr]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian #Office365 Education customers: you have 10 days left to opt-in to be moved to the Australian datacentre https://t.co/Wz1Vh3ufb1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian #Office365 Education customers: you have &lt;2 weeks left to opt-in to be moved to the Australian datacentre https://t.co/Wz1Vh3ufb1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's info on Microsoft's Disability Answer Desk in Australia https://t.co/HBzDipXSA7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The plural of anecdote is not 'anecdata' https://t.co/SYxRh7aLNw on @LinkedIn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HoloLens available in Australia in Nov https://t.co/oW5RZ6eTPL [Umm, which can I justify for Xmas - Developer Edition or Corporate Edition?]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 global courses for teachers and education leaders from EdX\Microsoft includes 1 from University of Queensland #UQ https://t.co/cdpDnKmwF9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MT @ryanbonnici: Not a designer? No problem. Here's how to create infographics in Powerpoint! https://t.co/vlKon0oBqM [Handy for teachers]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learning and Discerning: Why Machine Learning can't solve every education problem  https://t.co/eYDVh7HEre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simplifying Single Sign On for students: How to integrate @Blackboard Learn with #Azure Active Directory https://t.co/hS2xZGfGJw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Data Science Track in the Microsoft Professional Program is a course leading to professional certification https://t.co/Ey2Bbkerzi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Swedish researchers build dyslexia screening tool with cloud-based analytics solution https://t.co/DpHfP5X9Up #Azure #machinelearning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Predicting student dropout a new way" https://t.co/26g0JnbPFN by @RayFleming on @LinkedIn #edtech #machinelearning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Australia's Not for Profit sector? Microsoft have just added Azure cloud services to our donation scheme https://t.co/vvYU8kryeS #nfp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another excellent 'Analytics with Power BI Desktop' course coming on 25 Oct in Melbourne from @BizData_News https://t.co/N203L24EwK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Currently working from a coffee shop. I have 33 different Wi-Fi networks showing up on my PC #constantlyconnected]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mesterman So you got me watching it online - it looked like they zoomed in on the minister as almost everybody else left the room?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoying the view from the 3P Learning offices. Sydney at its best today https://t.co/3VvpRk099z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulrunslong +ves of garmin: wifi sync, fast GPS fix, sync with Garmin connect (yrs of data) but -ves screen text small to read; no music]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Downside of living in Australia:  #TalkLikeAPirateDay is almost over before the rest of the world wakes up and reminds you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@paulrunslong What's your TomTom like Paul? Thinking of replacing my Garmin, but not sure if the TomTom has all the features I'm used to?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shenmaxiu @CAUDITinc What an awful Dad joke. I avoided the "tracking movement" gag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Webinar with @LiveTilesUI today at 12PM AEST - how Cath Ed SA deployed SharePoint with Mosaic to 44 schools https://t.co/036mq3B1CZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting twist on education exams - LinkedIn lets students sit one test to apply to 25 IT companies in India https://t.co/Jsgnlhlser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Genius discovery! I can use this for lots of other ideas too... https://t.co/pruYAdc13i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dan_bowen What have you done that's made you trend on Twitter? https://t.co/FW8p2ljFlL]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>