<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@rhettsnell @lyndondrake I’m just here to start the conversation...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AWSStats How many 50 partnerships w/o 1 of the players facing have there been?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Festival One - bands, wristbands &amp; a busy Student Lounge… https://t.co/YLMG2KuOZh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McHughD Why do you nae appear? https://t.co/WJJSc7D7Rg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoyed watching/listening to students play grown-up Guess Who today. #StudentLounge #FestivalOne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Late night in the Student Lounge  at Festival One. https://t.co/a8zaYjOx35]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TSCF is at Festival One. Come &amp; visit us in the Student Lounge… https://t.co/qBES9rpQJ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timmorrison44 Not as much as being a feeder club would be ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timmorrison44 Didn’t watch it - was away w/ work. Saw the 1st leg 2nd half though - sounds like both games were pretty poor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@WelshRugbyUnion PS Don’t tell them my boy was born in NZ to a English dad &amp; N Irish mum…hope we give you a 6 Nations thrashing ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@WelshRugbyUnion Appreciate your 7s squad taking the time to play w/ kids at a birthday party during thanks traini… https://t.co/Ta5JJvEIwF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamessercombe @rhodrielisjones @OJDBROWN @martin_downes You’ll be pleased to see my boy is doing his best for Angl… https://t.co/VgzDDJkLTX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's always a temptation to remove the cross https://t.co/CMexyMCPzo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamessercombe @kenny_robbo Pheasants, not peasants.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Student at Festival One? Come &amp; hang out in the Student Lounge #FestivalOne2017 https://t.co/9ycoXRIE0o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9yrs ago today, we left the UK to serve in NZ. It’s been hard, but good. Thankful to family &amp; all those who have sacrificed to be part of it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@saclokey Just re-read ‘Spiritual Leadership’ - J Oswald Sanders (the famous unknown Kiwi). If you’ve not read it, make sure you do this yr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TedTurnau You mean to stop time?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TedTurnau Why don’t you have it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@saclokey Are you doing the 100 book challenge?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@interislander beats @BluebridgeFerry on the inside lane https://t.co/JEEJc1v5vc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@papatoetoetiger Sounds a bit more positive. https://t.co/96UQ3moNtF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Our society is abnormally secular &amp; passed this off as common sense." Elizabeth Knox, Kiwi novelist &amp; atheist #NZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["NZers haven't just forgotten God, they've forgotten that they've forgotten" Quoted by Ron Hay at our TSCF Staff &amp; Families Camp #NZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@FlyAirNZ Are people who signed up to Flexitime membership going to be sent a survey every time they fly using it? I’d rather I didn’t...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HistoryInPics Are you sure that's not an iPad?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@saclokey That's his style. But he's brilliant too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikepilav I’ve heard that attributed to Spurgeon...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TedTurnau @FastCompany Have you seen a S African plug?! They're surely uglier?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Took this pic tonight here in NZ - lift up your eyes. Still true today.  https://t.co/689WPTn34G https://t.co/2UMZ8wRTrk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grabaseat Yes, I realise that, but I have to do that every time. Is there a way to automatically set it so I don’t?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grabaseat Is there anyway to set your homepage so that you are shown the deals from your local airport first, rather than always AKL first?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_timdennis My concern is more it seems to be the standard activity. As Elvis said "A little less conversation, a little more action']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_timdennis I don’t think Brits realise how many conferences we have - seems to the standard ‘go to’ solution. Could be over-saturated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_timdennis Absolutely-I get that, but if you only go to the conferences everyone goes to, you’ll miss the chance to think about other stuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_timdennis Why not go to one that everyone else isn’t going to? #Goagainsttheflow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couldn't agree more with both these comments. https://t.co/G1GCu6CSvn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Andy_Shudall Surely someone at your church can? https://t.co/xdwZtW38Yj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lacymel "Never underrate the under 8s" Hudson Pope]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pmbillenglish Congratulations! And keep going!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rhettsnell I'd still rather that ride than the other.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The Son of God became the servant of God in order to do the mission of God. That image provides the pattern for believers" J Oswald Sanders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many are called, but few are chosen :) https://t.co/a5vBjnIL7n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rhettsnell USA are experiencing democracy. Whether they enjoy it may remain to be seen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I find it quite sad watching Brits disputing the democratic process when so many around the world don’t enjoy democracy #Brexit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JDSayersMish I find it quite sad watching Brits disputing the democratic process when so many around the world don’t enjoy democracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JDSayersMish I'm saddened watching from afar that Britain appears more divided &amp; so many appear to place hope in one camp or the other.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MackStiles Good to see that big smiling face. Keep smiling…and sharing the reason for the smile :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TedTurnau @OJDBROWN Sadly not…it’s the same people who start tweets “Brothers…"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gordieww @TheoWeir Or…a bit more  direct would be ’The Case for Christ’ Lee Strobel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gordieww @TheoWeir How about a book written by my old man - ‘Before you say I don’t believe’? https://t.co/qyQfg6QYME]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlyAirNZ Having completed 1 survey about flexitime membership trial, I've been asked 2 more times to do it again. Any reason?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OJDBROWN What’s currently showing at Aber cinema? When I was there in the late 90s, I think Singing in the Rain was just being released ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jdcarswell10 You’d probably enjoy this. https://t.co/BOKvagja7K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikepilav Have you seen the video of the crazy man body boarding down it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@joethorn Just finished ‘Note to Self’. Enjoyed it. Thanks for writing it.  The ch on ‘Initiate’ in particular is superb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Grant_Russell @JarradVZ When I was there recently I was amazed how many people were at the beach early on a Sat am out for a swim.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OJDBROWN @TedTurnau Absolutely. I cringe at how many tweets start "Christian..." Who speaks like that?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Grant_Russell @JarradVZ I'm surprised by this. Doesn't seem to tie in with my experience of the two countries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could a reason why the church is in decline in NZ be partly b/c we as Christians have such a poor view of what it is?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cjsbishop @BasinReserve @BLACKCAPS Oh for the life of a politician 😜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Horrible scenes at the Basin Reserve. No one wants to see an ambulance involved in any live sport. Hope he's ok. #NZLvBAN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McHughD We have plenty more tat passed off as Kiwiana like that to sell you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daihankey Read a super chapter on prayer in Oswald Sanders' "Spiritual Leadership" last night. It's (prayer) essential.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@papatoetoetiger God is still God though…but I know it’s hard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daihankey Thanks - they’re all things out of our control, but a reminder to trust in God &amp; work hard at the things we can do. Appreciate it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daihankey It’s like losing 2/3 of your financial support &amp; not because you’ve offended anyone!  Still, God is still God, in control &amp; good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daihankey When we moved to NZ, it was £1=NZ$2.75 today, it’s £1=NZ$1.68,meaning we need to raise nearly £20k more in support to cover costs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today’s look at the UK-NZ exchange rate is another reminder to trust God for His provision &amp; not be too depressed by the situation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you want to be useful to God, you will need to be the person who moves first. You have to take the initiative to move..." Joe Thorn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tom_peters Welcome back to NZ. Hope your time here trumps anything the USA has to offer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am I living in fear or by faith? #BiOY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The love of one's country is a splendid thing. But why should love stop at the border?" Pablo Casals, cellist &amp; composer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Completely. https://t.co/TvX0J8ltWD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Risk and faith go hand in hand. Luke 5:17-20]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Knowing their thoughts, Jesus said..." Is there a more terrifying thought than Jesus knows what we are thinking?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kouya Absolutely. Am moved that we hear v little of them in our celebrity obsessed world. True heroes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This morning, I finished reading Brian Keenan's ‘An Evil Cradling’ - Horrific situation. Slavery is an awful thing, freedom is Divine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theweeflea Some helpful perspectives here. As you suggest, it's not always black &amp; white, particularly in a missions context.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewnorbury @jamessercombe @abercecminister Thankfully not 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abercecminister @andrewnorbury @jamessercombe It was clearly memorable though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is brilliant. Have said the same to football fans myself before &amp; been jeered. Well done GT. https://t.co/Przm7ADmRz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishRugby @IrishTimesSport Would be fantastic to be in a "smaller country" again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@His_Grace How did Prince Charles make this list? Would he even call himself a Christian?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jdcarswell10 Did you see this clip y’day? I saw it live &amp; loved it. #Horsforthlad https://t.co/uXwKCUBLtZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blessing for yourself &amp; others doesn’t always come thru staying in your country,w/ your people &amp; your family - for Abe, it came thru leaving]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rvannest The issue isn't so much with Calvin as some who use his name.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bawads Would love you to find out why tickets are more expensive for today's Test than last year's v Oz. Part of why we've not gone today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@BLACKCAPS Is anyone able to answer why tickets are more expensive for today's Test than last year's v Oz?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realMChalmers @jamessercombe You were talked about. Hope your ears were burning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamessercombe Are the files recoverable? Would love to listen  to Ted again. I often quote something he said in them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OJDBROWN Is that what @michael_ots is called these days?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@nzherald Seriously, the standard of your proofreading is dreadful -read the article &amp; see the error in yr headline https://t.co/JkWWoY0aWA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamessercombe We both look terrified - loved chatting with you.  Miss you mate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamessercombe You too…you up for a quick Skype/Facetime?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bawads Aye…didn’t feel strong in the Hutt, but it also looks wetter than your pic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shakey shakey in my office. #EQNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My mate Dan Strange has written a super tribute to his friend Mike Ovey -helpful perspective in light of who God is. https://t.co/jqGMmTP7fQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThomRainer As is an evangelistic staff/eldership.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@BLACKCAPS What’s w/ the massive price rise for Test tickets v Bangladesh compared to Test tickets last year v Aus?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>