<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@ExorsusWoW congratulations to you all &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRoot We've crashed it :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton Don't give up, wait until every vote is counted.  I believe in you &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WarcraftDevs @WatcherDev Forums are being wonky, keeps changing my character and errors posting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeelvsBabyface I'm with you still &lt;3 I would love to see what else is out there in the gaming world with you &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't forget to check fellas &lt;3 #inthenipoftime https://t.co/3rUNKnGEgS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I remember when he killed me :) https://t.co/W7AgjJDLCN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WatcherDev Thank you &lt;3 Babylonia 110 BM Hunter US Kirin Tor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PreachGaming Yes, I would love you to do a guide for frost mages please &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[75CM Ombre Cosplay Hair Layered Long Wavy Heat-Resistant Fashion Lolita Harajuku Costume Wig https://t.co/Gi3mKzoHug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WatcherDev congrats on the promotion &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WatcherDev If it's not too much trouble, can you ask Ornyx to please return to the hunter forum thread he started and engage with us please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted 4 photos on Facebook in the album "Duke Ellington School of the Arts" https://t.co/qKUvofAkN2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[yes it should be uniform among the schools both public and charter. https://t.co/sHaMSGF8Oy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeelvsBabyface I don't like that profession progression involves dungeons.  Why should I be forced to do content I'm not interested in :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Justinmccray87 I'm on Kirin Tor US, what server are you on? Sent you a private message also :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Justinmccray87 @JasonHayesMusic Katie has done a little cello as well.  Right now in school, she's doing piano theory along with violin!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonHayesMusic Katie spent today with her new music having a blast! Thanks again &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonHayesMusic AWESOME &lt;3 thanks so much :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonHayesMusic Katie wants to know if there are any violin sheet music available for WOW to purchase?  I didn't see any in the store.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EliotHine The pic of the graduating class in front of the school in their caps and gowns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EliotHine  How do parents get this pic?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeelvsBabyface I'm ready now.  Bring on the Legion! #FORAZEROTH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WatcherDev There were tears.  I'm 51 and I sobbed like a baby for the Alliance.  I was truly broken at the Broken Shore.  Well done &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YAY!!! and can't wait for demon hunters &lt;3 https://t.co/sDbMbbWyvf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I probably should not let my daughter see this lol https://t.co/E2xsdJwK3m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Muffinus I'm a BM hunter and I'm not sure how I feel about the changes.  I'm gonna play some more and get back to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How precious, congratulations &lt;3 https://t.co/zMmQxc6alu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeelvsBabyface I hope you do a patch notes video for 7.0 because I am so unhappy.  Also BM seems totally ruined now :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeelvsBabyface Can you do the treasure chest scenario with a party?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This could be fun, either way I'm on board for Legion! https://t.co/QlcIG3APLJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attention Eliot Hine parents:

There will be no PTO meeting on Wednesday, June 8th.  Look forward to information... https://t.co/y2ZVrU1dZU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arpedrio @JasonHayesMusic It just pumps you up and lifts your spirit, you feel like you can do anything :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonHayesMusic @arpedrio My daughter plays violin and likes to try to learn music from WOW by ear, she loves the music in the elven areas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonHayesMusic My favorite piece is still the music for the opening cinematic of World of Warcraft, I still get goosebumps &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonHayesMusic Are you responsible for all the awesome music in game and on the soundtracks?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wait, there's a book and here I was just living my life https://t.co/t9Y9a1nkjY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cpt_ass How are you feeling about the legion beta now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NBCTheVoice The talent was so awesome and inspiring this season, can't wait to see what happens next season. #BestShowEver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How awesome is that, it pays to continue to hold out for me https://t.co/MeKRdx7Voa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BellularGaming how does scaling impact the fishing skill, can you fish in peace or do you always have to worry about mobs?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeelvsBabyface can we get a vid on the whole spec switching fee, thanks &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeelvsBabyface How are you feeling about Legion going live 30 Aug, will it be ready?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attention Parents of Eliot Hine:

You should have been notified by robocall and by a letter sent home with your... https://t.co/Win0BSW4ox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're invited to DCYOP's Champagne in the Park: https://t.co/eAGPNRGmWE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EliotHine @HeatherSchoell I hope they had a great time! #welldeserved]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EliotHine @HeatherSchoell totally awesome &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to all my family and friends for the birthday wishes, I had a wonderful birthday &lt;3 — feeling thankful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8th grade parent meeting at @EliotHine has been rescheduled and will not take place tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attention Eliot Hine parents and incoming parents:

The 8th grade parents meeting has been rescheduled to May... https://t.co/R3D977JcnS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WatcherDev Need more clarification on pristine realms in the thread please and thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WatcherDev Ion is there an incentive for current WoW players to see the movie, pet, game time?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeelvsBabyface maybe this is the end of WOW after all :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sigh :( https://t.co/MdTEnr2kGW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeelvsBabyface Did you do a broken shore event video? I watched the horde and alliance events, does that come after?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DCYOPmusic We plan to be there &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeling uneasy about Legion :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeelvsBabyface If that's the case, I want more followers to manage it :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeelvsBabyface Is there still no hope for a tabard tab? Transmog will not free up space for me :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cpt_ass @HeelvsBabyface Better to get it running properly before launch :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cpt_ass @HeelvsBabyface I've been seeing on youtube that Legion may not drop until September now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cpt_ass @HeelvsBabyface Good luck on heroic :) Aiming for Mythic as well?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cpt_ass @HeelvsBabyface I worry for the future more and more, I'm not mythic caliber, but only LFR on my server (Kirin Tor US, low pop)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cw_spn Don't see how you can possibly wrap up this storyline #mindblown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeelvsBabyface So Paragon is truly gone?  I heard that, but it seems so hard to believe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too little too late unless the jobs return to the States, but a great start. https://t.co/TaRbvfcwLL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeelvsBabyface What major raiding guilds are left in WOW?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Music Education is Not Prepared (Yet) to Lead Whole School Reform · https://t.co/UzXEl1eeY5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Anime_USA Is the program ready? And any additional room blocks at the hotel available yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SouL_TGN @YouTube Sasuke still treats her like an annoyance, makes you wonder why she is so hung up on him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SouL_TGN That would suck, can't see him dying so soon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just entered the Ultimate Crochet Giveaway! You should too:  http://t.co/jXOVLhrHuF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take Our Daughters and Sons to Work Day http://t.co/LJToFemVQO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help support DCYOP!: https://t.co/l1dKJyDMQi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoldRold stumbled acros you on deviantart and now hooked on a truth crystallized]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ViolinMyStyle Are you still playing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drumroll please...: http://t.co/zbpBqJXXWQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jarpad Just saw the finale, it's gonna be a long summer waiting to see what happens, until S11, have fun with fam and friends!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeartbrkLambo @OfficiallDre @SpoonsCHAMP Cheap Sunglasses Sale $24.99

@http://www.topgearsup2015.com http://t.co/juR2hcipuc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TVKEHOES @TRVPDOLLS @angelnicole1613 RayBan Sunglasses $24.99

@http://www.topgearsup2015.com http://t.co/xMaeqTBUH7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stupidking801 @Bezmelnitsin @BrooklynsDodger RayBan Sunglasses $24.99

@http://www.topgearsup2015.com http://t.co/onw9GKyzdm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MurielBowser @EliotHine @George_Noory Ray Ban Sunglasses only $24.99

@http://www.topgearsup2015.com http://t.co/7Mj9utg6Kv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cib110 @gotmefckedup23 @DuckinDitch RayBan Sunglasses $24.99

@http://www.topgearsup2015.com http://t.co/3MPjq4MVlr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@qzfrombooks @wealthydmo @SharpturnNet RayBan Sunglasses $24.99

@http://www.topgearsup2015.com http://t.co/n457sDTy1m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZodiacPartMatch @wooomeen @ClassyButNasty2 RayBan Sunglasses $24.99

@http://www.topgearsup2015.com http://t.co/5Mm0BLsEps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TommyWells @CharlesAllenW6 @cmdgrosso RayBan Sunglasses Sale $24.99

@http://www.topgearsup2015.com http://t.co/ugFhdtRx93]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sweeney_kate @MauryPrincipal @joeweedon Cheap Sunglasses Sale $24.99

@http://www.topgearsup2015.com http://t.co/ePVUbWchU9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SocialMedia_FB1 @OfficialHillel @SelfieInfo RayBan Sunglasses $24.99

@http://www.topgearsup2015.com http://t.co/NqVRjuIEwJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hulu @spaceapps @maurythinktank RayBan Sunglasses $24.99

@http://www.topgearsup2015.com http://t.co/2ikZCdcqXv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raybantwo @rayban_____24 @netflix RayBan Sunglasses $24.99

@http://www.topgearsup2015.com http://t.co/Zq0fvXboP9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Rah33m_ @Marlo_Davinci @THATZDC RayBan Sunglasses $24.99

@http://www.topgearsup2015.com http://t.co/lM96rpZkzF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrekBack @StationCDRKelly @eschoell RayBan Sunglasses $24.99

@http://www.topgearsup2015.com http://t.co/QXyMoOzFZ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Working on updating page with all completed projects :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eschoell @joeweedon @EliotHine @MayorBowser @CHPSPO @michaelalison Don't forget most of the windows in the building are sealed as well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you heard the latest?: http://t.co/Cq2zaMgBFQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The FREE Noontime Cantata Series is BACH!: http://t.co/9iQlAxcpI3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Anime_USA Thanks and can't wait to see everyone again :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Anime_USA have you placed the children 3 day passes for purchase yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DCYOPmusic Are we in session on Saturday?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>