<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattNippert Do we include rich Australians with NZ citzenship? Must be a few of those out there? Russ Crowe for example?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Use_ful_idiot @MatthewHootonNZ @ReaganWorld If you've been to mexico via the U.S. You'll know there are no check points heading into mexico]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattNippert @Upstreamism @VFHIVE have you read his book "zero to one", lays a pretty solid argument that most big businesses are anayway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there a place you can go to find a list of NZ citizens?  I want to see who else has meandered in unnoticed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattNippert @TheSpinoffTV If you're Hans then who's Chewbacca?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattNippert @TheSpinoffTV I'd take the Hans Solo reference anyday mate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattNippert @nzheraldbiz he's an interesting guy to be interested in NZ...where he goes Silicone Valley kind of follows...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattNippert @nzheraldbiz So what exactly does one as prominent as Thiel need to do to get citizenship and it fly completely under radar...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@foundmyfitness Hello from NZ! Any advice on what type of magnesium should I be supplementing with? I've been using liquid mg chloride]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PresidentALJ Theatricality and deception...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mr_orgue How long is that second season though? First season was so good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So my cousins been busy. Grandad would be proud! https://t.co/lPbiBB9po4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That "man in black" story arc in #Westworld almost broke me. Great casting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone should watch this just to give the bird to Trump https://t.co/yte5PClZUO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fit2fat2fit that's crazy, would have thought you would be way higher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shakey shakey in Lower Hutt #eqnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok @tferriss, lets see if this @FourSigmatic is what it's all cracked up to be!!! Had to import from Australia to g… https://t.co/t8BGF72QFM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mishviews @NZParliament @dpfdpf @robhosking I'm thinking police or defence force...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@y_naumann @MatthewHootonNZ Ours brought up miscarriage 5 mins into first class...nearly walked out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClintVSmith She ruined rap music for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamieTahana @PaulWil84104469 She's an egg bro.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agree a minister for construction is a damn good idea, but also think there should be a minister for housing... #cabinet #nzpol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dpfdpf I'm being lazy and should look it up, but how did Wood poll c.f. to actual outcome?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dpfdpf Because the polls are so accurate and reliable these days...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dickbicknell It's not possible you took this photo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@josiepagani, the voice of reason I needed to hear as I ponder leaving the ship as well. They don't make it easy...https://t.co/FFsXRNLp0D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesNokise Woody is a good foot shorter than Guy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The weirdest thing about JK's resignation nd then endorsement for English is that I sort of forgot English was a) still there b) is number2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrevorMallard hopefully late May, the roar will be over then, best time to hunt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewshubPolitics @LloydBurr @NewshubNZ is National shifting to the left,Labour shifting too far left or is Leggett just MP or bust?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd have to say I would go @MittRomney over Patreas for Secretary of State any day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ValerieAdams84 Hope they pay their visitors levy...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New cordon in Lower Hutt on the chamber of Commerce Building. #eqnz https://t.co/RCZKm4Ntu7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeromeChandra #stretch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DuncanGarnerNZ @ToniStreet @RadioLIVENZ Don't tell Brian Tamaki...volcanoes will start heating up...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN @GraemeEdgeler New Zealand farming has changed.  20 years ago these would have been sheep.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrevorMallard How did it hold up?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dickbicknell Bro! You boys alright!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatthewHootonNZ How did the polls not see this? Why are they so inaccurate now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamespeshaw they don't like being called underclass.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PresidentALJ is this lead up to his second campaign? I think I saw a trailer.  Why does he do it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PresidentALJ So much wrong with everything in politics at the moment mate. Dark times. Dark times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PresidentALJ Hills by a nose.  Trump will go savage. Small riots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PresidentALJ My damn twitter feed is dominated by AJ tweets on yesterdays match.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PresidentALJ Less rugby tweets bro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@avancenz Good. Not all businesses make massive margins, they shouldn't be taxed/levied for finding solutions to stay competitive...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nzlabour wouldn't it be wiser to offer incentives to NZ businesses that do train kiwi's in skill shortage areas rather than levy them...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@avancenz They should be offering incentives to businesses to train not penalising them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always a great night!Great mates, great whisky and great tweed! @ginnyandersen @TrevorMallard @jacindaardern… https://t.co/HZKLPAVRcQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonMHamm @DuncanGarnerNZ @Jess2437 damn, I tht this was going to be an interview with Don Draper. Adam's worth more than Draper now though!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jo_moir the Pacific Putin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When did Crispin Glover enter the Auckland mayoral race?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fit2fat2fit @PlsReplyImmaFan that's insane]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Campbell_Barry @wikileaks what time is the drop?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wilderpeople @WorldOfTaika This is awesome. Loved Footrot Flats as a kid!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@y_naumann You know you're the one who has push right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@y_naumann 'Dad Bod' kicking in early?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@haydsofnz A good leader provides for the people. A bad leader denies the people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DuncanGarnerNZ who cares...they're child sex offenders...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now, about those trade agreements... https://t.co/sty98EHM7t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cjbrom Yes. They're called toffee milks and you can but them by the box at Moore Wilsons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeromeChandra That's next level mate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alicesoapbox @TrevorMallard @MatthewHootonNZ @barrysoper If the Loveridge conspiracy isn't true it should be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kirst_law @jonogaluszka It's probably his "good shirt"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm all for a predator free NZ.  Just leave my precious wild deer, wild boar and thar alone.  #nzpol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeirLeslie @MatthewHootonNZ @nzlabour Come on then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatthewHootonNZ  @ClintVSmith He has a good point though, you literally said @nzlabour would crash the market 50% last week...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patquin Do you think we'll see him rise again Pat?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatthewHootonNZ You could spend a billion on the paperwork for pipes and roads...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClintVSmith big problem for us is finding skilled staff, we r training apprentices bt it will take time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClintVSmith As someone who works in construction I've never seen it this busy, not sure if it includes apartments bt its full on out there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patquin Not certain on Brexit. Love Boris though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MatthewHootonNZ @lailaharre I don't understand this politics thing...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@y_naumann It's terrible right? I checked FB after putting the kids to bed and it ruined everything.  Was so gutted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leeflockton Hi Lee, make sure you are on the 'log in' screen not the 'sign in' screen.  Pm me your number and i will call you :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FranPaulKennedy @cjbrom I'm a fan but let's be honest here...she was a news reader not an investigative journalist...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattNippert Housing bubble?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonogaluszka Isn't it ironic?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think this guy would make to watch soccer. https://t.co/Vf9Jt6ZPBz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the App I developed to help New Zealand Carpentry Apprentices to organise notes and get qualified faster: https://t.co/AhvN6epref]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emmawehipeihana @GuyonEspiner @NzMorningReport Cracking interview this morning! So what was NZ Bus's profit last year?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonogaluszka @MOABEER Mint julip? How James Bond of you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I remember Wise Park being 30 people deep around the sidelines when #JonahLomu made his first appearance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another member of the Connery as Bond appreciation society. Love it.Verity Johnson: How Bond ruined me https://t.co/ndaOWuWWAm via @nzherald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonogaluszka Bro sand a bit off it - add it to your brew - call it "The Wall IPA"...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Richie McCaw and Dan Carter just defeated the dark side and brought balance to the force.... #RWC2015 #AllBlacks #AllBlackEverything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laurenjanecross It sucks doesn't it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it time to retire my 2002Tui Vic Uni Orientation t-shirt? Nah, she's a few more lawn mows in her yet. @TuiBeer https://t.co/b5F3eklV6L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MountRuapehu younknow you're getting old when retro day gear doesn't look that retro to you...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patquin just got mine last week...massive pain in the ass.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patrickgowernz Religion and politics...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patquin Say g'day to the big guy and his tribe for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katieabradford Offenders should have thought about that before they violated the victim's rights...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am reading "Zen and the Art of Motorcycle Maintenance". Bit of a slow burner so far...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KimDotcom Have aliens visited earth?  I want o believe 😀]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RodOramNZ Are there marketable health benefits/advantages to NZ grass feed milk solids c.f. Feedlot produced solids from the U.S.?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just learnt more about nz's dairy industry from @RodOramNZ article in the @SundayStarTimes than anything else I've read in the past 2 yrs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fit2fat2fit @tferriss @ShawnModel Ferris needs to get you on his podcast!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mad Men's final credits should have rolled to Bowie's "The man who sold the world". #madmen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mundens @mr_orgue Um, did he really say that? WTF?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>