<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you tweet about the white GOP guy, @VP, because you don't know a single black in history? #penceblackhistory… https://t.co/VIjAkbIOMT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenjySarlin PUTIN:  RETURN TO THE MOTHER SHIP, NOW.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jbendery My guess is he was called back to Russia the Mother Ship.  Hope they OJ white Bronco chase him!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeMyGod He's been called back to Russia the Mother Ship!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricBoehlert @whca He's been called back to Russia the Mother Ship?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brianbeutler Is this like the white Bronco chase or more legit following?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterbakernyt @lizzieohreally Called back to Russia the Mother Ship?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheFix He's been called back to Russia the Mother Ship?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheFix Can we follow it like the OJ chase?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterbakernyt @lizzieohreally Can we follow it like the OJ chase?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RoguePOTUSStaff With a useless 14 billion dollar wall planned, we weren't under the delusion that Trump/WH/GOP are fiscally responsible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pourmecoffee @jeffzeleny POTUS is mistaken to think anyone cares. Americans can't name current crew, let alone distinguish his white dudes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarbaraBoxer @JoeMyGod Also when he tries to wink seductively at Ivanka and she tells him once again, "No, Daddy!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@juliemason R we never going to revisit that Russia likely conspired/worked w/ Team Trump to win election? WH must be thrilled we moved on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How happy is the Kremlin West (White House/Trump campaign) that no one is talking about how they teamed/conspired w/ Russia to win election?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DLoesch See video of Sessions asking Yates at her hearing if AG has a duty to say no to the Prez if his ask is improper/unconst./unlawful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DLoesch Isn't that the ? asked of every AG nominee though - essentially will you stand up and not execute on an unconst. order of the Prez?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AriFleischer aren't we questioning AG nominee Sessions about his ability to stay independent and stand up to Trump if law violated?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenHowe I think Javanka may have checked out due to the path.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahkateellis @glaad thank you on behalf of my family!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EricLuedtke @JennyFZucker @LarryHogan I got thru easily around 9am this morning. Try tomorrow everyone!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is. cc: @SenatorCardin @RepCummings @GovernorHogan @LarryHogan https://t.co/miobaMIIwI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is so very disheartening. Shame on @Reince. https://t.co/OgkJTyawav]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretty shocked at @Reince. His active part in this will go down shamefully in history. Thought his ethics/morals/in… https://t.co/rrPCvwpKCC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He has now and @LarryHogan lack of courage was astounding. Shame. https://t.co/VuJsMoxOo3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This reminds me of the @LarryHogan statement today, in that it contains letters and punctuation. https://t.co/0eHCH6ibGm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimsciutto @MicahGrimes @MarkHertling That's always their go to. But it's the press, the liberals, the world. It's you not us @WhiteHouse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not living up to image he cultivates. Opposite --&gt;lacking spine, courage, leadership, humanity. Horrible statement… https://t.co/oELNbGX7Ec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @LarryHogan, save you time. Federal Judge already ruled on it. Very likely violated Constitutional Rights. Now… https://t.co/kEhBQsAA3z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YoungDemsofMD @MDSenate @LarryHogan @Reporterroblang no spine, courage, humanity, leadership. not living up to cultivated image.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonAbbruzzese @brianstelter @SarahPalinUSA @TheLastRefuge2 I'dve thought GOP would be unhinged @ US Prez violating Const rites 8 days in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Reporterroblang @LarryHogan @DanRodricks Gov. Hogan doesn't live up to image he cultivates - statement lacks courage leadership humanity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Reporterroblang @LarryHogan OUTRAGEOUS, I'm absolutely fuming at this horrible spineless statement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AliVelshi @KFILE is Kelly the Trump appt or Obama's person?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your next host of the #Emmys, 97 yr old Pundit Nanny. @TheFix http://t.co/PXitmQXbvJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billmaher Pundit Nanny would like to be on your show if there are no stairs to the green room! http://t.co/CDYc4cWmx9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HillaryClinton You have one vote if this 97 yr old's pacemaker doesn't give out! #punditnanny http://t.co/wnqjABxoog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We have a prediction! #punditnanny @HillaryClinton http://t.co/kIk4Wg8fs6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introducing 97 yr old Pundit Nanny! @maddow @HillaryClinton @TheEllenShow @chrislhayes @Lawrence http://t.co/KEysyhj9AY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[97-year old Pundit Nanny. Pt. 6 @maddow @TheEllenShow @chrislhayes @Lawrence http://t.co/SHccU8giIQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[97-year old Pundit Nanny. Pt. 5 @maddow @TheEllenShow @chrislhayes @Lawrence http://t.co/MB2j6U5e7g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[97-year old Pundit Nanny. Pt. 4 @maddow @TheEllenShow @chrislhayes @Lawrence http://t.co/eVDqj3SFnG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[97-year old Pundit Nanny. Pt. 3 @maddow @TheEllenShow @chrislhayes @Lawrence http://t.co/ilOfxvmBO5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[97-year old Pundit Nanny. Pt. 2 @maddow @TheEllenShow @chrislhayes @Lawrence http://t.co/s4CpuKHKdW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[97 year old Pundit Nanny. Pt. 1 @Lawrence @maddow @TheEllenShow @chrislhayes http://t.co/Lfq7YMxXs9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AllisonBeckman I'm locked out of her acct but @NannySez wanted to tweet u: Wow! @AllisonBeckman's team won all games 4 the gold! Way to go!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Support Hi, I have 2 accts tied to the same email (one I operate for my grandmother) and I can't get into my g-ma's. I've tried everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NFL, NHL, MLB Jerseys Online, Factory Sale Direclty, 80% off !     http://t.co/BEjxxmnh7U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oakley Sunglasses Official Website, Amazing Price!          http://t.co/mw3OJF7OZB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ray Ban Sunglasses, Factory Sale Direclty, only $25 !         http://t.co/YQkgrpJ1Yj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oakley Sunglasses, 3 PCS Free Shipping, only $16 !          http://t.co/mpdIlOaCkd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tiffany Jewelry, 100%  Authentic! Amazing Price !        http://t.co/QqmGFAlEBm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UGG Boots Online, 100%  Authentic, Amazing Price !       http://t.co/md7PY2EHQ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AllisonBeckman @sarena_sarena awesome. we're close by if she needs us!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScaryMommy yeah we came home w 4 boxes of the mix! why has no one copied that in every state in the nation?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScaryMommy oh and Cafe du Monde with those beignets!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScaryMommy Just back myself &amp; found out at NOLA Cochon Butcher Mr. B's Bistro The Gumbo Shop Commander's &amp; The Joint! Not getting on scale!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AllisonBeckman ooooh that sounds good. fun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AllisonBeckman oh I want to go to a food truck festival! Whatdya eat??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AllisonBeckman Happy Birthday! Have fun today and stay on the road! Love you tons and tons. And tons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AllisonBeckman "Sometimes good things fall apart so better things can fall together." -Marilyn Monroe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AllisonBeckman I wanted to FB that but forgot. Will do it now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donnabrazile not according to another guy on CNN tonight. Said Ramsey's is full of shit. Notice Ramsey 911 call doesn't say he got her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donnabrazile @mediaite CNN reporting another guy did the rescue and what Ramsey claimed he did. Ramsey's 911 call is consistent with that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RichelleCarey CNN reporting that another guy is saying he did what Ramsey is claiming and Ramsey came after all was done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@politico fix ur md question 6 numbers and I might not lose total respect for u. They r mixed up w the dream act nos.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @politico you have the md dream act nos. mixed up with the marriage equality nos. fix it now! Ur misleading thousands.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanFosterNRO but agreed it's a romney win b/c he didn't make a huge gaffe or sound like a total moron on FP per usual.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanFosterNRO So few people clear that he won is a loss. But agreed to some extent. He did so by playing Democrat though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanFosterNRO Not the math that I understand. That's like saying Mitt is up in the polls 55% to Obama's 10%, w/ 25% undecided. It's tied up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanFosterNRO @angerfarm you just gave 100% of the undecideds to Mitt?  WTF.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah-ha! I'm getting Romney-ese now. If he says he loves it, he's getting ready to massacre it. #bigbird #cars #teachers #women #debates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mitt Romney - I love cars. I love teachers.
Ann Romney - I love women.
#hmm #debates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is gonna blow my mind if again it appears that Romney is talking the entire time yet the time clock has Obama with more time. #debates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can someone please mention New Zealand?  #chinachinachina #debates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big bird, binders, bayonets. Memes that start with B are popular. Just saying. #debates #horsesstartwithHthough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bob: What is the greatest threat to the future of the US? Obama: China. Mitt: Gay marriage. #debates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm really agreeing with Romney.  It would be bad for America if Pakistan falls apart.  Totally, dude.  #debates #noshitsherlockromney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JRubinBlogger Biased much?  It's kinda gross.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why not draft Ann Romney's dressage horse?  #debates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plus there was a whole movie called War Horse.  I didn't see it, but apparently that horse warred.  #debates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really think we should have more horses in the military.  Look at the dog that was instrumental in killing Obama.  #sorryPETA #debates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aw shit.  Sarcastic-Obama, hello.  #debates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GovernorOMalley Why are you letting him say time and time again that MA schools were number 1?  Incorrect, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AriFleischer Better than Romney's bizarre "puppy love" look at Obama that he is in all of the time.  He isn't looking away either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Romney just said 30 vague things that no one can disagree with.  Ok.  #standbyourallies #haveastrongmilitary #standforpeace #debates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is Romney's side of the debate table set at 20 degrees hotter than Obama's?  #sweating #unfair #debates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Romney: Showing more care for women in the Middle East than for U.S. women.  #debates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Annoying corrector-rule-mongerer Romney is back!  #debates #gross]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DLoesch How was he wrong on Behnghazi?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama blowing his wad right now.  Nicely done.  #debates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advice for Mitt Romney: Don't smile during this debate.  Kinda weird.  #debates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We can't kill our way out of this mess." -said no Republican ever until now  #debates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It always appears as if Dick Cheney accidentally shot a hole through Mitt Romney's American Flag pin, but that must not be it.  #debates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How many questions in do I have to wait before I do my joke: "Why are all the questions about foreign policy??!"  #debates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope they have the defibrillator handy!  #debates #bobsheiffer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Romney to American women: Imma treat you just like I treated Candy Crowley, not that she can fit in my binder.  #debates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have to say I do think Romney sat nicely on the bar stool.  #debates  #practicemakesperfect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anamariecox It's Glorraine to Mitt Romney.  So you can go with a friend and be Lorraine and she can be Glorraine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those disposable cameras must be @CNN party favors! Hope they got little kazoos too.  #debates]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>