<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Ireland is expected to get 'large majority' of Apple's €13 billion unpaid tax b - https://t.co/hY5IZClEO1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Bank of Ireland warns customers over 'smishing' text scam  - https://t.co/CWTsTYhiFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Nurse who took €100 from MS patient found guilty of professional misconduct - https://t.co/DMDqm97HZa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: There's 'Tinder for orangutans' now - https://t.co/CCZnBSGEUg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Irish author Sebastian Barry scoops major Book of the Year prize - https://t.co/v2No2BWGyq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Austria promises ban on face veil in public places - https://t.co/j6C2RHlPg2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Celtic Tiger's Metro North likely to be fast-tracked  - https://t.co/4YKGYaajDf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'If ever there was a sign that the boom is back, it’s vultures building student - https://t.co/mq23lToMQK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Poll: Are you planning to attend an anti-Trump protest? - https://t.co/Z3y7WezC2B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Here's exactly what the Attorney General said before Donald Trump fired her - https://t.co/6VDLY4oPKt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Angela Kerins loses her case for damages against the Public Accounts Committee - https://t.co/GBDZ8TV1vX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: The secretary of Nazi leader Joseph Goebbels has died at 106 - https://t.co/tIhVbp1N1t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Greek police probe string of deaths in migrant camp - https://t.co/36K19LNveG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Court of Appeal dismisses 'Slab' Murphy's appeal against tax conviction - https://t.co/mkhr7cs5Yo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Poll: Should smoking be banned on restaurant and café terraces? - https://t.co/yPkWJeeeUE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: One person turned away at Dublin Airport since Trump's travel ban  - https://t.co/fcxg563Al2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Mother and child killer's life sentence appeal dismissed  - https://t.co/fGVlP3bhL4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Fianna Fáil is the most popular party in the country - https://t.co/VivwgnVJzj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Calls for Enda Kenny to cancel White House trip over Trump's refugee ban  - https://t.co/0AyFmyJeCs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Woman who threatened gardaí with blood-filled syringes in Dublin city centre avo - https://t.co/TI4igHyg0S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Refugees detained at airports after Trump bans them from entering US  - https://t.co/Y7yGTdWfIv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Gardaí seize cocaine worth €35,000 in wooded area in Laois - https://t.co/fhlTsGSkfl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Mark Zuckerberg drops controversial lawsuits seeking to buy Hawaiian land - https://t.co/7ZjtkJoPO9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Corn diet turning French hamsters into deranged cannibals which eat their young - https://t.co/9mE6GSX7RT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: A complete list of the sharks in Irish waters has just been published - https://t.co/NuFzFl7TrI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Why do people object to Lidl and Aldi in their towns? - https://t.co/nH8RUI76ST]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: New service means you can now track your passport application online - https://t.co/X6cViA90d4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Funding approved for 83 new houses to address homeless crisis - https://t.co/t1E6nZImUv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Dozens ordered to leave Cabinteely hostel due to 'fire and health risk' - https://t.co/Qb1Ng6qArx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Know Your Sport? Take our weekly quiz - https://t.co/g5gPLKbQot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Almost five million journeys were made on city bike schemes in 2016 - https://t.co/ppoGK5sDAl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Mortgage approval rates have shot up by nearly 30% in a year - https://t.co/zLGVeQ5d07]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Home care: The way we care for the elderly could be about to change - https://t.co/NSzQ2pY1eT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: No grass. No nappies. Here is a definitive list of what you can recycle - https://t.co/zGPGhTYyQy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Trump will publish a weekly list of crimes committed by illegal immigrants - https://t.co/Mkl3zVIvVv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Farmers furious at SuperValu 'stunt' which gives away free carrots and potatoes - https://t.co/vGmeJaPiWE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Man with 483 convictions sentenced to 18 months for road crash which killed teen - https://t.co/0Xmg33us2q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Defence department justifies sale of Government jet for €418k - https://t.co/eaWWAtMEIT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Mexican President cancels US trip over border wall row with Trump - https://t.co/h7nY701OuE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Irish Water issued a small business a bill of over €200,000 for 3 months - https://t.co/9jyY0gw0wi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Irish scientists' breakthrough could lead to virus immunity - https://t.co/inDyXIVMfX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'People are tired of beef-or-salmon': 6 expert tips on planning a modern wedding - https://t.co/LoLlyiJSCi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Babestation changes phone number after Westport residents plagued with calls - https://t.co/BCu3Asufam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Poll: Do you think a wall along the US-Mexican border will actually be built?  - https://t.co/nUguovyz9d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Trump plan for a wall in Clare slammed by international experts - https://t.co/FYYduL07vS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Independent person to review new details from Stardust fire tragedy - https://t.co/7qnse4skCv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: End of heavy schoolbags? Students welcome eBooks to classrooms - https://t.co/TY8DuAbKBi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: A large gorse fire has broken out on the Dublin Mountains this evening - https://t.co/Cpph5Ulsxv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Quiz: How well do you know the book 1984? - https://t.co/PyNNCOnhdP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Man who distracted tourists as accomplices robbed them jailed for three years - https://t.co/W9N9BTdazU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Is it time Ireland had its own Independence Day? - https://t.co/t8oCWOyBi6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Trump issues executive order for wall to be built along Mexican border - https://t.co/g1aXjbMuu4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Career coach: 'Why over 70% of students drop out of first year in some courses' - https://t.co/D75fK2IkAW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Poll: Would you go public if you won the Euromillions jackpot? - https://t.co/nqfB8BOg7P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Over 300k belonging to criminal gang discovered in woman's home following search - https://t.co/QAx4z4kB7R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'My 12-year-old son's bag weighs 1.8 stone': How to tackle heavy school bags - https://t.co/sMl17e8d3P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Five people died in prison custody last year - https://t.co/ZX9sqYhVUQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Trump takes first step towards building Mexican wall  - https://t.co/xN7MNZuqo5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Gardaí stop driver five times over legal alcohol limit  - https://t.co/WZmC0kCNM5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Rory McIlroy reveals he can't even run at the moment, let alone swing a golf clu - https://t.co/OHZIlCSqEP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Pro-life group wants to raise €18,000 to fund Facebook page targeting Irish tee - https://t.co/xYFeqS4kRu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Raping someone when they are asleep will now be explicitly illegal - https://t.co/cdIAwOt5jC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Someone in Ireland has won €88 million in the Euromillions tonight - https://t.co/BqWQHX3yN6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Here's what $20 million hidden under a bed looks like - https://t.co/170K35EBUP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: The Irish Girl Guides is to start allowing transgender children into their ranks - https://t.co/edwVHTnHbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Explainer: What happens now the UK parliament will have to vote on Brexit? - https://t.co/iakhVHzVkW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Apartment owners could face 'up to €30 million' bill to bring complex up to reg - https://t.co/mAcEMu5MIK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Controversial Roman Catholic group Opus Dei names its new leader - https://t.co/qCcEoMLTK4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Six die in helicopter crash close to site of Italy avalanche  - https://t.co/hVtOvNBp0Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Poll: Should people with a free travel pass have to pay a small charge for it? - https://t.co/Nmxd1bpnVQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Apartment owners could face 'up to €30 million' bill to bring complex up to reg - https://t.co/mAcEMuno7k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unfair Irish Car Tax Law - Sign the Petition! https://t.co/UVlrThlDd9 via @Change]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Here are the policy decisions Donald Trump made over the weekend - https://t.co/xir9sIujPu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Dublin primary school badly damaged in early morning fire - https://t.co/Qsfv7J8No2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: From a home in Wales to a camper van in Dublin to realise the UFC dream - https://t.co/eZfyrQvtxz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Demand for crèches: For the first time, there are over 100,000 children in free  - https://t.co/UK2zAATrfj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Poll: Do you support yesterday's anti-Trump marches across the world? - https://t.co/NsAZKus15E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Women's March Dublin attracts thousands as part of global protest against Trump - https://t.co/YcZuH1vLT7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'The whole street is dying' - Moore Street traders feel they're being wiped out - https://t.co/LbfYB5PDsA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'If this many people were dying in another way, there’d be war over it' - https://t.co/m3RUjGDqX5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: No arrests made as cannabis worth €37.5 million found in tractor parts - https://t.co/JBrgrcCEDm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Poll: Should Dublin open a drug injecting centre? - https://t.co/ZntrFtOk2i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Hopes for new group of survivors at Italian mountain hotel following avalanche - https://t.co/kdLwDPMJel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@parrylel Hmm, fully support bilingualism but they might at least feature the Welsh in a different font!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Irish banks have frozen Al-Qaeda assets of over €1 million - https://t.co/1Zfw7nJjNP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Poll: Will you be watching President Donald Trump's inauguration? - https://t.co/dfuuDTXrE6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Owners of Savoy cinema say screen size won't be changed - https://t.co/buLMauwkQg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Obama cuts the sentences of 330 drug crime inmates on his last day as President - https://t.co/PNNcaCV6Ic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'Not a single patient in the building': PAC to investigate €7 million overspend - https://t.co/mMFCdxXbLe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Former manager admits to stealing €4.5 million from singer Alanis Morissette - https://t.co/eKRSJQPtLz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: NASA scientists to spend eight months in Hawaiian dome for 'Mars simulation' - https://t.co/4UHOrjr7n3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Czech man wanted for deliberately spreading HIV arrested in Thai resort - https://t.co/EuMry29RTl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Case of BSE found in Irish cow - but 'no public health risks' - https://t.co/BYeEaCgsaP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: How British and German media reacted very differently to May's speech - https://t.co/yS01YMpiwJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Homecare for the elderly a 'priority' in wake of Brendan Courtney documentary - https://t.co/3qFQGXMLjx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Department of Social Protection overpaid welfare recipients by €420 million ove - https://t.co/7OV2uudGCI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Man receives lifetime ban from keeping animals after pig "eaten alive" by dogs - https://t.co/KKNsTuvOju]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie:  QUIZ: How Good Are Your People Skills, Really?  - https://t.co/sSaF5bJ640]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Unite hits out at RTÉ coverage, says building was offered for homeless accommoda - https://t.co/KhopaCGwGy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Gardaí appeal for help finding Dublin man missing since before Christmas - https://t.co/OH6qZM3FDT]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>