<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@xGrumpyOldManx seems to have backfired then. @ezlusztig was satirising Nawaz et al. Christian terrorists presented as lone wolves,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xGrumpyOldManx what's your point? Your link shows you're 7x more likely to be killed by a white terrorist than a Muslim terrorist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Uptomyknees imagine these words spoken by a person with a normal level of confidence. You'd think they were nervously babbling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think he might actually be threatening to nuke DC. https://t.co/D4Vg0fyVNA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xGrumpyOldManx It really is. Since 9/11, right-wing extremists killed more Americans in US than Islamic extremists

https://t.co/PpvUL8vkY4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@TimRunsHisMouth Only weeks ago America was the leader of the free world. Now they want to be judged by the same standards as Sudan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovely to see Olivia Colman is trending just because it's her birthday and everyone thinks she'd be the perfect Doctor Who.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine actually lacking the ability to feel shame. https://t.co/gS79LjqjVO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dogrob tell that to Giuliani.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doesn't the tone of these alt/rogue accounts seem a bit off? And so similar?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seeing a lot of dodgy looking sources and unverified alt accounts on my timeline. Feel like we're walking into a disinfo trap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Glinner Mensch is, I think, about 3 weeks in to an epic nervous breakdown. Still, treat these alt/rogue accounts with caution.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'd think these supposed not-racist Trump supporters would look around their own ranks and figure something was up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RepRickLarsen what have you done to make a stand? Tweet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GailSimone is that a type of German sausage?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Ed_Miliband why can't it be the timeline where you are the prime minister?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theresa May, like all politicians not making a stand against the #MuslimBan, is a careerist, immoral, selfish coward who believes in nothing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's insane, evil #MuslimBan is a humanitarian catastrophe. So sad to see racists cheering it on, and the UK gov… https://t.co/aIAsfYwkpA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DARKROOSTER1 I literally do not understand how this can be happening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ex Neo-Nazi weighs in on punching Nazis.

https://t.co/6g4EPYtHXl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just realised Trump is getting his powers from a cursed monkey paw. He can have anything he wants but it always turns to shit in his hands.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PostConservativ I guess that's a 'no' then or you'd have caught my point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PostConservativ ever read any Isaiah Berlin during that fancy education of yours?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PostConservativ what a waste of an education- and you'd think you'd have some basic knowledge of demographics from travelling so much]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PostConservativ also the US is not a white 'homeland'. My apartment is older than your country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PostConservativ @NataliaAntonova who's in charge shouldn't come down to something as superficial as race.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PostConservativ do you ever worry that your racism is just a simple way to rationalise things you don't understand and unexamined biases?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PostConservativ you're American? Fuck me. Have you read the inscription on the Statue of Liberty?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love will win. Although in a way it's a shame we have to beat them with love, beating them with sticks would have been way more satisfying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PostConservativ you want to live in a state where ethnic tensions cause daily bloodshed?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PostConservativ may I interrupt your furious googling (bet you tried Iceland!) to ask you to concede your "every other nation on Earth" BS?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AbiWilks Amazing how you three (and others) are always written off by people who don't actually read your stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PostConservativ So? There are ethnic minorities in all of those countries that are fully enfranchised. You've yet to name an ethno-state.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what happens when you sack all the smart people. https://t.co/u2lgwslYZk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PostConservativ it took me all of 2 mins to look that up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PostConservativ Israel is 20% Arab. Cameroon has 250 distinct ethnic groups. Saudi Arabia is 33% foreign nationals and 10% Afro-Asian.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck me this is the funniest thing i've seen all year. https://t.co/NWSfpD6LsC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PostConservativ Even feudal Europe didn't have ethnostates. Even ancient Rome wasn't an ethnostate. You're living in a racist fantasy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FreeSargon. Ideally, into the sea. https://t.co/z5tT4ZjDP9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AbiWilks Same in Singapore: welfare is the bugbear of nearly everyone, but every discussion about it eventually leads to race.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonnaSotoMorett we're not going to convince racists that they don't have popular support. The argument comes off as deluded to them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonnaSotoMorett don't think we should use language to try to hide how popular racism is. We're way past trying to stuff the genie back in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonnaSotoMorett it's a term that goes back over a century and has always had connotations of racism through association with fascism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@steph93065 @robert737373737 @jaketapper @Stonewall_77 @CarmineZozzora @LindaSuhler @carrieksada @2ALAW is Fox News the entire media now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know that #FF isn't a thing anymore, but you really should follow @MSF_Sea if you need your faith in humanity restored.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a kid I watched tape of Hitler denouncing compassion and wondered how that could happen. Now I see people do it every day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mfrost11 is this legit?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BM_Damo a) racism was found to be the greatest predictor of voting Leave b) the past months have shown Leavers are beyond reasoning with]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mrmarkmillar "I was just pretending to say silly things to bait you into thinking I was daft. Haha, joke's on you, somehow..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New truth condition for 2017: if a member of the Trump family said it, it's unquestionably true. https://t.co/tUH9KWZaQT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday: "Punching Nazis is bad!"
Today: "Torturing suspected enemy combatants is good!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MartinDaubney Illiberal tweeters think the role of the state is just to manage the global economy, and never act morally.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@preetbasson well then you must know less than nothing, since I had to correct several of your factual errors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@preetbasson amazing how you people twist away from every argument you lose and just end up saying stuff everyone agrees with.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@preetbasson hacks are journalists. if you're not white then you're even dumber than i thought.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@preetbasson why do you care? your guy wants to do it all over again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@preetbasson "let us be white supremacist bigots in peace or we'll keep electing tyrants! Don't question us or we'll bring down democracy!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@preetbasson scurry back to your alternative fact safe space then. Sorry for throwing history at you, didn't realise how weak your ideas are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@preetbasson do you not follow the news? Congress passed a law to prevent Obama closing Gitmo. https://t.co/40daSWvRRu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@preetbasson Like his 2009 executive order to end torture? https://t.co/o3n44rLQV2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@preetbasson at what point does it stop being 'fake outrage'? why aren't people allowed to oppose and get back on with their lives?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@preetbasson Obama and Clinton ended torture. No evidence it happened under Bill Clinton either. Torture is a GOP pastime.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@preetbasson what do the left need to do? Quit their jobs and become full time protesters?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@preetbasson what about the thousands who do work for Amnesty and Stop the War, and the millions who donate?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@preetbasson where are you getting your news? Obama tried to close gitmo but was frustrated by GOP house. Left have always fought torture.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@preetbasson I remember when Fox News was the pro-Bush, pro-torture Iraq war cheerleader. It was the left that opposed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@preetbasson You can't blame people for going on with their lives. What's the alternative? Not everyone can afford to work for Amnesty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@preetbasson we marched in the biggest global protests ever over the Iraq war, the Bush admin and torture. The left always opposed this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@preetbasson then how is outrage over something agreed to be barbaric and despicable "Fake Outrage"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@preetbasson waterboarding is torture. Torture is illegal both domestically and internationally under the Geneva convention.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just waiting for Nick Hancock to turn out to be an utter twat for the hat-trick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@2010LeeHurst your torturer is trying to extract information, but doesn't know what that info is. Victims just say anything to make it stop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@THETXEMBASSY who calls themselves 'alt left'? Who says Russian election interference involved casting illegal votes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheYoungHag I prefer the Paxman approach: keep asking the same question until you get a yes or no answer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think she's finally lost it. https://t.co/KFueBTtuGU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Legalise punching Nazis. Just a small concession from the state monopoly on violence, and an easy solution to a terrible problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a 33 year old man who compulsively corrects people about the minutiae of kids movies. STOP GETTING STAR WARS WR… https://t.co/c8cQRlOuuB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@casersatz Already in the last movie the force had 'awakened' and there was only one jedi left.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warren Ellis on punching Nazis. https://t.co/JCvF443r0q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheYoungHag I'm sure he could argue provocation. Hey- maybe we all could.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what Trump sees when he reads Twitter.

https://t.co/VtD4CQeVkV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine what these people would be saying if Obama hadn't spent two terms at war, and instead the al-Qaeda leadersh… https://t.co/9rjJA7kcZi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what Trump sees on his twitter feed. It's like Stepford Wives.
https://t.co/VtD4CQeVkV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then why did you... but what... huh? https://t.co/Fvx1CqxjUa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the fuck is a 'safe space'? I have no idea anymore. https://t.co/Za5lc6Ue8z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterboghossian full epistemic relativism is actually pretty rare. A few fringe nutters and academics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterboghossian Conway's bullshit suddenly belongs to the entire right now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nope it's because you're a prick. https://t.co/Kq9P5YFhCO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ContraPoints we don't prefer it, it's just easier. In power we shatter back into a million tiny agendas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crowmagnone that's an extreme epistemic relativism. There is a real world with objective facts, true whether anyone believes them or not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RandomHero30 never happen. Scotland isn't full of whiny pussies like America. Wouldn't fall in line behind a bully.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterboghossian so Nazis aren't objectively odious? Are there no moral truths then?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Armando Iannucci on Donald Trump: 'This is the best moment, isn't it?'

https://t.co/qp37A7GKRu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RandomHero30 this is just another exaggerated threat you're scared of way out of proportion. https://t.co/4ZXonU6twk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RandomHero30 you can be arrested for inciting violence. There's no 'anti-Islamic tweet' law.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RandomHero30 they tolerate everything except intolerance, right? And like, harm to your physical wellbeing. What monsters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RandomHero30 step out of your bubble sometime. I know they've programmed you to treat all opposing ideas with scorn, but try.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RandomHero30 no you're thinking of Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PennyRed I think you might have just found a crucial weapon for the coming fight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trumpets:

All the bad things I've heard about people I hate are true, but everything they're saying about people I like is #FakeNews]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>