<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@rodmickleburgh @JenStDen no Rod. City has/continues to advocate on bc assessment changes: tax based on existing, not potential zoning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SunCivicLee  says farewell to City Hall by sharing his favorite #vanpoli stories with senior management team https://t.co/sh1GlkLeDj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good to hear PM Trudeau speak at @FCM_online about the urgency of dealing with fentanyl crisis; how it’s a national… https://t.co/T7NgYYX8wc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@MayorGregor speaks to PM Trudeau about huge impact fentanyl crisis is having on Vancouver’s first responders.… https://t.co/E6S0woUXdB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@MayorGregor speaks to PM Trudeau about fentanyl crisis and the need for more federal gov intervention #vanpoli https://t.co/1C41vDGzY6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How quickly we forget #vanpoli polls....@MayorGregor approval rating up 10 points since 2014 https://t.co/otceor702V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FYI for #vanpoli, the City was covering the Park Board costs for opening warming centers during cold snap. Not coming out of Parks budget]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In middle of longest cold stretch in 50 years, 2000+ visits to City's overnight emergency warming centers. https://t.co/zS20bjbg4M #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikePHager @VanCourierNews bring back the good news! More K and K, pls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For context: the 0.5% additional property tax to deal with fentanyl OD crisis = extra $11 for single family home, $4 for strata #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CMHC last week: Vancouver housing supply "lacking." CMHC today: Vancouver supply at record levels https://t.co/oZ0DNmFkxs #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your photo shows a clear road MT @604commuter: incompetent @MayorGregor did not send trucks to clear roads #vanpoli https://t.co/qZq3tjIwNt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CMHC says Metro Van's response to housing supply is "lacking", but their data shows record levels of housing starts… https://t.co/NaEd6igRbd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big win for transit riders RT@VanMayorsOffice: Phase 1 = 10% bus, 15% handyDART, 20% sky train increases across metro #vancouver  #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“I was proud when the Prime Minister was at COP21 and said Canada is back, climate leadership is back” - @MayorGregor #vanpoli #stopkm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Let’s call on the federal government to do the right thing, to make the right decision on climate leadership” @Mayorgregor #stopKM #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@loxyisme I was much more youthful in 2008 https://t.co/daGRYLzjs9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why empty homes tax at 1%? B/c when added to the current residential prop tax, it's equivalent to the tax on a business property #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For some context: the proposal to tax empty homes brought out 8 speakers to council. Pt Grey Road bike lane: 100+ speakers #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@stopdisplacemnt calling for 77,000 new units of social housing from fed gov. That's less than what @MayorGregor has called for #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erikrolfsen @MikeKlassen @Editorinblog 100% renewable plan doesnt need a ban to achieve goals. Eg City uses renewa… https://t.co/oHERxO8JZb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@MikeKlassen @Editorinblog actually it's completely false. ad spend was $20k. Like the "natural gas ban," another myth #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Activists who disrupted #readdresshousing want less social housing from fed gov than what @MayorGregor has advocated for #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vicki Been: disappointing that the urban agenda is not a bigger issue in the US election. #vanpoli #readdresshousing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vicki Been: Biggest change in NYC: people dont believe in supply/demand.  don’t believe it will make a difference #readdresshousing #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buildings with less than 6 units house half of all low-income residents in NYC #vanpoli #readdresshousing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NYC’s Vicki Been: Accused of destroying families b/c we reduced parking requirements in new seniors housing. #readdresshousing #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NYC affordable housing plan: reduce excessive parking requirements. Lower construction costs. Sound familiar? #readdresshousing #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NYC Housing Commissioner Vicki Been: every neighborhood council in NYC opposed mandatory inclusionary zoning #readdresshousing #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MT@vancouvermetro: #Airbnb properties w complaints now achieving compliance w #Vancouver city bylaws https://t.co/qwHZwkXTAM #vanre #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#vanpoli RT @VanMayorsOffice: @CityofVancouver staff are working to fill emergency shelter spaces. Pls share https://t.co/WEJgMHw26v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#vanpoli RT@VanMayorsOffice: Extreme weather alert for #vancouver tonight. Additional shelter capacity available for this evening #bcstorm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Richmond #vanpoli MT @grescoe:  not just Pacific islands: 5 Cdn communities imminently threatened by global warming… https://t.co/zw3Z6CIcYy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MyLoverArlo @CityofVancouver @CityofOaklandCA I did not! thanks for sharing. any links?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So did Mayor say to Globe "ive been calling for a foreign buyer tax for years and it's coming too late" as some #vanpoli pundits think? Nope]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@MayorGregor on foreign buyer tax: Didn't call for it, but support it as any intervention desperately needed in overheated market #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Mayorgregor issued statement on foreign buyer tax back in July. Nothing new in Globe story
https://t.co/KLK5IpUvSW #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@MayorGregor been calling for intervention on global capital for some time. Here's May 2015 statement https://t.co/u3H6beODzf #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Note ref to Van AND Toronto. Gov intervention - including feds - didn't happen sooner. Not specific to foreign buyer tax #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@MayorGregor: "have probably passed because the interventions didn't come." 2/2 #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's what was said. @MayorGregor: "middle class Canadians being able to buy a house in Vancouver or Toronto - those days..." 1/2 #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Q to @MayorGregor: "why are govs now talking about cooling the market - why did take so long." Not specific to foreign buyers tax. #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[good reminder that headlines don't always reflect what's actually in the story. #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Globe headline "too little too late" falsely implied Mayor said "been calling for a foreign buyer tax # should have come sooner."  #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[reminder of importance of recording interviews. I was at ed board, so reviewed my tape (great way to spend a day off in Toronto) #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see #vanpoli digging into Globe story on @MayorGregor/foreign buyer tax. What was actually said? #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Toronto, Vancouver’s short-term rental policy getting noticed. “Great first step” “leading the charge” #vanpoli https://t.co/4SUqJWPK4l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[spring 2015 @MayorGregor outlined gov policy interventions needed on global capital in Van housing https://t.co/rOS6EQufkh #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@MayorGregor: we’re looking at modular housing built on vacant city land. #TOhousingsummit #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@MayorGregor references Community Land Trust delivering 350+ new co-ops in Vancouver #TOHousingSummit #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@MayorGregor: “we have global capital pouring into our city. We need to make sure that people who keep their homes empty pay a higher tax”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@MayorGregor: on affordable housing: “it’s a human rights issue. Homelessness is Impacting cities across Canada.” #TOhousingsummit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At #TOHousingSummit, @MayorGregor  + big city mayors call for CMHC mandate review + 2/3 of federal social infr $ to go to housing #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["the cheaper path is to keep wrecking the planet"  @MarkJaccard rebuts false claim of ban on natural gas https://t.co/xpTeuKzGu0 #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Reports of an all-out ban on natural gas are unfounded." @cbcbc https://t.co/TZFmP7SdPy #vanpoli #Vancouver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see @downtownvan @hcma  public space activation profiled in @NextCityOrg https://t.co/JRDbMACVzr #vanpoli #AlleyOop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Councillors outraged about City goal of 100% renewable energy seem to forget plan passed unanimously Nov 15 https://t.co/JT66aaWNqD #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Vancouver is banning natural gas!" = same guy who said there was secret plan to close Lions Gate bridge https://t.co/9ENCNVe6KY #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@GlobalBC reported on City's "leaked" plan for renewable energy. Here's press release from 2 months ago https://t.co/pvZ3ugQmcA #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staff: short term rentals won't allow people to avoid empty homes tax. Doesn't count as occupied https://t.co/FedVlmbj5G #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[. @VancouverSun editorial got facts wrong on empty homes tax. "primary residence" avoids issues like lights on timers etc #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Updates coming this morning at City Council on Vancouver empty homes tax. https://t.co/63KxoBbfcJ #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tomdavidoff: About to do Almanac on "vacant" home tax. I love what the City of Vancouver has done. #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vancouver offer of 20 sites City land for affordable housing "receiving positive response" in Ottawa https://t.co/aqbzfUzNvQ #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#vanpoli #emptyhomes MT@TomDavidoff: @REITCanada impression is enforcement shouldn't be too bad. Did someone pay tax? Driver's license...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@globeandmail says City chooses to not get info, despite City commissioning BC hydro study on empty homes https://t.co/Xj3Pt9kqGR #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@globeandmail criticizes empty homes tax but unaware of BC hydro study, or use of primary res as criteria https://t.co/qjpgXPX2cX #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Empty Homes tax based on existing programs: Homeownr Grant, income tax. Self-report as part of property tax bill, w selective audit #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nope. RT @jordanbateman: unclear about Gregor's vacancy tax: do short term vacation rentals &amp;/or AirBnB count as tenancy? #bcpoli #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[City’s empty home tax framework uses primary residence as key distinction. Keeps it simple, avoids issues like energy use, timers #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PJCavan thanks - took a lot of work to get it there. staff did a great job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gwomand @CityofVancouver @Uber ride sharing fine if it meets basic standards. https://t.co/YoN2SLLHZn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gwomand @CityofVancouver @Uber need enabling legislation for fair playing field. Starts at provincial level https://t.co/dUVyeRPx8B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gwomand @CityofVancouver @Uber doesn’t work that way in BC, we have a provincial transportation board]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lidsville @eastsidedads @VanMayorsOffice signing off for afternoon. if have AirBNB complaints, send to city staff for inspection follow-up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lidsville @eastsidedads @VanMayorsOffice agree the crisis is serious. But how does ban work? Again, need evidence to prosecute violations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lidsville @eastsidedads @VanMayorsOffice city already sends warning letters based on complaints. But AirBNB not the only online platform]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lidsville @eastsidedads @VanMayorsOffice a bylaw officer would have to. need more than just a photo of someone with a suitcase.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lidsville @eastsidedads @VanMayorsOffice many struggling renters use Airbnb to make extra $ for rent. Mass ban won’t work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eastsidedads @Lidsville @VanMayorsOffice not straight forward. a listing online doesn’t violate bylaw. Need evidence for prosecution]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@MayorGregor says he "strongly supports" #GWPlan, with changes to enable @KettleSociety to expand mental health services #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New #GWplan brings in protections for renters, heritage incentives. Delaying only increases land speculation, demos, evictions #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vancouver new housing supply at record levels. Spike in prices shows clear disconnect between homes/income https://t.co/mhkY1CaRlp #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BCHydro data analysis uses algorithm to identify fixed (lights on timer) vs regular energy use https://t.co/cNxu5Zoh5C #vanpoli #emptyhomes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@MayorGregor letter to BC Gov in May 2015 on need for tools to address speculation, empty homes https://t.co/0BGwt18fnS #vanpoli #bcpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A good read RT @LausterNa: quickest fix for Vancouver's housing affordability crisis: change the standard. https://t.co/wvWLkLGL1q #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transit funding needs to be for entire 10 year plan, not just "Phase 1". Can't buy new buses without $ to pay for more drivers, etc #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What was the outrageous event that led NPA/Green to storm out of council? Clr Stevnson asked staff for more info on tree protection #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEB: operation of #KinderMorgan will create 313 jobs in BC. Comparison: 2000 job openings in Vancouver today in digital media #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEB finds "modest benefit" to local communities from #KinderMorgan pipeline because it requires emergency management upgrades #vanpoli.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[City's online survey on empty homes set a new record. More than 15,000+ respondents #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elliottchun City doesn't control taxi regs like Toronto does. starts with Province https://t.co/xYT7qJtce0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad to hear Tom Durning from TRAC is retiring. a tireless advocate for renters, and for creating a fairer, more inclusive city #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today Council votes on adopting Access Without Fear policy. In 2014, Harper gov fought Vancouver on it https://t.co/bpAfmP8Mu6 #cdnpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many thx @HCMA @Lanefab @ianrossmacdonald @DIALOGvancouver @Shrubadub @Campos_studio for thoughts on supporting culture of design in city]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BLAH_CITY @BigJarrett @JSadikKhan @CityofVancouver @VancouverPD except numbers don't back that up https://t.co/FY9YxQvFMy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SiriAgrell that is an impressive trifecta. I can only claim 2/3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Key detail in fed budget that's good for #vanpoli: signif portion of $2.9B for housing to go to where affordable housing need is greatest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 big boosts for Metro Van transit in federal budget: fed $ can go to design work, and funding based on ridership. #vanpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Important #vanpoli ask that is in federal budget: creating a National Housing Strategy. long overdue + urgent]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>